<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Car owners forced to sleep in vehicles while waiting for parking...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-parking-nightmare-kingsbridge-heights-bronx-20220327-ojigaxes5zbvldzqoazmaaj2w4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s a parking war,” said Sandy Blackwell as she pulled her SUV into a space on University Ave. near W. 195th St. in Kingsbridge Heights last Tuesday afternoon, minutes after a city street sweeper made its weekly run along the west side of the street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abduction, hostage-taking to threaten journalists...</title>
      <link>https://rsf.org/en/news/russians-use-abduction-hostage-taking-threaten-ukrainian-journalists-occupied-zones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rsf.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever since the start of the war in Ukraine, the Russian armed forces have been bullying and threatening journalists and local media in the conquered territories to prevent them reporting the facts and get them to spread Kremlin propaganda. Reporters Without Borders (RSF) condemns these acts of intimidation, which include abduction, and calls on the Russian authorities to stop harassing Ukrainian journalists. What with death threats, kidnapping and enforced disappearance, the Russian soldiers have been getting more and more inventive in their attempts to make Ukrainian journalists cooperate as the war in Ukraine enters its second month. Their latest misdeed was to take journalist Svitlana Zalizetska’s 75-year-old father hostage in the southeastern city of Melitopol on 23 March. As a condition for his release, they say that Zalizetska – the editor of the city’s main newspaper, Golovna Gazeta Melitopola, and the RIA-Melitopol news website – must come to the Russian army. She fears the city’s occupiers will demand her collaboration or the shutdown of her news site. This is not the first time Russian soldiers have taken a journalist or relative hostage. On 8 March in Berdiansk, a coastal city 120 km east of Melitopol, Russian soldiers stormed a building housing radio Novosti Berdiansk, the newspaper Berdianskiye Vedomosti and a local TV channel Youg TV. They took control of the radio station and TV channel within minutes, and then the Novosti Berdiansk Telegram channel and Instagram account. And they took hostage around 50 employees of these media outlets who were present. “They proposed to us that we should cooperate in exchange for a salary and food, but no one accepted,” one of the journalists told RSF on condition of anonymity. “For more than five hours they threatened us with their weapons, they tried to explain to us why they were attacking our country, they said that the war was not against civilians but against the Nazis in Ukraine, and that the Russians were there to protect us.” This journalist and one of his colleagues were badly beaten by the soldiers, who threatened to kill them. He is now at home, terrified about the possibility of reprisals. Ever since this hostage-taking, Novosti Berdiansk has been broadcasting Kremlin propaganda calling on Ukrainians to lay down their arms. Access to its website, one of the most visited in the region before the start of the war, is blocked. “By taking hostages, after bombing TV towers and shooting at cars marked ‘Press,’ the Russian authorities are demonstrating their determination to censor all reporting that contradicts their military propaganda,” said Jeanne Cavelier, the head of RSF’s Eastern Europe and Central Asia desk. “We strongly condemn these acts of intimidation and call on the Russian authorities to stop targeting journalists. They will have to answer for their actions before international courts.” Abduction, forced statement When the Russian army doesn’t take journalists hostage, it kidnaps them. Viktoria Roshchina, a Hromadske Radio journalist who disappeared in Berdiansk on 12 March, was freed ten days later after being forced to record a video saying the Russian soldiers “saved her life” and that she was “treated well.” Oleg Baturin, a journalist kidnapped by Russian soldiers in Kakhovka (in the Kherson region), was held and tortured for eight days and then released. A Radio France fixer who does not want to be identified suffered a similar fate after being abducted near Kyiv. Journalists in the occupied territories sometimes receive “visits” from Russian soldiers and are temporarily detained. Melitopolskie Vedomosti reporters Yulia Olkhovskaia, Liubov Chaika and Mikhailo Kumok and editor Evgenia Borian were arrested at their homes in Melitopol on 21 March and were taken by force to an unknown destination before being released a few hours later. The Russian military have threatened to kill Irina Stariselets, a correspondent for the national news agency Ukrinform in the Kherson region who is actively involved in covering the war. “The Russians keep calling me to explain what they are going to do to me,” she said. Pro-Russian activists are sometimes responsible for the threats. The mobile phone number, address and passport data of Anastasia Volkova, a journalist for the LOT TV channel in the Lugansk region, were posted online by pro-Russian activists at the start of March along with calls for her to be punished for criticising the Kremlin. Since the beginning of the war, local media are being prevented from operating - completely or temporarily - in at least six cities now occupied or under pressure by the Russian armed forces like Melitopol, Vinnytsia and Kherson, according to the Institute of Mass Information (IMI), RSF’s local partner, which says in a report published yesterday that a total of 70 local media outlets have been forced to stop working. Where they have not yet been forced to stop working, media outlets such as Pushkinskaya, Media-Inform, Reporter, Third Digital, Dumskaya, 048, Volnorez and All.news have been receiving anonymous letters calling on them to “abandon their anti-Russian activities” in order to have “a chance of being saved.” The Russian armed forces have also bombarded ten radio and TV towers since the start of the war – attacks that constitute a war crime and are the subject of two complaints that RSF has filed with the International Criminal Court’s chief prosecutor. At the Press Freedom Centre opened in Lviv, RSF is also providing support to Ukrainian journalists who have sought refuge in the west of the country. Since the start of the war, five journalists have been killed in the course of their work and nine have been wounded by gunfire or as a result of air or artillery bombardment. Ukraine is ranked 97th out of 180 countries in RSF's 2021 World Press Freedom Index, while Russia is ranked 150th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killed at extraordinary rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-generals-are-getting-killed-at-an-extraordinary-rate/ar-AAVxc1n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If prosecutors are finished investigating The Don, they should say so...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-if-prosecutors-are-finished-investigating-trump-they-should-say-so/ar-AAVwScx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Prepping Nuke Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10656435/North-Korea-preparing-nuclear-test-five-years-report-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un's secretive regime appears to be hastily constructing a 'shortcut' to a tunnel at its nuclear test site in Punggye-ri in preparations for a seventh underground nuclear detonation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wallace Says Life at FOXNEWS Became 'Unsustainable'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/27/chris-wallace-says-life-at-fox-news-became-unsustainable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I just no longer felt comfortable with the programming at Fox.” Chris Wallace uttered those words matter-of-factly, in between bites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pandemic puppies' returned to shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/home/pets/uptick-in-pandemic-puppies-being-surrendered-to-shelters/news-story/889893b1afb026e52ba0a0482cf8fb19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surge in the number of dogs being surrendered by their owners in Victoria has left animal shelters reeling with unprecedented numbers of pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky asks if West afraid of Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/ukraine-russia-war-live-updates-biden-denounces-putin-he-ends-n1293242#ncrd1293246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington quickly sought to clarify Biden's remarks, with Secretary of State Antony Blinken reiterating Sunday that the U.S. was not pursuing "a strategy of regime change" in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Georgia, Trump Tries to Revive Sputtering Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-georgia-trump-tries-to-revive-a-sputtering-campaign/ar-AAVwAqa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain rolling out crypto regulations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/27/crypto-britain-to-reveal-stablecoin-regulation-plans-sources-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Finance Minister Rishi Sunak is expected to announce a new regulatory regime for crypto in the coming weeks, sources tell CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLINKEN:  USA not seeking regime change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/27/russia-ukraine-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State AntonyÂ BlinkenÂ has sought to clarify President Joe Biden's comments that Russian President Vladimir Putin "cannot remain in power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With eye to China investment, Taliban now preserve Buddhas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-afghanistan-business-china-europe-3a5074c2043729df5d8f147d6aa0ee3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MES AYNAK, Afghanistan (AP) — The ancient Buddha statues sit in serene meditation in the caves carved into the russet cliffs of rural Afghanistan. Hundreds of meters below lies what is believed to be the world’s largest deposit of copper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FOO FIGHTERS drummer found dead in hotel before show...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/25/taylor-hawkins-dead-dies-foo-fighters-drummer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Hawkins, the drummer for the Foo Fighters, Alanis Morissette and his own band, is dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data of 820,000 NYC students compromised in hack of online grading system...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/data-of-820000-nyc-students-compromised-in-hack-of-online-grading-system-officials-say/ar-AAVx1Fb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk slams 'very, very ancient' leadership...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10655955/Musk-reveals-does-not-want-humans-live-longer-touch-politicians-stifling-America.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk, 50, was asked in an interview with Business Insider CEO Mathias Döpfner about why he wasn't passionate about longevity or interested in humanity living longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had ten different drugs in his system...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10655733/Foo-Fighters-drummer-Taylor-Hawkins-10-different-drugs-died.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Hawkins had 'ten different types of drugs in his system' when he died in the five-star Casa Medina hotel in Bogota, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find microplastics in blood for first time...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-03-scientists-microplastics-blood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have discovered microplastics in human blood for the first time, warning that the ubiquitous particles could also be making their way into organs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California makes history with first openly trans judge appointed to bench...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-makes-history-first-openly-033358956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andi Mudryk will be the state's second openly trans judge and the first to reach the bench by a governor's appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Covid infections nearing record highs...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2022-03-uk-covid-infections-nearing-highs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus levels reached all-time highs in Scotland and Wales and are nearing record levels in England, with around 4.2 million people infected across the UK last week, official figures showed Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Manhattan lost 7% of its population in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/manhattan-lost-6-9-of-population-in-2021-the-most-of-any-major-u-s-county/3616010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City experienced a significant population shift last year, with four of its five counties losing a greater percentage of people than almost any other major county in the United States, the U.S. Census Bureau detailed Thursday. Data analysts from the Census Bureau point to migration as the primary factor behind such significant shifts in population from 2020 to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Biden sparked global uproar with ad-libbed words about Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-biden-sparked-a-global-uproar-with-nine-ad-libbed-words-about-putin/ar-AAVxgGu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian troops firing at nuclear reactor...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-troops-firing-nuclear-reactor-26565217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine's foreign affairs first deputy minister Emine Dzheppar warned that the Russian attack on Kharkiv's Institute of Physics and Technology risked a 'major environmental disaster'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin Wants $1 Trillion Tax Increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/manchin-wants-1-trillion-tax-increase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tax hike violates Manchin promise to WV voters: “I can’t look the people in West Virginia in the eye and ask them to pay a penny more until I know we’re running this government efficiently.” “Moderate” Democrat Senator Joe Manchin wants to impose a $1 trillion tax increase, according to an Axios scoop. But this […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change is in the air...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-oscars-show-9a69424884de11649b68a12a284353a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — For the first time in two years, the Academy Awards are rolling out the red carpet at Los Angeles’ Dolby Theatre for what the film academy hopes will be a back-to-normal Oscars. Except for all the stuff that’s changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Strange Rebirth Of Imperial Russia...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/the-strange-rebirth-of-imperial-russia-694?s=w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And why it could be here to stay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers think they've found last surviving Pilgrim ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/researchers-think-theyve-found-the-last-surviving-pilgrim-ship/ar-AAVwu9Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida reports 1,167 deaths, over 16,000 cases over last 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-reports-1167-deaths-over-16000-cases-over-the-last-2-weeks/ar-AAVx3Hl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor London Breed taking on San Fran's far left. Can she prevail?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mayor-london-breed-taking-san-120040980.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tricky San Francisco politics could be a proving ground for Mayor London Breed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mayor at War: Vitali Klitschko on keeping himself and Kyiv alive...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2022/03/kyiv-mayor-vitali-klitschko-on-russias-war-on-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One month after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, Vitali Klitschko talks about keeping himself and Kyiv alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad purge of 'traitors' scoops up pensioners, foodiess, peaceniks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-e2-80-99s-purge-of-e2-80-98traitors-e2-80-99-scoops-up-pensioners-foodies-and-peaceniks/ar-AAVwt5H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands rally against Putin in Prague...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220326-thousands-of-russians-rally-against-putin-in-prague</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of largely Russian protesters rallied against President Vladimir Putin in central Prague on Saturday, calling on him to stop the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia loses 7th general...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60807538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western officials believe low morale among Russian troops is forcing generals to the battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas scrutiny intensifies after latest revelations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/599821-thomas-scrutiny-intensifies-after-latest-revelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Clarence Thomas faces mounting ethical questions after reports of his wife’s aggressive effort to help overturn former President Trump’s electoral defeat have intensified scrutiny over the justice’s refusal to step aside from related cases before the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16,000 Russian troops dead as Vlad faces defeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18074447/russian-troops-dead-zelensky-kherson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Zelensky has said 16,000 Russian troops have been killed so far in Ukraine as his soldiers fight to retake the first city that Putin seized. The Ukrainian leader, 44, said his troops had …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slams 'Butcher' Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/hes-a-butcher-biden-slams-putin-moments-after-meeting-with-ukrainian-refugee-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An emotional President Joe Biden called Russian President Vladimir Putin a "butcher" following a visit with Ukrainian refugees, many of the children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland embraces West after years of drifting away...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Poland-embraces-West-amid-Ukraine-crisis-after-17030678.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW - As a presidential caFndidate, Joe Biden cited Poland as a country at risk of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet nuke USA keeps in Germany, just waiting to not be used...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Meet-the-nuke-the-U-S-keeps-in-Europe-just-17028878.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Near steep vineyards of riesling grapes, in an underground vault at an air force base in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial over brutal killings sheds light on MS-13 and power of US street gangs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/26/ms-13-gang-new-york-long-island-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complex social and political elements swirl round gang – with roots in El Salvador – accused of hacking four US teens to death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clown and biochemist at fortress Kyiv's barricades...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220326-clown-and-biochemist-at-fortress-kyiv-s-barricades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional clown Serhii Shershun has swapped the big top for a checkpoint in Kyiv, and says Russia's invasion is no laughing matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Orban criticized for 'neutrality'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-business-budapest-viktor-orban-c289237f0c626ce9447bd1c78ebcd8ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST, Hungary (AP) — Widely seen as Russian President Vladimir Putin's closest ally in the European Union, Hungarian Prime Minister Viktor Orban has sought to assert Hungary's neutrality in the war in Ukraine , even as his allies in the EU and NATO assist the embattled country and punish Russia for launching the largest armed conflict in Europe since World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls for Western unity as Russia suffers setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/ukraine-russia-war-live-updates-biden-call-western-unity-russia-n1293191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will set out how the "free world" should unite to resist Russia's invasion of Ukraine in a major speech in Poland on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee after Philippine volcano erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220326-thousands-flee-after-philippine-volcano-erupts-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people fled their homes near a Philippine volcano Saturday after an eruption sent ash and steam hundreds of metres into the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Boom Towns Risk Ghost Town Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/what-happens-to-u-s-oil-boom-towns-when-fossil-fuel-industries-go-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Oil Boom Towns Risk Ghost Town Future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes rule for Navy and vax requirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/25/1086789991/supreme-court-gives-partial-ok-to-navy-for-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vote was 6-to-3 to partially overturn a decision by the Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals, which had blocked a Department of Defense vaccine mandate for military personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife's Pro-Trump Texts Put Husband's Court Role in Focus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ginni-thomas-e2-80-99s-pro-trump-texts-put-husband-e2-80-99s-court-role-in-focus/ar-AAVuH60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden planning digital currency. Here's why should be worried...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/599768-biden-is-planning-a-new-digital-currency-heres-why-you-should-be-very-worried</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s clear that the Biden administration and Fed are working together to create a controllable, traceable, programmable digital currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subvariant spreading rapidly in L.A. and across nation...</title>
      <link>https://richmond.com/ap/national/omicron-subvariant-ba-2-spreading-rapidly-in-l-a-and-across-the-nation/article_b27a33e5-0645-5ffa-a365-c83fd679d378.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The percentage of omicron subvariant BA.2 cases is rising in Los Angeles County, a trend seen elsewhere nationwide as officials sound the alarm about Congress’ failure to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Don't Know Much About Jay Penske. And He's Fine With That...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/26/you-dont-know-much-about-jay-penske-and-hes-fine-with-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the media executive Jay Penske, awards season is money season. It’s the time of year when Disney and Netflix,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Took Over. Will It Take Best Picture, Too?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/26/streaming-took-over-hollywood-will-it-take-best-picture-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years ago, Hollywood was engaged in a knock-down, drag-out fight over the future of cinema — what, exactly, constitutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhol-mania: Why Famed Pop Artist Everywhere Again...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/25/warhol-mania-why-the-famed-pop-artist-is-everywhere-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Warhol left behind a lot of self portraits. There was the black-and-white shot from a photo booth strip, from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Cursing eases pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4979848/swearing-eases-pain-like-pills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORGET popping a paracetamol — swearing like a trooper will ease your pain, a study shows. Effing and blinding, especially shouting s**t and f***, is so effective, researchers say it should be enco…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAINT PETER'S delivers another shock to college basketball establishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Saint-Peter-s-delivered-another-shock-to-the-17030448.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA - The impossible dream became even more impossible Friday night. Or, more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethics experts see problem for Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-s-clarence-thomas-released-from-hospital-after-week-long-stay/ar-AAVuSqT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On last Europe day, Biden meets with Polish leader, refugees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-biden-migration-world-war-ii-warsaw-652da1c2ab1c88de3032241089bfa516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Twenty-five years ago, Joe Biden visited Poland's capital with a warning: Even though the Soviet Union had collapsed, some of NATO’s original members were not doing enough to ensure the alliance’s collective defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring break crackdown puts focus on future of South Beach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-miami-florida-ap-top-news-8e176168a6dfc49084d249116245fabb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Miami Beach officials have spent recent years trying to control the raucous crowds, public drinking and growing violence associated with the city's world-famous South Beach neighborhood during spring break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump returns to Georgia confronting test of his grip on GOP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-georgia-atlanta-election-2020-donald-trump-ca84cfe92c6f6c07a501f7bc2be74f31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — In Donald Trump's push to fundamentally reshape the Republican Party , few places are a higher priority than Georgia.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
