<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>World's first remote brain surgery performed...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/454056-remote-brain-surgery-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese surgeon has performed the world’s first remote brain surgery using 5G technology, with the patient 3,000km away from the operating doctor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign national arrested after attempt to tour Ft. Bragg 'special ops facility'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fayobserver.com/news/20190314/foreign-national-allegedly-repeated-requests-to-tour-bragg-special-operations-facility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fayobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nouran Ahmad Shihab Sueidan remains detained</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia teen stabbed 100 times, set on fire in MS-13 murder...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2019/03/5-charged-in-ms-13-related-slaying-of-va-teen-who-was-stabbed-100-times-burned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people, including two teens, have been arrested in the slaying of a Virginia teen who was stabbed 100 times before his body was dumped in a remote area of Stafford County, Virginia, and set on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rupert Murdoch begins Hollywood goodbye...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/3002086/rupert-murdoch-begins-his-hollywood-goodbye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murdoch family will create new entity known as Fox after the breaking up of 21st Century Fox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches open doors to businesses in order to survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/churches-are-opening-their-doors-to-businesses-in-order-to-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday looks very different from Monday at White Rock United Methodist Church in Dallas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's iPhone 11 may have folding screen, triple camera and FART sensor...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8647084/iphone-11-features-foldable-screen-triple-camera-fart-sensor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is keeping its rumoured iPhone 11 under tight wraps – but we can still guess at the fancy features it might boast. We’ve tracked down some of the wackiest features that could make it in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to six babies in nine minutes defying one in 4.7 billion odds...	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8656992/mum-gives-birth-6-babies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MUM gave birth to six babies  — two sets of twin boys and one lot of twin girls — in just nine minutes. Defying remarkable odds of one in 4.7billion, Thelma Chiaka delivered her sextuplets betwee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter, 74, among 'elite' wildlife killers after shooting dead 500 animals for fun...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8656852/brit-kills-wildlife-shooting-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 74-YEAR-OLD Brit has been exposed as an “elite” wildlife killer who has shot dead hundreds of animals worldwide for fun. Pensioner Malcolm King has been named as one of the world̵…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest 'ultimatum' rally in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/violence-returns-as-frances-yellow-vest-protests-enter-fourth-month-idUSKCN1QX0B1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters set fire to a bank and ransacked stores on Paris's Champs Elysees a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading geneticists propose moratorium on genome editing... </title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00726-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nature.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Lander, Françoise Baylis, Feng Zhang, Emmanuelle Charpentier, Paul Berg and specialists from seven countries call for an international governance framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: High-performing robots demoralize human co-workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-what-robots-destroy-when-they-compete-with-humans-2019-03-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has something to say about the toll of workplace automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 million videos of attack removed by FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190317-new-zealand-mosque-attack-videos-facebook-ardern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said it removed 1.5 million videos globally of the Christchurch mosque attack in New Zealand in the first 24 hours after the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was called 1,800 times: When robots collect bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/16/robocalls-about-your-bills-can-pour-in-every-day-all-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quarter of consumers receive calls each month about a debt they owe. For some people, the calls are relentless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Still Released into USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/13/ice-union-thousands-of-illegal-aliens-are-being-released-into-u-s-with-catch-and-release-in-overdrive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) union says agents are being overwhelmed by unchecked illegal immigration to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAFFTASTIC DAY!</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/beto-orourkes-gafftastic-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not ready for prime time?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Sports: Interactive, Immersive, Intense...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-future-of-sports-is-interactive-immersive-and-intense-11552827600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you’re watching March Madness, the Super Bowl or ultimate frisbee, it will soon be more interactive, more immersive—and a lot more like sitting courtside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-year-old driver jumps out of moving car...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Elderly-Driver-Suffers-Minor-Injuries-Jumping-13694761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH SAN FRANCISCO (BCN)  An 80-year-old driver was injured Saturday night when he jumped out of his car as it rolled south on Interstate Highway 280 at the Westborough Boulevard offramp, the California Highway Patrol said.  The CHP got a call about 6:30 p.m. Saturday of a man driving on the freeway opening his driver's door and diving out of the car, CHP Officer Bert Diaz said. The elderly driver tumbled several times before coming to rest against the freeway's center divider.  The man's now-driverless car also hit the divider, and then veered back across all traffic lanes before coming to a stop on the right shoulder, Diaz said. The car didn't hit any other vehicles, Diaz said, but a minor non-injury crash resulted when a car swerving to avoid the driverless vehicle struck another car.  The elderly man suffered a cut on the head and was taken to Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital for treatment of his injury and a psychological examination.  "There was no statement, and no reason given as to why this happened," said Diaz, adding that this whole incident could have turned out far worse for the 80-year-old man and perhaps others.    Copyright © 2019 by Bay City News, Inc. Republication, Rebroadcast or any other Reuse without the express written consent of Bay City News, Inc. is prohibited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters give Kamala break on 'problematic comments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Voters-give-Harris-a-break-on-problematic-13694327.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. GEORGE, S.C. - Before Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., stepped out of her white minivan, no presidential candidate had ever visited St. George, at least as far as any local officials could remember. But the shadow of the ever-growing Democratic field fell on Harris even here, when a young voter named Essence Williams asked her about fellow Democratic candidate Andrew Yang's proposal to give $1,000 of basic income to every American ages 18 to 64.  "Do you think this program is feasible in our economic climate?" Williams asked. "And is it possible to increase the standard of living for low-income families?"  "I haven't analyzed that policy," Harris said, pivoting instead to discussions of how she hopes to reduce student loan debt and "uplift" young people.  After Harris finished, Williams said she "absolutely" still had questions about where Harris stood, even as she was grateful for the senator's candor.  "It's all about trust," she said. "I'd rather she be honest with me [like that] and tell me she hasn't looked into it."  In the first weeks of Harris' campaign, the 54-year-old has fielded criticism for equivocal and imprecise answers to questions about her stances on specific policies and her record as a prosecutor.  The language contrasts with the message Harris hammers to receptive crowds at every stop: defining herself as the candidate speaking truth and confronting the uncomfortable conversations the country needs to have. But there is little indication that the approach has cut into her popularity, and she is not shying away from further controversy.  In an interview with MSNBC on Thursday, Harris said it was "outrageous" that Vice President Mike Pence will not have one-on-one meetings with women - a critique that exaggerated a long-ago Pence comment that he does not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California awash in cannabis cash. Some used for bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-pot-corruption-20190317-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the two years since California voters decided to allow the restricted sale of recreational marijuana, the state has seen a rash of government corruption cases. Some in the cannabis black market are trying to game the system with the use of bribery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete says he's hit significant 65,000 donor mark...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/politics/2019/03/16/south-bend-indiana-mayor-pete-buttigieg-donors-dnc-debate/3184796002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mark would qualify Buttigieg to be invited to the first Democratic National Committee debate in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing movement calls on media to avoid naming shooters...</title>
      <link>https://www.daytondailynews.com/news/national/growing-movement-calls-media-avoid-naming-shooters/Z3fTVGAR8eFyUHLIIVUjhI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.daytondailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few months after teen shooters killed 12 classmates at Columbine High School, Coni Sanders was sta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video captures dozens of illegals cutting way through hole in fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6815035/Video-shows-dozens-migrants-crossing-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident, which led to the capture of 52 people, was caught on camera at California's Border Field State Park, on the border between San Diego and Tijuana, Thursday at about 4pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax refund fraud: IRS crackdown ensnares legitimate taxpayers...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/03/16/tax-refund-fraud-irs-crackdown-may-ensnare-legit-taxpayers/3166441002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the IRS efforts to reduce tax refund fraud have been successful, legitimate taxpayers have been caught up in the process, delaying refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES: Just another pretty face?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-beto-orourke-democrats-20190316-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most striking thing about Beto O'Rourke is that he’s so hard to pin down. He spent six years as a congressman from El Paso but has few detailed positions on issues. Instead, he mostly deploys sunny attitudes. He’s a lanky, buzzy Rorschach test: Democrats can project on him any view they like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet gets 10 year prison sentence for insulting Iran 'supreme leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/u-s-navy-vet-detained-in-iran-sentenced-to-10-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy veteran first detained in Iran while visiting a girlfriend was sentenced to 10 years in prison on charges of insulting the country’s supreme leader and posting a photograph on social media, his lawyer said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President threatens 'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE' with federal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6819181/Trump-threatens-Saturday-Night-Live-federal-investigation-Sunday-morning-tweet-storm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump began his Sunday morning venting about 'Saturday Night Live,' complaining the show should be investigated by federal regulators for mocking him but not Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iditarod dog dies after finishing race...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/outdoors-adventure/iditarod/2019/03/17/iditarod-dog-dies-two-days-after-finishing-the-race-to-nome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oshi, a 5-year-old female, crossed the finish line with rookie musher Richie Beattie on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS CASINO SHOOTOUT:  Attempted robbery at BELLAGIO ends in gunfight...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/alleged-robber-bellagio-casino-trades-gunfire-police-las/story?id=61727817</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was shot by police and died a few hours later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcomes gun control; 'There will be no opposition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/17/new-zealand-welcomes-jacinta-ardern-gun-control-af/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Zealand leader’s promise of tightened gun laws in the wake of the Christchurch mosque shootings has been widely welcomed by a stunned population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychiatrist found bludgeoned to death in trunk of Vegas car...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecalifornian.com/story/news/2019/03/16/salinas-doctor-found-trunk-car-murdered-las-vegas/3189401002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecalifornian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burchard died from blunt forceÂ to theÂ headÂ and his death was ruled a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic floods hit Nebraska after 'bomb cyclone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-weather-idUSKCN1QY00Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large parts of Nebraska and the U.S. Central Plains were underwater on Saturday ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In movies and TV, plus-size actresses finally assume lead roles...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190317-movies-tv-plus-size-actresses-finally-assume-leading-roles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In movies and TV, plus-size actresses finally assume leading roles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  DC Protesters Would Trade Trump for Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/16/hands-off-venezuela-protest-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's mind-boggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born into al-Qaida: Hamza bin Laden's rise to prominence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a70a4562831e4ce0a8da88b0c888e16c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Years after the death of his father at the hands of a U.S. Navy SEAL raid in Pakistan, Hamza bin Laden now finds himself in the crosshairs of world...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO:  Being white male no disadvantage...</title>
      <link>http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2019/mar/16/beto-orourke-being-a-white-male-doesnt-put-me-at-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Beto O’Rourke said Saturday that being a white man in a 2020 Democratic field that’s so deeply diverse won’t be a hindrance because his gender and race have given him inherent advantages for years. While he’d spoken before about his gender and race, O’Rourke had largely dodged campaign-trail questions about whether his party would go for a white man in a year when a historic number of women and minorities are running to deny President Trump a second term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive manhunt underway after West Bank shooting, stabbing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/17/west-bank-shooting-stabbing-spree-prompts-manhunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Palestinian killed an Israeli and seriously wounded two others in a West Bank shooting and stabbing spree Sunday before fleeing and setting off a massive manhunt, the Israeli military said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport closed after suspicious package...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12213645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source has told the Otago Daily Times the bomb squad has been called in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand digs graves as mosque massacre toll rises to 50...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/419df740e2464e47b416b2dcc6128cdb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHRISTCHURCH, New Zealand (AP) — Anguished relatives were anxiously waiting Sunday for authorities to release the remains of those who were killed in massacres at two mosques in the New Zealand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SXSW Shooting Sends Austin Into Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/shooting-at-sxsw-leaves-at-least-one-injured-1202577063/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The celebratory mood Saturday night at the South by Southwest festival in Austin, Texas ended in chaos, after a shooting erupted at the corner of 6th Street and San Jacinto, according to an eyewitn…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
