<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Israeli lab: Existing drugs could stop Covid 100%...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-lab-some-existing-drugs-could-stop-covid-at-almost-100-percent-674426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A research team found 18 drugs that they felt could be effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In propaganda video, China threatens to nuke Japan...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/in-propaganda-video-china-threatens-to-nuke-japan-after-japan-vows-to-defend-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (SBG) &amp;mdash; In a now-deleted propaganda video, China threatened to nuke Japan following comments made by Japanese leaders vowing to defend Taiwan from Chinese invasion. The nearly six-minute video, which was posted to the Chinese Communist Party-sanctioned channel Xigua, featured images and videos of Chinese war machines, such as tanks and fighter jets, edited into pictures of a devastated 1940s Japan following the World War II U. S. nuclear strikes on Hiroshima and Nagasaki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys Leader Pleads Guilty To Burning BLM Banner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/07/20/proud-boys-leader-pleads-guilty-burning-black-lives-matter-banne.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Henry Tarrio admitted to partaking in two crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Extradicted To LA; Faces 140 Years If Guilty On Rape Charges...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/harvey-weinstein-extradition-los-angeles-rape-charges-1234796616/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of delays, Harvey Weinstein is finally on his way to Los Angeles to face multiple rape charges. Facing up to a 140 years behind bars if found guilty in the California courts, the alrea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE foe named DOJ antitrust chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/20/biden-picks-doj-antitrust-chief-500310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The selection adds to the perils for tech industry giants like Google, Facebook and Amazon, as progressives clamor for aggressive enforcement of laws against anti-competitive abuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sees cases surge 224% in last 3 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9806537/US-sees-cases-surge-224-three-weeks-Delta-variant-makes-83-new-infections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. recorded 52,111 new COVID-19 cases on Monday with a seven-day rolling average of 34,682, representing a 224% increase from the 10,678 average recorded three weeks ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin hails Russia air power as new fighter goes on view...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-europe-business-russia-14f649c0a20dfca9136bdf07fddb253b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Alabama Freshman QB Already Offered 'Almost Seven Figure' Deals...</title>
      <link>https://247sports.com/Article/Alabama-Crimson-Tide-football-Nick-Saban-Bryce-Young-name-image-likeness-deal-seven-figures-168001730/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;247sports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculed for 'Tone-Deaf' Victory Lap Thanking Workers, Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jeff-bezos-ridiculed-for-tone-deaf-victory-lap-thanking-amazon-workers-and-shoppers-you-guys-paid-for-all-this/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos was bashed on social media in response to "tone-deaf" commentary that was made during a press conference Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phones of Macron, French ministers targeted in Pegasus affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210720-phones-of-macron-and-some-french-ministers-targeted-by-morocco-in-pegasus-affair-le-monde</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cell phones of French President Emmanuel Macron and 15 members of the French government may have been among potential targets in 2019 of surveillance by spyware made by the Israel-based NSO Group…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA agent arrested for participating in Jan. 6 Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/dea-agent-arrested-for-participating-in-jan-6-capitol-riot-by-trump-supporters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Drug Enforcement Administration agent has been arrested for allegedly participating in the Jan. 6 Capitol riot by supporters of then-President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfside collapse response dog now needs help...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/20/surfside-condos-response-dog-teddy-unable-to-walk-needs-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m scared of him not being able to walk again,” owner Sophia Barrett said of the 6-year-old dog, who may have a herniated disc and torn knee ligaments after three weeks of non-stop caregiving.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans cop sues, claims colleagues called him 'it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trans-officer-sues-port-authority-claims-colleague-called-him-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender police officer with the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey sued the agency over allegations he was referred to in a discriminatory way as "it" and "transvestite" by colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT OR FLIGHT:   Cabin crew being taught aggressive moves to take down unruly passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3316869/flight-attendant-fight-training-planes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLIGHT attendants are being taught fighting skills including ear slapping, eye poking and groin kicks to defend themselves against unruly passengers. Disruptive incidents on flights have risen in r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bride dislocates knee during first dance with groom...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wedding-nightmare-local-bride-dislocates-knee-during-first-dance-with-groom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania couple is sharing their story and laughing off a wedding nightmare after the bride seriously injured her knee as they danced at their wedding reception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-year-old robbed in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/brooklyn-man-arrested-for-stealing-scooter-from-7-year-old</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 59-year-old Brooklyn man faces robbery charges after allegedly stealing an electric scooter from a 7-year-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House official, Pelosi aide test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/white-house-pelosi-covid-positive-41dd58f1-f4a3-4111-a6ae-492810f79703.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pelosi staffer helped usher a delegation of Texas Democrats around the Capitol last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Capsule Lands Back in TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3274747/jeff-bezos-space-flight-watch-live-blue-origin-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON founder Jeff Bezos has landed safely after blasting into space on board a rocket ship built by his company Blue Origin. Bezos and his brother lifted off at 9.10am ET (2.10pm UK time) on boar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRISON THREAT!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/fauci-rebukes-rand-paul-for-threatening-him-with-prison-in-fiery-clash-you-do-not-know-what-you-are-talking-about/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci faced off with Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) during a Tuesday Senate hearing that witnessed Paul threatening Fauci with imprisonment for "lying" to Congress — over Fauci's dismayed protestations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Businesses Requiring Proof Of Vax Upon Entry...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/19/some-sacramento-businesses-require-proof-of-vaccination-upon-entry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No proof of vaccine, no entry without a mask. It’s a new policy some Sacramento businesses are adopting for safety reasons as concern over the Delta variant increases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police officer calls for backup after 'being pursued by a drone'...</title>
      <link>https://notthebee.com/article/police-officer-calls-for-backup-after-being-pursued-by-drone-which-was-actually-just-jupiter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;notthebee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh man, this story can't be real!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Americans Growing Increasingly Desensitized To Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-risk-taking-desensitized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that despite the death toll continuing to increase, people are generally showing less concern about COVID-related news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul throwdown with Fauci...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/if-anybody-is-lying-here-senator-it-is-you-fauci-tells-sen-paul-in-heated-exchange-at-senate-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Will Include 'Black National Anthem' During Pregame Ceremonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/sports/2021/07/16/nfl-black-national-anthem-pregame-ceremonies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Lift Every Voice and Sing” will be performed before every game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein extradited to California; Faces more sex assault charges...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/20/harvey-weinstein-extradited-to-face-california-sex-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein was being extradited to California on Tuesday to face more sex-assault charges there, New York prison officials told The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EGO TRIP'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/19/bezos-flight-is-an-ego-trip-but-it-sets-the-stage-for-much-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos is scheduled to take off for outer space Tuesday morning. Showing faith in his engineers, he will ride the first passenger flight of his space company Blue Origin’s New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France broadens use of health pass...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210719183629-zlkr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health pass will be required in venues including cinemas, bars, restaurants, hospitals and long-distance train and planes, a decision that led to protests at the weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA Strangest Encounters With Unidentified Aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41573/the-strangest-encounters-with-unidentified-aircraft-weve-found-in-the-faas-huge-database</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We found over 50 highly unusual incidents with our new FAA data mapping tool. And yes, there even are a few flying 'disks' and 'cylinders' in there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans model makes history: 'If don't like it, go somewhere else'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trans-model-makes-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-cover-history-e2-80-98if-you-don-e2-80-99t-like-it-you-can-go-somewhere-else-e2-80-99/ar-AAMlQaJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This moment heals a lot of pain in the world. We deserve this moment,” Bloom said on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 'BLACK WIDOW' ticket buying suddenly drying up, growing questions for DISNEY about what did it in...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/with-black-widow-ticket-buying-suddenly-drying-up-growing-questions-for-disney-s-marvel-about-what-did-it-in/ar-AAMmdap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Marvel fans are tiring of the franchise, it would imperil the most lucrative movie universe of all time at precisely the post-pandemic moment movie theaters need it most and throw Marvel’s larger financial future into question along with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger charts path from Illinois to new political battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/adam-kinzinger-charts-path-from-illinois-to-new-political-battlefield/article_60a99450-2aa3-53fa-99a5-d9ce8685ab23.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORRIS, Ill. — U.S. Rep. Adam Kinzinger, an Air Force veteran, is again on the frontlines. But it’s a different battlefield for the northern Illinois Republican. This one’s closer to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tiny little step' toward plan to build road to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/jeff-bezos-says-this-is-a-tiny-little-step-toward-blue-origins-plan-to-build-a-road-to-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos said Blue Origin's space tourism venture is one step toward the company's mission of building a road to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snakes look like monsters as fungal disease spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article252866068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snakes turn crusty with milky eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Brady, BUCS Honored At White House...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/tom-brady-in-attendance-as-buccaneers-make-white-house-visit-with-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Buccaneers made their trip to the White House on Tuesday. Tom Brady was in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to Postpone Return to Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apple-reportedly-delay-employees-return-to-office-093544574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is reportedly delaying its return-to-office deadline by about a month due to a resurgence in COVID-19 cases..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems lay out vision for Civilian Climate Corps...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/equilibrium-sustainability/563848-dozens-of-democrats-lay-out-vision-for-civilian-climate-corps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of more than 80 House and Senate Democrats on Tuesday laid out their vision for a climate jobs program called the Civilian Climate Corps that is expected to be part of a sweeping $3.5 trillion budget reconci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight just 11 mins. Reverberations will last much longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/07/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-successful-flight/619484/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flight was just 11 minutes. The reverberations for the world’s richest man will last much longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW MILESTONE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/jeff-bezos-worlds-richest-man-set-inaugural-space-voyage-2021-07-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos, the world's richest man, and three crewmates soared high above the Texas desert aboard his space venture Blue Origin's New Shepard launch vehicle on Tuesday and returned safely to Earth, a historic suborbital flight that helps to inaugurate a new era of private commercial space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Capsule Lands in West Texas After Trip to Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/jeff-bezos-space-capsule-lands-in-west-texas-after-flight-to-space/ar-AAMmgC1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos and three others landed after Blue Origin’s first flight to space with passengers aboard, a key milestone in the company’s effort to make space tourism viable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pegasus project turns spotlight on spyware firm ties to Israeli state...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/20/pegasus-project-turns-spotlight-on-spyware-firm-nso-ties-to-israeli-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclosures about political figures put Israel under increasing pressure over extent of surveillance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE Calls in Lawyers Over PORNHUB Hardcore Reenactments...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/louvre-calls-lawyers-over-pornhub-103208032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wikimedia CommonsROME—Long before hairless strangers were streaming loveless sex to the lonely, European classic artists were painting scintillating scenes that were even quite lewd by today’s standards. At least that’s what Pornhub would like would-be adult entertainment consumers to think as they launch their new “Show me the Nudes” interactive website and app. Classic masterpieces from some of Europe’s top museums are recreated by porn stars who then come to life, which in the case of Venus o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll in India ten times higher than govt estimate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-health-india-pandemics-334c326d86efa73a0631bf7cb6e3f92e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India's excess deaths during the pandemic could be a staggering 10 times the official COVID-19 toll, likely making it modern India’s worst human tragedy, according to the most comprehensive research yet on the ravages of the virus in the South Asian country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chilling world of mind control as scientists experiment on monkey brains, tape memories, create 'remote control' mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/tokyo-olympics-2020/3315497/swimming-triathlon-poo-ecoli-water-games/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Tokyo 2020 Olympics have been dealt a fresh crisis after fears were raised athletes will be swimming in POO and catch E.coli after a suspected sewage leak. Both the swimming leg of the triathlo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporary or not, inflation rattling restaurants and broader economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/temporary-or-not-inflation-is-rattling-restaurants-and-broader-economy/ar-AAMm3Wy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While President Biden and Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell chairman insist rising prices will prove short-lived, their effects are still being felt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: 2020 Set Records for Negative Emotions...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/352205/2020-sets-records-negative-emotions.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 was the most stressful year in recent history. A record-high 40% of adults worldwide said they experienced stress during a lot of the previous day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family farm swaps cows for goats amid changed dairy industry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-dairy-farm-goats-cows-milk-b541c273e309621d6f0b12727766be9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HYDE PARK, Vt. (AP) — Grappling with a changed industry, two brothers operating their family's dairy farm in Vermont have made the drastic decision to give up hundreds of cows for goats. The Jones family, which had raised cows for 150 years at Joneslan Farm, houses about 1,000 goats in their barn that remains adorned with painted cut-outs of dairy cattle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tMHhXzpwupU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On July 20, Blue Origin will fly its 16th New Shepard flight to space, and its first with astronauts on board. Broadcast starts at T-90 minutes to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dramatic photos from NASA highlight severity of CA drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/dramatic-photos-from-nasa-highlight-severity-of-californias-drought/ar-AAMlgbp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shasta Lake, once full and surrounded by green banks, is now bordered by a "bathtub ring" that indicates just how far the water has fallen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH'S RICHEST MAN SET TO LEAVE PLANET!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jeff-bezos-space-e0afeaa813ff0bdf23c37fe16fd34265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VAN HORN, Texas (AP) — Jeff Bezos is about to soar on his space travel company’s first flight with people on board. The founder of Blue Origin as well as Amazon on Tuesday will become the second billionaire to ride his own rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant risk to Biden promise of swift comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/delta-variant-poses-major-risk-to-biden-e2-80-99s-promises-of-swift-economic-comeback/ar-AAMlVrZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House had expected the economy to roar in 2021, but the growing number of cases has raised concerns about a setback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly spider venom could help heart attack victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/deadly-spider-e2-80-99s-venom-could-someday-help-heart-attack-victims-australian-scientists-say/ar-AAMlrp0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in Australia, home to some of the most poisonous creatures on Earth, have made a discovery about spider venom that eventually could lead to a new class of drugs to help heart attack victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia man ties bedsheets together to escape 4th floor hotel quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210720074525-vvju0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA-ESCAPE (PIX):Australia man ties bedsheets together to escape 4th floor hotel quarantine - police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yield Plunge Stirs Thoughts of 1% Treasuries...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/long-term-treasury-yields-plunge-134445715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Long-term Treasury rates tumbled to the lowest levels in months on Monday as the spread of the delta coronavirus variant called into question optimistic assumptions about economic recovery, also touching off a global stock market slump.Market-implied expectations for a Federal Reserve rate increase were pushed further into the future amid stronger-than-normal debt-market volumes, and the rally in bonds drove benchmark 10-year yields down as much as 12 basis points to 1.17% on Mond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLION DOLLAR VIEWS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3310172/blue-origins-new-shepard-rocket-bezos-launch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS BLUE Origin’s 60ft New Shepard rocket readies for launch its founder Jeff Bezos has guaranteed those on board will have the best views possible. The capsule – which is entirely autom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH'S RICHEST MAN SET TO LEAVE PLANET!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-magnate-bezos-ready-ride-011406157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealthiest man on the planet Jeff Bezos will ride his own rocket to outer space on Tuesday, a key moment for a fledgling industry seeking to make the final frontier accessible to elite tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mandates make a return -- along with controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mask-mandates-make-a-return-along-with-controversy/ar-AAMkFmO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing calls to reinstate mask mandates have renewed their status as a cultural and health flashpoint a year and a half after the virus landed in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL Menu Hit Hard By Nationwide Shortages Of Ingredients...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/taco-bell-menu-ingredients-shortage-chicken-beef-lettuce-tortillas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chain cites "transportation delays happening throughout most of the industry" as reason why its eateries are out of some items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Employers CAN Fire You for Not Getting Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.worth.com/vaccine-workplace-employers-legal-questions-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.worth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worth sat down with Domenique Camacho Moran, a partner at Farrell Fritz, to discuss the legal questions associated with going back to the office coming off a global pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer creates wedding dress made entirely from dumped face-masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3313195/wedding-dress-made-from-dumped-face-masks/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DESIGNER has created a wedding dress made entirely from dumped face-masks – as all wedding restrictions were lifted. Designer Tom Silverwood stitched together material from 1,500 masks to create …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside BLUE ORIGIN craft where everyone gets window seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3310172/blue-origins-new-shepard-rocket-bezos-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS BLUE Origin’s 60ft New Shepard rocket readies for launch its founder Jeff Bezos has guaranteed those on board will have the best views possible. The capsule – which is entirely autom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems propose requiring women to register for military draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/19/senate-democrats-propose-women-military-drafts-500153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Armed Services Chair Jack Reed has proposed changing draft registration requirements to include all Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat Wave Bakes Rockies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/heat-wave-bakes-the-northern-rockies/ar-AAMjywt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A summer of unrelenting heat in the western United States and Canada hit the Northern Rockies this weekend, where temperatures reached the upper 90s and lower 100s with a heat wave that is expected to peak on Monday but ease only slightly through the week. It was the fourth major heat wave to afflict parts of the West since early June, bringing dangerously hot temperatures and helping fuel the deepening drought and exploding wildfires across the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Firm paid top Biden adviser...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9801185/Israeli-firm-Pegasus-spyware-paid-Biden-adviser-Anita-Dunn-PR-advice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NSO, the private Israeli firm behind the controversial spyware Pegasus, had previously launched a public relations crusade led by Anita Dunn's PR firm SKDKnickerbocker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Washington power brokers gained...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/How-Washington-power-brokers-gained-from-NSO-s-16324343.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli surveillance giant NSO Group and companies linked to it or its founders have...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
