<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of phone call now imperiling Trump presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ab67c31d9b3c4acdada93a624052ddc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — There were dozens of ears listening to President Donald Trump's 30-minute phone call with the leader of Ukraine that is at the center of a House impeachment inquiry , and as many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Johnson back in spotlight for 1868 impeachment brush...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9c876cd412a443b79be5f0bd9f569031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president traveled the country, fanning racial animus. He viewed the Congress with disdain. He also tried to undo some of the most important achievements of his predecessor, using executive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador clash site has party clowns, recycling, tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3163699112084840882bcb603cb7aa2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — As a military helicopter circled overhead, a volunteer clown in a red rubber nose sang a nonsense song to laughing children outside a public theater. Volunteers inside...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell tightlipped as furor grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/465368-mcconnell-tightlipped-as-impeachment-furor-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is keeping a low profile amid the growing impeachment battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq War whistleblower film has Bush and Blair in its sights...</title>
      <link>https://sg.style.yahoo.com/iraq-war-whistleblower-film-bush-blair-sights-100150825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British whistleblower responsible for a dramatic leak in the run-up to the 2003 invasion of Iraq and now the subject of a Hollywood film hopes it will refocus attention on the flawed evidence that led to war. Ex-spy Katharine Gun -- played by British star Keira Knightley in the new movie "Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, several injured in Brooklyn club shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/12/4-dead-3-seriously-injured-in-brooklyn-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four men were killed and five others injured in a gruesome mass shooting on Utica Avenue in Brooklyn early Saturday, authorities said. The shooting unfolded just before 7 a.m. at what is believed t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amkara steps up assault on Kurds defying sanctions threats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/turkey-steps-assault-syria-kurds-defying-sanctions-threats-130548288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ras al-Ain (Syria) (AFP) - Ankara stepped up its assault on Kurdish-held border towns in northeastern Syria on Saturday, defying mounting threats of international sanctions, even from Washington. Buoyed by a night of steady advances in the countryside, Turkish troops and their Syrian allies entered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgy on Yacht Testing Orban's Iron Grip on Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sex-video-scandal-engulfs-orbans-080529072.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A video of one of Prime Minister Viktor Orban’s allies participating in an orgy on a luxury yacht has presented an unexpected gift to Hungary’s opposition on the eve of local elections. Can it make a difference?In neighboring Austria, a damaging tape was able to bring down a government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accounting Tricks Making Earnings Look Stronger Than They Are...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beware-funny-financials-000005786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- However frothy valuations currently seem to be, optimists can always argue they’re justified by strong earnings. In the past four years, S&amp;P 500 operating earnings per share have grown by nearly 40%.Those numbers, however, may be as airy as the asset prices they support. The U.S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American forces come under Turkish artillery fire in Syria...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191011235548-5tqgx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-USA-BLAST (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-U.S. troops in Syria came under fire from Turkish positions -Pentagon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American forces come under Turkish artillery fire in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/us-troops-syria-turkey-1464727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT CELEBRATES</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/oh-thats-a-shame-trump-gleefully-reacts-to-shepard-smiths-fox-news-exit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was no fan of Fox News anchor Shepard Smith. And the news that Smith is leaving the network seemed to make the president's day. Speaking outside the White House en route to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHEP LEAVES FOX</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-shephard-smith-leaving-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News announced late Friday afternoon the anchor is out after 23 years with the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLEAGUES STUNNED</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/a-little-stunned-and-a-little-heartbroken-watch-foxs-neil-cavutos-shocked-real-time-reaction-to-shepard-smiths-departure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Neil Cavuto opened his broadcast Friday looking positively shocked by the suddenly-announced departure of long time colleague Shepard Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA WILDFIRES RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-10/saddleridge-fire-sylmar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-moving Saddleridge fire in the San Fernando Valley has charred dozens of homes, closed freeways and forced thousands to flee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Said to Be Under Investigation for Ukraine Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/12/giuliani-is-said-to-be-under-investigation-for-ukraine-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Federal prosecutors in Manhattan are investigating whether President Trump’s personal lawyer Rudolph W. Giuliani broke lobbying laws in his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man becomes first ever to run marathon in under two hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/othersports/article-7565337/Eliud-Kipchoge-begins-attempt-beat-two-hour-marathon-barrier-Vienna.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid jubilant scenes in Vienna on Saturday morning, Eliud Kipchoge became the first runner to finish a marathon in under two hours. He celebrated with his arms outstretched and waved to crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man using oxygen tank died within mins of power shutoff...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/2019/10/11/pollock-pines-family-says-man-died-when-oxygen-tank-lost-power-during-pge-shut-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLLOCK PINES -- The family of 67-year-old Robert Mardis Sr. believes he would still be alive if PG&amp;E didn't shut off their power this week in Pollock Pines. "He had health issues," Mardis' daughter, Marie Aldea, told FOX40. "He had really bad COPD, which didn't help, and he had congestive heart failure and other health issues, but the power going off and him not being able to get to his oxygen is, I believe, is what did it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CRITIC EXITS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6b9f26f305ba4846b35bd8aa165d9959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Shepard Smith, whose newscast on Fox News Channel seemed increasingly an outlier on a network dominated by supporters of President Donald Trump, abruptly quit after signing off his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Distances Himself from Rudy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/politics/donald-trump-rudy-giuliani-ukraine-fallout/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the career ambassador ousted by President Donald Trump was describing to lawmakers Friday the shadow diplomacy carried out by Rudy Giuliani, the President was across town beginning to doubt his attorney's continued ability to defend him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK cryptocurrency coalition falling apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/11/ebay-drops-out-of-facebook-libra-cryptocurrency-one-week-after-paypal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news comes one week after PayPal announced its withdrawal as government regulators continue to scrutinize the plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House accidentally sends talking points to Dems -- again...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/465457-white-house-accidentally-sends-ukraine-talking-points-to-democrats-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House accidentally sent Democrats a list of talking points related to ex-Ukraine Ambassador Marie Yovanovitch’s Friday House deposition, two sources with knowledge of the email told The Hill, the second time in a month the administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESAME STREET Muppet Reveals Mother Battling Opioids...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/2019/10/11/sesame-street-fans-react-muppet-karli-mother-opioid-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, Sesame Street introduced a new character, a green Muppet with yellow hair named Karli, and [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: ISIS militants break out of prisonafter bombing by Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-turkey-syria-prison-bombing-kurds-sdf-a9152536.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stinging Blow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-accountant-told-appeals-court-142207180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump, under siege from House Democrats weighing impeachment, suffered a stinging blow as a federal appeals court upheld a subpoena ordering his accountants to provide Congress with his financial records.The ruling, by a divided three-judge panel of the U.S. Court of Appeals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEADED TO THE SUPREME COURT?</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7563373/Federal-appeals-court-turns-Trumps-attempt-block-Democrats-getting-tax-returns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An administration official with knowledge of the case said Friday that Trump will 'in all likelihood be headed to the Supreme Court for [legal] relief.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Police Response at Capitol Metro After Stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.popville.com/2019/10/huge-police-emergency-response-at-capitol-south-metro-confirmed-stabbing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo by Max Max writes at 1:01pm "What's going on??" From Metro Transit Police: "Confirmed stabbing. Police, medics o/s.  Capitol South Station: MTPD, MPD, USCP &amp; DC EMS o/s responding to a confirmed stabbing. Details will follow. The station is CLOSED at this time. Trains on Blue/Orang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incarcerated Felons Could Be Allowed To Vote In DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/local/305/2019/10/10/769086866/incarcerated-felons-could-be-allowed-to-vote-in-bill-moving-through-d-c-council</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine, Vermont and Puerto Rico currently allow residents in prison for having committed felonies to vote in elections. And D.C. may not be far behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising benefits of trash talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191010-the-surprising-benefits-and-risks-of-trash-talk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Channelling your inner Muhammad Ali might not always be as reckless as it sounds. Zaria Gorvett explains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter Of US Companies Now Allowing Employees To Work 4-Day Work Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/10/10/4-day-work-week-new-employees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With unemployment at historic lows, many companies around the country are attracting employees with all kinds of perks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanism At US Naval Academy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanconservative.com/dreher/satanism-at-the-us-naval-academy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanconservative.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Christian midshipman calls for 'civil dialogue' in response. A USNA source says, 'Dialogue with Satanism? Seriously?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Walking slowly is sign of aging fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7563395/People-walk-slowly-45-higher-risks-dementia-study-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duke University researchers found that the same people who were already walking slowly at age 45 looked older, had early signs of dementia, and had scored lower on mental tests at age three.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon deploying 3,000 troops, advanced equipment to Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/11/us-deploying-3000-troops-advanced-equipment-saudi-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military is significantly increasing troop deployments to Saudi Arabia, the Pentagon said Friday, announcing that 3,000 American personnel — including two fighter squadrons and an air expeditionary wing — will be sent to the Persian Gulf nation, as well as advanced missile defense systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE 'WHISTLEBLOWERS' CONTACTING CONGRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/more-potential-whistleblowers-are-contacting-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first two officials who came forward about the president’s pressure campaign on Ukraine seem to be just the beginning, according to Hill sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Slow walkers more likely to get sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/walking-slowly-aging-brain-body-sick-later-study-a9151976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fonda arrested in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/jane-fonda-arrested-protesting-dc-1247035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress was demonstrating on the Capitol with the group Oil Change International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 83&amp;#176; To 13&amp;#176;: Extreme Temp Drop In Denver Second Largest On Record!</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/10/11/denver-weather-largest-day-change-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official temperature in Denver dropped 70 degrees from Wednesday to Thursday. That change just missed the record for the largest 2 day temperature drop in Denver's history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine envoy shows up for depo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/470b8da7d0da439686342904906c5f43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch told lawmakers Friday that President Donald Trump pressured the State Department to oust her from her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0bca0959ed7a45939b7c922608c3dcc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A wildfire raged out of control along the northern edge of Los Angeles early Friday, forcing thousands of people from their homes as firefighters battled flames from the air and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Giuliani's relationship with arrested men subject of investigation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/rudy-giulianis-relationship-arrested-men-subject-criminal-investigation/story?id=66212654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The business relationship between Rudy Giuliani and men charged in a campaign finance scheme is a subject of the ongoing criminal investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen girls cry tears of joy at Trump rally --  that looks more like a Justin Bieber concert!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10112113/donald-trump-rally-minneapolis-minnesota-us-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s rally in Minneapolis has turned heads after people pointed out that it looked more like a Justin Bieber concert rather than a political meeting. Teenage girls and boys were see…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR IN RED SEA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10111909/iranian-oil-tanker-hit-by-explosion-near-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Iranian oil tanker was today hit by two rockets in a suspected terrorist act, according to reports. The huge blast struck the vessel belonging to the National Iranian Oil Company 60 miles from t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda moving to DC with plans to get arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/11/jane-fonda-steps-up-political-activism-moves-to-dc-for-four-months-to-stage-civil-obedience-rallies-fire-drill-fridays-at-the-capitol-over-climate-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two time Oscar winner Jane Fonda is once again trail-blazing with her legendary political activism. She’s moved to Washington, DC for the next four months to help stage civil disobedience ral…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU ambassador to testify in impeachment inquiry, defying State Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/e-u-ambassador-sondland-testify-impeachment-inquiry-defying-state-department-n1064966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for Gordon Sondland said he would speak to House Democrats, but that he would not turn over documents viewed as property of the State Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says oil tanker struck by missiles off Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/55f68b50763c40eeb25ee19027573d86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran said Friday two missiles struck one of its oil tankers traveling through the Red Sea off the coast of Saudi Arabia, a mysterious assault not immediately corroborated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELLEN LIKES BUSH!</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/10/11/why-ellen-degeneres-friendship-with-george-w-bush-is-so-controversial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s a list of stars DeGeneres has banned from her show because they had different beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forces push deeper into Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2beb641ae63a4a4fb07e77cfa962d68f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AKCAKALE, Turkey (AP) — Turkish forces pushed deeper into northeastern Syria on Friday, the third day of Ankara's offensive against U.S.-allied Syrian Kurdish fighters, as casualties mounted,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan State University bans 'racially, culturally, or ethnically based' costumes for Halloween...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/michigan-state-u-bans-mustaches-sombreros-aliens-in-orange-suits-mexicans-japanese-hypersexualized-racism-for-halloween/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students at Michigan State University are getting an education in how they can avoid offending people with culturally inappropriate Halloween costumes in what’s becoming a new tradition that undermines the university’s own identity. The unsolicited advice on what to wear on fright night appeared on message boards in campus residences this week to help students …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witches Having Resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/11/style/pam-grossman-witch-feminism.html?emc=rss&amp;partner=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pam Grossman, author and host of the popular “The Witch Wave” podcast, said witches are having a resurgence among feminists who want authority over their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not Weinstein Incident That May Bring Down NBC Execs. It's Everything Else...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/its-not-the-weinstein-incident-that-may-bring-down-nbc-execs-its-everything-else/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current unfolding of NBC News (mis)handling of sexual misconduct within its ranks is, without question, the biggest media story of the year (at least one that doesn't involve President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clock ticks as SPACEX builds craft for NASA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/clock-ticks-as-spacex-builds-craft-for-nasa/article_91b21da7-8fa4-577a-9efc-18f0d2c4f615.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks ago, the head of NASA seemed sick of waiting for SpaceX and Boeing Co. to finish developing the capsules that are supposed to carry U.S. astronauts to and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest of Giuliani associates ensnares 'Congressman 1'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd7b2b04b101440e9a5559b9501e24b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Businessmen with ties to Rudy Giuliani lobbied a U.S. congressman in 2018 for help ousting the American ambassador to Ukraine around the same time they committed to raising money...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Will Smith 'GEMINI MAN' Ossified Bore...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/10/gemini-man-review-will-smith-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Save your money and wait for it any minute now on late night cable TV.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
