<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NFL player tweets threats, racial slurs after loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/sports/browns-condemn-jermaine-whitehead-twitter-rant-containing-death-threat-racist-language-040542210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Browns called Jermaine Whitehead&amp;#39;s Twitter outburst &amp;#39;totally unacceptable and highly inappropriate.&amp;#39;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones Used in Crime Fly Under Law's Radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/drones-used-in-crime-fly-under-the-laws-radar/ar-AAJMnzH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'mother of all bubbles' could blow up economy, warns strategist...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-mother-of-all-bubbles-could-blow-up-the-economy-if-profits-dont-improve-warns-blackstone-strategist-2019-11-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our call of the day anticipates a recession will hit hard, but not for at least six months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPLACE HUMANS?</title>
      <link>https://interestingengineering.com/russian-firm-sells-autonomous-robot-clones-of-real-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;interestingengineering.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One family has ordered the robot clones to greet guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARAMCO Starts IPO With Saudi Prince's Economic Vision at Stake...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/saudi-capital-market-regulator-approves-050253953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want the lowdown on European markets? In your inbox before the open, every day. Sign up here.Saudi Arabia is pulling out all the stops to ensure the success of Aramco’s initial public offering after Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman finally decided to offer shares in the world’s largest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS POLL: 49%  WANT TRUMP REMOVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/nbc-wsj-poll-49-percent-now-back-trump-s-impeachment-n1075296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the president's support among Republicans remains strong one year out from Election Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON JR:  'BULLSHIT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-booed-at-second-sporting-event-in-less-than-a-week-this-time-at-ufc-championship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump went to New York City tonight to watch a mixed martial arts championship, and was greeted by boos according to videos and reporters at the event. Trump was also apparently not s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple earthquakes rattle Kansas, Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/kansas/article236963833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL: 49% WANT TRUMP REMOVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-49-percent-favor-impeaching-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of voters want President Trump impeached and removed from office, according to a new Fox News Poll. In addition, 6-in-10 believe the president did ask foreign leaders to investigate political opponents -- and two-thirds say that action is inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE FLOCK PRAISES CHRIST</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/03/over-1000-commit-lives-to-christ-at-kanye-wests-sunday-service/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL: Biden in dead heat  -- with Hillary?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/shock-poll-hillary-only-1-point-behind-biden-in-hypothetical-match-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Hillary Clinton entered the presidential race today, she would essentially be vying to be the frontrunner. Despite some 20 candidates competing for the nomination, a weak media-appointed leading candidate is providing an opportunity for the 2016 loser to rethink getting into the race. A new poll from Harvard Harris finds Clinton nipping at the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Schiff Takes His Case to a Bigger Ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/adam-schiff-a-trump-punching-bag-takes-his-case-to-a-bigger-ring/ar-AAJLmZe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tops Trump by 12 points in head-to-head matchup...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-biden-leads-nomination-race-tops-trump-by-12-points-in-matchup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic primary voters increasingly feel the need to nominate a candidate who can beat President Trump in 2020, and more think Joe Biden can do that than any of the other top Democratic hopefuls.  In addition, while most Democratic primary voters are satisfied with their field, over a quarter wish they had other options, according to a new Fox News Poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 person, 1 vote? Maybe not. NYC mulls ranked choice voting...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/government-news/2019/11/1-person-1-vote-maybe-not-nyc-mulls-ranked-choice-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A measure on New York City’s ballot this week will give voters in some future elections the chance to rank their choices 1 through 5 rather than picking just one candidate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death knell or $1M idea? Campaign tries to turn gaffes into gold...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/03/trump-campaign-2020-branding-064443</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Defends:  'You can cut through any wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/02/trump-smugglers-sawing-border-wall-064446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Health Now an Issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-warren-sanders-stay-on-top-health-is-now-an-issue-for-sanders-poll/ar-AAJL5OX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test could detect breast cancer 5 years early...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/blood-test-could-detect-breast-cancer-five-years-before-clinical-signs-11852901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test, which identifies the body's immune response to proteins produced by cancer cells, could be available in four years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Year Out: Divided nation lurches toward 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8149c3ca0e7461bb3cc3bd303063eff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One year from Sunday, voters will decide whether to grant President Donald Trump a second term in office, an election that will be a referendum on Trump's vision for America's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interest growing. So is anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eada3111efdf4880b492cac1ef376abe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A year out from the 2020 general election, there already is significant interest in the presidential campaign. But a poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigate Milwaukee acid attack as hate crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/local/2019/11/02/milwaukee-battery-acid-attack-man-burned-police-looking-suspect/4140669002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milwaukee police are searching for a suspect they believe threw acid on the man after an altercation Friday night near S. 13th St. and W. Cleveland Ave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans fury at birth coach who said only women can have babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7643251/Charity-hounds-birth-coach-post-saying-women-children.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doula UK found that Lynsey McCarthy-Calvert's Facebook post, said that only women have kids, breached their equality and diversity guidelines after trans rights activists prompted an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concussion rate for teen female soccer players rivals football...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional/concussion-rate-for-teen-female-soccer-players-rivals-football-study/iTmHIe0vmbSonev1LLNsNO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concussion rates in U.S. high school soccer are much higher for females than males, according to a UNC study published in Pediatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian capital Delhi gasps under choking smog...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/indian-capital-delhi-gasps-under-choking-smog-073555612--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India&amp;#39;s capital New Delhi was enveloped in heavy, toxic smog Sunday -- the worst levels in recent years -- with flights diverted or delayed as politicians blamed each other for failing to tackle the crisis. Every winter, the megacity of 20 million people is blanketed by a poisonous smog of car fumes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal drones ground water-dropping helicopters in CA fire battle...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/11/02/illegal-drones-interrupt-water-dropping-helicopters-during-critical-moment-in-maria-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As flames rapidly spread along a hillside in Santa Paula early Friday morning, firefighters were faced with a perilous dilemma: ground night-flying helicopters working to contain the growing fire or risk an aerial collision with a thrill-seeking drone. A Ventura County Fire Department helicopter pilot radioed in at 3:19 a.m. that a drone had been spotted flying above the flames, apparently trying to take a photograph or video of the scene below. Air operations were immediately stopped for at least 45 minutes until the sky was clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot police storm Hong Kong malls to nip more protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74137204c9d04da7b72bac4f53665a4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Riot police stormed several malls in Hong Kong on Sunday in a move to thwart more pro-democracy protests, as the city's leader heads to Beijing for talks on deepening economic...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
