<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AMLO under pressure over 'hugs not bullets' policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/05/mexicos-security-failure-grisly-cartel-shootout-shows-who-holds-the-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amlo strategy of alleviating poverty and a ban on corruption questioned amid recent cartel violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts fear voters will be deceived by 'deepfake' videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-05/deep-fakes-2020-election-silicon-valley-cure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technologists unveil the first significant effort to arm reporters and campaigns with software tools to combat the growing problem of "deep fake" videos. The effort faces formidable hurdles — both technical and political — and developers say there's no time to waste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Protesters Want to Soak the Rich, But That's Not All...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-protesters-want-soak-rich-050000214.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.Sharp divisions between the rich and poor are fueling a global wave of unrest -- but that’s just one of the grievances driving people onto the streets, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running just once a week could significantly lower risk of death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-running-just-once-week-could-significantly-lower-105213397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research has found that any amount of running, and even at a slow pace, could be beneficial for health and could help lower an individual's risk of death. The researchers analyzed the data to investigate the association between running/jogging and the risk of death from all causes, cardiovascular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orwell exhibit bares 'doublespeak' legacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d00f819347c04c08833fd3b419935b31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — War is Peace. Freedom is Slavery. Ignorance is Strength. Those were the slogans of the Party in George Orwell's 1949 novel "1984" that allowed the superstate of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elections in 4 states offer tests of 2020 voter enthusiasm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a713901560a8432ba36d24e65e68f4d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gubernatorial and legislative elections in four states Tuesday will test voter enthusiasm and party organization amid impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump and a fevered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aviation industry to counter 'flight shaming' movement...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191105110922-soqa0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIRLINES-ENVIRONMENT/IATA (PIX):Aviation industry to counter flight shaming movement: IATA chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORSESE: I Said MARVEL Movies Aren't Cinema. Let Me Explain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ie/entertainment/indepth/martin-scorsese-i-said-marvel-movies-arent-cinema-let-me-explain/ar-AAJSMU9?li=BBr5KbJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORMON MASSACRE: American mothers, children executed by cartel gunmen in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7650129/Relatives-say-5-US-citizens-killed-northern-Mexico.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventeen family members from the LeBaron and Langford families were 'ambushed' eight miles apart while heading to celebrate a wedding anniversary in three cars from La Mora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone trial promises political drama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf3e43dc56f244bda7dd6c4308d38e1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a longtime Republican provocateur and former confidant of President Donald Trump, is going on trial over charges related to his alleged efforts to exploit the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOBBS:  BETTER THAN GEORGE WASHINGTON</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dear-leader-goes-full-circle-trump-praises-great-lou-dobbs-for-praising-trump-as-greatest-president-in-us-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dear Leader goes full circle at Kentucky Rally: Donald Trump praises 'Great' Lou Dobbs for praising Trump as 'greatest president' in US history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST:  Pure, brazen contempt for Congress on full display...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Trump-s-pure-brazen-contempt-for-Congress-is-on-14809452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This editorial appears in The Washington Post.  - - -  "He must be brought forward to testify," President Donald Trump fumed on Twitter on Monday, regarding the whistleblower who revealed the president's corrupt attempts to extort political favors from Ukraine. "Written answers not acceptable!"  The president considered written answers more than adequate when special counsel Robert Mueller sought information from Trump during the Justice Department's Russia investigation. More to the point, if Trump were interested in fact-finding and truth-telling, rather than distracting from the substance of the charges against him, he would provide documents and encourage all relevant witnesses to testify. Instead, administration officials are refusing to testify before the House Intelligence Committee - officials who likely have firsthand knowledge crucial to the House's impeachment inquiry.  Robert Blair, an aide to acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney, was on the call during which Trump pressed Ukraine's president to investigate former vice president Joe Biden. John Eisenberg, a National Security Council lawyer, reportedly suggested limiting access to the transcript of that call and told others not to discuss it. Russell Vought, the acting director of the Office of Management and Budget, might shed light on Trump's peremptory suspension of military aid to Ukraine, an act that appears to have been an element in the president's corrupt pressure campaign.  These no-shows are just the latest examples of the contemptuous war Trump and his allies have waged on Congress and its legitimate, constitutional oversight role, starting well before the impeachment inquiry. Even when Republicans controlled both chambers, former White House adviser Steve Bannon absurdly claimed executive privilege to refuse to answer congressional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 most vulnerable senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/10-vulnerable-senators-2020-republicans-play-defense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;List includes two GOP senators running in states that Democrat Hillary Clinton won in 2016, but the most vulnerable senator of all is a Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China presses for more tariff roll-backs in 'phase one' trade deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-7649805/China-pushing-Trump-remove-tariffs-ahead-trade-deal--media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By David Lawder and Andrea ShalalWASHINGTON, Nov 4 (Reuters) - China is pushing U.S. President Donald Trump to remove more tariffs imposed in September as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING ABOUT 'WARNING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7648605/Donald-Trumps-Justice-Department-tries-BLOCK-Anonymous-tell-all.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Department has warned the anonymous author of a forth-coming tell-all about Donald Trump's White House  he or she may be violating nondisclosure agreements by writing the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN:  AMAZONFACEBOOKGOOGLE engage in abuse of personal privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/edward-snowden-says-facebook-amazon-and-google-engage-in-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking remotely at Web Summit, Snowden slams big tech companies, saying they make people vulnerable to surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubles, what troubles? Trump basks in populist love...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/troubles-troubles-trump-basks-populist-love-020104750.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking the stage in a packed Kentucky arena to the strains of America's unofficial patriotic anthem, "God Bless the USA," Donald Trump didn't look like a man in trouble. The ear splitting cheers from the crowd of around 20,000 in Lexington's Rupp Arena explained why. Dressed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARAMUCCI: President is Like Jim Jones cult leader...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/president-trump-will-be-out-of-office-by-march-2020-says-anthony-scaramucci-210434593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump insider Anthony Scaramucci predicts Republican leadership will force President Trump to leave office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman goes blind tattooing eyeballs...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/beauty/face-body/dragon-girl-24-who-has-spent-over-37k-modifying-her-body-goes-blind-for-three-weeks-after-tattooing-eyeballs-blue/news-story/43d40d9c7ca3af99cbc2c8fa8a07f360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who has spent over $37,000 modifying her body reveals she went blind for three weeks after getting her eyeballs tattooed with blue ink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER BURNS THROUGH ANOTHER BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/uber-shares-tumble-6-on-116-billion-quarterly-loss-2019-11-04?mod=newsviewer_click</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber has lost more than $7 billion so far this fiscal year, prompting a flurry of questions from some analysts about its long-term prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARAMUCCI: President is Like Jim Jones; GOP Drinking Kool-Aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/11/04/scaramucci-trump-is-like-jim-jones-unfortunately-gop-is-drinking-kool-aid-punch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During an interview on Monday's with Yahoo! Finance, former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci said he was disappointed Republican lawmakers have not turned on President Donald Trump yet because he believed Trump is like cult leader Jim Jones. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris and Corbyn Trade Brexit Barbs as UK Election Heats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnson-corbyn-trade-brexit-barbs-230030434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Prime Minister Boris Johnson and his main rival, Labour Leader Jeremy Corbyn, traded blows over Brexit as the U.K. prepares to vote next month on which of the two men should lead it out of the European Union.Johnson wrote an open letter to Corbyn asking him to clarify his strategy for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky governor looks for last-minute boost from Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dde5664a631345dea7fe1ce1e5c3597f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) — Pushing to help a Republican governor hold onto his office, President Donald Trump barnstormed for Gov. Matt Bevin of Kentucky on Monday, delivering a raucous election eve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a18021c61d964b0a94555b208ae7ebe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Dow Jones Industrial Average returned to a record on Monday, joining other market gauges at all-time highs, as the stock market's rally carried into a fifth week. Oil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat lays out White House campaign to oust her...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/19a3091850b546e9af821a5a4d9c1701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It started with a warning to watch her back, that people were "looking to hurt" her. From there, former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch told House investigators, it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Defeated' ISIS finds safe haven in Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/defeated-isis-has-found-safe-haven-ungoverned-part-iraq-n1076081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though President Donald Trump declared "100% of the ISIS Caliphate" defeated, the group is roaming freely in a remote part of Iraq, military officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT experimented with 4-day workweek; Productivity jumped 40%...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/microsoft-4-day-work-week-boosts-productivity-2019-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft said a four-day workweek in its Japan offices led to a 40% jump in productivity in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After blackface scandal, Va. Dems poised to take control...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/04/blackface-scandal-northam-virginia-election-may-go-way-democrats/4122064002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Ralph Northam's blackface scandal and Justin Fairfax's sexual assault allegations, Virginia Democrats were in chaos. Now they may win the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The Coming Middle East Conflagration...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/11/israel-preparing-open-war/601285/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel is bracing itself for war with Iranian proxies, as Tehran escalates its provocations. But what will the United States do if conflict comes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani associate now willing to comply...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-parnas-exclusiv-idUSKBN1XE297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lev Parnas, an indicted Ukrainian-American businessman who has ties to President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT 4-day work week 'boosts productivity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-50287391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology giant closed its offices in Japan on Fridays during the month of August 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demanding the impossible, Israel says pork can only be imported if kosher...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/in-effective-ban-economy-ministry-says-only-kosher-pork-imports-allowed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu's caretaker government quietly changes regulations to bar entry of pig products into country, though domestic production remains intact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checkpoint Charlie: Berlin bans 'US soldiers' from Cold War crossing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50293886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say local performers exploit tourists seeking photos at the iconic Cold War crossing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA formally pulls out of Paris climate agreement...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/468591-trump-pulls-out-of-paris-climate-accords</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday began the yearlong process of withdrawing the U.S. from the Paris climate accord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey says it captured slain ISIS leader's sister in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/turkey-captured-slain-leaders-sister-syria-66748048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Turkish official says Turkey has captured the older sister of the slain leader of the Islamic State group in northwestern Syria, calling the arrest an intelligence "gold mine."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALS revel in White House visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/11/04/kurt-suzuki-nationals-maga-hat-white-house-trump/4156375002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump called Suzuki to the podium and the MLB veteran put on the red cap that the president and his supporters have made famous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. career diplomats testify that State Dept. was misused for domestic politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/us-career-diplomats-testify-that-state-department-was-misused-for-domestic-politics/ar-AAJP99T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo's wife in talks to join 'Cartel Crew' reality show...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/04/el-chapos-wife-emma-coronel-aispuro-in-talks-to-join-vh1s-cartel-crew/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman might finally be able to see his beauty-queen wife — on a prison TV. Emma Coronel Aispuro, the 30-year-old wife of the notorious drug kingpin, is in talks to join VH…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. targets soon-to-be-published 'Anonymous' book...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/trump-admin-targets-soon-be-published-insider-book-anonymous-n1076161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'A Warning' — expected to be highly critical of Trump — is set to hit bookshelves later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Oklahoma inmates released in largest commutation in U.S. history...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/hundreds-oklahoma-inmates-will-be-released-monday-largest-commutation-u-n1076056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state has the highest incarceration rate in the country. But the governor wants to lose that ranking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice columnist sues for defamation over denial of rape allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/advice-columnist-e-jean-carroll-sues-trump-for-defamation-over-denial-of-rape-allegation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime advice columnist E. Jean Carroll filed a lawsuit against President Trump Monday, accusing him of defamation over his response to her allegation that he raped her in a department store dressing room in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Megachurch Pastor: Evangelical support 'incredibly damaging to the Gospel'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/468844-ex-evangelical-pastor-joshua-harris-says-supporting-trump-has-been-damaging</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former megachurch pastor and evangelical author Joshua Harris said in a recent interview that he believes some of the massive support President Trump has enjoyed from the evangelical community has been “incredibly damaging to the Gospel and t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorbachev warns US-Russia nuclear arms race has put world in 'colossal danger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10274411/mikhail-gorbachev-nuclear-war-fears-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Soviet leader Mikhail Gorbachev has warned the nuclear arms race between Russia and the US poses a “colossal danger” to humanity. The former world leader has now urged all nations to destroy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese 'IRISHMAN' Such an Event on Broadway  --  Tickets Are Being Scalped!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/04/martin-scorseses-the-irishman-is-such-an-event-on-broadway-that-tickets-are-being-scalped-on-stubhub</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to see Martin Scorsese’s “The Irishman”? In Manhattan, at Broadway’s Belasco Theater, the month long screening is such an event that tickets are being scalped on StubHu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In governors' races, president takes a risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-governors-races-president-takes-a-risk/ar-AAJONn6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump loses appeal of tax returns case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/04/trump-loses-appeal-of-new-york-tax-returns-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three-judge appeals panel in New York rejected President Donald Trump's argument that he is immune as president from criminal investigation by Manhattan D.C. Cyrus Vance Jr. while in the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screen time changing children's brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2019/11/04/too-much-screen-time-changes-brains-says-cincinnati-childrens-study/4124393002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cincinnati study is among at least half a dozen in 2019 revealing the harmful impact on young children of too much screen use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Reporter 'Cracker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/11/04/browns-cut-jermaine-whitehead-after-calling-reporter-cracker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cleveland Browns have dumped safety Jermaine Whitehead after he threatened a reporter and called him "cracker," in a Twitter post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews grow concerned over Internet antisemitism...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2019/11/04/wjc-president-ronald-lauder-demands-stricter-laws-against-antisemitism-on-the-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Jewish Congress Ron Lauder demanded action against antisemitism, especially new laws that would regulate its spread over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBUM HITS #1...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/business/chart-beat/8542364/kanye-west-jesus-is-king-billboard-200-debut-no-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West returns to a familiar spot on the Billboard 200 albums chart, as his latest release, Jesus Is King, debuts at No. 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside a wealthy LA man's effort to help pilots fight wildfires from a remote mountain base...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/inside-a-wealthy-la-man-s-effort-to-help-pilots/article_fb510d5e-2eb7-5e51-a560-e4a673470464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Perched atop the Santa Monica Mountains, there’s a prime chunk of real estate with stunning ocean views that’s owned by a wealthy former radio executive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Megachurch Pastor: Evangelical support 'incredibly damaging to the Gospel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joshua-harris-christians-evangelicals-donald-trump-bc402e29-6e43-462f-8067-5cc720426093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't think it's going to end well. "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  TRUMP STRONG IN BATTLEGROUND STATES...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/only-biden-tops-trump-battleground-113503041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump is competitive in head-to-head match ups with top Democrats in six key battleground states, according to a new set of New York Times/Siena College polls.Across Michigan, Pennsylvania, Wisconsin, Florida, Arizona and North Carolina -- the six states that Trump won most narrowly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From toast of town to toxic: FACEBOOK CEO on outs with Liberals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9cbd0627e4a4a90a778d5b819967cda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mark Zuckerberg's social network in Washington is shrinking. Bipartisan hostility against Facebook has been building for months, fueled by a series of privacy scandals, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress prepares for open impeachment hearings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b67704472c4c47889aecbe53eb4c32e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For only the fourth time in U.S. history, the House of Representatives has started a presidential impeachment inquiry . House committees are trying to determine whether President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censorship or caution? Culture war burns in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/22827c2b4a134c12a7162460d0b104b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — The clowns were already on stage, faces painted white, costumes carefully adjusted. It was to be the troupe's second show of "Abrazo," a play for children about a fictional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs Outnumber Children in San Francisco...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2019-11-2/marking-their-territory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Sheeler on the lavish life of Silicon Valley pups. As it turns out, San Francisco is not only home to Google and other innovators, it's also a dog-loving city, where dogs are treated better than Amazon employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferiority Complex: 8 In 10 Millennials Believe They Aren't 'Good Enough'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/inferiority-complex-8-in-10-millennials-believe-they-arent-good-enough/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 2,000 millennials reveals troubling statistics regarding how young adults see themselves in comparison to peers and older generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In historic shift, SALT LAKE TRIBUNE gets IRS nonprofit approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/11/04/historic-shift-salt-lake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Salt Lake Tribune is now a nonprofit, an unprecedented transformation for a legacy U.S. daily that is intended to bolster its financial prospects during a troubling time for journalism nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers to test election machines for vulnerabilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.routefifty.com/tech-data/2019/11/plan-engage-hackers-election-security/161045/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.routefifty.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Information Technology-Information Sharing and Analysis Center wants to create a coordinated vulnerability disclosure program that could alert vendors about security flaws in their voting systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are so many people over 55 going bankrupt?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-are-so-many-people-over-55-going-bankrupt-2019-11-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s one big reason bankruptcies have skyrocketed among older Americans, and how to bounce back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBUM HITS #1...</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/04/kanye-wests-jesus-is-king-debuts-at-number-1-on-billboard-200-chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West’s long-awaited “Jesus is King,” which released on October 25, has debuted at number one on the bellwether Billboard 200 chart. The explicitly Christian-themed album sold 264,000 equivalent album units in the U.S. in the week ending Oct. 31, according to Nielsen Music. 109,000 were physical album sales, while the rest was made up … More</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOCK PRAISES CHRIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/03/over-1000-commit-lives-to-christ-at-kanye-wests-sunday-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people gathered for Kanye West’s “Sunday Service” in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, after a last-minute announcement Friday. Curvine Brewington, a pastor at Crossroads Church in Lafayette, Louisiana, attended the event and shared his experience on Instagram, saying there was an “altar call” and “over 1,000” people gave their lives to Christ: Tonight, worship was … More</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  HILLARY BEATS TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/876179/hillary-clinton-leads-trump-new-fox-news-poll-yes-november-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll released Sunday did not have great news for President Trump. His approval rating was 42 percent, with 57 percent of registered voters disapproving of his job performance and 46 percent strongly disapproving. A year before the 2020 election, he is behind all of the top-tier Democrats, including former Vice President Joe Biden (51 percent to 39 percent), Sen. Elizabeth Warren (46 percent to 41 percent), and Sen. Bernie Sanders (49 percent to 41 percent). Even worse, Trump is losing to Hillary Clinton, who isn't even running, 43 percent to 41 percent. Since Clinton is not running, it isn't clear why Fox News decided to ask voters to choose between her and Trump. The pollsters noted that the last time they included Clinton in a matchup against Trump was Nov. 3-6, 2016, during which period she was also leading Trump, 46 percent to 42 percent â€” and also actually running for president. Which, again, she isn't currently. The poll was conducted Oct. 27-30 under the joint direction of Beacon Research (D) and Shaw &amp; Company Research (R). They surveyed 1,040 voters nationwide on cellphones and landlines, and the poll's margin of error is Â±3 percentage points. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Majority say not better off financially...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/468802-majority-says-they-are-not-better-off-under-trump-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of respondents in a new poll said they are not in better shape financially since President Trump assumed office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Crowd Chants 'Lock Him up'... </title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-bernie-crowd-chants-lock-him-after-rep-omar-starts-trashing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘And place his cruel ideology in the dust bin where it belongs’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren, Mayor Pete circle each other in Iowa as caucuses near...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/61a81c3ffb4344dc85afe4438e35e267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECORAH, Iowa (AP) — Gaining momentum in the final three months before the Iowa caucuses, Elizabeth Warren and Pete Buttigieg offered sharply different messages this weekend as they inched closer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage over political 'kill list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20191104/outrage-in-germany-over-neo-nazis-political-kill-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel's government on Monday strongly condemned death threats against two leading Green party politicians by a neo-Nazi group, as concern mounts in Germany over a rise in right-wing extremism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNICIDE: MORE PEOPLE THAN THINK WANT TO DESTROY HUMANITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/omnicide-more-people-than-you-think-want-to-destroy-humanity_11032019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems fear candidates aren't ready for brutal Trump attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/04/democrats-tiptoe-pocahontas-hunter-trump-063942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: DOW RECORD HIGH!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/04/dow-futures-open-us-china-trade-deal-uber-marriott.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average reached a milestone as investor sentiment was lifted by optimism around a potential U.S.-China trade deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Outrage over killing of 'forest guardian' in Amazon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/outrage-over-killing-forest-guardian-brazils-amazon-211420729.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists expressed outrage Sunday at the killing of an indigenous "guardian of the forest" in Brazil's Amazon and called on the government to thwart illegal loggers in the region. Paulo Paulino Guajajara and another tribesman, Laercio Guajajara, were ambushed by loggers late Friday as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS 'Schooled' By RAVENS' 22-Year-Old QB...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/11/04/ups-downs-not-much-goes-right-for-patriots-in-loss-to-ravens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Belichick is going to have a field day with this game film during New England's bye week. The Patriots suffered their first loss of the season Sunday night, 37-20 to the Ravens in Baltimore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Of Quakes Rattle USA; Seismic Activity Rising...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/hundreds-of-earthquakes-rattle-the-u-s-as-the-level-of-seismic-activity-in-north-america-continues-to-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is the mainstream media being so quiet about all of the seismic activity that has been happening all across the United States?  During the last 7 days, there has been an earthquake swarm directly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf thanks police officer who arrested him 'for changing my life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/movies/2019/11/03/shia-labeouf-charlize-theron-al-pacino-hollywood-film-awards/4153334002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shia LaBeouf, Charlize Theron, Al Pacino, Antonio Banderas all had their moments to shine at the Hollywood Film Awards Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California conservatives leaving state for 'redder pastures'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-04/california-conservatives-republicans-leaving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Republican and conservative voters in California have decided to leave the state, for some because of disenchantment with its liberal political culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar As Finland's Rich Win Right To Hide Income From Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/uproar-finlands-rich-win-right-hide-income-media-2859447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finland may lack light in the autumn, but there's always national envy day to brighten the mood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran announces sharp rise in enriched uranium production...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191104-iran-announces-sharp-rise-in-enriched-uranium-production</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran announces sharp rise in enriched uranium production</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked audio allegedly captures racist tirade by White Nationalist Spencer...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2019/11/04/racist-tirade-from-alt-right.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Spencer sought to cast his brand of clean-cut ethnic nationalism as a respectable conservative alternative to nazism, coining the term “alt-right” to refer to it and successfull…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
