<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WEATHERS STORM</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/22/joe-biden-south-carolina-fish-fry-1376705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly 90 minutes on a sweat-soaked stage in South Carolina on Friday night, it was almost as if Joe Biden had put the uproar surrounding his comments about segregationists behind him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Rover on Mars Detects Puff of Gas That Hints at Possibility of Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/22/science/mars-curiosity-rover-methane.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Curiosity mission’s scientists picked up the signal this week, and are seeking additional readings from the red planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACK:  Extensive details of border security online...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Hacked-documents-reveal-sensitive-details-of-14028128.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent cyberattack on a U.S. Customs and Border Protection subcontractor didn't expose just the faces and license plates of thousands of U.S. travelers. It also revealed the inner workings of a complex surveillance network that border authorities have long sought to keep secret.  CBP officials have downplayed the significance of the material taken in the hack, saying only that fewer than 100,000 photos of travelers had been compromised and that none of those had been posted to the "dark Web," the corner of the Internet where stolen documents are often traded and displayed.  That assessment, however, woefully understates the number of sensitive documents that are now freely available on the Web - so much material, totaling hundreds of gigabytes, that The Washington Post required several days of computer time to capture it all.  The documents offer an unusually intimate glimpse of the machinery that U.S. officials depend on for the constant monitoring of legal immigration through the border. They also illuminate the government's plans for expanding its use of license plate readers and facial-recognition cameras, including such details as how many cameras are focused on which traffic lanes at some of the busiest border crossings in the world.  The hoard of hacked documents includes detailed schematics, confidential agreements, equipment lists, budget spreadsheets, internal photos and hardware blueprints for security systems.  Among potentially sensitive government material are internal Department of Homeland Security handbooks, border surveillance diagrams and dozens of signed nondisclosure agreements between the subcontractor and government authorities, as well as companies such as Microsoft and the defense-contracting giant Northrop Grumman. Microsoft and Northrop Grumman did not respond to requests for comment.  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete confronted by protesters after fatal police shooting...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/449839-buttigieg-confronted-by-protesters-after-fatal-police-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg (D) was confronted by protesters Friday night as the presidential hopeful and his city continue to grapple with the fallout from a fatal police shooting of a black man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel to remove liquor dispensers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/22/dominican-republics-hard-rock-hotel-to-remove-liquor-dispensers-after-tourist-deaths/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino in Punta Cana is removing all liquor dispensers in guestroom minibars after a string of suspicious deaths and illnesses in the past year at the Dominican Republic r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem presidential hopefuls seek black support at SCarolina fish fry...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-south-carolina/democratic-presidential-hopefuls-seek-black-support-at-south-carolina-fish-fry-idUSKCN1TM15M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fish fry in South Carolina on Friday drew the largest crowd of Democratic pres...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDS START SUNDAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ice-raids-targeting-migrant-families-slated-to-start-sunday-in-major-us-cities/ar-AADegXN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion world shaken by cultural appropriation claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190622-fashion-world-shaken-cultural-appropriation-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion world shaken by cultural appropriation claims</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCAL OFFICIALS WON'T COOPERATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/officials-agents-in-impending-ice-raids-shouldnt-expect-cooperation-from-local-authorities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal immigration agents can expect pushback from some public officials when they begin a mass roundup of migrant families with deportation orders, an operation slated to begin Sunday at the direction of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Brush With Police Puts Leadership Bid in Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/boris-johnson-s-brush-with-police-puts-leadership-bid-in-turmoil-1.1277059</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO MAYOR DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chicago-mayor-vows-shield-migrants-001052489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot condemned the Trump administration over planned raids of migrant communities and said she had ordered police to cut federal agents’ access to databases related to immigration enforcement activities.“We are all aware of the threat from President Trump regarding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police called to loud altercation at Boris Johnson home...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/jun/21/police-called-to-loud-altercation-at-boris-johnsons-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Neighbour records shouting and banging at flat MP shares with Carrie Symonds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road to 'BOND 25' full of potholes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/The-road-to-Bond-25-is-full-of-potholes-14028959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off his Oscar win for a film plagued by drama, Rami Malek has again found himself working on a rather chaotic production. He's been shooting scenes in Norway as the villain of "Bond 25," a working title for the 25th installment in the spy film franchise, but has yet to do so with James Bond himself.  That's because star Daniel Craig had to undergo ankle surgery last month after hurting himself on set in Jamaica, the latest injury to afflict an actor who famously once said he would rather kill himself than play Bond again. While filming a fight scene for 2006′s "Casino Royale," his first outing as the iconic character, Craig reportedly lost a couple teeth after getting hit in the face. With 2008′s "Quantum of Solace," he both tore his shoulder and sliced off the tip of his finger. Production on 2015′s "Spectre" halted for a few days so Craig could undergo a minor procedure after injuring his knee on set. (This guy commits.)  It's not unusual for production issues to set back a film - not even for Bond movies, given the mess that occurred with "Quantum of Solace" script revisions in 2007, when Craig himself stepped in to help after the Writers Guild of America went on strike for a few months. But everything has played out quite publicly with "Bond 25," to the point where actors have even addressed the issues on the record. Malek insisted in an interview with the British news website Digital Spy this week that Craig's latest injury doesn't spell doom for the film, which Cary Joji Fukunaga (TV's "True Detective," "Maniac") is directing.  "Daniel was injured, so they are shooting what they can," Malek said. "I talked to Cary yesterday and the schedule has been altered. I know that. But with a franchise like this, I think they have it together."  Perhaps, as Malek suggested, drama present since the very start of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/immigration/article231823753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor says won't cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/449819-chicago-mayor-says-city-wont-cooperate-over-reported-ice-raids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot (D) said she would take “concrete steps” to support immigrant communities after reports emerged that Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Iran reversal, did Trump break pledge to never 'telegraph' military ops?</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/with-iran-reversal-did-trump-break-pledge-to-never-telegraph-military-ops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said he would never signal U.S. military operations. Then he canceled strikes on Iran after an attack was in motion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaners find abandoned fetus blocking plane's toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cleaners-abandoned-foetus-blocking-planes-toilet-africa-094911270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cleaners found an abandoned foetus blocking the toilet of an plane in South Africa on Friday, the domestic FlySafair airline said, prompting the offloading of passengers and a police investigation. The foetus was discovered by cleaning staff as the plane was being prepared and passengers boarded for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than 100,000 'Got Away' From Agents So Far This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/20/illegal-immigrant-got-aways-five-year-high-border-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol has documented more than 100,000 immigrants who they know managed to illegally sneak past them and get into the interior of the country, the agency’s chief told Congress on Thursday, saying it’s the most in five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACK:  Extensive details of border security available online...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/06/21/hacked-documents-reveal-sensitive-details-expanding-border-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hack revealed the inner workings of a complex surveillance network that border authorities have long sought to keep secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying objects over Kansas City leave locals suspecting aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/06/20/flying-objects-kansas-city-locals-suspecting-aliens/1520096001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two flying objects in Kansas City, Missouri, left locals suspecting aliens and the National Weather Service with "no explanation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: The Norwegian island that abolished time: 'Cut lawn at 4am'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/20/sommaroy-island-norway-attempt-create-first-time-free-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Sommarøy, bright 24/7 in summer, say they want to do ‘what we want, when we want’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Robot Has Been Stuck on Mars for Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/06/nasa-mars-insight-lander-stuck/592234/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA will conduct a delicate rescue mission to free a probe trapped just inches below the Red Planet’s surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Work, Expertise Falling Out of Favor...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/07/future-of-work-expertise-navy/590647/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These days, it seems, just about all organizations are asking their employees to do more with less. Is that actually a good idea?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Hispanic population on pace to surpass whites...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2019/06/20/texas-hispanic-population-pace-surpass-white-residents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New census estimates show Texas' Hispanic population growth continues to surpass white population growth, with Hispanics on pace to soon represent a plurality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  GOOGLE 'Chrome' now surveillance software...</title>
      <link>https://www.siliconvalley.com/2019/06/21/google-chrome-has-become-surveillance-software-its-time-to-switch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.siliconvalley.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tech columnist’s latest privacy experiment found Google Chrome ushered more than 11,000 tracker cookies into our browser — in a single week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faced with rising far right, Soros looks West...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-soros/faced-with-rising-far-right-soros-foundations-look-west-idUSKCN1TL233</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Soros's Open Society Foundations, best known for funding civil right...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloves off...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/20/2020-election-democratic-primary-1373202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was the week that the battle for the nomination got real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Top Gay Donors Have Mixed Feelings About Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/06/20/in-hollywood-lgbtq-donors-like-buttigiegbut-theyre-keeping-their-options-open-227161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The young mayor’s candidacy may be historic, but many gay bundlers and donors in Los Angeles are skeptical of his ability to win in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIL NAS X More Than Just A Meme Lord...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/06/21/734485423/lil-nas-x-is-more-than-just-a-meme-lord-apparently</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet native parlayed his brilliance for virality into a breakout career via the year's most indelible single, and its most unlikely cultural flashpoint. But that was then.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground Robots to Probe Tunnels?</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/06/border-patrol-wants-robots-can-go-underground-and-report-back/157846/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security is looking for innovative robots that can navigate underground tunnels and communicate with headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000 targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/ice-launch-mass-raids-targeting-undocumented-families-sunday-n1020446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive roundup, which President Donald Trump telegraphed in a Monday night Twitter post, will take place in several cities across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold cut: America can't quit processed meat love affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/americans-are-still-eating-lot-processed-meats-study-finds-n1020371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The good news: American are eating less red meat and more poultry than 18 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ORDERED ATTACK... THEN PULLED BACK! </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-approves-strikes-on-iran-but-then-abruptly-pulls-back/ar-AADaA3K?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How seaweed is ruining Miami Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article231709143.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW on track for best June in 80 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-dow-is-now-on-pace-for-its-best-june-return-in-80-years-but-the-fed-could-change-that-in-a-heartbeat-2019-06-18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock benchmarks enjoy a nearly unfettered run-up toward records on the back of hope of an easy-money Fed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN:  U.S. PLANE WITH 35 ON BOARD SPARED...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Iran-says-it-refrained-from-shooting-down-US-plane-with-35-on-board-Tasnim-news-593262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden ties to segregationist senator spark campaign tension... </title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/nation/joe-biden-james-eastland-segregation-democratic-primary-20190621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has described his relationship with Sen. James Eastland, a well-known segregationist, as one he "had to put up with." But letters between the two men show a different kind of relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian's Mysterious Suicide Baffles Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/inside-comedian-brody-stevens-tragic-death-1219210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For A-listers like Zach Galifianakis and Sarah Silverman, Stevens wasn't just a friend, he was a comic savant, one of the few acts they would drop everything to watch — leaving them to wonder: Why did he take his own life just as his career was heating up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People who spend more time outdoors lead more fulfilling lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/People-who-spend-more-time-outdoors-lead-more-14025910.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been established that people who spend more time in parks and other natural settings tend to report higher levels of health and happiness, but new research shows there's actually a magic number for it.  According to a study published this week in the journal Nature Scientific Reports, spending 120 minutes a week strolling a tree-lined street or sitting by a lake can greatly enhance a person's overall sense of well-being. Less time didn't yield any significant benefit, the research showed.  Those who got in two to three hours in nature were about 20% more likely to report high overall satisfaction with their lives than those who spent no time outdoors at all. The benefits to physical health were even greater, with those who met the outdoors benchmark being 60% more likely to report being in good health than their cooped-in counterparts.  The figures were adjusted for a number of characteristics known to influence health and happiness, including socioeconomic factors, neighborhood characteristics and general demographics.  People who already spend a lot of time outdoors aren't likely to find these results surprising: There's already a substantial body of work linking green spaces to lower risks of heart disease, diabetes, obesity, asthma, mental health problems and overall mortality; and to greater rates of health, happiness, and cognitive development in children.  But most of these studies simply measured the physical characteristics of neighborhood environments. They didn't actually ask people how often they experience the natural world to create a gauge of nature exposure at the individual level.  That's exactly what the current research does, using a nationally representative sample of 20,000 people living in England. The authors note their approach is similar to what governments have used in the past to develop...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK lawmaker suspended for violently grabbing protester by neck...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/british-lawmaker-suspended-after-video-shows-him-violently-grabbing-female-protester-by-the-neck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British lawmaker was suspended Friday by Prime Minister Theresa May’s office after video appeared to show him violently removing a protester from an event the previous night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to longest day! Revellers, druids celebrate summer solstice...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7165391/Hordes-sun-worshippers-gather-Stonehenge-ahead-traditional-summer-solstice-sunrise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who observed the spectacle at the neolithic Wiltshire monument encountered a chilly morning accompanied by clear skies as the sun glinted over the horizon at 4.52am.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN: Forget polls, he is going to win easily...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7163567/PIERS-MORGAN-Trumps-going-win-easily-2020-unless-Democrat-ostriches-drag-heads-sand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The polls don't look good for Donald Trump. I mean, by any normal yardstick, the President is heading for a defeat in the 2020 election.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SOAR TO NEW HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/21/stock-market-us-stocks-focus-on-tensions-with-iran.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 fell slightly on Friday after reaching a fresh record high earlier in the day as Wall Street concluded a strong week of gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billion-dollar back surgery scam involved doctor kickbacks, fake hardware...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/whistleblowers-expose-billion-dollar-back-surgery-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men join forces to expose a scheme involving sometimes unnecessary spinal fusion surgery, kickbacks to doctors and dangerous counterfeit surgical hardware implanted in some patients' bodies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK court orders forced abortion for disabled woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/uk-court-orders-forced-abortion-for-disabled-woman-34728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British judge has authorized doctors to perform an abortion on a pregnant Catholic woman with developmental disabilities and a mood disorder, despite the objections of the woman’s mother and the woman herself. The woman is 22 weeks pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOYS 'R' US Back From Dead; Will Open Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-06-21/toys-r-us-back-from-the-dead-will-open-u-s-stores-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Living drug' has cancer 'on the run'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-48706822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors say some lymphoma patients are being completely cured in a way "never been seen before".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 30,000?</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/the-dow-jones-industrial-average-could-hit-30-000-this-is-how-51561127084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years ago, we predicted the Dow Jones Industrial Average could hit 30,000 by 2025. With the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates, and a possible trade deal, it could happen sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DEPORTING ILLEGALS AT SLOWER PACE THAN OBAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/immigration-ice-deportation-trump-obama-a72a0a44-540d-46bc-a671-cd65cf72f4b1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But there have been more deportations so far than any other full fiscal year of Trump's presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller prosecutor Weissman inks book deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/andrew-weissman-book-deal-mueller-investigation-2b3c18de-9d5a-4f47-98bc-04af73d84f94.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Weissman worked on the team that prosecuted Paul Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man strips naked in security line at Detroit Airport...</title>
      <link>https://wwjnewsradio.radio.com/articles/man-strips-naked-detroit-metro-airport-mcnamara-terminal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wwjnewsradio.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers at Metro Airport got quite an eyeful this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCarolina trip may test if stumbles matter...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/nation-world/bidens-south-carolina-trip-may-test-if-stumbles-matter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has sat atop the crowded Democratic presidential field from virtually the moment he joined the race, leading the polls, raking in money and campaigning with the air of an inevitable nominee. But his recent fumbles on abortion and race are a reminder that early front-runners often face the most intense scrutiny. The former vice president&amp;rsquo;s strengths and weaknesses will be on display this weekend when he joins virtually every other White House hopeful in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: President threatened reporter with prison time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/449688-time-reporter-confronts-trump-were-you-threatening-me-with</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump reportedly appeared to threaten a Time magazine reporter with prison time after a photographer tried to take a picture of a letter from North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, Time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special prosecutor appointed in Jussie Smollett case, new charges possible...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/c/jussie-smollett-special-prosecutor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Empire" star could be prosecuted again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more Americans reported dead after Dominican Republic vacations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/21/two-more-americans-reported-dead-after-dominican-republic-vacations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more Americans — a man from Kansas and a woman from Pennsylvania — died during vacations in the Dominican Republic, amid a recent spate of tourist deaths in the country, according to a new repo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows chaos in Philly after massive explosion at oil refinery...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/21/massive-explosion-at-philadelphia-oil-refinery-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the moment a massive fireball erupted from a 150-year-old oil refinery in south Philadelphia when a vat of butane exploded early Friday — in a spectacle that could be seen from miles away a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Michael Jackson costume for Brussels' peeing boy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-michael-jackson-costume-brussels-peeing-boy-104743965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brussels has decided against decorating its iconic Manneken-Pis statue in a Michael Jackson costume as planned for the 10th anniversary of the US pop icon's death, officials said Friday. The decision was made in the wake of a new documentary, "Leaving Neverland", which since its release</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLINK OR BLUFF?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/did-trump-just-blink-bluff-100815556.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics Was it all a bluff? After news leaked that President Donald Trump approved and then called off U.S. airstrikes on Iran last night, it emerged he’d warned Tehran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Puzzled By 'Alarming' Number Of Dolphins Turning Up Dead Along Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/06/19/researchers-trying-figure-out-dolphins-dying-gulf-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are puzzled by a disturbing trend in the waters along four Gulf Coast states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOO LATE TO BE BULLISH'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/too-bullish-record-stock-run-215017117.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The S&amp;P 500 is up 18% and powering toward its biggest first half since 1997. For bulls, things are great. Will they get any better?To a handful of cross-asset strategists who turned skeptical on stocks before this week’s manic sessions, that’s becoming the most pressing question. Increasingly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants could be 1st to get genetically modified salmon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef674ab9b2ad48b39a7203d9535e3957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial telescope to be built on sacred Hawaiian peak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed9b871b97314a0e832fb4116a8d22b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New drug to boost women's sex drive approved in US...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e05529a07a7942479327843ddfa1896c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 wander through military bombing range...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/border-agents-rescue-illegals-wandering-through-az-bombing-range/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents rescued more than a dozen illegal immigrants who strolled onto a military bombing range in Arizona Monday night and got lost. Officials said the 17 illegal immigrants who lost their way are lucky they weren’t blown to smithereens or consumed by the unforgiving desert, though they will be prosecuted for immigration violations. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of Haitians crossing into Texas...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/surge-of-haitians-arrested-at-southern-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Border Patrol agents assigned to the Del Rio Station in Texas have arrested a group of Haitian nationals every day this past last week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
