<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LA Masking Up -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/los-angeles-county-health-order-bring-back-face-masks-public-transit/11777635/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County will issue a new COVID-19 health order effective Friday that will again require masks to be worn on all public transit within the county.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris's chief of staff exits...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/harris-selects-new-chief-of-staff-as-top-aide-departs-white-house/ar-AAWsIeA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretly Filmed Footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10740809/Isnt-happy-hour-anytime-Johnny-Depp-makes-courtroom-laugh-asked-drinking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under cross examination from Heard's lawyer Benjamin Rottenborn, Depp spoke about his drinking and drug use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA STRIPS DISNEY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10740583/Florida-strip-Disney-privileged-tax-self-governing-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida lawmakers have voted to strip Disney of its special status as a self-governing area. The legislation potentially come into effect on June 1, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner Earth: Healing ozone hole, less smog, more eagles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-science-health-business-canada-14e791bd2f718ff052ba935435cac0b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With climate change, plastic pollution and a potential sixth mass extinction, humanity has made some incredible messes in the world. But when people, political factions and nations have pulled together, they have also cleaned up some of those human-caused environmental problems, including healing the ozone hole , clearing perpetually smoggy air and saving many species from the brink of extinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBEr Purposely Crashed His Plane, FAA Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-YouTuber-Purposely-Crashed-His-Plane-in-17114946.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration has found that Trevor Jacob, a daredevil YouTuber who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN+ to shut after only month...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/tv/news/cnn-plus-shut-down-warner-bros-discovery-1235237913/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. Discovery is shutting down CNN+ as of April 30, marking one of the company’s first significant maneuvers since completing the merger of WarnerMedia and Discovery less than two we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axed staffers 'aghast and furious'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/21/cnn-shutdown-leaves-axed-staffers-aghast-and-furious/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shock announcement that CNN+ would be shutting down operations less than a month after it launched has left out-of-work staffers “aghast and furious” over the company’s handli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired from Egypt into Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-704808</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the town of Shlomit in the Eshkol region near the Egyptian border reported hearing gunshots from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE PEN:  Choose 'between Macron and France'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220421-le-pen-calls-on-voters-to-choose-between-macron-and-france-at-final-campaign-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right candidate Marine Le Pen urged voters to choose "between Macron and France" as she held her final campaign rally in the northern town of Arras on Thursday, hoping to sway undecided voters ah…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill stripping DISNEY special tax status sent to DeSantis' desk...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/21/florida-lawmakers-send-bill-stripping-disneys-special-tax-status-to-ron-desantis-desk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida’s Republican-led House voted in favor of a bill on Thursday seeking to eliminate the Walt Disney Company’s special tax district which allows the company to self-govern its land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin prepares to wade into national politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/21/youngkin-midterms-national-politics-00026793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia's Republican governor will use new political groups as a vehicle to get involved in other state races in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkinson's -- Caused By Gut Imbalance?</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/imbalance-gut-bacteria-parkinsons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite being a disease in the brain, new research suggests an unhealthy gut could lead to the development of Parkinson’s disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV hosts giggle uncontrollably discussing NUKING New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10739749/Russian-state-TV-hosts-giggle-discuss-NUKING-New-York-Putins-hypersonic-missile.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The television hosts on the state-owned Russian television channel Russia 1 laughed as they talked about striking New York City with the Sarmat missile, which is also known as Satan 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp Fumes On  Stand As Drug History and Violent Texts Read...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/johnny-depp-drugs-trial-testimony-amber-heard-abuse-defamation-1235007235/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 10:05 AM: Johnny Depp faced further harsh and messy revelations today about his alcohol and drugs use while under cross examination in the $50 million defamation trial against Amber Heard. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman catches virus twice -- within 3 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/21/woman-31-catches-covid-twice-within-21-days-spain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists report shortest known gap between infections in fully vaccinated healthcare worker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Says Businesses Must Install Cameras -- and Cops Can View Without Warrant...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/04/21/houston-says-businesses-must-install-surveillance-cameras-and-cops-can-view-footage-without-a-warrant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: The Warrant for Metadata Act, DOJ will appeal order ending mask mandate, and more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  'Speak softly and carry a large Javelin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/speak-softly-and-carry-a-large-javelin-biden-unveils-latest-800m-military-aid-package-ukraine-updates/ar-AAWrvHq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents creating new last names for kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220414-the-parents-creating-new-last-names-for-their-children</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child taking the father’s surname by default? For many parents, it’s no longer such a simple choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostilities between 'Proud Boys' and 'Oath Keepers' Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/january-6-proud-boys-oath-keepers-hostilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House select committee is investigating not only coordination, but also animosity between two leaders of the Proud Boys and Oath Keepers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MASKED SINGER' HITS RATINGS LOW WITH GIULIANI...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/tv/ratings/masked-singer-rudy-giuliani-ratings-1235236880/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of criticism and anticipation, “The Masked Singer” episode featuring the unmasking of Rudy Giuliani finally aired Wednesday on Fox. The show’s installment with the fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding spirals into chaos after bride laces food with pot...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/pot-wedding-420856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 20--A Florida bride and a caterer are facing felony charges for allegedly adding marijuana to food served to wedding guests, many of whom fell ill after unknowingly ingesting the cannabis-lace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY BECOMES LONGEST-RUNNING PRIMETIME NEWS HOST IN TELEVISION HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andymeek/2022/04/21/fox-news-channels-sean-hannity-just-broke-a-primetime-cable-news-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hannity is now the longest-running primetime cable news host on TV today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All military bases exposed on GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-exposed-google-maps-russias-26759713</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secret Russian army bases and military infrastructure have reportedly been 'exposed' on Google Maps after users claimed that images of key locations had been 'unblurred'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old Jewish survivor of Nazi occupation dies during siege...</title>
      <link>https://www.chabad.org/5495941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chabad.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Seniors Really Are Happier, Kinder Thanks To Abundance Of Oxytocin...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/21/old-people-love-hormone-oxytocin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seniors really are kinder than younger generations thanks to the "love hormone" released in older people's brains, according to new research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Faces Probe on Whether He Lied Over Partygate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-faces-probe-on-whether-he-lied-over-partygate/ar-AAWs5vB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA company accused of faking hundreds of COVID test results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/beyond-outrageous-la-company-accused-of-faking-hundreds-of-covid-test-results/ar-AAWrjOt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE TYSON REPEATEDLY PUNCHES MAN ON PLANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/04/21/mike-tyson-repeatedly-punches-man-face-plane-bloodies-passenger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Tyson seemed to lose his cool on a plane on Wednesday night ... repeatedly punching a man in the face after the guy had apparently annoyed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jon Stewart Lost His Edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2022/04/the-problem-with-jon-stewart-tucker-carlson/629608/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon Stewart is comedy royalty. But the world has changed since he was at the height of his powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The superyacht that FLIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10738823/Luxury-656ft-vessel-transported-world-AIRSHIP-unveiled-new-concept-design.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept of the AirYacht, thought up as an eco-friendly alternative to a conventional luxe cruiser, would contain no engine and be positioned in harbour by tugboats once dropped off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fast Walkers Live 16 Years Longer!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/walking-faster-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Leicester have discovered a link between a person's walking pace and the rate at which they age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iger comeback?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/20/as-disney-flails-hollywood-weighs-a-possible-bob-iger-comeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood insiders questioned whether 71-year-old Bob Iger would be able to restrain himself from reaching for the wheel at Disney after a series of missteps by Bob Chapek.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad claims Mariupol win but won't storm holdout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-kyiv-business-europe-f0e1cd893715eda1e6bef696d9c47db3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin tried to claim victory in the strategic port of Mariupol on Thursday, even as he ordered his troops not to storm the last pocket of Ukrainian resistance in the war’s iconic battleground .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewest Americans collecting jobless aid since 1970...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-economy-unemployment-629c9afb8baaaed5502b12573ff27822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Applications for unemployment benefits inched down last week as the total number of Americans collecting aid fell to its lowest level in more than 50 years. Jobless claims fell by 2,000 to 184,000 last week, the Labor Department said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Wants Free Speech on TWITTER After Spending Years Silencing Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/musk-wants-free-speech-on-twitter-after-spending-years-silencing-critics/ar-AAWrjGk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia missile test fuels fears of isolated Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/04/21/world/russia-missile-test-fuels-us-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is growing concern in Washington that Russia is now so cut off from the world that Putin sees little downside to provocative actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Army plane heading to Nationals Park parachute jump prompts Capitol evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/national-international/police-order-evacuation-of-us-capitol-over-aircraft-threat/3030383/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident suggested a stunning communications failure between the military, the Federal Aviation Administration and the Capitol Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-year-old awakes to man groping her on flight. He says he had 'nightmare'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/19-year-old-awakes-to-man-groping-her-on-flight-feds-say-he-says-he-had-nightmare/ar-AAWqpEx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror master Cronenberg makes art from 'beautiful' kidney stones...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-horror-master-cronenberg-makes-art-from-beautiful-kidney-stones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian film-maker David Cronenberg has been shocking audiences for decades with his graphic "body horror" movies but he has now gone further by creating art from his own insides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reinforces tight control over plane crash mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-china-reinforces-tight-control-over-plane-crash-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of China's deadliest air crash in decades remains a mystery, with authorities giving few details in a preliminary report on Wednesday while enforcing strict censorship one month after the d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Pardon for Bannon, 2 to Admit Bilking Donors to Border Wall...</title>
      <link>https://thenyledger.com/news/after-pardon-for-bannon-2-to-admit-bilking-donors-to-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenyledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The defendants defrauded hundreds of thousands of donors, capitalizing on their interest in funding a border wall to raise millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of era as NETFLIX faces stagnation challenges...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-04-era-netflix-stagnation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having lost subscribers for the first time in more than a decade, Netflix faces the new challenge of stagnation from a position of strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After life of trauma, Liberian lab chimps settle into retirement...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-04-life-trauma-liberian-lab-chimps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floating on a river boat near a Liberian island, vet Richard Ssuna watches intently as animal carers wade towards the shore hurling fruits and imitating chimpanzee calls as they go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I've Had It With This Guy': GOP Leaders Privately Blasted Trump After Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/21/ive-had-it-with-this-guy-g-o-p-leaders-privately-blasted-trump-after-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days after the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol building, the two top Republicans in Congress, Representative Kevin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA's Star Witness: Indict The Don Now or I'm Out...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/manhattan-da-star-witness-indict-091218324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast/GettyIf Manhattan prosecutors don’t indict former President Donald Trump with the grand jury they’ve got in the next nine days, the key witness investigators have used to build their entire case says he won’t help revive it in the future.Michael Cohen, the New York lawyer Trump used for years as his family company’s trusted consigliere, told The Daily Beast he’s already wasted too much of his time on a case that slowly and then suddenly doesn’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Zelensky's blue-collar hometown, praise for president's 'steel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-zelensky-e2-80-99s-blue-collar-hometown-praise-for-the-president-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98steel-e2-80-99/ar-AAWrah0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old Jewish survivor of Nazi-occupied Mariupol dies during Russian siege...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/91-year-old-jewish-survivor-of-nazi-occupied-mariupol-dies-during-russian-siege/ar-AAWr3We</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding spirals into chaos after bride laces food with pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wedding-spirals-into-chaos-after-bride-allegedly-laced-food-with-pot/ar-AAWqBH9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busing migrants, halting trade: Abbott bets future on border plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/busing-migrants-halting-trade-abbott-bets-future-on-divisive-border-plans/ar-AAWqpWg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of federal dollars to cut emissions will come with few strings attached...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/billions-of-federal-dollars-to-cut-emissions-will-come-with-few-strings-attached/ar-AAWqSO4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers push to uncover riches shielded by state secrecy laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/lawmakers-push-to-uncover-riches-shielded-by-state-secrecy-laws/ar-AAWrm1v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas Split With SPOTIFY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/topstocks/the-obamas-are-leaving-spotify/ar-AAWrAUU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA sticks to tough stance on unruly flyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/transportation/unruly-airplane-passengers-tsa-20220420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,200 unruly passenger incidents were reported this year through mid-April, roughly 800 of which were related to masks, according to the FAA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan state senator gains national spotlight pushing back against 'hateful garbage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/michigan-state-senator-gains-national-spotlight-pushing-back-against-hateful-garbage/article_8e014b02-3ec2-5e62-b93b-fa2728a96224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. — A five-minute speech from Michigan Sen. Mallory McMorrow gained national attention Tuesday and more than 9 million views on social media as the Royal Oak Democrat spoke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to appeal ruling...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/20/cdc-asks-doj-to-appeal-ruling-to-bring-back-mask-mandate-on-planes-trains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department filed a notice Wednesday that it will appeal a Florida federal judge’s order striking down the long-running rule that forced plane and train passengers to wear masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Giuliani unveiled on 'MASKED SINGER,' prompting judge to walk off...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rudy-giuliani-unmasking-masked-singer-081444123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The Hangover’ star was not impressed by the revealing of Donald Trump’s former advisor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Stumble Warning Sign for Streaming Industry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/20/netflixs-stumble-could-be-a-warning-sign-for-streaming-industry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many entertainment executives, tired of playing catch-up to a Silicon Valley interloper, have been waiting for the comeuppance of Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza violence intensifies as Jerusalem clashes resume...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-jerusalem-middle-east-tel-aviv-gaza-strip-f9eb9b51e57ac3883de98a0c64cfa692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israel’s air force and Palestinian militants traded fire across the Gaza frontier early Thursday as clashes erupted again at Jerusalem’s most sensitive holy site, worsening an escalation that has been eerily similar to the lead-up to last year’s Israel-Gaza war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy 'kills' drone with LASER for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5164733/us-navy-kills-drone-with-electric-powered-laser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Navy has deployed a new electric laser weapon with massive defensive upside. The weapon can take lethal and non-lethal measures to disable or destroy targets. The laser was tested on a drone…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai children in Hazmats...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5168424/unsettling-footage-children-shanghai-hazmat-suits-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNSETTLING footage appears to show young children in Shanghai dressed in hazmat suits amid China’s zero Covid policy. The dystopian clip shows a group of youngsters covered from head to toe h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron, Le Pen in final push for votes after fiery debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-macron-le-pen-in-final-push-for-votes-after-fiery-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron and far-right rival Marine Le Pen on Thursday launched a final push for votes in working class heartlands of France after a pre-election debate marked by bitter clashes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskaholics still covering...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/the-failed-covid-policy-of-mask-mandates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wearing a mask may still give some people a sense of security, but they could breathe more easily if they’d face the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING IS BLEEDING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-canada-netflix-inc-abd9845644a87b434e53c1c13bbb377a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — An unexpected drop in subscribers sent Netflix shares into freefall Wednesday, forcing the company to consider experimenting with ads and -- hold onto your remote -- cracking down on millions of freeloaders who use passwords shared by friends or family .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Carnival parade is back, as street bands ache to party...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-travel-business-arts-and-entertainment-559b38d96a78810da8bdf4e41fca78e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Rio de Janeiro's Mayor Eduardo Paes on Wednesday ceremonially handed control of the city to King Momo, a ritual representing the upheaval of the status quo -- but it remains to be seen how much post-pandemic partying is in store during the first Carnival in two years.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
