<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Saudi women mount 'inside-out' abaya protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-women-mount-inside-abaya-protest-010827371.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi women have mounted a rare protest against the abaya, posting pictures on social media wearing the obligatory body-shrouding robe inside out. Powerful Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman in March said wearing the robe was not mandatory in Islam, but in practice nothing changed and no formal edict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No end game in sight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dem-power-players-want-pelosi-centrists-push-back-081605940--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now they just need a speaker of the House. The standoff over Nancy Pelosi's bid to regain the gavel intensified Friday as Democrats left Washington for the Thanksgiving holiday, an unsettling finish to an otherwise triumphant week that saw them welcome a historic class of newcomers to Capitol Hill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Preps Drama About First Lady Who Divorves Husband...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/first-lady-of-the-united-states-drama-produced-by-michael-weatherly-eric-christian-olsen-in-works-at-cbs-1202503904/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bull star Michael Weatherly and NCIS: Los Angeles co-star Eric Christian Olsen have teamed up to produce First Lady, a provocative drama, which has been put in development at CBS. Written/executive…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked chat logs on hacks may be part of case...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/leaked-chat-logs-may-used-prove-julian-assange-directed-hackers-204302522.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While transparency advocates and First Amendment activists have consistently worried that Assange’s arrest and conviction would set a bad precedent for the media if Assange is charged with espionage for publishing classified documents, it’s possible the charges will have to do with his solicitation of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind killing of Khashoggi...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cia-concludes-saudi-crown-prince-behind-khashoggi-murder-002605778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Central Intelligence Agency has concluded Saudi's powerful Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was behind the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, The Washington Post reported Friday, citing people close to the matter. The US assessment directly contradicts the conclusions of a Saudi prosecutor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At U.S. border, migrant caravan will slow to a crawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/at-the-us-border-migrant-caravan-will-slow-to-a-crawl/2018/11/16/01374426-e84e-11e8-8449-1ff263609a31_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. border guards can process 100 migrants per day, meaning months of waiting in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA:  PRINCE DID IT...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/middle-east/saudi-crown-prince-ordered-khashoggi-s-assassination-cia-20181117-p50gn3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Republicans look for way forward after stunning losses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e11342c7cb04477ea584013ad80f8cd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — In a speech to fellow Republicans in May, U.S. Rep. Mimi Walters issued an ominous warning about the coming election — California Democrats, she said, were "coming for all of us." She was right. The congresswoman's stunning defeat Thursday in the heart of Orange County, once a nationally known Republican stronghold, extended a Democratic rout that has seen five GOP-held House seats fall in the state, with another one threatened. Last week's election delivered mixed results around the U.S. — Republicans held the Senate, Democrats seized the House — but in California voters turned the state an even deeper shade of Democratic blue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials try to account for hundreds missing in fire's wake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8c36c0c9e664a90abe812f86a813736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — With the confirmed death toll standing at 63 in the Northern California wildfire, authorities on Friday struggled to determine how many of the more than 600 people listed as missing have turned up, or whose remains could still be in the ashes. President Donald Trump, meanwhile, will travel to the disaster zone Saturday to get a look at the grief and damage caused by the deadliest U.S. wildfire in a century, and he could face resentment from locals for blaming the inferno on poor forest management in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi meets with freshmen Dems key to speakership bid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59f12b3c780d4fa993a26004b7abcf08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi met privately Friday with several newly-elected Democrats who could be crucial to her bid for House speaker, as she works to tamp down discord and fend off a challenge from a small but persistent group determined to stop her from reclaiming the gavel. The freshmen entering and exiting Pelosi's stately office off the House floor indicated they were having good meetings with the leader as they prepare to join Congress as part of the largest Democratic class since Watergate. But few said the talks had changed their minds to vote to support her as speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIERY SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/stacey-abrams-to-speak-live-on-channel-2-action-news-at-5/874160971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coverage of this developing story throughout the night on Channel 2 Action News and on WSBTV.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Baker:  'Sword hanging over our heads'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/16/trump-jim-acosta-cnn-999675</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is drawing up rules for White House reporters' behavior, and the president said if journalists don't follow them, 'we'll end up back in court, and we'll win.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Social Credit System'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/11/15/report-chinese-telecom-giant-building-venezuela-social-credit-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese telecom giant ZTE is helping Venezuela to create a social credit system known as the "Fatherland Card," similar to the Beijing's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDUCT 'RULES' COMING...</title>
      <link>https://wwd.com/business-news/media/trump-tells-foxs-chris-wallace-conduct-rules-coming-for-press-1202908956/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wwd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president said “rules” are being written and if they’re not followed, reporters can still be thrown out of briefings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk building 'disturbingly long' tunnel underneath people's houses... </title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/elon-musk-is-building-a-disturbingly-long-tunnel-underneath-peoples-houses-and-theyre-not-happy-8146827/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the billionaire make our congested cities more pleasant - or ruin the lives of people living near his massive hole?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 1/3 of workers would prefer robot boss...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/15/plenty-of-brits-reckon-a-robot-would-make-smarter-decisions-than-a-human-boss-8143300/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would you take orders from a robot?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange charges opens door to criminal investigations of news orgs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/16/julian-assange-charges-wikileaks-997122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some liberals have defended Assange as a journalist, conservatives celebrated him in 2016 and Trump once declared his 'love' for WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP WARNS:  BEHAVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-warns-acosta-after-judges-ruling-if-he-misbehaves-well-throw-him-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army guardsman arrested for smuggling illegals over border...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/11/15/national-guard-soldier-arrested-charged-with-smuggling-mexican-nationals-into-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Guardsman was arrested Nov. 10 near San Diego when his car was stopped just north of the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northern Cal Air Quality WORST IN WORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/Smoke-From-Wildfire-Lingers-Spare-the-Air-Through-Friday-500543151.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke from the Camp Fire continued to smother the Bay Area on Wednesday, and there were few signs of it clearing soon, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathing San Fran air 'like smoking 11 cigarettes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-wildfires/article/air-cigarettes-smoke-breathing-aqi-unhealthy-13399240.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breathing the smoke-filled air in San Francisco today is equivalent to smoking more than a half-pack of cigarettes, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking backwards boosts your memory?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6398085/Walking-backwards-boost-short-term-memory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts from the University of Roehampton asked 114 volunteers to watch a video in which a woman had her bag stolen and then answer a questionnaire about what they could recall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Grave Threats to Press Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/11/16/as-the-obama-doj-concluded-prosecution-of-julian-assange-for-publishing-documents-poses-grave-threats-to-press-freedom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump DOJ's prosecution of Assange will be cheered by Democrats, as they unite to criminalize the core of investigative journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Sticky-fingered 'masseuse' nabs $60k from gambler...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/hollywood/fl-ne-hollywood-casino-masseuse-grand-theft-20181116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman posing as a masseuse stole $10,000 in cash, $6,100 in poker chips and a $50,000 Patek Philippe watch from a player at the Seminole Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino in Hollywood, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PREP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d2d1afb5fb545b1b4f526aed38f4cb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange will not willingly travel to the United States to face charges filed under seal against him, one of his lawyers said Friday, foreshadowing a possible fight over extradition for a central figure in the U.S. special counsel's Russia-Trump investigation. Assange, who has taken cover in the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, where he has been granted asylum, has speculated publicly for years that the Justice Department had brought secret criminal charges against him for revealing highly sensitive government information on his website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant species collects skulls, uses chemical weapons to kill prey...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2018/11/16/Florida-ant-species-collects-skulls-uses-chemical-weapons-to-kill-prey/6381542389215/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is filled with strange creatures, but skull-collecting ants are near the top of the creepy list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FLORIDA RECOUNTS BY HAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/politics/elections/2018/11/16/florida-recount-hand-count-ballots-whats-happening-senate-race-bill-nelson-rick-scott/2020142002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the Sunshine State's 67 counties, a small army of election workers and volunteers are examining ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Stacey Abrams ends run -- but won't concede!</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/kemp-holds-steady-lead-over-abrams-state-prepares-certify-vote/WI5zxjHjLNR2WbvcEBVYWL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Stacey Abrams ended her run for Georgia governor on Friday as the state prepared to certify...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs seized, beaten, killed in Chinese city amid harsh crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/dogs-seized-and-beaten-in-china-amid-harsh-crackdown-from-officials-on-strays-and-banned-breeds-a3992331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs are being seized and beaten by police in the city of Hangzhou, China, following a crackdown on strays and banned breeds.  Horrifying images and video shows animals being hit and drowned by the city's police who have issued a banned list of 34 dog breeds.  Owners are also banned from walking their pets between 7am and 7pm and face a fine of over £500 for violating the new rules.  Anyone found walking their dog at the permitted time but without a lead will face fines of around £100.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Iran to Be Declared in Breach of Chemical Weapons Ban...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-declared-breach-chemical-weapons-bans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is set to announce that Iran is not in compliance with the Chemical Weapons Conventions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City impounds 560 smart scooters, tells company to pay up...</title>
      <link>https://wtkr.com/2018/11/13/norfolk-has-560-bird-scooters-impounded-company-owes-over-93k-for-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtkr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bird will have to pay the city more than $93,365 dollars in order to get its scooters back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS WH correspondent throws shade at Acosta...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/major-garrett-throws-shade-on-jim-acosta-when-president-says-its-not-your-turn-you-give-up-the-mic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens getting drunk on boiled tampon juice...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/16/teens-are-now-getting-drunk-on-boiled-tampon-juice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kids these days will try just about anything to catch a buzz, from “boofing” beer to vaping vodka. Their latest cheap thrill? Feminine hygiene products. Teenagers in Indonesia are collecting menstr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD ousts chief who led Weinstein investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nypd-ousts-sex-crimes-chief-led-weinstein-investigation-210039743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The police commander who led the effort to arrest Harvey Weinstein has been removed as the chief of New York City's special victims division, part of a shake-up that was months in the making after a city watchdog found the unit was stretched too thin to properly investigate sexual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O Sells 725,000 Books on First Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michelle-obama-memoir-sells-well-1542399595</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama’s memoir “Becoming” got off to a hot start, selling more than 725,000 units on the day it was released, spurring its publisher to quickly order up more copies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea deports American, boasts of new weapon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9958adbb0ec84bb39b2ad29e51ecc0af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — North Korea on Friday deported an American citizen it says it detained for illegal entry, a U.S. official said, an apparent concession that came even as the reclusive nation announced the test of a newly developed but unspecified "ultramodern" weapon that will be seen as a pressuring tactic by Washington. The two whiplash announcements, which seemed aimed at both appeasing and annoying Washington, suggest North Korea wants to keep alive dialogue with the United States, even as it struggles to express its frustration at stalled nuclear diplomacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street newest billion-dollar battleground: Small town, USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/16/jp-morgan-and-goldman-are-on-collision-course-for-billion-dollar-deals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.P. Morgan and Goldman have been going head-to-head in investment banking arenas hundreds of miles from Wall Street, in places like Chattanooga, Tennessee and Carthage, Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Being Heckled, Portland Mayor 'Cannot Wait' for Term to Be Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/index.ssf/2018/11/portland_mayor_ted_wheeler_can.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he walked off stage Thursday after finishing a speech during which he was heckled, Portland Mayor Ted Wheeler muttered, "I cannot wait for the next 24 months to be over."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid robot prototype capable of heavy labor...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-humanoid-robot-prototype-hrp-5p-capable.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have developed a humanoid robot prototype, HRP-5P, intended to autonomously perform heavy labor or work in hazardous environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer Carcasses Left On Cars Outside YMCA...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/dead-deer-left-on-cars-of-somali-ymca-patrons-in-st-cloud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Cloud police are investigating a disturbing find on the hoods of two cars Wednesday night. Someone put deer carcasses on two cars parked at the St. Cloud YMCA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Survives CA Bar Massacre -- Loses Home In Wildfire Next Day...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/borderline-bar-shooting-woolsey-fire-destroys-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From bullets to flames, a woman survived two unthinkable tragedies less than 24 hours apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraplegic airline passenger forced to urinate in bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2018/11/16/paraplegic-flyer-forced-urinate-bottle-airline-investigates/2023540002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paraplegic athlete Darren Belling claims he was forced to urinate in a bottle on aÂ flyDubai flight because he couldn't access the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol deaths soar for middle-aged, women...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/11/16/alcohol-deaths-emergency-room-increase-middle-aged-women-addiction-opioids/1593347002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From 2007 to 2017, the numberÂ of deaths attributable to alcohol increased 35 percent. The death rate rose 24 percent. Deaths among women rose 67 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Foster kids forced to drink semen not sex assault, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2018/11/15/senon-louis-ramirez-conviction-overturned-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adams County District Attorney Dave Young on Thursday urged the Colorado legislature to update the state’s laws after a court overturned a man’s conviction in a graphic child sexual assault case on grounds that his actions did not constitute the crime of which he was found guilty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Says He Has Answered Mueller Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-says-he-has-answered-questions-from-mueller-1542392074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said he has answered a set of questions provided by special counsel Robert Mueller, but hadn’t yet submitted them to investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARE:  91,000 pounds of raw turkey recalled amid salmonella outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/salmonella-outbreak-91000-pounds-jennie-o-raw-turkey-recalled-today-2018-11-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jennie-O-Turkey recall is the first tied to an outbreak the U.S. Department of Agriculture says is widespread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage crews sick of being treated like trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/torpy-large-atlanta-garbage-crews-sick-being-treated-like-trash/FJ6ff0bMIdLORMXoDhL32M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AJC columnist Bill Torpy on the low pay and high on-the-job death rate of Atlanta's sanitation workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Trump Asking, Is Pence Loyal?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/16/us/politics/mike-pence-trump-administration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has repeated the question so many times that he has alarmed some of his advisers. But Mr. Trump has not openly suggested dropping Mr. Pence from the ticket in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Air in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-chokes-toxic-air-wildfires-rage-170430103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools and tourist attractions across the San Francisco Bay Area were shut Friday as smoke from California's deadliest ever wildfire a three hour drive away produced air quality levels worse than in polluted megacities in South Asia. The closures came as the number of people missing from the giant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA INFERNO TOLL RISES TO 66...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/officials-order-evacuations-camp-fire-threatens-8000-acres/story?id=59065896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Camp Fire is now the most destructive and deadliest in California's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimmel Begs Michelle O to 'Save Us'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/16/jimmy-kimmel-begs-michelle-obama-to-save-us-from-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC late-night host Jimmy Kimmel begged former First Lady Michelle Obama to "save" the United States from the Trump presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACOSTA GETS A PASS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ffb3a155f454a0893dc2d9db18c81d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge ordered the Trump administration on Friday to immediately return the White House press credentials of CNN reporter Jim Acosta, saying Acosta suffered "irreparable harm" from the decision to bar him. U.S. District Court Judge Timothy Kelly, an appointee of President Donald Trump, announced his decision following a hearing. The judge said Acosta's credentials would be returned immediately and reactivated to allow him access to the White House. CNN had asked the judge to force the White House to return the credentials that give Acosta, CNN's chief White House correspondent, access to the White House complex for press briefings and other events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Trump aide tell-all due to hit shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/16/trump-white-house-cliff-sims-book-996198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former top White House aide Cliff Sims is modeling his book on George Stephanopoulos’ tell-all memoir &amp;quot;All Too Human.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University mandates 'all students' take 'diversity and inclusion' courses...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11530</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You can’t map out social change."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FL RECOUNT BY HAND...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/797e56eb5f694a0787cbebfcf9370797</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — A hand recount began Friday in Florida's acrimonious U.S. Senate contest after an initial review by ballot-counting machines showed Republican Gov. Rick Scott and Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson separated by fewer than 13,000 votes out of more than 8 million cast. Under state law, a hand review is required when the victory margin is 0.25 percentage points or less. A state website's unofficial results show Scott ahead of Nelson by 0.15 percentage points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Brexit referendum 'more likely than ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7756229/second-brexit-referendum-more-likely-than-ever-as-fresh-poll-shows-voters-want-another-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SECOND referendum on Brexit is now “more likely than ever” as Theresa May’s political future remains on the brink, Tom Watson has said. Labour’s deputy leader said yet ano…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP JUDGE SIDES WITH CNN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/media/cnn-trump-lawsuit-hearing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal judge Timothy J. Kelly sided with CNN on Friday, ordering the White House to reinstate chief White House correspondent Jim Acosta's press pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers Can Track Thanksgiving Turkey's 'Life Story'; Personal Details Including Where Came From...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/thanksgiving-turkey-tracker-consumer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just a week to go until Thanksgiving, it's time to buy your turkey. But this year, you can also read about your turkey's story with a tracker code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  WINTER STORM BLAST NORTHEAST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — The first snowfall of the season lingered Friday in the Northeast as thousands of exhausted commuters pointed their fingers at politicians and meteorologists for leaving them creeping along highways or stuck in mass transit hubs because of a storm that left seven dead as it moved through the Midwest and South. Some students in West Orange, New Jersey, were forced to sleep at their schools after their buses turned back, while others were taken to a diner to eat because snow-covered roads were clogged with traffic Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE MEDIA MESS</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6398199/Federal-judge-restores-CNNs-Jim-Acostas-White-House-press-pass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge handed CNN a major victory, ruling the Trump White House must restore the press credentials it stripped from the network's chief White House correspondent last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ accidents in NJ...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-gov-don-t-blame-me-for-the-mess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers were stranded for hours, mass transit was a mess and stranded students were forced to spend the night at their school. &amp;nbsp;New Jersey&amp;#39;s first snowstorm of the season was a disaster and the state&amp;#39;s response left them seething.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Israel set for early elections after cabinet breaks up, source says...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/israel-set-for-early-elections-after-cabinet-breaks-up-source-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elections to be brought forward from November 2019 after talks among coalition fail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban ranching: Socialist commune's response to crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/urban-ranching-socialist-communes-response-venezuelas-crisis-145527022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Corina Pons CARACAS (Reuters) - A socialist commune has drawn the ire of its neighbors in a wealthy area of Caracas with an unusual response to the hyperinflation and food shortages afflicting Venezuela: turning its backyard into an urban cattle pasture. The leaders of the Apacuana commune, devotees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 536 AD was worst year to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6397621/Why-536-AD-worst-year-alive.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers claim the awful year was likely caused by a cataclysmic volcanic eruption in Iceland and it kick-started a century of economic misery, disease, death and suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramer says CEOs telling him off record economy has quickly cooled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/cramer-says-ceos-are-telling-him-off-the-record-the-economy-has-cooled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Cramer outlines what he's hearing from chief executives about the state of the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband: Republican Party has become 'personality cult' under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/george-conway-republican-party-become-personality-cult-trump-130234835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — George T. Conway III, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, said the Republican Party has become “a personality cult” under President Trump and that he would “move to Australia” rather than vote for the president again. “I don’t feel comfortable being a Republican anymore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Cheney Aide in Mueller's Sights as Probe Expands...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/top-cheney-aide-in-muellers-sights-as-probe-expands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller’s investigators have examined an array of operatives with ties to Saudi Arabia, Israel, and the UAE—including John Hannah, Dick Cheney’s former national security adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 5, does 4,105 press-ups -- non-stop!?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/boy-5-gets-new-mercedes-for-doing-4105-press-ups-non-stop-8146111/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ramzan Kadyrov, a close lieutenant to Vladimir Putin, gave Rakhim Kurayev the keys to the luxury car as a reward for the boy’s 2 hours 25 minutes achievement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake generation too scared to cause a scene!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6396997/Snowflakes-SCARED-cause-scene-Half-16-24-year-olds-wouldnt-complain-bad-service.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three-quarters of Brits have delayed complaining or put it off entirely, study finds, and only 46% of young people would complain about bad service in a restaurant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini ice age could be on way...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/a-mini-ice-age-could-be-on-the-way-and-its-going-to-get-very-very-cold-8146529/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nasa fears that temperatures are about to plunge to grim lows which will leave the whole of humanity shivering and miserable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary advisers battle over whether she'll run...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/416981-hillary-advisers-battle-over-whether-shell-run-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Clinton’s former spokesperson, Philippe Reines blasted Mark Penn’s assessment of her chances of running, suggesting that Penn is out of the loop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new Egypt capital being built, what becomes of Cairo?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/with-new-egypt-capital-being-built-what-becomes-of-cairo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cairo is a city of 20 million people, a metropolis combining charm and squalor and a place where architectural treasures compete with overcrowded, impoverished neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ups cash rewards for citizens who report porn...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/china-ups-cash-rewards-citizens-report-porn-123139031--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is raising the cash rewards paid to citizens for reporting pornographic and "illegal" publications to authorities, government regulators said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury hotel built in former pit mine to open in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/gravity-defying-hotel-gives-new-mean-to-sleeping-with-fishes-1528524/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18-story Intercontinental Shanghai Wonderland Hotel has been built into the side of a huge hole in the ground left by a former pit mine. Sixteen of its floors are below ground level, looking ou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller probe to go on, Whitaker tells Graham...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/72660937c96d4db6aec8826e14abde2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker has told Republican Sen. Lindsey Graham in a meeting that special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation will proceed, according to a person familiar with the meeting. The meeting with Graham and Whitaker Thursday comes as a bipartisan group of senators is pushing legislation to protect Mueller's job. The senators are concerned about Whitaker's past criticism of the Mueller probe, which is looking at Russian interference in the 2016 election and ties to President Donald Trump's campaign. Trump appointed Whitaker acting attorney general last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruling expected in CNN credentials case... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/judge-announce-ruling-cnn-reporters-credential-case-055213240--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge is expected to announce Friday whether he will order the Trump administration to return the White House press credentials of CNN reporter Jim Acosta. U.S. District Court Judge Timothy Kelly, an appointee of President Donald Trump, has set a hearing for Friday morning to announce his decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian woman gets jail after exposing philandering boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/indonesian-woman-gets-jail-after-exposing-philandering-boss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOMBOK, INDONESIA (AFP) - An Indonesian woman who exposed her cheating boss has been slapped with a six-month jail term for her trouble.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu battles to save weakened ruling coalition...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/netanyahu-battles-save-weakened-ruling-coalition-doc-1aw1101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy-Paste Error Reveals Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-16/copy-paste-error-reveals-assange-already-facing-us-indictment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK can now tell who live with based on pictures, captions...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90269076/facebook-can-now-tell-who-you-live-with-based-on-your-pictures-and-captions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t want to tell Facebook who your family is composed of? Doesn’t matter–Facebook will find out anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abrams push for new Georgia Gov. vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7985be43fa4c4422bfece25cb0204307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Stacey Abrams' campaign and legal team is preparing an unprecedented legal challenge in the unresolved Georgia governor's race that could leave the state's Supreme Court deciding whether to force another round of voting. The Democrat's longshot strategy relies on a statute that's never been used in such a high-stakes contest. It is being discussed as Georgia elections officials appear to be on the cusp of certifying Republican Brian Kemp as the winner of a bitterly fought campaign that's been marred by charges of electoral malfeasance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGMENT DAY FOR MAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7754150/theresa-may-future-balance-michael-gove-decides-resignation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REBEL Tories have enough support to topple Theresa May, they claimed today. Brexiteer shop steward Steve Baker told the hardline European Research Group that at least 48 MPs have called for a vote …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT CHAOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/11/16/brexit-deal-latest-news-theresa-may-faces-battle-save-premiership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty Tory MPs have publicly said they have submitted letters of no confidence in Theresa May as the Prime Minister fights to keep her job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No confidence vote 'likely'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/no-confidence-vote-against-theresa-may-is-now-looking-likely-8146609/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government whips have been told to cancel engagements today and return to London with a source saying a no confidence vote in the Prime Minister is now 'likely'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home DNA tests doom anonymity for sperm, egg donors...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-11-home-dna-doom-anonymity-sperm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Ryan Kramer had to do was to swab his cheek and embark on nine days of geneological research to identify his biological father, a man who thought he would remain anonymous when he donated his sperm and never took a DNA test himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare white lion to be auctioned off 'and shot by trophy hunters'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fury-over-rare-white-lion-13599126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majestic beast, named Mufasa, is at the heart of a legal battle in South Africa as campaigners desperately bid to save his life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first oral sex robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7753384/first-oral-sex-robot-autoblow-ai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first oral sex robot — named Autoblow A.I. — has been created. US developers taught it the actions after studying 108 hours of video porn. They say the device for men, yet to be patente…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut bacterium fountain of youth? </title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/space/go-for-launch/la-sci-sn-gut-bacteria-aging-20181115-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move over Bifidobacterium and Lactobacillus. There’s a new health-promoting gut bacterium in town, and it appears to maintain — and even restore — health as we age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA INFERNO TOLL RISES TO 63</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-cool-weather-aids-fight-north-california-fire-154905743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAGALIA, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on wildfires in California (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600+ MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/us/california-fires/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of rescue personnel dressed in white overalls are sifting through smoldering rubble and mangled cars, searching for human remains in California's deadliest wildfire. At least 63 people were killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Reality Is Cooling, Not Warming'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/boston-weather-snow-snowiest-decade-northeast-storms-weatherbell-trends-beyond-the-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How this November snowstorm could impact the rest of our winter snowfall totals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-necked man and Joker lookalike are upping the 'Florida Man' mugshot game...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article221698600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mugshots out of Florida took off on social media this week. One showed an Escambia County man, Charles McDowell, with a large neck, who was arrested on multiple charges. Another showed a heavily tattooed “Joker” lookalike, Lawrence Sullivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to make original movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/apple-enters-multiyear-agreement-with-a24-to-make-original-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The multi-year deal involves the New York-based film and TV studio producing multiple films for Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC area hit with biggest November snowfall in 29 years...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2018/11/more-snow-than-expected-thursday-meteorologists-explain/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday had far messier weather than people seemed to expect. And many thought forecasters dropped the (snow)ball. But they didn’t. Here’s what happened and how meteorologists are often faced with a “lose-lose” situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut bacterium fountain of youth? </title>
      <link>ttps://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/space/go-for-launch/la-sci-sn-gut-bacteria-aging-20181115-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKEBOOK DELETES 1.6 BILLION ACCOUNTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/11/15/facebook-transparency-report-fake-account-removal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been less than a day since the New York Times published a brutal report about the state of affairs at Facebook, including a deep look at the company's fail...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey develops AUTISM symptoms in world first as it's given antidepressants...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/742743/autism-study-research-monkey-autism-prozac-fluoxetine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela ID card [manufactured in China] can track, punish citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/venezuela-id-card-tracks-citizens-like-china-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela is rolling out a new, smart-card ID manufactured by China's ZTE Corp that will help the government track, reward, and punish citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blots Out Sun, Cools Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/california-air-is-so-bad-it-s-blotting-out-the-sun-cooling-land#gs.8x6QLlU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Air Is So Bad Itâ€™s Blotting Out the Sun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly assertive Melania puts first back in First Lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/newly-assertive-melania-trump-puts-first-back-first-lady-doc-1av5vz1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Suicide rates increasing among American workers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/416953-cdc-suicide-rates-increasing-among-american-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suicide rate among Americans of working age increased 34 percent from 2000 to 2016, according to a report released Thursday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed camera will catch drivers on phones from over half mile away...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/15/this-speed-camera-will-catch-drivers-on-their-phones-from-over-half-a-mile-away-8143422/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's probably time you stopped using your phone behind the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuees set up camp in WALMART parking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/751ea83a0e454bb8a7dcf0e2e5229dc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — Fire refugee Anna Goodnight sat on an overturned shopping cart Thursday in a Walmart parking lot as she ate scrambled eggs and tater tots while her husband drank a Budweiser. The couple was trying to put a good face on a weeklong ordeal that left them uncertain of the fate of their home and now had them camping next to the store with hundreds of others forced to flee from a deadly Northern California wildfire . But William Goodnight finally lost it and began to cry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Cut to Be Eroded Next Year by Inflation Switch...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-tax-cut-to-be-eroded-next-year-by-inflation-switch-1542302217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS announced the tax code’s parameters for 2019, implementing a new method for making inflation adjustments that will result in higher tax payments over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke spreading from California fires sparks health concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0082d079001472b8e9c223dc384ac88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke masks. Eye drops. No outdoor exercise. This is how Californians are trying to cope with wildfires choking the state, but experts say an increase in serious health problems may be almost inevitable for vulnerable residents as the disasters become more commonplace. Research suggests children, the elderly and those with existing health problems are most at risk. Short-term exposure to wildfire smoke can worsen existing asthma and lung disease, leading to emergency room treatment or hospitalization, studies have shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US PREPARING TO PROSECUTE ASSANGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-is-optimistic-it-will-prosecute-assange-1542323142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is preparing to prosecute WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange and is increasingly optimistic it will be able to get him into a U.S. courtroom, according to people in Washington familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY ON BRINK; MINISTERS QUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7752634/stubborn-theresa-may-geoffrey-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May vowed to dig in like cricket legend Geoff Boycott as she found herself on a sticky wicket. Two key ministers were among seven to quit over her Brexit agreement. But the PM pledged to ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUP!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6392287/Its-Jeremy-Corbyn-persuaded-Cabinet-Brexit-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister used a press conference in Downing Street to double down on her determination to press ahead with her controversial pact with the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER STORM BLAST NORTHEAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/destructive-ice-storm-major-snow-event-to-pummel-northeastern-us-through-weeks-end/70006623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gridlock Across NYC...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-11-14-winter-storm-avery-impacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what we know so far about the impacts from this winter storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port Authority Bus Terminal closed after overcrowding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/15/port-authority-bus-terminal-closed-due-to-snowstorm-overcrowding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Port Authority Bus Terminal is so crowded with commuters waiting for buses amid a massive winter storm that the agency is blocking any more people from entering, officials said. Officials close…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  Meditation works well as traditional therapy for vets with PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/759bf5a933db41c6bb2be1263aec6165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meditation worked as well as traditional therapy for military veterans with post-traumatic stress disorder in a small experiment sponsored by the Department of Defense. One method preferred by the Department of Veterans Affairs is exposure therapy, but it doesn't work for everyone and many can't handle what it requires: purposely recalling traumatic events and confronting emotions. Meditation could be a better choice for some, the researchers said. The experiment tested meditation against exposure therapy, which involves working with a therapist and gradually letting go of fears triggered by painful memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA  RECOUNT BY HAND</title>
      <link>http://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/11/15/florida-orders-first-ever-statewide-hand-recounts-as-legal-fights-continue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unprecedented statewide hand recount is now under way in the Sunshine State, further extending a high-stakes, partisan battle over every last vote in Florida's crucial U.S. Senate race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hockney Painting Sells for $90M, Living Artist Record...</title>
      <link>http://www.artnews.com/2018/11/15/david-hockneys-famed-pool-scene-sells-90-3-m-christies-new-record-work-living-artist-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.artnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orcas share personality traits with humans...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-killer-whales-personality-traits-humans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killer whales display personality traits similar to those of humans and chimpanzees, such as playfulness, cheerfulness and affection, according to new research published by the American Psychological Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Special Counsel allowed to proceed in troll farm case...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/judge-rules-mueller-proceed-case-russian-firm-linked/story?id=59224515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. District Judge ruled on Thursday that special counsel Robert Mueller’s case against Concord Management and Consulting can proceed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
