<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Makes semi-secret delivery of missiles to Serbia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-china-serbia-nato-682ab79c4239f14ecc1133ff5c7addc9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Russian ally Serbia took the delivery of a sophisticated Chinese anti-aircraft system in a veiled operation this weekend, amid Western concerns that an arms buildup in the Balkans at the time of the war in Ukraine could threaten the fragile peace in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada: Epicenter of midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/717157/nevada-the-epicenter-of-the-2022-midterms/?unlock=4YM5N3Q43L24J4IE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans could score a clean sweep in the state this year, which would be a sign of a national Republican tsunami. But with GOP candidates pulled to the right, nothing is inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street gone wild: Bankers spend big on debauchery...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/09/wall-street-bros-wild-nights-of-sex-debauchery-on-the-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Streeters are finally back in Manhattan, flush with cash and ready to get up to late-night trouble after two years of working from home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Fight Over Critical Race Theory Became Religious War...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/how-the-fight-over-critical-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the wrong time to close Christian hearts and minds to challenging debates about race and justice in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money and morals: Psaki latest to swap White House for cable TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/apr/10/jen-psaki-white-house-tv-msnbc-news-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer switch to cable news likely to sharpen perception in America that both sides are just really in it for the money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KJB Marks Rise of Black Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/justice-ketanji-brown-jackson-is-the-latest-sign-of-a-world-changing-for-and-being-changed-by-black-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somewhere Shirley Chisolm cannot contain her broad smile. And perhaps she is joined by Barbara Jordan and, maybe even Harriet Tubman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO Republicans embrace election conspiracy theories in nominations for secretary of state, Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2022/04/09/tina-peters-ron-hanks-colorado-gop-election-conspiracies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election deniers received the support of the Colorado Republican Party faithful on Saturday as delegates voted to put candidates like indicted secretary of state candidate Tina Peters and U.S. Sena…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 private jets owned by oligarchs stuck in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/more-than-100-private-jets-owned-by-russian-oligarchs-are-stuck-in-dubai-after-being-flown-there-to-escape-sanctions-reports-say/ar-AAW3OiI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier arrested after footage emerges of 'baby being raped'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-soldier-arrested-after-footage-26678116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soldier, who is understood to be in his early to mid-20s, was detained in Russia after the horrifying video clip was wildly circulated on social media platform Telegram</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holds vote to ask if HQ should become homeless shelter...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10704147/Elon-Musk-sarcastically-suggests-turning-Twitter-HQ-homeless-shelter-no-one-turns-anyway.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outspoken Tesla CEO, known for his social media antics, purchased a 9.2 percent stake in the social media giant earlier this week and was then named to the company's board of directors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump from balconies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/09/how-china-brutalizes-its-people-to-try-to-achieve-covid-zero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like China’s previous efforts to contain the highly infectious Omicron variant, this one too is doomed to fail, although not before extracting an enormous cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai residents question human cost of quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/shanghai-residents-question-human-cost-of-chinas-covid-quarantines/ar-AAW3J1u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locals scream from windows amid food shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/health/nutrition/shanghai-locals-scream-from-windows-protest-as-city-faces-food-shortage-amid-covid-19-spike-viral-videos/ar-AAW3sQu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the stringent Covid lockdown drags on in China's Shanghai, videos are doing the rounds on social media, purportedly showing the city's residents complaining of lack of food and medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Much, Too Little, Too Late: Members React to Smith's Oscars Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/will-smith-oscars-ban-academy-reactions-1235127609/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of Oscar voters offer their assessment of the decision to keep the 'King Richard' star from attending the awards ceremony or any other Academy event for the next decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellites Show 8-Mile Military Convoy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-04-10-22/h_892b884ecacd2ed726131bca647d5627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Russia shifts its plans after failing to take Kyiv, President Vladimir Putin names Army Gen. Alexander Dvornikov to run the war for him, a US and a European official say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO planning large, permanent military presence on border...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/nato-jens-stoltenberg-military-presence-eastern-border-army-ukraine-russia-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Now the world is changing, and NATO is changing,’ alliance secretary-general says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trauma among health care workers comparable to combat vets...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/betrayal-guilt-shame-trauma-health-care-workers-comparable-combat-vets-rcna22918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forced to ration care amid a deluge of Covid patients while others flouted safety measures during the pandemic, health care workers are left with "moral injury."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland chilled by violence worthy of its noir novels...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220410-iceland-chilled-by-violence-worthy-of-its-noir-novels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long considered the "most peaceful country in the world", Iceland's tranquillity has been shattered by a spate of shootings and stabbings involving criminal gangs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student accused of sexually assaulting teacher...</title>
      <link>https://www.8newsnow.com/news/16-year-old-student-accused-of-battering-sexually-assaulting-teacher-identified/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.8newsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (KLAS) — A 16-year-old Eldorado High School student accused of sexually assaulting, punching, and strangling a teacher until she lost consciousness has been identified as Jonathan E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garland under pressure to charge ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/apr/10/merrick-garland-charge-donald-trump-january-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s legal jeopardy about the January 6 insurrection is growing but experts say attorney general must move carefully</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman faces Texas murder charge after 'self-induced abortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.valleycentral.com/news/local-news/starr-county-woman-arrested-for-self-induced-abortion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.valleycentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STARR COUNTY, Texas (ValleyCentral) — A woman has been charged with murder after authorities say she performed a “self-induced abortion.” Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested on Thur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Campaign for Sex-Free Internet...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/04/09/the-new-campaign-for-a-sex-free-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex, money, and the future of online free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Bitcoin Party: Bros, Believers, Bottle Girls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-bitcoin-party-bros-believers-040821212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastMIAMI—It’s 2 a.m. and a group of four men and I are trying to get into E11even, a trendy downtown dance spot that doubles as a strip club and is best known for being the spot where Drake and Rihanna were spotted kissing in 2016. At this point in the night, the line is so long that people are spilling into the street. There is a woman walking around in stilts and lingerie and another dressed like a cat and tied to a leash, held by yet another woma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FDA'S FOOD FAILURE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2022/fda-fails-regulate-food-health-safety-hazards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POLITICO investigation based on more than 50 interviews finds the FDA is failing to meet American consumers expectations on food safety and nutrition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL QB Haskins Dead After Hit By Dump Truck...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/pittsburgh-steelers-qb-dwayne-haskins-struck-killed-by-car-in-south-florida/2732756/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pittsburgh Steelers quarterback Dwayne Haskins, 24, was struck and killed by a dump truck in Broward County on Saturday morning. According to Florida Highway Patrol, Haskins was attempting to cross the westbound lanes of I-595 on foot for unknown reasons. Haskins was then struck by an oncoming dump truck and was pronounced dead on the scene, according to FHP. “I…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian rioters vandalize Joseph's Tomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-703723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The vandalism of Joseph’s Tomb is a grave event and a serious violation of freedom of worship in one of the holiest places for every Jew," said Defense Minister Benny Gantz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson surprise Kyiv visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/09/europe/ukraine-uk-boris-johnson-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSIONS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-tel-aviv-west-bank-religion-71bd1f3e308f8e52bca6815f058ede77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Palestinians set fire to a West Bank shrine revered by Jews as Israeli forces operated in the occupied territory following a spate of recent Palestinian attacks in Israel , the Israeli military said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves Hit on New Scam: Synthetic Identity Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/04/07/thieves-hit-on-a-new-scam-synthetic-identity-fraud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Your wallet and your purse could be a crime scene any day of the week.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Orban be wedge Vlad drives between Western allies?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/will-hungarys-orban-be-the-wedge-putin-drives-between-western-allies/ar-AAW23gH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-LGBTQ Proposals Flooding State Legislatures at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-lgbtq-proposals-are-flooding-us-state-legislatures-at-a-record-pace/ar-AAW0kr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge appears likely to allow Jan 6-related candidacy challenge against Greene...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/08/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-candidacy-challenge-lawsuit/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge signaled Friday that she'll likely allow a group of Georgia voters to move forward with their constitutional challenge against GOP Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, which claims she can't run for reelection because she aided the January 6 insurrectionists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakeholder Musk tweets 'Is Twitter dying?'</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-twitter-stakeholder-elon-musk-tweets-is-twitter-dying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter's newest board member and largest stakeholder Elon Musk tweeted Saturday to ask if the social media network was "dying" and to call out users such as singer Justin Bieber, who are highly foll…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sour and angry America poised to punish Dems this fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/09/angry-voters-biden-inflation-midterms-00024218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and his top advisers know that the window to change the economic narrative through executive action is rapidly closing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we witnessing beginning of de-dollarization?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/3262514-are-we-witnessing-the-beginning-of-de-dollarization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hegemony of the U.S. dollar was reliant on America’s hegemonic status in the world. With the world moving toward multipolarity and with the U.S. no longer the world’s largest trading nation (it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In outcome of Whitmer case, some see freedom, others danger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whitmer-kidnap-plot-trial-adam-fox-gretchen-whitmer-presidential-elections-violence-e2f805952538cdbef69c3dca82ddbfd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside the Michigan courthouse where a jury did not convict any of the four men charged with planning to kidnap Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEELERS QB Haskins Dies After Hit By Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/5088876/dwayne-haskins-dead-steelers-nfl-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star Dwayne Haskins has died after being hit by a vehicle while training with the Steelers just weeks after signing a new contract with the team, according to reports. Football fans mourn the f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stop the Steal' Rally Organizer Agrees to Cooperate with Jan. 6 Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-trump-stop-the-steal-rally-organizer-agrees-to-cooperate-with-jan-6-criminal-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activist and Trump rally organizer Ali Alexander has agreed to cooperate with the committee investigating the January 6 attack on the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson surprise meeting with Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/boris-johnson-ukraine-zelensky-2283122f-3d5a-487a-91df-95eb62d81f5b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Right now Boris Johnson's visit to Kiev began with a tet-a-tet meeting with President Zelensky," a Ukrainian official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loses his NINTH colonel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10702421/Ukraine-war-Putin-loses-NINTH-colonel-tank-commander-latest-Russian-officer-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A funeral was held for Colonel Alexander Bespalov on Friday in the closed Russian city of Ozersk, according to a local announcement, which said he was killed during 'special operation'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE TURNS RIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-france-prepares-for-first-round-of-tight-macron-re-election-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France on Saturday prepared for the first round of presidential elections projected to produce a run-off rematch between President Emmanuel Macron and far-right leader Marine Le Pen that will be far…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow First Default in Century Looks All But Inevitable Now...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-first-default-century-looks-073000013.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Sanctions Against Putin’s Daughters, IMF AccountNations Eye Modern Arms for Ukraine as Soviet-Era Stocks DwindleFinland Hit by Cyber Attack, Airspace Breach as NATO Bid WeighedDHL Jet Skids Off Runway, Breaks Up After Emergency LandingShanghai, Guangzhou Plan More Mass Tests as Covid Cases RiseRussia’s first external default in a century now looks all but inevitable after another brutal week for the country’s finances.First, the Treasury hal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson, COVID and retirement show Congress' partisan path...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-ketanji-brown-jackson-us-supreme-court-covid-business-f5a7b68b0a4e0c17792de15412c87e8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A milestone Supreme Court confirmation that endured a flawed process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
