<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HIS TURN?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/may/24/boris-johnson-favourite-as-uk-to-have-new-pm-by-end-of-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tory leadership frontrunner sets out hardline Brexit stance after Theresa May’s resignation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Clash Over Secrets Looms Between Justice Dept. and CIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/potential-clash-over-secrets-looms-between-justice-dept-and-cia/ar-AABRnEn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Social media giants ill-prepared for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/technology/la-fi-tn-pelosi-fake-video-facebook-twitter-youtube-20190524-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the 2016 election, social media companies said they would change their policies to prevent the spread of misinformation. How's that working?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  The sky's falling in on 007...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7068721/From-Daniels-sore-ankle-MeToo-backlash-string-disasters-stirred-trouble-Bond.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Craig (left and bottom right) is making is feelings known as he joins with Cary Joji Fukunaga (bottom right) along with the female Bond cast (top right) while Phoebe Waller-Bridge (bottom) is gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big girls DO cry...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7068621/JAN-MOIR-valiant-voice-faltered-did-Mrs-weakness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAN MOIR: For most of her resignation speech Theresa May managed to keep it together. It was when she expressed her gratitude for ‘serving the country I love’ that the tears fell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders new troops to Middle East; Counter Iran threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-orders-troops-middle-east-counter-iran-threat-201533911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States announced Friday it was deploying 1,500 additional troops to the Middle East in response to what the Pentagon called an "campaign" of recent attacks approved by Iran's top leadership. The escalation of the US military presence follows a decision in early May to send an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malaria back with vengeance in crisis-hit Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/malaria-back-vengeance-crisis-hit-venezuela-013605102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it weren't for the Center for Malaria Studies in Caracas, Francelis Pacheco would have been unable to get treatment for a disease she has contracted around 20 times. Pacheco, 25, sells clothes and cigars in the claustrophobic tunnels of gold mines in southern Venezuela's Bolivar state, where</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films in running for top prize...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/films-running-cannes-top-prize-202340071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino apparently slaved for four months straight in the editing room to get his odyssey through Tinseltown's darkest year in as a late entry for Cannes. This panorama of 1969 has Brad Pitt as the stunt double to Western star Leonardo Di Caprio and takes in everything from Bruce Lee to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU votes as populists seek historic breakthrough... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eu-votes-populists-seek-historic-breakthrough-014700596.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU parliamentary elections entered a third day of voting on Saturday, as populists hoped to win a major breakthrough and disrupt European politics for the next five years. Voters from Malta, Slovakia and Latvia headed to the polls, with most of the bloc's 28 member states -- including big players</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 prosecutors argued AGAINST 'espionage' charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/some-federal-prosecutors-disagreed-with-decision-to-charge-assange-under-espionage-act/2019/05/24/ce9271bc-7e4d-11e9-8bb7-0fc796cf2ec0_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prosecutors feared such charges posed serious risks for First Amendment protections and had other concerns, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cure for hate: Former skinheads recall what turned them around...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2019-05-11/cure-for-hate-former-skinheads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White nationalist beliefs can be reversed, experts say, but it is not a fast or easy process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors suing over pig fumes spur 'right-to-farm' push...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/05/22/neighbors-suing-over-pig-fumes-spur-right-to-farm-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The downfall of Theresa May, the prime minister broken by Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-downfall-of-theresa-may-the-prime-minister-broken-by-brexit/ar-AABRXaC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami bounty hunters armed with battering ram storm home over $750 bond, video shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article230692964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Catholic priests charged in Michigan sex abuse investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/05/24/michigan-catholic-priests-sexual-abuse-nessel/1221964001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel announced criminal sexual conduct charges against five Catholic priests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rushed to Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/powerful-democrat-rep-jerry-nadler-has-health-scare-at-nyc-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler had to receive medical attention Friday after a health scare at an event in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Police Chief Apologizes, Admits Mistakes In Raid On Freelance Reporter's Home...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/05/24/san-francisco-police-chief-admits-mistakes-raid-freelance-journalist-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SFPD Chief William Scott on Friday apologized for a raid on a freelance journalist's home which sparked national criticism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Assange indictment set dangerous precedent for journalists? </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/does-assange-indictment-set-dangerous-precedent-journalists-012751661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does the indictment of WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange under the US Espionage Act for publishing classified military and diplomatic documents threaten the constitutional right to freedom of the press? Many legal experts fear it does, and say journalists could find themselves facing similar charges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing accuses Trump officials of misleading public on trade war...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190524183618-vhgk7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA (WRAPUP 1, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 1-China accuses U.S. officials of misleading public on trade war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK: No 'Must Be True' Policy, But 'Heavily Reducing' Pelosi Clip...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Facebook-acknowledges-Pelosi-video-is-faked-but-13894687.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When an edited video of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., began spreading across the Web this week, researchers quickly identified it as a distortion, with sound and playback speed that had been manipulated to make her speech appear stilted and slurred.  But in the hours after the social-media giants were alerted, Facebook, Twitter and YouTube offered widely conflicting responses that potentially allowed the viral misinformation to continue its spread.  YouTube offered a definitive response Thursday afternoon, saying the company had removed the videos because they violated "clear policies that outline what content is not acceptable to post."  Twitter declined to comment. But sharing the video would likely not conflict with the company's policies, which permit "inaccurate statements about an elected official" as long as they don't include efforts of election manipulation or voter suppression. Several tweets sharing the video, often alongside insults that Pelosi was "drunk as (a) skunk," remained online Friday.  But Facebook, where the video appeared to gain much of its audience, declined Friday to remove the video, even after Facebook's independent fact-checking groups, Lead Stories and PolitiFact, deemed the video "false."  "We don't have a policy that stipulates that the information you post on Facebook must be true," Facebook said in a statement to The Washington Post.  The company said it instead would "heavily reduce" the video's appearances in people's News Feeds, append a small informational box alongside the video linking to the two fact-check sites, and open a pop-up box linking to "additional reporting" whenever someone clicks to share the video.  That didn't satisfy lawmakers such as Rep. David N. Cicilline, a Rhode Island Democrat, who took to Twitter to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human cells 'wired' like computer chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/05/190524102755.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran arrests entire yoga class for 'inappropriate outfits'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/iran-yoga-arrests-outfits-clothing-religious-gorgan-a8928901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Asks Beto: How Can We Cover Campaign Better?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/nicolle-wallace-invites-beto-orourke-to-play-media-critic-what-can-we-do-better-to-cover-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicolle Wallace invited Beto O'Rourke to "play media critic," asking him about what reporters covering the 2020 campaign trail could do better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN &amp; JERRY'S CEO: We Do NOT Support Bernie!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/ben-jerry-ceo-says-the-ice-cream-company-doesnt-support-bernie-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben &amp; Jerry's is distancing itself from co-founder Ben Cohen, an outspoken supporter of Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Noah's Ark' biblical replica owners sue -- over rain damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/2019/05/24/ark-encounter-owners-sue-over-rain-damage/1220627001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ark Encounter, the Kentucky attraction that boasts a 510-foot long replica of Noak's Ark, has sued its insurers for failing to cover rain damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Mississippi 'heartbeat' abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/24/mississippi-abortion-law-heartbeat-ban-bill-blocked-carlton-reeves/1227194001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling will prevent the law from taking effect on July 1 as scheduled after being signed by Gov. Phil Bryant earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowiest May Ever Means August Skiing at Mammoth...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/05/24/mammoth-mountain-records-snowiest-may-on-record-and-theres-a-full-week-left-in-the-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After receiving a record amount of snow for May, Mammoth Mountain on Friday announced it would be extending its ski and snowboard season into August. With one week left in the month, Mammoth has already received 29 inches of snow, the most ever recorded in the month of May.  The total beats the previous record of 28 inches, set in May 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighs pardons for servicemembers accused of war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/vets-contractors-families-await-trump-pardon-decision-after-war-crime-convictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is considering potential pardons for military members and contractors accused of war crimes as Memorial Day approaches -- deliberations that have prompted warnings from critics that the move could undermine the rule of law but also raised the hopes of their families who say the servicemembers were wrongly prosecuted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW longest weekly losing streak since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/stock-market-slight-rebound-after-trade-fears-roil-markets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Friday, but notched weekly losses as investors worried the U.S.-China trade war is hurting economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum sorry for racist 'no watermelons' remark...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-48402601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teacher accuses staff at the Museum of Fine Arts in Boston of racism towards her pupils.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo 'elaborate ruse' to escape prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/24/el-chapo-is-lying-about-prison-life-to-plot-an-escape-prosecutors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman is only whining about his lack of earplugs and outdoor activity as an elaborate ruse to escape prison ahead of sentencing, according to a new court filing. Guz…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 600 birds and pit bulls rescued tied to animal fighting...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2019/05/23/nearly-600-birds-dogs-rescued-from-indiana-properties-allegedly-tied-to-animal-fighting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGAN COUNTY, Ind. – A Crime Stoppers tip led to a pair of search warrants being served in Morgan and Owen counties, where hundreds of birds and dogs were recovered as part of an animal fighting investigation. As a result of the raids, Martin Anderson of Camby was arrested at his home on Hadley Road at about 9 a.m. Thursday. At that location, investigators say they seized one pit bull and searched for documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botswana hires Hollywood firm to fight elephant hunting PR...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtrf.com/entertainment/botswana-hires-hollywood-firm-to-fight-elephant-hunting-pr/2024969841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtrf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - The Botswanan government has enlisted a public relations firm with deep ties to Hollywood to push back against the bad publicity generated by the southern African nation's decision to lift its ban on elephant hunting.42 West, a firm mostly known for its work with celebrities and the film industry, notified the U.S. Justice Department last week that it will be working with Botswana's tourism ministry, according to a filing made under the Foreign Agents Registration Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Bolton's dangerous 'obsession'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190524-john-bolton-nuclear-iran-military-trump-usa-ayatollah-khamenei</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the US announced plans on Friday to send 1,500 more troops to the Middle East amid hostilities with Iran, analysts say the ultra-hawkish National Security Adviser John Bolton has driven much of the escalation in tensions between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils 372MPH train...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/china-highspeed-maglev-prototype/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new high-speed maglev train capable of hitting speeds of 600 kilometers per hour (about 372 miles per hour) is one step closer to reality in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian heroes to power new MARVEL series...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/asian-asian-american-heroes-power-new-marvel-comics-series-n1010126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marvel Comics is giving ink to an unprecedented team-up of its mightiest Asian and Asian American heroes, also known as the new Agents of Atlas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY WORLD employee busted trying to lure child for sex...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/disney-world-employee-charged-with-trying-to-lure-child-for-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, FLA. (WSVN) - A Disney World employee has been arrested and accused of trying to lure an 8-year-old child for sex. According to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to get respite from Washington woes in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/445444-trump-to-get-respite-from-washington-woes-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump arrives in Japan this weekend for a visit heavy on ceremony and light on pressure to get things done, offering him a respite from a series of difficult developments in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 more deaths on traffic-jammed Everest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-more-deaths-overcrowded-everest-075220256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A traffic jam of climbers in the Everest "death zone" was blamed for two of four new deaths reported Friday, heightening concerns that the drive for profits is trumping safety on the world's highest peak. Nepal has issued a record 381 permits costing $11,000 each for the current spring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Companies Building Exoskeleton Around Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/05/spacex-satellites-starlink/590269/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX and its competitors plan to envelop the planet with thousands of small objects in the next few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL HUMILIATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2019/05/theresa-may-resigns/590218/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British prime minister, who said she will resign on June 7, had one job: to deliver Brexit. She failed to do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking temps expected as 'death ridge' hits Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2019/05/24/heat-wave-more-like-death-ridge-weather-tennessee-georgia-memorial-day/1220545001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high temperatures are expected to hit portions of the South as a dangerous heat wave, also dubbed death ridge, spreads across the region over Memorial Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA okays $2M medicine, most expensive ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/05/24/hold-novartis-zolgensma-approval/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as Zolgensma, the gene therapy treats children under two years of age with spinal muscular atrophy, an inherited neuromuscular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle explores congestion pricing...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/seattle-explores-congestion-pricing/952094235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle said Thursday it’s exploring possibly charging drivers to use some city streets to ease congestion and reduce pollution – using tolls to clear roads during peak driving times and shift people to public transportation and carpools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP MORGAN slashes GDP forecast to just 1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/jp-morgan-slashes-second-quarter-gdp-forecast-to-just-1percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.P. Morgan economists say they now see a much slower economy in the second quarter, with growth of just 1%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will use loophole to sell arms to Saudis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4a1fef7a381045a783b27479f191809d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration notified Congress on Friday that it is invoking a rarely used provision in federal law to bypass congressional review of arms sales to Saudi Arabia, two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon eyes expanding DARPA future warfare research...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190524104353-xy3gm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DEFENSE/RESEARCH:Pentagon eyes expanding DARPA future warfare research office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband on team Nancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7067171/Kellyannes-husband-blasts-Trump-saying-Pelosi-playing-like-drum-impeachment-battle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Counselor to the President Kellyanne Conway’s husband George Conway believes House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is winning the impeachment battle against President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: 'Medical Episode'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/24/rep-jerry-nadler-medical-episode/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nadler is the chairman of the House Judiciary Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK plans cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/may/24/facebook-plans-to-launch-globalcoin-cryptocurrency-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg met governor of Bank of England last month to discuss decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Newspaper Editors Alarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/top-newspaper-editors-dean-baquet-marty-baron-matt-murray-alarmed-by-assange-indictment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newsroom chiefs at NYT, WaPo, and WSJ raised concerns about the Trump administration’s latest threat to the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glittery film festival literally costs the earth... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannes-glittery-film-festival-literally-costs-earth-110019310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fleet of energy-guzzling luxury yachts and private planes, kilos of gourmet food dumped, limousines driving stars just a few hundred metres: for environmentalists, the Cannes film festival is just "one big mess". "There is, without a doubt, a huge amount that needs to be done by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenya's High Court Upholds Ban on Gay Sex...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/kenyas-high-court-unanimously-upholds-ban-gay-sex-150352631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Same-sex relationships are a crime in more than 70 countries around the world, almost half of them in Africa. Neighboring Uganda once enacted a law imposing a life sentence for certain acts of gay sex although it was later nullified by court. South Africa is the only African nation to have legalized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sending 1,500 more troops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/10044ee6ce494283ba4c2e7f86f7b650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration notified Congress on Friday that it plans to send about 1,500 additional troops to the Middle East amid heightened tensions with Iran, officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: The conspiracy to bring down Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/05/gridlock-first-then-down-impeachment-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a stroke felled Woodrow Wilson during his national tour to save his League of Nations, an old rival, Sen. Albert Fall, went to the White House to tell the president, “I have been praying for you, Sir.” To which Wilson is said to have replied, “Which way, Senator?” Historians are in dispute as to […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Director Trolls Cannes With 3-1/2 Hour Pornographic 'Provocation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mektoub-my-love-intermezzo-film-review-abdellatif-kechiche-trolls-cannes-nsfw-excess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannes 2019: This sexually explicit three-and-half-hour-long provocation feels like a director self-immolating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog survives after shot rescuing family during home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/crime/dog-rescues-family-before-being-shot-during-home-invasion-police-say/285-ee5ba32d-b5b6-4b06-8e16-4341204e58fb </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog attacked the gunmen, allowing the father to grab his gun and chase the intruders away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Ratings Freefall: 90% of Broadcast Shows Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ratings-broadcast-network-series-2018-19-1213344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Same-day numbers may not tell the whole story, but nearly every show's starting point retreated from the previous season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Wants To Scan Bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90355120/would-you-let-amazon-3d-scan-your-body-for-a-25-gift-card</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because the company is looking for volunteers to do just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to Testify IN PRIVATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/robert-mueller-wants-to-testify-in-private-before-congress-jerrold-nadler.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler says Mueller told the committee he would make his opening statement before the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter of Americans say in credit card debt to pay for necessities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/23/nearly-25-percent-of-americans-are-going-into-debt-trying-to-pay-for-necessities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey found that 23% of Americans say that paying for basic necessities such as rent, utilities and food contributes the most to their credit card debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says talks won't resume unless Trump changes position...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c20ba627fe4c4c38a45246e4df5ffb8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Friday that nuclear negotiations with the United States will never resume unless the Trump administration moves away from what Pyongyang described as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ramps up war of rhetoric in trade standoff with US...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67e83f62aa7340249637c83c77a7597b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Stepping up Beijing's propaganda offensive in the tariffs standoff with Washington, Chinese state media on Friday accused the U.S. of seeking to "colonize global business" with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS, VOICE CRACK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ac10eef56b941b6b2f405a3319a7720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Bowing to the inevitable, Theresa May announced Friday that she will step down as U.K. Conservative Party leader in two weeks, admitting defeat in her attempt to take Britain out of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal swims across Niagara River...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-accused-of-swimming-across-niagara-river-to-enter-us-illegally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday evening U.S. Border Patrol agents assigned to Niagara Falls Station responded to a report of a man swimming across the Niagara River, just south of the Whirlpool Bridge in Niagara Falls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-U.S. marine held by Russia on spying charge complains of threats...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190524143843-58dwl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/ESPIONAGE-WHELAN (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Ex-U.S. marine held by Russia on spying charge complains of threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley loves sanctuary label, but housing crisis testing liberal values...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Berkeley-loves-its-sanctuary-label-but-a-housing-13890080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY, Calif. - This eccentric Northern California enclave was a sanctuary long before the designation became a must-have merit badge for any left-leaning city.  Berkeley politicians proclaimed the place a refuge for Navy sailors resisting deployment to the Vietnam War nearly a half-century ago. It was the birth of a movement to protect the outcast - and, in some cases, the outlaw - from rules that this beat-of-its-own-drum city and its followers found immoral, most recently the deportation of undocumented immigrants.  But California's housing crisis is testing whether Berkeley can remain that kind of place.  Faced with sharp criticism from a changing population, city leaders have banned people from living in recreational vehicles here, proving that even the most accepting of cities is not immune to the demands that often accompany wealth and gentrification. Businesses and residents have complained about the RVs' blighting of city streets and the burden they place on public safety and sanitation services.  "We had to do something," said Mayor Jesse Arreguín, referring to the March city council vote. "The ordinance we passed, I will admit we rushed into it. But we were facing a lot of pressure from businesses and residents."  The outcry over the ban was instant. The anger came from progressive neighbors such as Oakland, which feared that a scores-long caravan of RVs would soon head across the invisible city limits to its streets. The council suspended the law's enforcement until a more collective approach to the borderless problem might be found.  But Berkeley's move serves as a parable for how one seemingly small government decision and a lack of basic coordination can rumble through a region short on housing and high on frustration. The ban was itself a reaction to steps larger cities and the state have taken that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air rage passenger collapses, dies after 'trying to strangle woman' on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/air-rage-passenger-collapses-dies-16192810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed 32-year-old from Russia was pronounced dead by paramedics waiting for the Red Wings plane on the runway</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenya's High Court Upholds Ban on Gay Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/24/health/kenya-lgbtqi-ruling-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a blow to the LGBTQI movement in Africa, Kenya's High Court ruled Friday that a colonial-era law banning same-sex relations should remain in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After shark attacks, Cape Cod ready for tourist season?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9081f9d149714b68921f705a68b38203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLFLEET, Mass. (AP) — As Cape Cod's tourist season gets underway, there's uncertainty after two shark attacks — including Massachusetts' first fatal attack since 1936 — rattled beachgoers last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJO'S TO LOSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9145100/theresa-may-resigns-boris-johnson-favourite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson looks set to take over from Theresa May as Prime Minister now she’s finally announced she will step down. The 54-year-old ex-Foreign Secretary revealed last week he WOULD run to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX successfully deploys 60 internet satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/05/23/spacex-starlink-launch/?utm_campaign=homepage&amp;utm_medium=internal&amp;utm_source=dl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 SpaceX Starlink satellites are on their way into orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shows Employee Bathing In WENDY'S Kitchen Sink...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/23/viral-video-appears-show-man-bathing-wendys-kitchen-sink/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee who appeared to be taking a bath in an industrial sink at a Florida Wendy's "no longer works" at the restaurant, according to the franchise owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Shirtless Man Goes On Rock-Throwing Rampage In Middle Of LA Boulevard...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/23/shirtless-man-goes-on-rock-throwing-rampage-targeting-buses-motorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the passengers were brave enough to go back onto the bus and, together, they threw the man off the bus and slammed him to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley loves sanctuary label, but housing crisis testing liberal values...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/berkeley-loves-its-sanctuary-label-but-a-housing-crisis-is-testing-its-liberal-values/2019/05/23/805b2b48-7721-11e9-b3f5-5673edf2d127_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As homelessness surges, the Northern California city’s move to push out campers and their occupants triggers anger from its neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil at 'TONIGHT SHOW' after Fallon stunning ratings loss...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/05/23/turmoil-at-tonight-show-after-jimmy-fallons-stunning-ratings-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve learned that Fallon’s longtime producer Katie Hockmeyer has now left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_t25xAp270o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May has named 7 June as the day she will step aside as Conservative leader, drawing her turbulent three-year premiership to a close. May says it has ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANCE ARMSTRONG: It wasn't legal but I wouldn't change a thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/may/24/lance-armstrong-it-wasnt-legal-but-i-wouldnt-change-a-thing </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeach Bolsonaro? Just Five Months In, Talk Has Already Begun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeach-bolsonaro-just-five-months-090001196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Propelled to the presidency by a vociferous army of online ideologues, including his sons, Bolsonaro’s government comprises an uneasy mix of radicals, pragmatists and economic liberals. In his five months in office, Bolsonaro has done little to rein in the extremist fringe, even when they target Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY CALLS IT A DAY... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9144415/theresa-may-resigns-brexit-tory-leadership-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEARFUL Theresa May today finally admitted her time was up and quit as Prime Minister insisting: “I’ve done my best”. The PM was forced to resign after she failed to deliver Brexi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPERM COUNTS DECLINE; PLASTICS TO BLAME?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/24/toxic-america-sperm-counts-plastics-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study that tested both men and dogs added to concerns that chemicals in the environment are damaging the quality and quantity of sperm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS, VOICE CRACKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/theresa-resignation-live-pm-holds-16192866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After almost three years of gridlock, Theresa May has named her resignation date and plunged the nation into a chaotic Tory leadership race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1131491/theresa-may-resigns-next-prime-minister-Tory-leader-boris-johnson-dominic-raab-andrea-lead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA MAY has tearfully announced she will stand down as Prime Minister and Conservative leader in two week’s time on June 7 following significant pressure for her to quit - but who will replace her in the top job? Here are all the runners and riders for the top position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'VE DONE MY BEST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7066101/PM-summons-inner-circle-Downing-Street-gets-ready-quit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM announced her departure in an emotional statement on the steps of Downing Street after meeting Tory backbench chief Sir Graham Brady and giving the news to her staff behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/uk-politics-48394091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest reaction as Mrs May announces she will step down as party leader on 7 June</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinating genius: Did da Vinci have attention disorder?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190523224436-nov8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-DAVINCI/ (PIX):Procrastinating genius: did da Vinci have attention disorder?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
