<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Husband, wife die day apart after being married 68 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/03/minnesota-husband-wife-married-68-years-die-day-apart/2594742001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert and Corinne Johnson were married for 68 years. They lived in the same farmhouse for 67 years, raising their children and farm animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Require citizens be photographed at airports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96804155575044d5908e0697c53d6a70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Federal officials are considering requiring that all travelers — including American citizens — be photographed as they enter or leave the country as part of an identification system...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORMER SLAVE GIRL CONFRONTS CAPTURED ISIS TERRORIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.memri.org/tv/former-yazidi-slave-girl-confronts-isis-terrorist-who-violently-raped-her-ashwaq-hamid-abu-humam-faint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.memri.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On November 26, 2019, Al-Iraqiya Network (Iraq) aired a report about Ashwaq Haji Hamid, a Yazidi girl who had been held ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Page steps down as CEO of ALPHABET...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/larry-page-steps-down-as-ceo-of-alphabet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Page said in a blog post that "it's the natural time to simplify our management structure." Co-founder Sergey Brin will also step down as president of the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi felons push court to restore voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b34a318e6e594ea586756d82ce7c718d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — The man at the center of a Mississippi case aimed at restoring the voting rights of felons said Tuesday that he is fighting on behalf of everyone like him who "made a mistake in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair STILL hold more than 50% voting shares...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/955f9c26bcc346e28fffcb6afb364dd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The co-founders of Google are stepping down as executives of its parent company, Alphabet, ending a remarkable two decades during which Larry Page and Sergey Brin shaped a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes slaps CNN with $435 million defamation lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/3/devin-nunes-slaps-cnn-435-million-defamation-lawsu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Devin Nunes on Tuesday filed a defamation suit against CNN for its Nov. 22 “demonstrably false hit piece” that said the California Republican traveled to Vienna in 2018 to dig up dirt on former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani calls, texts at center...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/giuliani-mystery-phone-calls-texts-uncovered-democrats-impeachment-report-n1095086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's personal lawyer is at the center of questions about Trump's handling of aid to Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Warn Of Deadly Drug-Resistant Fungus; 806 Cases Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/12/03/over-140-confirmed-cases-candida-auris-deadly-drug-resistant-fungus-new-jersey-health-department-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC calls C. auris a "serious global health threat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pundits Furious At Whiteness Of Dem Field...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/03/democrats-2020-candidates-white-males/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skin color of Democratic 2020 frontrunners moved to the forefront of discussion among left-of-center pundits after Kamala Harris dropped out of the race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: CA man now highest-ranked American in terror group...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-man-now-highest-ranking-American-14878582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are re-upping a $5 million reward related to the capture of a 37-year-old man on the FBI's Most Wanted Terrorists List whom it called "the highest-ranking U.S. citizen fighting overseas with a terrorist organization."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested 'for making 24,000 complaint calls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50651355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 71-year-old pensioner from Tokyo allegedly called his phone operator for two-and-a-half years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Loses 'Top Destinations' Status As Tourists Pick Asia Over USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90438500/fewer-tourists-are-visiting-america-nyc-pushed-out-of-top-10-world-destinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here comes another sign of doom and gloom for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL AND HILLARY 'FREQUENT GUESTS' AT RANCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7748467/Bill-Hillary-Clinton-frequent-guests-Jeffrey-Epsteins-New-Mexico-ranch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill and Hillary Clinton would stay at Jeffrey Epstein's New Mexico ranch almost every year, former estate workers told DailyMail.com. They didn't stay at the main house but a Western-themed village.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron crushes hand again in power shake...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10475279/macron-crushes-trumps-hand-isis-fighters-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH their eyes locked on their presidential counterpart, Donald Trump and Emmanuel Macron crushed each other’s hands in yet another power shake. Their tense grip came as Trump bizarrely thre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Average Person Will Watch 78,000 Hours Of TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-the-average-adult-will-watch-more-than-78000-hours-of-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey finds that the average TV viewer will watch an astounding 78,705 hours of programming (movies, sports, news, etc) in their lifetime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang of teens brutally beats officer defending woman at mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article237996109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley giants accused of avoiding over $100 billion in taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/02/silicon-valley-giants-accused-of-avoiding-100-billion-in-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six of Silicon Valley's biggest companies had a combined "tax gap" of more than $100 billion this decade, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump deploys 'surge' of park rangers to patrol Mexican border...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/03/trump-deploys-park-rangers-patrol-mexican-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diverting rangers is a way to direct federal resources to the border without the need for congressional approval</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN BOOK SPILLS SECRETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/the-shocking-spy-story-behind-the-jeffrey-epstein-scandal-revealed-in-epstein-dead-men-tell-no-tales-300967846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prnewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/PRNewswire/ -- A new investigation led by best-selling true crime author Dylan Howard breaks stunning new ground in the case of disgraced billionaire sex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURPEME BATTLE FOR TRUMP FINANCIALS?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-loses-appeal-block-banks-handing-over-his-financial-records-n1094831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump sued the banks to stop them from complying with subpoenas seeking the information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans becoming less charitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fewer-americans-are-giving-money-to-charity-and-it-could-be-because-theyre-spending-less-time-at-church-2019-10-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 20 million fewer households donate to charity than they did two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Queen Economy 'Booming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hollywood-is-finally-catching-booming-drag-queen-economy-1258829?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive success of 'RuPaul's Drag Race' has launched dozens of stars and ignited red-carpet appearance deals for films like 'Frozen 2.' Still, for a queen, "your money is on the road."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court sides with Congress over bank records...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-financial-records-subpoena-deutsche-bank-8ad4507e-aa16-4641-ae5f-5dbc022cb030.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank and Capitol One were ordered to comply with a congressional subpoena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinance Forbids Throwing Snowballs In City...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/12/02/ordinance-forbids-throwing-snowballs-in-wausau-wisconsin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snowballs are lumped in with missiles, rocks, arrows, none of which are you allowed to throw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER DIGITAL TAX INTENSIFIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-trade-france-macron/frances-macron-hopeful-of-settling-digital-tax-dispute-with-u-s-idUSKBN1Y71UC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron said on Tuesday he was hopeful that trade and e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Tiger Woods catch Nicklaus? He's got a shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.golf.com/news/2019/12/02/tiger-woods-reaching-18-majors-who-knows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods said at the Hero World Challenge on Monday that Jack Nicklaus' 18 major titles is still in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Would you like some nice ISIS fighters?'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7750351/Donald-Trump-kicks-NATO-meetings-London-unloading-Emanuel-Macron.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump blasted French President Emanuel Macron for his own comments that the alliance was suffering 'brain death' at the start of two days of NATO meetings in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Florida mansion sells for record $111 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/billionaire-steven-schonfeld-buys-florida-mansion-for-111-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founder of New York-based hedge fund Schonfeld Strategic Advisors closed on the six acre-estate known as La Reverie Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden woos Iowa voters, Pete seems increasingly to be in his way...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-12-03/joe-biden-woos-iowa-voters-pete-buttigieg-increasingly-in-his-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among centrist voters inclined to like Biden, the 37-year-old Buttigieg is becoming plausible as an alternative, and he highlights what Biden is not: energetic, articulate and young.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW drops 400 points... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-south-america-trade-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In some ways, I like the idea of waiting until after the election for the China deal, but they want to make a deal now," Trump said from London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four ousted GOOGLE workers to file charges with federal labor board...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/472750-four-ousted-google-workers-file-charges-with-federal-labor-board</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's decision last month to fire four longtime employees involved in worker activism has kicked off a firestorm of internal protest and public demonstrations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami's buzziest buildings open ahead of Art Basel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/03/miamis-buzziest-buildings-open-ahead-of-art-basel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of planning and construction, many of Miami’s most anticipated new developments are finally open. Perhaps the most significant is Paramount Miami Worldcenter, the biggest building proje…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches NATO summit with attack on 'nasty' France...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/squabbles-overshadow-nato-70th-anniversary-summit-013415153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump launched a two-day NATO meeting Tuesday with a blistering attack on France's criticism of the alliance and on "delinquent" members that do not pay their way. At a news conference held to celebrate NATO's success in cajoling European allies to boost their defence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's First 'Fly And Drive' Car To Be Unveiled In Miami...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/03/worlds-first-fly-drive-car-miami-debut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's first 'fly and drive' car will be unveiled Tuesday night in Miami.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decapitated body found in Los Angeles' Griffith Park...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/News/decapitated-body-found-los-angeles-griffith-park/story?id=67456952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have opened a homicide investigation after dismembered human remains were discovered in Los Angeles’ Griffith Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Tom Brady play in 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/columnist/nancy-armour/2019/12/02/nfl-tom-brady-had-better-heed-warning-signs-when-considering-2020/2589900001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady's struggles this season are not the result of a weakened offense, but instead the quarterback's skills are deteriorating at age 42.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Read More In Presence Of Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/barks-for-books-children-read-more-when-in-the-presence-of-dogs-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Canada found that simply sitting down with a book in the presence of a dog can help motivate children to read more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small town that can't afford night patrols turns to cameras watched by citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-small-town-cant-afford-cops-at-night-so-its-turning-to-cameras-watched-by-citizen-patrols/ar-BBXGxyd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD takes page from Batman, testing device that uses tethers that wrap suspects' bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-03/lapd-new-restraint-device</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD will test a new device that fires a Kevlar tether that wraps around a person's body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for 'making 24,000 complaint calls'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japanese-man-71-arrested-making-24-000-complaint-045021696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Japanese pensioner has been arrested after ringing a phone company 24,000 times to complain they had violated his contract, police and local media reported. Tokyo police said they took 71-year-old Akitoshi Okamoto into custody last week after he made hundreds of toll-free calls over eight days to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 'largest animal sacrifice' begins in defiance of ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/gadhimai-hindu-festival-largest-animal-sacrifice-nepal-india-buffalo-a9230786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots, Smart Carts, AI: Grocers Testing High-Tech Food Shopping...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2019-automated-grocery-stores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Warren Could Get Wealth Tax Past Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warren-could-wealth-tax-past-090000500.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democratic presidential candidates Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders want to enact a wealth tax to pay for their large government programs. The biggest barrier may not be Congress, but the Constitution.The Constitution says the federal government is prohibited from imposing “direct taxes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Gives Trump 'Christmas' Choice in Veiled Threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-gives-u-christmas-045002181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- North Korea said it was preparing a choice of “Christmas” gifts for President Donald Trump, in the country’s latest effort to pressure the U.S. to offer more concessions in nuclear talks before the new year.Top North Korean diplomat Ri Thae Song said in a statement Tuesday that the onus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's New Test: Keep Mouth in Check at 'Pedo Guy' Trial...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-test-keep-mouth-120000245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elon Musk is known to mouth off -- and get in trouble as a result.His ability to keep his emotions, and words, in check will be put to a test this week when -- barring a last-minute settlement -- he’s set to take the witness stand in a high-profile defamation trial.The chief executive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland security' proposes face scans for American citizens...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191202231619-0717f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan has already drawn opposition from some privacy advocates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's schoolchildren now smartest in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2019/12/03/china039s-schoolchildren-are-now-the-smartest-in-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING: Chinese students far out-stripped peers in every other country in survey of reading, math and science ability, underscoring a reserve of future economic strength and the struggle of advanced economies to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane passengers rage after horse spotted in economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/plane-passengers-say-enough-enough-21015230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Passenger Shaming Instagram page shared a photo of a miniature horse in the economy cabin of a flight - dividing opinion over whether people would like to share a journey with the animal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MARRIAGE STORY' Tops GOTHAM Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/gotham-award-winners-2019-list-full-1258785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Uncut Gems' and 'The Last Black Man in San Francisco' both received multiple nominations, only to be completely shut out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr disputes key inspector general finding about FBI's Russia investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/barr-disputes-key-inspector-general-finding-about-fbi-s-russia-investigation/ar-BBXFJKW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican GA Governor Set to Snub Trump with Senate Pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/02/brian-kemp-to-spurn-trump-appoint-establishment-backed-kelly-loeffler-to-senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Kemp will announce he will appoint business executive Kelly Loeffler to the U.S. Senate despite staunch conservative opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE 18,000 YEAR OLD PUPPY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9fc66ba009db4a19a79c6f3369569f77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YAKUTSK, Russia (AP) — Russian scientists on Monday showed off a prehistoric puppy, believed to be 18,000 years old, found in permafrost in the country’s Far East. Discovered last year in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY STILL ON FENCE?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-dont-forget-me-yet-will-have-to-make-my-mind-up-really-quickly-on-entering-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton acknowledged over the weekend that she is going to have to make up her mind “really quickly” about whether or not she’ll jump into the presidential race. During an appearance on Britain’s Graham Norton Show, Clinton was asked if she is going to run. ﻿ Clinton was asked about one of the subjects …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
