<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Homebuyers turn to baby boomer parents to help with purchases...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/real-estate/homebuyers-turn-baby-boomer-parents-help-purchases-n1275552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s absolutely everywhere": In suburbs and in cities, competitive home prices have millennials turning to their baby boomer parents for financial help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missed debt ceiling deadline kicks off high-stakes fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/565745-missed-debt-ceiling-deadline-kicks-off-high-stakes-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal limit on how much debt the U.S. government can owe was reimposed Sunday, kicking off a high-stakes battle over federal spending with dire implications for global financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outgoing Iran president says govt not always truthful...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-iran-coronavirus-pandemic-6951ab6b5e0b77efe435d1bab3b80f94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran's outgoing president on Sunday acknowledged his nation at times “did not tell part of the truth” to its people during his eight-year tenure, as he prepares to leave office with his signature nuclear deal with world powers in tatters and tensions high with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds defy ban in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-arrests-coronavirus-pandemic-berlin-874d5e69750ffbb0e8364d15351cc3ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — BERLIN — Hundreds of people turned out in Berlin on Sunday to protest the German government’s anti-coronavirus measures despite a ban on the gatherings, leading to arrests and clashes with police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says more 'pain and suffering' still ahead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-93924608c51944c64c05de736fafb168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation’s top infectious disease expert, is warning of “some pain and suffering in the future” as coronavirus cases continue to rise. Fauci, speaking on ABC’s “This Week” on Sunday, said he doesn’t foresee more lockdowns in the U.S., but warned that the situation surrounding the coronavirus pandemic will continue to get worse because so many Americans are still unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami of deferred debt to hit homeowners no longer protected by foreclosure moratorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/a-tsunami-of-deferred-debt-is-about-to-hit-homeowners-no-longer-protected-by-a-foreclosure-moratorium/ar-AAMOqX5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeowners behind on their mortgage payments who aren’t forced out will still be displaced if selling is their only option, and an estimated one in ten10 borrowers in forbearance will not have enough equity to sell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros' right-hand man accused of BDSM crimes in his sex dungeon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/31/how-george-soros-money-manager-was-accused-of-bdsm-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the glamorous public life and shocking private world of Howard Rubin — accused of beating up women in his secret sex lair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITAL HELL</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/30/covid-delta-variant-summer-spike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is becoming the epicenter of the coronavirus outbreak, and Just this week, cases jumped 50 percent, with more than 110,000 new cases reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-business-arts-and-entertainment-florida-01fa89e1d9491ab075c5deb689af1ea8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Florida reported 21,683 new cases of COVID-19, the state’s highest one-day total since the start of the pandemic, according to federal health data released Saturday, as its theme park resorts again started asking visitors to wear masks indoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As cases surge, Thai hospital uses containers to store bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/covid-19-thai-hospital-containers-store-bodies-15348720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK: A Thai hospital morgue overwhelmed by COVID-19 deaths has begun storing bodies in refrigerated containers, resorting to a measure it last ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For US teen Buddhist lama, it's faith, school, football...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-football-music-religion-0f95496cb1ed092694234f1d4284a741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA HEIGHTS, Minn. (AP) — In most ways, Jalue Dorje is a typical American teen — he grew up in a suburb of Minneapolis, loving football, Pokémon and rap music. Yet a few years from now, he’s expecting to say goodbye to his family and homeland and join a monastery in the foothills of the Himalayas — from an early age, he was recognized by the Dalai Lama and other Tibetan Buddhist leaders as a reincarnated lama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Caeleb: Dressel Joins Elite Club With 5 Golds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-sports-great-britain-olympic-team-italy-olympic-team-375d46aa731faa359d5103cdb07d6447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — There was no joy in the process for Caeleb Dressel. Sleepless nights. Hardly any appetite. A virtual cocoon of an Olympics, cut off from his wife, family and friends back in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day the Space Station Lurched...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-day-the-space-station-lurched/ar-AAMOj4W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent arrival at the International Space Station created a little too much excitement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer arrested after man assaulted, left with brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/influencer-hayes-grier-arrested-after-a-man-was-assaulted-and-left-with-brain-damage/ar-AAMO26u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influencer Hayes Grier was arrested in Charlotte, North Carolina, after a man was left with a broken eyeball socket, brain damage, and bruised ribs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will high-res image of monkey brain unlock secrets?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3143188/chinese-scientists-hope-unlock-secrets-human-brain-high-res</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found a way to get a full 3D image providing an unprecedented level of detail that could be used for research into neurological conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery nightly siren coming from Census HQ keeping residents awake...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/prince-georges-county/unidentified-noise-keeping-suitland-residents-up-at-night/2753920/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Suitland, Maryland, say an unidentified siren sounds off regularly through the night, making it difficult to sleep. They want to know where the noise is coming from and they want it to stop so they can get some sleep. “It sounds kind of like a combination of a tornado siren and a spaceship taking off, like the siren…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions at risk of eviction as moratorium expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210801-millions-of-americans-at-risk-of-eviction-as-moratorium-expires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pandemic-related U.S. government ban on residential evictions expired at midnight on Saturday, putting millions of American renters at risk of being forced from their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People experiencing hair loss months after Covid infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1470608/hair-loss-coronavirus-long-covid-symptoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONG COVID sufferers can experience hair loss months after an infection, a doctor has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Aaliyah Drugged Before Fatal Plane Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-books-shock-claim-aaliyah-was-drugged-before-her-fatal-plane-crash/ar-AAMOdfr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This month marks the 20th anniversary of rising star Aaliyah’s death. The Princess of R&amp;B tragically died in a plane crash in the Bahamas after shooting the music video for “Rock the Boat,” a song that would become part of her final album. Still, two decades later, an air of mystery surrounds what went so tragically wrong on Aug. 25, 2001, when an hour-long flight from the beachy shores of the Abaco Islands to Miami claimed the lives of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Paradise burning -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9848737/Thousands-flee-Dixie-Fire-California-races-Paradise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dixie Fire is currently burning as California's largest active blaze relocating thousands and burning nearly 241,000 acres, or about 375 square miles. The flames burned through Meadow Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine quick reaction force deployed twice in last 30 days to defend embassies...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/us-marine-force-deployed-twice-defend-embassies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Marine Security Augmentation Unit has deployed twice in the past 30 days to support and protect embassies in Africa and the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL star's pregnant wife says he tanked games for gambling profit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/01/evander-kane-tanked-games-for-gambling-profit-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose Sharks forward Evander Kane was called out by his pregnant wife on Instagram for being a gambling addict who’s even thrown his own games. The NHL is now intending to investigate the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON APPEARS TO SHOVE FAN...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/07/31/lebron-james-appears-shoves-fan-video-usher-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a video tweeted by @Stephreyy26_, LeBron James was at an Usher concert in Las Vegas when he appeared to shove a fan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mayor Partied Maskless Hours Before New Mask Rules...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/31/dc-mayor-muriel-bowser-mask-mandate-birthday-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor's maskless birthday party was also attended by comedian Dave Chappelle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bible-reading, 65-year-old woman became Wall Street's hottest stock picker...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2021-7-31/prophet-of-the-golden-bull</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's a Bible-reading, Trump-supporting, divorced mother with a $53 billion investment fund and a rabid band of followers who hang on her every word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dressel Joins Exclusive Club With 5 Golds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/dressel-joins-exclusive-club-with-5-golds-at-tokyo-olympics/3190465/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caeleb Dressel has earned his fifth swimming gold medal of the Tokyo Olympics as part of Team USA’s winning 4x100m medley relay squad, putting him in elite company. Earlier in the day, the 24-year-old Dressel cruised to a relatively easy victory in the 50-meter freestyle, touching in an Olympic record of 21.07 seconds. With his fifth victory, Dressel joins Americans…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
