<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana Use At 'Historic High' Among College Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/marijuana-use-college-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the National Institute on Drug Abuse (NIDA) say marijuana use hasn't been this high since the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan evacuee flights halted over 'health concerns'...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/government/2021/09/us-afghan-evacuee-flights-halted-from-two-key-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has halted all U.S.-bound flights of Afghan evacuees from two main bases overseas for unspecified “health safety concerns,” a move U.S. officials warn will have a severe impact on the evacuation operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC member of Congress denies setting zebras loose...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/09/my-alibi-is-solid-dc-del-norton-denies-setting-zebras-loose-in-prince-georges-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A D.C. representative known for fighting for freedom is denying any responsibility for setting a group of zebras loose in Prince George's County, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive war games with 200,000 troops spanning 1,200 miles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16099913/putin-launches-massive-war-games-along-europes-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has launched massive war games with 200,000 troops spanning 2,000km on Europe’s doorstep in a warning to the West. The Zapad-2021 military drills include Belarus and run north …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many Americans will buck mandate -- and quit jobs?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-many-americans-will-buck-biden-s-vaccine-and-testing-mandate-and-quit-their-jobs/ar-AAOiPJi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washington Post-ABC News poll showed that as many as 7 in 10 unvaccinated people say they would quit rather than get a required vaccination. But that probably oversells the resistance that lies ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE SERVED: Suit Accusing Andrew of Sexually Abusing Epstein Victim Reaches Royal...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/prince-served-lawsuit-accusing-andrew-of-sexually-abusing-jeffrey-epstein-victim-reaches-embattled-royal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew, the embattled Duke of York, has been successfully served with a lawsuit by a woman who claims he sexually assaulted her in three locations when she was 17 years old, court documents indicated on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's rep says royals back BLM movement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-television-arts-and-entertainment-queen-elizabeth-ii-death-of-george-floyd-abe2adc9e5e3910339ebe8ef0c642867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II and the royal family back the Black Lives Matter movement, one of her senior representatives said in a television interview to be broadcast Friday. Philanthropist Kenneth Olisa, the first Black Lord Lieutenant of Greater London, told Channel 4 News that he had discussed the issue with members of the royal family since George Floyd died in police custody in the United States last year, sparking global protests over racial injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia blames U.S. tech giants for interference in election...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910165847-5cogd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/DIPLOMACY-ELECTION (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia blames U.S. tech giants for interference in election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4mECX60FVJQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Blue Banisters’ The New Album Out October 22nd Pre-Order - https://Lana.lnk.to/BlueBanistersAlbumIDListen to Arcadia - https://Lana.lnk.to/ArcadiaIDFollow L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY WARNS IN SONG:  AMERICA NEEDS A MIRACLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.justjared.com/2021/09/08/lana-del-rey-debuts-new-song-arcadia-watch-the-music-video-read-the-lyrics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justjared.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch inside and read the lyrics!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mental Health Hinges On Diet?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mental-health-diet-and-lifestyle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BINGHAMTON, N.Y. — The old saying goes “you are what you eat,” but a recent study finds it may be more accurate to say your mood is what you eat. Researchers from Binghamton University find people can optimize their mental health through diet and lifestyle changes. “There is increasing evidence that diet plays a major…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA to DOUBLE fines on mask violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/tsa-will-double-fines-on-mask-mandate-violations-at-airports-on-flights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new range of penalties, which take effect Friday, will be $500-$1000 for first offenders and $1000-$3000 for second offenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesale prices jump 8.3% in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/august-wholesale-prices-rise-8point3percent-on-an-annual-basis-biggest-advance-on-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The producer price index for final demand products was expected to increase 0.6% in August, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie calls on Republicans to stop 'pretending we won' in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/christie-calls-on-gop-to-renounce-the-conspiracy-theorists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie offered a sweeping critique of the GOP on Thursday, urging it to become "the party that's perceived to be telling the American people the truth" after months of "pretending we won" the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feud escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon-takes-personal-swipe-at-musk-as-satellite-feud-escalates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.'s satellite subsidiary, Kuiper Systems LLC, filed a scathing comment with the Federal Communications Commission, accusing Elon Musk and his companies of flouting regulations with a general attitude that "rules are for other people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New deepfake tool will transform you in real-time during live streaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/deepfacelive-deepfake-live-streaming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new deepfake tool known as 'DeepFaceLive' will let users change their appearance in real-time during live video streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the Amish take over America?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/will-the-amish-take-over-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So writes David Larson in Crisis magazine, examining the rapid growth of a community which has doubled in size in just 20 years. There are now 350,000 Amish in the United States, and their demographic growth shows no real sign of letting up. The Amish are notorious for their restrictive lifestyles, with their communities essentially [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/911-20-years-world-affairs-cc497f11743fcbd48b0b3e0c3ed2da5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the ghastly rubble of ground zero's fallen towers 20 years ago, Hour Zero arrived, a chance to start anew. World affairs reordered abruptly on that morning of blue skies, black ash, fire and death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply bottlenecks continue...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910134804-4c8jj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Supply bottlenecks keep heat on U.S. producer prices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing risk of once-in-century solar superstorm that could knock out internet...</title>
      <link>https://ktvz.com/cnn-regional/2021/09/10/growing-risk-of-once-in-a-century-solar-superstorm-that-could-knock-out-internet-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktvz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Alexandra Mae Jones Click here for updates on this story     TORONTO (CTV Network) — Imagine if one day the internet was down not just in your neighbourhood, but across the globe, knocked out by a threat from space: an enormous solar superstorm. It sounds like science fiction, but a new study says it could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia begins military games with Belarus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-begins-major-military-drills-with-belarus-after-moves-toward-closer-integration/ar-AAOiCXU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s Putin plans to unify Russia’s military space with Belarus, but offered no details on what it means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden-Xi Call Raises Key Question: Who Will Blink First?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-xi-phone-call-raises-key-question-who-will-blink-first/ar-AAOisZy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of little progress in U.S.-China relations, Joe Biden’s frustration led him to initiate a call with Xi Jinping in search of a breakthrough. Now the question is who will be first to take concrete action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapiro Says DAILY WIRE Will Defy Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ben-shapiro-declares-the-daily-wire-will-use-every-method-and-resource-to-defy-biden-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Wire, the conservative website co-founded by Ben Shapiro, announced on Friday that it will be resisting the Biden administration’s vaccine requirement for employers. The emergency rule announced by President Joe Biden on Thursday night will require all private-sector businesses with more than 100 employees to require their workers to be fully vaccinated against […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't call it relaxation. On this Maine island, vacation is for rusticating...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Don-t-call-it-relaxation-On-this-Maine-island-16448721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a big year for Mount Desert Island, a craggy hump of pink Maine granite that's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin weeps over coffin of friend killed in drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3635235/putin-weeps-over-pals-coffin-who-died-in-arctic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTRAUGHT Vladimir Putin has wept over the coffin of a close pal who died “trying to save a man’s life in an Arctic drill”. A grief-stricken Putin appeared devastated as he said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's best superyachts revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-9972911/The-worlds-best-superyachts-2021-revealed-including-British-built-floating-work-art.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fourteen trophies were handed out to 12 vessels at Boat International's World Superyacht Awards, with the British-built 33.9m (111ft) Geist taking home the coveted award for Sailing Yacht of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In China elite circles, thousand-dollar soups, detention roulette...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/New-book-details-on-China-s-elite-circles-16448244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese businessman is offering a rare peek into the luxe lifestyles of former premier...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans turn pessimistic amid concerns over economy, virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/10/politics/americans-biden-economy-coronavirus/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tentatively positive public outlook that marked the first months of the Biden administration has faded, according to a new CNN poll conducted by SSRS. The survey, released Friday, finds a rising share of Americans who say things in the US are going badly and that the economy is in poor shape, with increased worries about the coronavirus, the economy and crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food getting more and more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/climate-change-supply-chain-and-labor-issues-are-making-food-pricier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change, labor costs, transportation issues, Covid catalysts and other supply chain disruptions are wreaking havoc on the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 MILLION AMERICANS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-executive-branch-18fb12993f05be13bf760946a6fb89be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In his most forceful pandemic actions and words, President Joe Biden on Thursday ordered sweeping new federal vaccine requirements for as many as 100 million Americans — private-sector employees as well as health care workers and federal contractors — in an all-out effort to curb the surging COVID-19 delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creator says mass boosters may be unnecessary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-immunizations-65f8508c653fd6be7c1a8e7537e47c13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Booster shots to extend the protection of COVID-19 vaccines may be unnecessary for many people, a leading scientist behind the AstraZeneca vaccine said on Friday. Oxford University Professor Sarah Gilbert told The Telegraph newspaper that immunity from the vaccine was holding up well — even against the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury brands flock to suburbs, vacation hot spots where rich riding out pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Luxury-brands-flock-to-suburbs-and-vacation-hot-16448294.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Fifth Avenue and Rodeo Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Capitol rioter says ankle monitor beeps too loudly. He wants judge to let him remove it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-alleged-capitol-rioter-says-his-ankle-monitor-beeps-too-loudly-he-wants-a-judge-to-let-him-remove-it/ar-AAOigwO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabriel Garcia, who's accused of inciting a mob of rioters to charge Capitol police on Jan. 6, wants a judge to let him remove his GPS ankle monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strategists Say Storm Brewing in Stock Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-10/deutsche-team-sees-risk-of-hard-equity-valuation-correction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strategists from almost all the top Wall Street banks have come out this week with a nervous message about the U.S. stock market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA flags 44 Afghan evacuees as potential national security risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-has-flagged-44-afghan-evacuees-as-potential-national-security-risks-over-the-past-two-weeks-vetting-reports-show/ar-AAOihU8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials said that evacuees who have been flagged for additional checks or denied admission to the United States show how the vetting process is working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk dominating space race. Bezos trying to fight back...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/elon-musk-is-dominating-the-space-race-jeff-bezos-is-trying-to-fight-back/ar-AAOi7Sa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What began as a fight over a NASA contract to land astronauts on the moon has become especially bare-knuckled and personal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Useful protection or not warranted? Third jab debate rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-useful-protection-or-not-warranted-third-jab-debate-rages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Useful protection or not warranted? Third jab debate rages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark lifts all curbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-the-way-we-were-denmark-lifts-all-covid-curbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The way we were: Denmark lifts all Covid curbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech made billions during 'war on terror'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-big-tech-made-billions-during-war-on-terror-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Tech made billions during 'war on terror': report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine warns all-out war with Russia possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9976697/Putins-new-challenge-West-Russia-Belarus-alarm-NATO-huge-war-games.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their torrid relationship took a turn for the worse earlier this year when fighting in eastern Ukraine intensified seven years after Russia seized the Crimean Peninsula from Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find talking duck!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910105122-1jmtc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NETHERLANDS-DUCK/ (TV):All jokes aside, scientists find talking duck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin, Sanders set for clash over spending package...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571605-manchin-sanders-set-for-clash-over-biden-spending-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) are hurtling toward a showdown over President Biden's $3.5 trillion spending plan, as they draw red lines around their legislative priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAVIN REMAINS: New poll finds Newsom could easily beat recall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poll-finds-newsom-could-easily-100012435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poll shows 60.1% of likely voters surveyed oppose recalling Newsom compared to 38.5% in favor of ousting the governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus-sniffing dogs unleashed at Miami airport to detect in employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/coronavirus-sniffing-dogs-unleashed-at-miami-airport-to-detect-virus-in-employees/ar-AAOgN94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami is the first American airport to use the specially trained dogs in its battle against the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden speaks with Xi as tensions continue to rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Biden-speaks-with-China-s-Xi-for-a-second-time-as-16447868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden spoke with Chinese President Xi Jinping for the second...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New season, same Brady: BUCS down COWBOYS in NFL thriller...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/tom-brady-leads-great-game-winning-drive-in-thrilling-opening-night-victory-over-cowboys-035558965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady still has it, especially with the game on the line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS, former anchor Henry must face sex misconduct lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210909212739-lbjlw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXNEWS-LAWSUITS/:Fox News, former anchor Henry must face ex-producer's sexual misconduct lawsuit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES REQUIRES JAB FOR ALL STUDENTS 12+...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-los-angeles-coronavirus-pandemic-school-boards-3e6d32b5545965d20128953478ee144d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles board of education voted Thursday to require students 12 and older to be vaccinated against the coronavirus to attend in-person classes in the nation’s second-largest school district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed presidents to sell stocks to address ethics concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/09/feds-rosengren-to-sell-individual-stock-portfolio-to-address-ethics-concerns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed officials will sell all their stocks by Sept. 30 and put the proceeds in passive investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany probes claims of pre-election MP hacking by Russia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-probes-claims-pre-election-201408789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German federal prosecutors said Thursday they are probing alleged hacking attacks against lawmakers ahead of this month's German election that Berlin has blamed on Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder says 'racial epithets' were yelled during egg attack, calls out silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/larry-elder-racial-epithets-yelled-egg-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican candidate told Fox News in a phone interview that the racist phrases were screamed at him while a White woman wearing a gorilla mask with neon magenta hair threw an egg at him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Oahu median home sale price tops $1 million for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/09/08/hawaii-news/oahus-median-home-sale-price-tops-1m-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $1 million house on Oahu has officially become run-of-the mill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Want Justice Stephen Breyer To Retire. His Response? Not Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/09/1035092720/progressives-want-justice-stephen-breyer-to-retire-his-response-not-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with NPR, the 83-year-old said: "When exactly I should retire, or will retire, has many complex parts to it. I think I'm aware of most of them, and I ... will consider them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT delays return to work indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/microsoft-return-to-u-s-offices-delayed-indefinitely</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft told employees Thursday that it has indefinitely delayed their return to U.S. offices until it’s safer to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA BANS ALL NEW VIDEO GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/china-announces-blanket-ban-new-24943641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have banned all new video games from being released indefinitely, as the government attempts to tackle what it calls gaming addiction in the under-18s. The suspension was revealed at a meeting with game company Tencent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran adds mindfulness, meditation to public school curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/san-francisco-school-district-adds-mindfulness-to-curriculum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco public schools add mindfulness meditation to curriculum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 80% Oppose Tax Hikes Coming Out of Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/poll-80-oppose-tax-hikes-coming-out-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#13;By an 80-20 margin voters oppose tax increases as the U.S. comes out of the pandemic, according to a new poll conducted by HarrisX.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The poll was conducted by HarrisX between Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of baby at center of Roe v. Wade revealed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/09/roe-v-wade-baby-revealed-to-be-shelley-lynn-thornton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her biological mother had been 22, unmarried, unemployed, and pregnant with her third daughter in 1969 when she sought to have an abortion in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden in December '20: 'I Don't Think' COVID Vaccinations 'Should Be Mandatory'...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/washington/michael-w-chapman/biden-december-2020-i-dont-think-covid-vaccinations-should-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(CNS News) -- Democratic President Joe Biden is expected to sign an executive order today requiring all federal workers to receive the COVID vaccine, without the option of regular COVID testing to opt out of the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Man gets 10 years in prison for stabbing woman with semen-filled syringe...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/syringe-stabber-sentenced-982150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 8--The 53-year-old fiend who jabbed a woman in the rear end with a semen-filled syringe has been sentenced to a decade in state prison following his guilty plea to assault charges. A Maryl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY TAKES THE SEX OUT OF LEWINSKY...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/09/no-cigar-ryan-murphys-monica-lewinsky-series-impeachment-opens-low-fails-to-score-a-million-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Impeachment” is impaired. The Ryan Murphy FX series about Monica Lewinsky and Bill Clinton failed to score 1 million viewers on Tuesday night. The total came in at 916,000. Since FX is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ sues Texas over abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/justice-department-sue-over-texas-restrictive-abortion-law-n1278783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law bans abortions after six weeks of pregnancy, before many women know they are pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Can Liberals Be Convinced Genetics Matters?</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/09/13/can-progressives-be-convinced-that-genetics-matters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior geneticist Kathryn Paige Harden is waging a two-front campaign: on her left are those who assume that genes are irrelevant, on her right those who insist that they’re everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Office air quality affects workers' cognitive function...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-office-air-quality-affects-workers-cognitive-function-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Office air quality affects workers' cognitive function, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN CRUSHED IN FREAK ACCIDENT AT MCDONALD'S DRIVE THRU...</title>
      <link>https://www.bellinghamherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article254107763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bellinghamherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He leaned out to pick up something and the vehicle rolled.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
