<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Serial toilet clogger sentenced to 150 days in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.sheboyganpress.com/story/news/2019/07/01/sheboygan-toilet-clogger-sentenced-probation-150-days-jail/1569553001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sheboyganpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick D. Beeman was sentenced Monday to three years of probation, including 150 days in jail, for a string of incidents where he clogged toilets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanks move in to DC for Trump's grandiose July Fourth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7203327/Stage-Trumps-July-4-celebration-takes-shape-Lincoln-Memorial-president-promises-TANKS.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has promised to go all out for Independence Day this year by sending tanks down the National Mall and having Air Force One do a flyover before the fireworks begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tombs to be opened in Vatican City in 1983 missing teen case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6530486d771b4a8c804eb81111713e5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Of Dog Owners Turn To Canines Over Family For Emotional Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/confide-fido-nearly-half-dog-owners-turn-canines-over-family-comfort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs have been considered man's best friend for hundreds of years, but according to a recent survey, they may also be man's (or woman's) best therapist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans pick partners with similar smell...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7204321/Human-scent-impacts-choice-partners-pick-people-naturally-smell-like-us.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by Caroline Allen of the University of Newcastle, researchers took body odour samples from 30 heterosexual couples who had been in relationships for at least six months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much streaming content causing viewer 'paralysis'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/01/too-much-streaming-content-is-causing-viewer-paralysis-nielsen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stuck between The Rock and “A Quiet Place”? You’re not alone. Nielsen’s new Total Audience Report found that the average TV viewer takes seven minutes just to pick what to watch. Chalk …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOLDEN GIRLS' appears to get better with pop culture age...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/803d42ed224049ca9747001fe3e43032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reluctant Mueller Dems' Best Shot to Revive Investigations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/reluctant-mueller-democrats-best-shot-080005542.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Robert Mueller will appear grudgingly before House committees this month, but the former special prosecutor’s testimony is the best chance Democrats have to revive their stymied probes of President Donald Trump.House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s resistance to a politically risky impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In post-AVICII electronic dance world, DJs pushing genre's limits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/post-avicii-electronic-dance-world-djs-pushing-genres-052613897.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just over a year after the death of dance music superstar Avicii, the electronic scene is in flux, faced with hip-hop's dominance as the youthful party music du jour. Avicii was one of the first DJs to take electronic music mainstream, playing to massive crowds at festivals and collaborating with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hong Kong is not China': Protests pose major test for Xi...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-not-china-protests-pose-major-test-082853130.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping faces a major test in Hong Kong after protesters stormed the semi-autonomous city's legislature and graffitied a defiant message on its walls: "Hong Kong is not China". Beijing has trod carefully since massive protests erupted last month over a bill that would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile, Argentina prepare for spectacular solar eclipse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-argentina-prepare-spectacular-solar-eclipse-060708474.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vicuña (Chile) (AFP) - Day will briefly turn to night Tuesday over large parts of Chile and Argentina as a total eclipse of the Sun plunges a vast swath of the southern Pacific and the cone of South America into darkness. Both countries will be under the narrow, 6,000-mile long band that will experience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roubini Lives Up to 'Dr. Doom' Alias With Global Recession Call...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roubini-lives-dr-doom-alias-062940284.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S.-China trade war and a spike in oil prices from geopolitical tensions have the potential to push the world into recession next year, according to renowned doomsayer Nouriel Roubini.“It’s a scary time for the global economy,” the head of Roubini Macro Associates, sometimes known</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says suspected U.S. spies face death sentences...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190702091757-sq06r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-IRAN/USA-SPIES:Iran says several suspected U.S. spies face possible death sentences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synagogues conducting active shooter drills during services...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/synagogues-are-now-conducting-active-shooter-drills-during-services/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After gunmen massacre worshipers at Poway and Pittsburgh, US congregations learning how to hide, flee and fight back against attackers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Woman Who Sneaked Into George Washington's Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/02/arts/design/the-woman-who-sneaked-into-george-washingtons-army.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rediscovered diary, now at the Museum of the American Revolution, sheds light on the life of Deborah Sampson, who fought in the Continental Army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening hurricane danger to Hawaii?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/hurricane-barbara-forms-does-the-strengthening-hurricane-pose-any-dangers-to-hawaii/70008693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cockroaches evolving to point where they'll be nearly impossible to kill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-cockroach-evolve-chemicals-impossible-kill-20190701-wvdtptorwbc7pcuyiw5weyde3u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New study finds cockroaches being born with an immunity to pesticides</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles War on Smog Slipping After Years of Improvement...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-smog-southern-california-20190701-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smog is getting worse in Southern California, and the stakes are high for health and the economy. Officials say it’ll take $14 billion to fix the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STYLES UP FOR 'ELVIS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/harry-styles-ansel-elgort-miles-teller-running-play-elvis-baz-luhrmann-film-1222173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Taylor-Johnson and Austin Butler also tested for the part, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems face added pressure on racial issues... </title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/After-debate-Democrats-face-added-pressure-on-14065391.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - An impassioned argument over racism in America has boiled to the surface in an increasingly muddled Democratic presidential primary campaign, triggered by an electrifying debate encounter that has reverberated across the campaign for days.  Former vice president Joe Biden, who since his April 25 entry into the presidential contest has held a consistent lead in polls, is experiencing the most unsteady period of his campaign so far in the aftermath of his heated exchange with Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., over his past views on school desegregation, with demands from some civil rights leaders for him to further clarify his 1970s-era opposition to mandatory busing.  The moment has taken on particular salience because it showcased Biden, 76, who has premised his candidacy in part on his ability to win back working-class white voters, under attack from one of the country's most prominent black political figures in Harris, who addressed the issues in deeply personal terms.  Harris and a second black presidential candidate, Sen. Cory Booker, D-N.J., have spent the past week casting Biden as an anachronism who should apologize for his busing position and his willingness to work with segregationist senators.  The rising tensions have the potential to reshape the race, with Biden at risk of losing support from crucial African American voters and Harris appearing to gain momentum. But the emerging dynamics are also sparking concern among some in the party who fear that renewing painful debates over school busing risks turning off centrist voters whom Democrats hope to win next year in their shared goal of defeating President Trump.  "There is a narrow pathway if we continue on this path of being the quote-unquote Whole Foods party," said J.D. Scholten, the Democrat who nearly defeated Rep. Steve King, R-Iowa, in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Charged in TWITTER Threat to Lynch Muslim Lawyer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-charged-online-threat-lynch-181738490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Carolina man has been charged with posting an anonymous threat on social media to lynch a Muslim-American candidate for a state Senate seat in Virginia. A warrant for the arrest of Joseph Cecil Vandevere, 52, of Black Mountain, was issued after his June 20 indictment, federal court records show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BODY FALLS FROM PLANE IN LONDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9414837/stowaway-falls-3500ft-jet-sunbather/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A JET stowaway’s body fell 3,500ft and smashed into a back garden — as the house’s horrified tenant sunbathed 3ft away. The tragic migrant plunged from the landing gear bay of the Kenya Airways pla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Trump's hard line approach softens in meetings with world leaders... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-s-hard-line-approach-appears-to-soften-in-14065230.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump entered his meeting with President Xi Jinping over the weekend promising to take a tough approach on trade negotiations and pressure his Chinese counterpart into a sweeping deal.  But the meeting did not produce an agreement - and Trump's stance seemed to only soften as he announced he was relaxing limits on Chinese telecommunications giant Huawei and delaying new tariffs on Chinese goods in hopes of restarting trade talks with Beijing.  "We discussed a lot of things and we're right back on track," Trump said. "We'll see what happens."  Trump's meetings with Xi and other leaders at the Group of 20 economic summit suggest that despite his promise to use negotiating savvy and personal relationships to extract concessions from rivals or uncooperative allies, he often leaves one-on-one sessions with fellow world leaders without firm agreements in hand.  Trump emerged from his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin with no specific public commitments, although both nations had pledged in principle beforehand to explore a new arms control pact. Despite concerns over Turkey's plan to purchase Russian defense systems, Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan said Trump told him the United States would not punish his government with sanctions over the decision.  And while his meeting with Kim Jong Un following the G-20 appeared to provide the North Korean dictator with a propaganda victory to tout back home, Trump did not publicly secure more than a commitment to resume nuclear talks that have so far yielded no breakthroughs.  "In the case of Putin, Erdogan, and others, I don't see him pushing that hard. He pushes harder with allies than with adversaries," said Richard Haass, the president of the Council on Foreign Relations. "In some cases, even with North Korea or Iran, it's not clear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> FACEBOOK GROUP UNDER SCRUTINY</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/secret-border-patrol-facebook-group-agents-joke-about-migrant-deaths-post-sexist-memes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three-year-old group, which has roughly 9,500 members, shared derogatory comments about Latina lawmakers who plan to visit a controversial Texas detention facility on Monday, calling them “scum buckets” and “hoes.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 35,000 MORE Africans on way... </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/report-35000-more-africans-on-way-to-us-via-south-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They just keep coming. A report from the Center for Immigration Studies indicates another 35,000 African migrants are on their way to the United States. According to CIS’s Todd Bensman: Like the proverbial “bulge in the belly of the snake,” unusually high numbers of non-Latino migrants, obviously not from Central America, are now reportedly passing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BODY FALLS FROM PLANE IN LONDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9413758/body-of-stowaway-falls-from-kenya-airlines-plane-and-lands-in-south-london-garden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE body of a male stowaway has landed in the garden of a South London home after falling from the underside of a Kenya Airways flight. The gruesome discovery was made at a property in Offerton Roa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-life Hamburglar cooks himself dinner after breaking into WENDY'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/os-ne-martin-county-hamburglar-20190701-sufnsjan6zafnheibblsgkq5au-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida has its own real-life Hamburglar, and he spent part of his weekend in jail after being caught on video firing up a grill and cooking himself a burger at a Wendy's he broke into after hours, deputies said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoax call about a murder sends cops to newspaper columnist door...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hoax-call-about-a-murder-sends-cops-to-columnist-leonard-pitts-jr-s-door-cops-apologize/ar-AADHo1G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese test anti-ship ballistic missile in hotly contested South China Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/01/chinese-military-conducts-missile-tests-in-the-south-china-sea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The development comes as the U.S. and China have paused tensions in their ongoing trade battle. U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping agreed over the weekend at the G-20 summit in Japan to not impose new tariffs on each other's goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost Half of Cars Sold in Norway Are Electric...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/almost-half-of-all-cars-sold-in-norway-in-2019-are-electric-cars-1.1281058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border crossing shut down after 'large and unruly group' forms near El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/451223-border-crossing-shut-down-after-large-and-unruly-group-forms-in-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities closed an international border bridge in El Paso, Texas, early Monday in response to Central American and Cuban migrants protesting on the Mexican side of the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ BATTLES BORDER POLICE!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/01/aoc-says-migrants-forced-to-drink-toilet-water-after-tense-border-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez claims Border Police agents are forcing migrants to drink out of toilets and live under other extreme conditions — while the officers sit back and laugh. “I see …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Antifa' Keep Attacking Journalists Despite Sympathy From National Media...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/07/01/andy-ngo-antifa-attack-journalists-list/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antifa members violently attacked Portland-journalist Andy Ngo, sending him to the hospital. Here's a list of other Antifa attacks on journalists and media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protests descend into chaos in direct challenge to China...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190701161126-9oint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-EXTRADITION/ (WRAPUP 15, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 15-Hong Kong police fire tear gas as protesters vandalise legislature</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  'Secondhand drinking' hurts 53 million Americans...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/01/effects-of-secondhand-drinking-hurt-53-million-americans-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget secondhand smoke. Now you have to worry about the secondhand drinking. One fifth of adults — or an estimated 53 million people in the United States — suffer from other people’s boozing annua…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB STAR FOUND DEAD IN HOTEL ROOM... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/07/01/angels-pitch-tyler-skaggs-dies-dfw-rangers-angels-game-postponed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Angels announced Monday afternoon, pitcher Tyler Skaggs, 27 passed away in DFW.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: THINKPROGRESS for sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/center-for-american-progress-puts-think-progress-up-for-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News site launched during the Bush years is running millions of dollars short. Its parent think tank says it will consider the editorial leanings of prospective owners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acclaimed novelist rejected by UK orgs because of Jewish faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.commentarymagazine.com/anti-semitism/jewish-writers-literature/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commentarymagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jewish writers, particularly but not exclusively those who write anything positive about Israel, are being drummed out of publishing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia court agency hacked in ransom attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/georgia-court-agency-hacked-ransom-attack/P3UaTuigNhT6JfREQaiKZK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malware infected computers at Georgia Administrative Office of the Courts, which shut down its website and applications to contain the hack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN POLL: Biden 22%, Harris 17%, Warren 15%, Sanders 14%...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/07/01/politics/2020-democratic-candidates-poll/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens. Kamala Harris and Elizabeth Warren have made steep gains after the first Democratic presidential debate, a new CNN poll conducted by SSRS. shows, with former Vice President Joe Biden's lead over the field shrinking to a narrow 5 points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK site evacuated after mail tests positive for sarin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/062ed1865a1a4521abd601fb594d563a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia proposes prisoner swap with USA...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190701123424-t41y3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/PRISONERS (URGENT):Russia proposes prisoner swap with U.S. - Ifax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON partners with cops for elaborate sting operation PR stunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/43jmnq/how-amazon-and-the-cops-set-up-elaborate-sting-operation-that-accomplished-nothing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Behind-the-scenes emails show how Amazon and Ring worked with police in Aurora, Colorado to make people scared of each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to ban beer, pizza? Mandatory keto diet may be coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2019/07/01/defense-department-to-ban-beer-and-pizza-mandatory-keto-diet-may-enhance-military-performance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial ketogenic or “keto” diet may be the future of the military, some defense officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15-year-old beats Venus Williams to make Wimbledon history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7201657/American-teen-15-takes-idol-Venus-Williams-week-sitting-exams.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an electrifying match, Cori 'Coco' Gauff, 15, beat the seven-time Grand Slam singles winner, 39, on Court One - just a week after finishing her exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOK circling Africa with huge undersea cables...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/africa/1656262/google-facebook-building-undersea-internet-cable-for-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech companies are betting on improving connectivity in Africa to ensure that millions of potential customers get—and stay—connected to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age Isn't Everything, Says Bernie..</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/06/30/737351246/age-isnt-everything-says-bernie-sanders-it-is-what-you-stand-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential hopeful told NPR that arguments he and Joe Biden are too old to be president are "pretty superficial." And he warned that moderation may not excite voters enough to win in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD ALASKA HEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2019/06/30/more-record-breaking-heat-and-wildfire-smoke-forecast-for-fourth-of-july-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Think of what we’ve been experiencing and tack on 2-4 degrees.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Trying to Buy Back Banned Military-Style Weapons. It's Not Easy...</title>
      <link>https://inhomelandsecurity.com/new-zealand-is-trying-to-buy-back-the-military-style-weapons-it-banned-in-april-its-not-so-easy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inhomelandsecurity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand: A near-unanimous parliamentary vote in April to ban military-style rifles and similar weapons now has growing opposition from pro-gun groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media told story of man surviving Santa Fe shooting. He wasn't there...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2019/07/01/santa-fe-shooting-texas-david-briscoe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who claimed he was a substitute teacher at Santa Fe High during the 2018 shooting told a harrowing story of survival. But the school district says he never worked there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Kamala Harris faces debate backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/30/kamala-harris-joe-biden-2020-1391212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden supporters lash out against Kamala Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for feeding meth to 'attack squirrel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/Man-Accused-of-Feeding-Meth-to-Attack-Squirrel-Arrested-511997911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man accused by police of feeding methamphetamines to his pet squirrel to make him an 'attack squirrel' has been arrested. Police officers in Alabama had been looking for Mickey Paulk for nearly two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of Americans cut spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/28/why-one-third-of-americans-have-decided-to-cut-back-on-spending.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One-third of Americans have cut their spending this year, according to the CNBC + Acorns Invest in You Spending Survey released on Monday. The reasons they cite include fear of a job loss, high medical bills and fear of a recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Call To Regulate Big Tech While Raising Money Off Big Tech... </title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/07/01/dems-call-regulate-big-tech-money-big-tech-execs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of lawmakers scrutinizing big tech companies, former Vice President Joe Biden raised money from Silicon Valley executives this past weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president says he would like to disband the nation's army...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190701142611-6q8w3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-POLITICS/:Mexican president says he would like to disband the nation's army</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election model that predicted 2018 blue wave has Trump losing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/election-model-that-predicted-2018-blue-wave-has-trump-losing-liberal-voters-terrified</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A university election model that predicted the blue wave in the House in 2018 almost to the seat is predicting a big loss by President Trump next year due to an explosion of bitter partisanship and Trump hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery UFO spotted over Korean DMZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9409033/ufo-korea-dmz-trump-kim-jong-un/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FIGHTER jets and helicopters were scrambled to investigate a mysterious UFO over Korea’s Demilitarised Zone – hours after Donald Trump’s historic meeting with Kim Jong-un at the b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Study Sheds Light On Tired, Overworked Nurses: 1 in 8 Takes Meds...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/new-study-sheds-light-tired-overworked-nurses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staggering number of nurses may suffer from insomnia and about one in eight admit to taking medication to help them stay awake during the day, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW TECH TO CHOOSE BABY GENDER?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/HEALTH-SCIENCE/Could-new-Israeli-research-allow-humans-to-choose-their-childrens-sex-594249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€œWe proved the concept in mouse models, but the concept could also be demonstrated in cattle, swine, goats, chickens and other animals," the lead researcher said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Buying of U.S. Treasuries Has Soared Since Trump Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/saudi-buying-of-u-s-treasuries-has-soared-since-trump-election-1.1280844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid sex abuse scandals, Vatican upholds confession secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1b49810bb1544e37b382bc7a1a9b49fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkland survivor slams Madonna's 'GOD CONTROL' video...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/01/entertainment/emma-gonzalez-madonna-god-control/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets Parkland survivor and activist Emma González has slammed Madonna's new music video, "God Control."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/aletweetsnews/status/1145689443380187138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They're in the chamber! Spray painting the walls, unfurling the British-era colonial flag. #AntiELAB https://t.co/ieaI6AskPG”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest ever economic expansion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/451155-us-breaks-record-for-longest-economic-expansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S broke its record for time without an economic recession Monday as it began the 121st consecutive month of gross domestic product (GDP) growth since the 2008 recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER: CDC warning about outbreaks of fecal parasite found in pools, water parks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/01/cdc-warns-fecal-parasite-found-in-public-pools-is-on-the-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans who enjoy taking a dip in public pools to cool off during the summer face the danger of encountering “crypto,” a diarrhea-causing fecal parasite that is on the rise, according to the Cent…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Craziest Movie Sex Scene of Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/midsommar-inside-the-craziest-movie-sex-scene-of-the-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A very bizarre sex sequence in the horror-comedy film ‘Midsommar,’ in theaters July 3, will surely have audiences talking. Filmmaker Ari Aster breaks down the NSFW scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stray missile hits holiday island of Cyprus turning hillside into fireball...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russian-made-missile-hits-17284600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents saw a light in the sky and heard three massive explosions when the stray missile hit just miles from Nicosia, Cyprus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box Office Revenue Down 10%...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-blues-2019-revenue-down-10-percent-midyear-1221934 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The summer season so far has been rougher than expected, as proven franchises underperform and original hits are nearly extinct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS TOUCH NEW HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/30/dow-futures-surge-220-points-at-the-open-after-trump-and-xi-agree-to-not-impose-more-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and China agreed to hold off on slapping additional tariffs on their products in an effort to resume trade talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Label Boss Disputes Claims...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/taylor-swifts-ex-label-boss-disputes-her-claims-about-scooter-braun-and-masters-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Cars Damaged As 1,000 Teens Wreak Havoc In Philly Streets...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/07/01/several-philadelphia-police-cars-damaged-after-hundreds-of-teens-gather-in-north-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos broke out overnight in North Philadelphia as police clashed with hundreds of young adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poachers Invading Botswana, Last Refuge of African Elephants...</title>
      <link>https://allafrica.com/stories/201907010064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;allafrica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis - The Botswana government recently reintroduced trophy hunting after a five-year moratorium. It did so on the pretext that Botswana has &amp;quot;too many elephants&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
