<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'STORM' COMING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-united-states-france-63b0c526d4f5d8ff6c7be2b3342d95eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Israel’s prime minister is warning that the country will soon see tens of thousands of new coronavirus cases a day. Prime Minister Naftali Bennett spoke at the start of the weekly Cabinet meeting in Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower warns baffling illness affects growing number of young adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/jan/02/neurological-illness-affecting-young-adults-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several new cases in New Brunswick involve caretakers of those afflicted, suggesting a possible environmental trigger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene booted from TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/twitter-reportedly-suspends-marjorie-taylor-greenes-account-for-spreading-covid-19-misinformation/ar-AASmjZ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France removes EU flag from Arc de Triomphe after rightwing anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220102-france-removes-eu-flag-from-arc-de-triomphe-after-rightwing-anger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French authorities removed a temporary installation of the European Union flag from the Arc de Triomphe monument in Paris on Sunday, after right-wing opponents of President Emmanuel Macron accused hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES: Thousands more canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10361075/US-flightmare-worsens-New-Years-Day-hitting-season-high-2-400-flight-cancellations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of cancelled flights since Christmas Eve now totals more than 14,000 - leaving thousands of Americans stranded over the holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mice: Searching for answers to autism puzzle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-lifestyle-health-genetics-3ade8474801201208a97e1af2222bb6a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — Jake Litvag leaned in for a closer look as a lab mouse scurried around an enclosure, stopping to sniff a large block. “Hi, Jakob 1. I’m Jake,” the 16-year-old said, naming the little furry creature engineered to have the same genetic abnormality he has.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With STDs soaring in CA, new law pushes at-home tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2022-01-02/sexually-transmitted-infections-california-pushes-at-home-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new law will make California the first state to require that health insurance plans, including Medicaid, cover home STI tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF strikes Gaza in retaliation to rocket fire toward Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-690329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho deals with violent, 'nasty' rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-offensive-as-it-is-it-s-not-illegal-idaho-deals-with-violent-nasty-rhetoric/article_68f92920-fc8f-51a6-96e8-d78818ff9327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho — On Monday, Oct. 25 — the same day a shooter killed two people and injured several others at the Boise Towne Square mall — an Idaho man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol rioters' tears, remorse don't spare them from jail...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/congress/2022/01/capitol-rioters-tears-remorse-dont-spare-them-from-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Florida business owner Robert Palmer cheered on the violence at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 before he joined the fray. Screaming obscenities, he hurled a wooden plank and a fire…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus rampant among deer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/covid-rampant-deer-research-shows-rcna10181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans have infected wild deer with Covid-19 in a handful of U.S. states and there’s evidence the virus has been spreading between deer, according to recent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of political schism, pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/1-in-3-americans-say-violence-against-government-can-be-justified-citing-fears-of-political-schism-pandemic/ar-AASld12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKE VACCINE CARD BIZ BOOMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/02/fake-vaccine-cards-selling-omicron-variant-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fake vaccine cards are selling like crazy ... and demand has shot up over the past few weeks as the Omicron variant surges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trumpism isn't gone. It's 'almost religion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/02/trump-capitol-riot-aftermath-526277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The riot at the Capitol briefly looked like it had broken Trump's hold on the GOP. Instead, he has reaffirmed his dominion over the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands gather in Amsterdam despite demonstration ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-riots-netherlands-22d23ceea93fb5d2d5d03eb08dc6bddf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM (AP) — Thousands of people in the capital of the Netherlands defied a ban and gathered Sunday for a demonstration against the Dutch government's coronavirus lockdown measures before police pushed the crowd off an Amsterdam square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorean makes rare defection to NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-59851097</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seoul said it had asked the North, which has a shoot-on-sight policy, to protect the person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>34% of Americans say violence against govt justified...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/02/34-percent-of-americans-say-violence-against-government-justified/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results found that 40 percent of Republicans agreed it could sometimes be “justified for citizens to take violent action against the government.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS OR PITBULL?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10362197/Jeff-Bezos-Lauren-Sanchez-celebrate-New-Year-family-crazy-disco-party-St-Barts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire Amazon founder, 57, took to Instagram on Saturday and shared several snaps from the bash where he put on a loved-up display with Lauren, 52.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding meteor blamed for ground shaking, loud boom in Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/02/exploding-meteor-blamed-for-ground-shaking-loud-boom-in-pittsburgh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials from the National Weather Service believe that a meteor exploded in the Pittsburgh area on New Year’s Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine won't rat out for lighter sentence, brother says...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/north-america/ghislaine-maxwells-brother-says-she-wont-rat-out-for-lighter-sentence/news-story/278b60eb586b853a94d114175f3f4022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell is a convicted sex offender and disgraced British socialite — but she’s no rat, her brother tells The Sunday Times of London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major blaze rips through South Africa parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-59850904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire parliamentary complex is severely damaged, according to a city official, with a roof gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Adams hits ground running in first day and promises to 'get stuff done'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/new-york-elections-government/ny-eric-adams-110th-mayor-911-call-cornell-hospital-103rd-precinct-20220101-44oaymil4jcf7hkyvvv5l5vnri-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams, New York City’s newly-minted 110th mayor, kicked off his morning waiting for the J train with a call to 911 after witnessing a fight. He then gave his first speech to New Yorkers — remotely from City Hall’s Blue Room. After that, he headed to New York-Prebyterian/Weill Cornell to check on a cop who’d been shot earlier in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals set fire to Key West's most famous landmark, causing 'extensive damage'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vandals-set-fire-key-west-192600623.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hunt is on for two men who defaced one of Key West’s most famous and most photographed landmarks on New Year’s Day: the giant and colorful Southernmost Point buoy. The vandals caused “extensive damage” to the buoy between 3 and 3:30 a.m. Saturday, according to Key West police. And, the incident was caught on video. The most noticeable damage is on the front of the buoy, with charring over ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fights New Hazard: 10 Inches of Snow...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/01/after-catastrophic-fire-colorado-fights-a-new-hazard-10-inches-of-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Colo. — Just two days after they fled a firestorm, residents of two Colorado suburbs gutted by flames slogged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady faces Wilson in largest age gap between QBs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-entertainment-tom-brady-florida-60b97f2aaf51b83f0e76c7d07e7dc2cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J. (AP) — Tom Brady was beginning his senior season at Michigan when he celebrated his 22nd birthday, a fresh-faced quarterback who was eight months away from being an unheralded sixth-round draft pick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crews use ropes, helicopters to rescue 20 on stuck tram car...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mountains-albuquerque-dcb3ce08d37d32627efffcfe8b70f348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — Search and rescue crews used ropes and helicopters Saturday to rescue 20 people who were stranded overnight in a tram car after an iced-over cable caused the car to get stuck high up in the Sandia Mountains overlooking Albuquerque, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: Prince Andrew can't halt suit with domicile claim...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-lawsuits-jeffrey-epstein-lewis-a-kaplan-3da2689ec7313c1136d09b76a58efb9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Prince Andrew’s effort to immediately block the progression of a lawsuit by a woman who says he sexually assaulted her when she was 17 — on the grounds that she no longer lives in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY SHATTERS COVID RECORD</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/covid-headlines-updates-latest-news-coronavirus/11413570/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York State is starting 2022 with a new single-day COVID case record - 85,476.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betty White remembered by animals rights groups as tireless activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-betty-white-animals-death-20220101-f24qviaruzg6zkopjklle5ssvy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White's death was announced Friday, just weeks shy of her 100th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Worrying About COVID Leads To Mental Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/worrying-covid-mental-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People dwelling on pandemic-related fears made poorer choices, miscalculated the risks of certain outcomes, and displayed slower mental processing speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futurologist predicts 'tormented year' as robots take jobs, water runs out...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/futurologist-predicts-2022-tormented-year-25830226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top futurologist Marian Salzman tells us her predictions for 2022 with robots stealing our jobs, political upheaval, hybrid schooling, angst and electronic pets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 People Trapped in New Mexico Cable Cars After Lines Freeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.krqe.com/news/albuquerque-metro/multiple-people-trapped-in-sandia-peak-tram-car-overnight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krqe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (KRQE) – Multiple people are stranded on the Sandia Peak Tramway after icy conditions late Friday night. According to General Manager Michael Donovan, moisture and winds caus…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC will consider race when distributing life-saving virus treatments...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/01/nyc-considering-race-in-distributing-life-saving-covid-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will take a patient’s race into account when distributing potentially life-saving COVID treatments, the Department of Health and Mental Hygiene revealed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
