<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Killer clown sparks terror peering through windows late at night...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7524289/killer-clown-sparks-terror-by-tapping-on-doors-and-peering-through-windows-late-at-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOWN has been gripped by early Halloween horror after killer clown started knocking on doors and peering in through windows late at night. The prankster dressed in the clown costume is terrifying…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Theresa May Be Forced to Hold Second Brexit Vote?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/can-theresa-may-be-forced-to-hold-a-second-brexit-referendum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Theresa May Be Forced to Hold a Second Brexit Referendum?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: TX DEMS ASK NONCITIZENS TO REGISTER TO VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/18/texas-democrats-ask-noncitizens-register-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Democratic Party asked non-citizens to register to vote, sending out applications to immigrants with the box citizenship already checked “Yes,” according to new complaints filed Thursday asking prosecutors to see what laws may have been broken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking state of plane after severe turbulence injures 15 passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7531866/shocking-state-of-plane-after-severe-turbulence-injures-15-passengers-on-eight-hour-flight-from-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PLANE was left strewn with food and safety equipment after being hit with severe turbulence in a nightmare eight-hour flight. More than a dozen passengers were injured during the terrifying fligh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE?  Saudi who arrived in Turkey day of Khashoggi disappearance dies in 'traffic accident'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/18/saudi-who-arrived-in-turkey-day-of-khashoggi-disappearance-dies-in-traffic-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the 15 Saudis who arrived in Turkey the same day Jamal Khashoggi disappeared has died in a “suspicious traffic accident” and the Saudi consul in Istanbul could be the “next…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South African city set to seize land in national 'test case'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/550d2a368f094eccb15d20276eabfc21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EKURHULENI, South Africa (AP) — As South Africa's passionate debate over land redistribution grows, one city outside Johannesburg is preparing what the mayor calls a "test case" for the nation — the seizure of hundreds of acres of land from private owners, without paying for it, to build low-cost housing. Like other South African cities, Ekurhuleni faces a dire housing crunch, with some 600,000 of its nearly 4 million people living in "informal settlements" and a shortage of land to build homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/republicans-could-still-control-congress-after-the-midterms-polls-suggest-2018-10-18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With less than three weeks to go before the midterm elections, there are signs a “blue wave” may not wash across Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN SHOWDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d52af53fc55b49cdbd320df9a19ff626</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECUN UMAN, Guatemala (AP) — Members of a 3,000-strong migrant caravan have massed in this Guatemalan border town across the muddy Suchiate River from Mexico, as U.S. President Donald Trump threatens retaliation if they continue toward the United States. The first members of the group began arriving in Tecun Uman on buses and trucks early Thursday, but the bulk of the caravan sloshed into town on foot in a downpour late in the afternoon and into the evening. Hundreds walked to the river's edge where they sang the national anthems of Honduras and Guatemala.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b154544a9a9c42ab8d77b8848313c324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSOULA, Mont. (AP) — President Donald Trump praised a Republican congressman for body-slamming a reporter last year, calling him a "tough cookie" and saying he thinks it might have helped him win election in Montana. At a campaign rally in Missoula Thursday, Trump lauded Rep. Greg Gianforte, who pleaded guilty to misdemeanor assault for an attack on Guardian reporter Ben Jacobs. The attack came a day before Gianforte won a 2017 special election to serve the remaining 18 months in the House term vacated by now-Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOV: COMPLAINT BEING INVESTIGATED...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/GregAbbott_TX/status/1053058984414982145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A complaint says the Texas Democratic Party asked noncitizens to register to vote, sending applications with citizenship box pre-checked. This is being investigated. If true there will be serious consequences. #txlege #tcot #PJNET https://t.co/dgSPT8f77G”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala proposes giving American families $500 a month...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article220239985.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Kamala Harris has introduced a bill that could give American families up to $500 a month, in the form of a tax credit, to help them afford rising cost of living expenses. It faces long odds in the Congress but could help Harris politically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State media accuses west of double standards...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang/china-state-paper-accuses-west-of-double-standards-on-xinjiang-idUSKCN1MT00N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The western media is guilty of "double standards" when it comes to rep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resignation fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/18/politics/john-kelly-john-bolton-immigration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A heated argument in the West Wing between chief of staff John Kelly and national security adviser John Bolton over a recent surge in border crossings turned into a shouting match Thursday, two sources familiar with the argument told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK:  Kelly, Bolton Profane Shouting Match Outside Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-18/kelly-bolton-in-shouting-match-as-white-house-tensions-reemerge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Republicans could [barely] hang on to House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/18/midterms-republicans-house-913906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlikely? Definitely. Impossible? No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA official sent sexual, racist messages over top secret computer network...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/jasonaleopold/a-senior-nsa-official-engaged-in-abusive-behavior-toward</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Subsequent to being disciplined, he did not cease his misconduct,” an NSA inspector general report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo listens to alleged execution recording, Turks say...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/pompeo-listened-alleged-recording-murder-jamal-khashoggi-source/story?id=58595725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has heard an alleged audio recording of Washington Post columnist Jamal Khashoggi's murder inside the Saudi consulate in Istanbul, according to a senior Turkish official. Speaking exclusively and on condition of anonymity to ABC News, the official claimed the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unwanted game of 'footsies' on SOUTHWEST flight ends in emergency landing, arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2018/10/18/unwanted-game-footsies-southwest-airlines-flight-ends-emergency-landing-denton-mans-arrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Denton man touched a woman on a Southwest Airlines flight this week and then yelled at flight attendants after she moved to a new seat, causing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble to escape world's deepest cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/adventure/2018/10/flood-escape-deepest-cave-veryovkina-abkhazia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A National Geographic photographer recounts his fight to escape the world's deepest cave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman torches own home before ambushing firefighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.kezi.com/content/news/Springfield-gunmen-posted-about-health-divorce-right-before-ambush-497879751.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kezi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About an hour before the ambush, Lance Jacobs wrote a lengthy post on his Facebook page about problems in his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sex with ex good for you?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/18/sex-ex-partner-might-actually-good-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conventional wisdom warns that jumping into bed with an ex-partner after a breakup can only lead to greater heartache.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uighur Americans Speak Against China Internment Camps. Their Relatives Disappear...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/uighur-americans-speak-against-china-s-internment-camps-their-relatives-disappear/17924910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROSSLYN, Va. — Speaking last month at a Washington think tank, Rushan Abbas relayed tales of suffering she had heard about China’s repression of ethnic Uighur Muslims — including the detention of members of her husband’s family in a widespread system of mass internment camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Shoplifter busted with 'Call My Lawyer' sweatshirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.roanoke.com/news/crime/roanoke_county/arrest-made-and-shoes-seized-after-roanoke-county-sneaker-store/article_4837e1ce-eeab-5c64-b34a-f0184f877af5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roanoke.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third recent break-in at a Roanoke County sneaker shop shows an intruder was, yet again, at least partially foiled by the fact that shoes come in twos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents planning 'pox parties' to immunize kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/health/colorado-facebook-groups-organize-play-dates-to-intentionally-share-chickenpox/73-604677522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the chickenpox vaccine was introduced more than 20 years ago, parents regularly exposed their kids to the virus to build an immunity. Today, some parents refuse to vaccinate their children fearing very rare side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for suburban women...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/411957-trump-attacks-fuel-gop-fears-about-losing-suburban-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's personal attacks on women are fueling GOP fears that the party may lose suburban female voters in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ignorant' Warren Takes Heat from Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/10/elizabeth-warren-shows-democrats-how-to-lose-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren’s maneuver stands as a warning sign for other presidential contenders. Getting into the mud pit with Trump has revealed itself as a sucker’s game. Like a scientist trying to argue with a climate-change denier, you’ll just end up drowning in a tide of bad faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Offers Prospects $125k as Alternative to College...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/18/sports/nba-g-league-one-and-done.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eighteen-year-olds who previously played for Duke or Arizona may now be suiting up for the Fort Wayne Mad Ants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker: Canada out-Americaning America...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/cory-booker-canada-is-more-american-than-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ probes Catholic Church sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/justice-department-probes-catholic-church-sex-abuse-pennsylvania-202321682.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department has opened an investigation into child sex abuse by priests in Pennsylvania, four Roman Catholic Church dioceses said on Thursday. The dioceses of Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, Erie and Allentown told Reuters that they had received federal subpoenas following a state grand jury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted rapist using TINDER claims 'easy-going guy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7526324/double-rapist-using-tinder-claiming-hes-an-easy-going-guy-after-release-from-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DOUBLE rapist is using Tinder claiming he is an “easy-going guy” after being released from prison. Vile Brian Davey is using the dating app to hook up with women despite being convict…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First case of Mad Cow in decade on UK farm...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com.au/2018/10/18/22/15/mad-cow-disease-confirmed-on-scottish-farm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico deploys hundreds of riot police as migrants near...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-deploys-hundreds-riot-police-migrants-near-184343226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico deployed hundreds of riot police Thursday to its border with Guatemala as a caravan of Central American migrants prepared to cross on their way to the United States, defying President Donald Trump's threats. Hundreds of federal police in riot gear fanned out on the international bridge in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH:   250 Snakes, Skunks, Ferrets, Gators Inside PA Home...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/10/18/officials-find-more-than-250-snakes-alligators-and-skunks-found-in-montgomery-county-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators believe the home is connected to a similar incident in Macungie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Headless Vehicles Will Reshape World...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-autonomous-vehicles-will-reshape-our-world-1539871201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-driving cars are just one piece of the puzzle. Former New York City traffic commissioner Samuel I. Schwartz (aka Gridlock Sam) explains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothel Owner Expected To Win Election Despite Death...</title>
      <link>http://www.wlsam.com/2018/10/18/nevada-brothel-owner-expected-to-win-election-despite-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wlsam.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just because you're dead doesn't mean you still can't win. That seems to be the message Nevada voters are sending as Dennis Hof will likely get elected to the state Legislature in a few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian town besieged by polar bears...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-town-besieged-polar-bears-173143073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coastal town in the Russian Arctic has been besieged by hungry polar bears who are spending more time on land as sea ice melts due to climate change.  At least six bears near Dikson, the most northern inhabited place in Russia, have kept its 500 or so residents “gripped with fear” whenever they venture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FBI Agent Sentenced 4 Years for Leaking...</title>
      <link>https://kstp.com/news/kstp-terry-albury-fbi-minnesota-sentenced/5113351/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kstp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terry James Albury, a former FBI agent in Minnesota, was sentenced  to four years in prison Thursday in U.S. District Court ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students sick from KANGAROO meat in school chili...</title>
      <link>http://sandhillsexpress.com/state-news/students-report-illness-after-consuming-kangaroo-meat-at-western-nebraska-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sandhillsexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POTTER – Some of the students at a western Nebraska high school and junior high may have fallen ill after consuming chili with kangaroo meat mixed with beef last week. News Channel Nebraska first reported the mystery meat in chili served at Potter-Dix High School and Junior High was that of the marsupial. The school’s head [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug pulled on Lena Dunham's feminist website...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/18/plug-pulled-on-lena-dunhams-lenny-letter-website/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lena Dunham’s feminist-leaning site, the Lenny Letter, is shutting down. The website from the co-creator of HBO’s “Girls,” which blasted twice-a-week e-mails with articles on women’s topics, will c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN:  Russians 'will go to heaven' in event of nuclear war...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russians-heaven-event-nuclear-war-putin-153648833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russians will "go to heaven" as martyrs in the event of nuclear war because Moscow will only ever use nuclear weapons in retaliation, President Vladimir Putin said Thursday. "We have no concept of a preemptive strike," Putin told a forum of international experts in the southern city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Reilly Scores #1 Book, Topples FOXNEWS Successor Tucker Carlson...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/bill-oreillys-book-hits-number-one-on-ny-times-best-seller-list-toppling-fox-news-successor-tucker-carlson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX braces for WSJ investigation into workplace culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/netflix-braces-investigation-workplace-culture-n921646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media company has been a runaway success in recent years, but The Wall Street Journal is looking behind the scenes to see what its employees think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis and Me...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6288743/Director-Michael-Moore-meets-Pope-Francis-outside-Vatican.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moore, who rose to fame as the director of harrowing documentary Bowling for Columbine, was pictured warmly shaking hands with the pontiff on Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 years after trauma of hack, DNC builds tech team with veteran bench...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-democrats-techteam-20181018-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON The digital operations team at the Democratic National Committee hit some dark days after Russian hackers mauled their networks in 2016, hijacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS selling stores, closing operations in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/starbucks-selling-stores-closing-operations-150820324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is restructuring its European operations after several years of slowing sales. The Seattle-based coffee chain is selling 83 company-owned stores in France, the Netherlands, Belgium and Luxembourg to its longtime partner, Alsea. Alsea will also take over operations at 177 other Starbucks locations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  $125 Million ASK for LA Mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hollywood-scion-asks-record-125-million-for-l-a-mansion-1539873135</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sports executive Casey Wasserman is selling a home on more than 3 acres of land that includes a parcel once owned by Frank Sinatra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of pounds of 'flushable wipes' clog sewer system...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/simply-not-flushable-thousands-of-pounds-of-wipes-clog-sewer-system/23887405</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ewwww.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh NOT helping key Republicans?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/backlash-kavanaugh-vote-not-helping-key-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bitter confirmation of Brett Kavanaugh to the Supreme Court, initially believed to be a benefit to Republican Senate candidates, appears now to be a mixed blessing that is helping some Democrats, according to three state polls released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What every CEO has spent on midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ceos-are-spending-their-own-money-on-the-midterm-elections-heres-how-2018-10-18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many S&amp;P 500 CEOs have been willing to fly a Democratic or Republican flag in the current election cycle, according to MarketWatch’s analysis of data on these executives’ political contributions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos #1...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/amazons-jeff-bezos-ranks-no-1-among-sp-500-ceos-in-political-spending-2018-10-18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s big political giving by the S&amp;P 500’s CEOs, and then there’s the giving by Jeff Bezos. His outlays in the current election cycle top the spending by any other S&amp;P boss by more than a factor of 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska's new tourism tagline: 'Honestly, it's not for everyone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/nation-world/national/article220207365.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska’s tourism commission announced a new promotion to attract out-of-state tourists that admits “honestly, it’s not for everyone.” But the campaign highlights pictures of the outdoors and other Nebraska assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Down to earth robots': Postmen, shoppers, builders...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/postman--shopper--builder--in-japan--there-s-a-robot-for-that-10840630</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol stops massive meth shipment...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/10/18/border-patrol-seizes-300-pounds-of-meth-in-arizona-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Customs and Border Protection seized more than 300 pounds of methamphetamine over the weekend in Arizona and California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for suburban women...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/ house/411957-trump-attacks- fuel-gop-fears-about-losing- suburban-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ: Like, Like, Like, for Sure, Like, Yeah, Yeah, Like, Like Yeah...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-kimmel-sure-yeah-yeah-yeah-montage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Yeah, yeah, for sure, for sure, um, yeah’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>127 cases of polio-like illness under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://mtstandard.com/lifestyles/health-med-fit/cases-of-polio-like-illness-under-investigation-cdc-says/article_cfbfc950-b648-5f73-9462-bf8219d2c365.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mtstandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has received reports of 127 patients under investigation for acute flaccid myelitis this year. Of these, 62 have been confirmed by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX show so scary making people vomit...</title>
      <link>http://www.wsfm.com.au/entertainment/entertainment-news/netflix-show-the-haunting-of-hill-house-is-so-scary-it-s-making-people-sick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsfm.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Netflix Horror Show The Haunting Of Hill House Is So Scary It's Making People Sick</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREATENS TO SEND MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6290511/Trump-Ill-send-MILITARY-seal-border-Mexico-doesnt-stop-Central-American-immigrants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stern, tweeted warning came as a group of more than 4,000 travels north through Mexico in the hope of reaching the United States, despite having no visas or other legal papers to enter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CARAVAN GROWS</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/more-honduran-migrants-seek-join-u-bound-group-182027226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Honduran migrants tried to join a caravan of several thousand trekking through Guatemala on Wednesday, defying calls by authorities not to make the journey after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened to cut off regional aid in reprisal. The migrants hope to reach Mexico and then cross its northern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles outbreak in Brooklyn...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/measles-outbreak-in-orthodox-jewish-community</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A measles outbreak that began when a child went on a trip to Israel now includes six cases in Williamsburg, Brooklyn and 11 cases in Rockland County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is America's Heartland? Study says 19 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/metro/what-exactly-is-america-s-heartland-missouri-s-in-the/article_49a5c383-9a3d-589d-886f-a40b30338c48.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the designation, St. Louis sits squarely in the middle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge bucks law, says boys as young as 10 can be locked up...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-juvenile-court-detention-20181017-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cook County judge on Wednesday refused to follow a county law that bans boys 12 and younger from being sent to the Juvenile Detention Center, instead siding with a state law that allows children as young as 10 to be locked up there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider swarm cloaks lake in 1,100-yard web...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spider-swarm-cloaks-greek-lake-1-000-metre-131844098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lake Vistonida in northern Greece has become an arachnophobe's worst nightmare after it was cloaked recently by massive webs spun by hundreds of thousands of small spiders. "It's caused by an overpopulation of spiders...there is an abundance of food available," local environmental</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore puts 230 desk officers on streets as murders mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/baltimore-puts-230-desk-officers-streets-murders-mount-131536561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — A day after 11 people were shot in Baltimore, the troubled police department said it's shutting down its administrative functions so that more officers can hit the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest corruption in Haiti as president calls for patience...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article220144215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-corruption protests broke out in Haiti Wednesday over about $2 billion in allegedly misused money from the PetroCaribe program sponsored by Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggered Texan tears up yard signs, rushes homeowner...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/i-hate-ted-cruz-triggered-texan-tears-up-yard-signs-rushes-homeowner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some progressives just can’t handle other people expressing their First Amendment rights. A man was caught on camera raging over the sight of Ted Cruz’s name, confronting the homeowner and rushing his cell phone camera. Nutty guy tearing up our Ted Cruz signs. #keeptexasred #turningmontrosered #VoteCruz pic.twitter.com/PG1cOcELOe — Alfredo Ramos (@reachhoustonseo) October 18, 2018 “I’m …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions to Take Part in California Earthquake Drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Drop-Cover-and-Hold-Millions-Expected-to-Take-Part-in-Great-ShakeOut-Drill-497899881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Great ShakeOut Earthquake Drill will be held Thursday, encouraging people in the Southland and around the globe to drop, cover and hold to test their level of preparedness for a major temblor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One More Bombshell Indictment?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-10-18/mueller-probably-has-one-more-bombshell-indictment-his-sleeve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herd turns on hunters after they gun down bull elephant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7524090/elephant-hunters-run-away-herd-charges-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the moment cowardly hunters flee in panic when a herd of elephants charged at them after they shot one of the bulls. Video shows two men trying to sneak up on the animals in the Nakabolelwa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS RETURNS: Terrorists take 700 hostage; Putin issues warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1033295/isis-news-putin-news-russia-war-Syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS has taken 700 people hostage in an area in Syria controlled by US-backed forces, Russian President Vladimir Putin has revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Midwestern comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/regional/the-midwest/article220188185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, the Midwest lifted Donald Trump to his upset in the presidential race. Two years later, many Democrats believe this region will be the site of their greatest success on Nov. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREATENS TO SEND MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/trump-threatens-to-call-us-military-to-close-southern-border-as-4000-strong-migrant-caravan-pushes-north</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump warned Thursday he will “call up the U.S. Military and CLOSE OUR SOUTHERN BORDER” with Mexico if officials there don’t stop the northward flow of a growing migrant caravan that's swelled in size to about 4,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders 2020? Many Bernie backers aren't feeling it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/18/bernie-sanders-2020-president-912082</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large contingent of his 2016 campaign staffers is wary of a Sanders sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLEENEX to rebrand 'mansize' tissues after gender complaints...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/kleenex-rebrand-mansize-tissues-gender-complaints-58582322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kleenex maker Kimberly-Clark says it will re-brand its "Mansize" tissues after consumers complained the name was sexist. The company says that following a "consistent increase of complaints on gender concern" the product will now be called "Kleenex Extra Large." Packages for the tissues...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blueprint unveiled for 'ultimate superhuman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6289831/Design-ultimate-superhuman-includes-Usain-Bolts-legs-Michael-Phelpss-arm-span.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a British poll athletics stars Usain Bolt and Mo Farah were named as the top real-life superhumans, with high marks for Roger Federer, Serena Williams and Jessica Ennis-Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENSPAN: Tightest labor market I've ever seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/18/alan-greenspan-this-is-the-tightest-labor-market-ive-ever-seen.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenspan served as chairman of the Fed of the United States from 1987 to 2006, spanning four presidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREATENS TO SEND MILITARY</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181018114535-ltrgt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (URGENT):Trump warns Mexico, threatens to close southern border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREATENS TO SEND MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1052885781675687936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“....In addition to stopping all payments to these countries, which seem to have almost no control over their population, I must, in the strongest of terms, ask Mexico to stop this onslaught - and if unable to do so I will call up the U.S. Military and CLOSE OUR SOUTHERN BORDER!..”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Interference Call Overshadows RED SOX Victory Over ASTROS...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/columnist/bob-nightengale/2018/10/18/astros-livid-over-controversial-home-run-call-alcs-game-4-red-sox/1680450002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Astros arenâ€™t blaming any fan, or even an umpireâ€™s call, but were left seething Wednesday believing that MLB cheated them out of a possible win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR BRETT: Exorcist plans counter-attack against witches cursing Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/thefreethinker/2018/10/exorcists-plan-counter-attack-against-witches-cursing-brett-kavanaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.patheos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Father Gary Thomas, exorcist for the Diocese of San Jose, California, is 'appalled' that a coven of witches are planning to 'hex' Trump's man in the Supreme Court, Brett Kavanaugh, on October 20. But he has a cunning plan to sabotage the cursing of Kavanaugh as well as “all rapists and the patriarchy which emboldens,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes as Hindu hardliners block women from Indian temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hindu-groups-return-indian-temple-block-women-entering-105444963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For centuries, the Sabarimala temple in Kerala state has banned women and girls between the ages of 10 and 50 from entering the holy site. Since then, the case has become a focal point for women's rights in India. Kerala's secular state government says it wants to uphold the court's decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their money worthless, Venezuela's desperate flee by foot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/business/article220212785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barely able to feed her daughter and struggling to earn a living, Sandra Cadiz made the desperate decision to leave Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As NASA's prized telescopes falter, astronomers fear losing eyes in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/As-NASA-s-prized-telescopes-falter-astronomers-13316847.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's Great Observatories - the Hubble, Chandra, Compton and Spitzer space telescopes - have peered into the unknown and made breakthrough discoveries about newborn stars, dark matter and the age of the universe itself. But these telescopes, whose era began in 1990, are aging, if not already dead, and there is no budget or political will to replace them. This sobering reality was underscored this month when two were beset by technical problems, including the Hubble Space Telescope, that temporarily halted their science. Shrinking budgets and delayed projects means astronomers will lose some of their key eyes in the skies before NASA can launch new telescopes. It will make some research impossible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK election 'war room' takes aim at fake information...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a2ac69b4033245a291a445690f71ee3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MENLO PARK, Calif. (AP) — In an otherwise innocuous part of Facebook's expansive Silicon Valley campus, a locked door bears a taped-on sign that reads "War Room." Behind the door lies a nerve center the social network has set up to combat fake accounts and bogus news stories ahead of upcoming elections. Inside the room are dozens of employees staring intently at their monitors while data streams across giant dashboards. On the walls are posters of the sort Facebook frequently uses to caution or exhort its employees. One reads, "Nothing at Facebook is somebody else's problem."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Look at this f---ing white guy!' bigot yells before attacking man in pizzeria...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-anti-white-attack-bronx-pizzeria-20181018-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bigoted attacker screamed anti-white statements at a man sitting in a Bronx pizzeria, then punched him in the face and fractured his eye socket, cops said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food, water, ride: Guatemalans aid Honduran caravan migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9919ff5a85e248d5aa96718027821aca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ZACAPA, Guatemala (AP) — Sweaty, sunburned and exhausted, Jonathan Zuniga had been carrying his 1-year-old baby in his arms for five hours when help arrived unexpectedly from a local woman who offered him a used baby carriage. "Thank you, thank you very much," Zuniga told her, accepting the gift with a broad grin. "I couldn't stand it anymore." Many of the more than 2,000 Hondurans in a migrant caravan trying to wend its way to the United States left spontaneously with little more than the clothes on their backs and what they could quickly throw into backpacks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
