<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Helen Mirren says questions over playing Golda Meir 'utterly legitimate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2022/feb/05/helen-mirren-says-questions-over-playing-golda-meir-utterly-legitimate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Lipman criticised decision to cast Mirren as former Israeli prime minister as she is not Jewish</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66-year-old retiree who left USA for Mexico: Here's what can buy here for $5 or less...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/05/66-year-old-retiree-who-left-the-us-for-mexico-what-you-can-buy-for-5-dollars-or-less.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mexico, retiree and American expat Janet Blaser lives an affordable lifestyle, where she spends less than $160 on eating out and shopping. From groceries to transportation to fun activities, here's what $5 or less can get you in Mazatlán, Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ottawa braces for covid protests as 'Freedom Convoy' blockades leave city on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ottawa-braces-for-increasingly-dangerous-covid-mandate-protests-as-freedom-convoy-blockades-leave-city-on-edge/ar-AATv7vz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics puts young Uyghur athlete at center of controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220205-beijing-olympics-puts-young-uyghur-athlete-at-centre-of-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's move to thrust a young Uyghur athlete into the spotlight at the climax of the Beijing Winter Olympics opening ceremony placed her at the centre of long-time controversy over rights abuses in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebellion sends warning across globe...</title>
      <link>https://denvergazette.com/ap/health/covid-rebellion-brews-in-canada-sending-warning-across-globe/article_20fed737-b09a-5bac-a611-fbacdc12cc11.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denvergazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadians have done as they were told during the pandemic. They lined up for shots until the country had one of the developed world’s best vaccination rates; they endured some</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for evidence? Trust us, Biden admin says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-russia-ukraine-health-europe-national-security-5c4182d83dd8b7585ac49fdbb5f91c45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When President Biden's administration was asked for evidence to back up dramatic claims about national security developments this past week, it demurred with a simple rejoinder: You’ll have to trust us on that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO MEDALS FOR USA ON FIRST DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/beijing-winter-olympics/team-usa-without-medal-after-day-1-of-olympic-competition-in-beijing/3536441/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six medal events were held Saturday morning and the United States could not find its way onto the podium in Beijing. Check out the latest from the 2022 Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's Brave Face Can't Hide His Fading Grip on Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/boris-johnson-s-brave-face-can-t-hide-his-fading-grip-on-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson’s Brave Face Can’t Hide His Fading Grip on Power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Humans Feel More Comfortable Interacting With 'Female' Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/humans-female-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washington State University researcher has found that people respond better to robots which have "female" characteristics instead of male ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heart Attacks 'Turbocharge' Mental Decline, Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/heart-attacks-mental-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show patients who show early signs of dementia after suffering a heart attack are more likely to deteriorate quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader's Death Another Blow for ISIS, but Hardly the End...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/05/leaders-death-is-another-blow-for-isis-but-its-hardly-the-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, Lebanon — For a man who sought to disappear, the leader of the Islamic State seemed to have done</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Inside the FOXNEWS Trump Helped Build...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/05/inside-the-fox-news-that-donald-trump-helped-build/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Roger Ailes ran CNBC in the mid-1990s, he gave himself a talk show called “Straight Forward.” It long ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Tough Election, Orban Turns to Putin for Support...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/05/facing-tough-election-orban-turns-to-putin-for-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST — Facing a tough election in two months, Hungary’s far-right populist prime minister, Viktor Orban, last week opened the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Elon's feud with Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4617215/elon-musk-joe-biden-feud-tesla-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you follow Elon Musk on Twitter you may have noticed that the SpaceX and Tesla CEO isn’t very happy with US President Joe Biden. Musk has accused Biden of snubbing Tesla and “treatin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History hangs over Queen Elizabeth as she marks 70 years on throne...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/diamond-jubilee-queen-elizabeth-ii-marks-70-years-throne-rcna14127</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We need to look at whether the public supports the institution or if the institution is riding the coattails of the queen,” the founder of the British Monarchists Society said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As alcohol returns to planes, flight attendants fear 'unsafe' workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/as-alcohol-returns-to-planes-some-flight-attendants-fear-an-e2-80-98unsafe-e2-80-99-workplace/ar-AATu6QK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT writer grilled for hours on second day of Palin libel trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2022/02/05/new-york-times-writer-grilled-for-hours-on-second-day-of-palin-libel-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys spent the second day of Sarah Palin’s defamation trial against the New York Times grilling the author of an erroneous editorial in sometimes excruciating detail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network faces new questions about post-Jeff Zucker future...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/592815-cnn-faces-new-questions-about-post-jeff-zucker-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Zucker’s abrupt resignation as CNN’s president this week has roiled the network internally and sent shockwaves across the media landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 arrested after passerby attacked by neo-Nazis in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/3-arrested-passerby-attacked-neo-022057418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people have been arrested days after a Jewish passerby was attacked by a group of self-proclaimed neo-Nazis who yelled antisemitic slogans outside a central Florida shopping plaza over the weekend, authorities said Friday. Group leader Burt Colucci, 45, and Joshua Terrell, 46, are each charged with battery with a hate crime enhancement, while Jason Brown, 47, is charged with grand theft, according to the Orange County Sheriff's Office. All three are members of the National Socialist Movement, one of the nation’s largest neo-Nazi groups, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Fed, MIT unveil model for electronic cash as policymakers mull whether to launch it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/boston-fed-mit-unveil-model-for-electronic-cash-as-policymakers-mull-whether-to-launch-it/ar-AATs01l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans united in worry over political divisions, but not much else...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/02/03/civility-downhill-biden-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civility has gone downhill since Biden took office, voters say in a new Georgetown University’s Institute of Politics and Public Service poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan addresses repeated use of N-word...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/02/05/joe-rogan-apologizes-for-repeated-use-of-the-n-word-in-viral-clip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I know that to most people, there is no context where a white person is ever allowed to say that word, nevermind publicly on a podcast, and I agree with that now.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUARANTINE HELL AT OLYMPICS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-quarantine-hotels-e2d2ffc60d9800cf1951cc3eaed323cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quarantine hotels are increasingly the target of criticism from athletes and their teams, who are lobbying organizers for improvements. There's a lack of transparency, too, with only some virus-positive athletes forced into quarantine hotels where their teams don't have access, while teammates in similar situations are allowed to isolate within the Olympic village.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>META adds 'personal boundary' tool after virtual world harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220204-meta-adds-personal-boundary-tool-after-virtual-world-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook parent Meta began rolling out Friday a minimum distance between users' avatars in its virtual reality Horizon network after reports of harassment, one of the thorny issues for its metaverse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis police kill Black man while executing no-knock warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/02/04/1078313707/amir-locke-killed-minneapolis-police-no-knock-warrant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Body camera footage shows that police shot and killed Amir Locke while he was on a couch, wrapped in a blanket, on Wednesday morning. Ruled a homicide, the death is being reviewed by prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whoopi Goldberg's fake Jewish past...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10474545/Whoopis-Goldbergs-offensive-1993-Jewish-American-Princess-recipe-chicken.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1993, Goldberg - whose real name is Caryn Johnson - submitted the recipe to Cooking in The Litchfield Hills, a charity cookbook comprised of recipes from residents of leafy Connecticut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA reverses pair of controversial policies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/manhattan-da-alvin-bragg-reverses-pair-of-controversial-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alvin Bragg reversed a pair of his most controversial policies with a new memo calling for commercial robberies committed with knives to once again be prosecuted as felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI HERALD Journalist Sued by Epstein Victims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-herald-journalist-julie-brown-235511651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty ImagesWhen Miami Herald reporter Julie K. Brown published her book on the Jeffrey Epstein case last year, she dedicated it to Courtney Wild and other victims of the wealthy sex-trafficker.Now Wild and fellow accuser Haley Robson are suing the star journalist, whose 2018 Herald series about Epstein’s shady plea deal for abusing scores of girls led to his indictment. The duo allege she defamed them in her book.In a stunning lawsuit, Wild and Robson say Brown published “</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Mayor called white cops 'crackers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mayor-eric-adams-called-white-nypd-officers-crackers-in-2019/ar-AATu4KD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  Trump 'wrong' to say election could be overturned...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-elections-donald-trump-election-2020-electoral-college-84ff467d9ff5bfaad084e274f69ac521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence on Friday directly rebutted Donald Trump's false claims that Pence somehow could have overturned the results of the 2020 election, saying that the former president was simply “wrong.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to gun down feral cattle spurs concern among ranchers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-travel-environment-and-nature-new-mexico-lifestyle-e968f6270da210b15313a6e98f6ad293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — A plan by U.S. Forest Service officials to put a dent in the population of feral cattle on national forest land near the New Mexico-Arizona border is drawing fire from ranchers who say gunning down the animals from helicopters is a violation of federal law and won’t help to solve the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffers Move to Unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/04/congressional-staffers-launch-push-to-unionize-00005742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes one day after Speaker Nancy Pelosi endorsed a union, but the House and Senate would have to approve a right to codify a union by certain workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German anger as Russia shuts DEUTSCHE WELLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60257581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany and the EU condemn a decision to shut down Deutsche Welle's bureau in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardi B Case May Have Ended Gossip Pages...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awqwp/what-does-cardi-bs-lawsuit-against-tasha-k-mean-for-youtubers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper’s libel case against Tasha K will change the way the internet engages with attention-seeking celebrity commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti convicted of stealing $300K from Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/michael-avenatti-convicted-of-stealing-300k-from-stormy-daniels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney-turned-criminal Michael Avenatti was convicted Friday of swiping nearly $300,000 in book-advance money from his then-client Stormy Daniels. The now-twice-convicted felon — and one-ti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JACKASS FOREVER' a 'masterpiece'? Critics rave 'tonic we all need'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/jackass-forever-reviews-1235087315/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics declare the latest stunt-filled gross-out spectacle "the tonic we all need" after years of pandemic and political division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Shocked at California's 'Third World' Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/04/clueless-newsom-shocked-at-californias-third-world-conditions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor needs to leave his fancy Sacramento-area compound more often to see what's going on throughout the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin 'falls asleep' at Olympics as Ukraine team introduced...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/vladimir-putin-falls-asleep-at-beijing-olympics-as-ukrainian-team-is-introduced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world leader was caught on camera slumped in his chair with his eyes closed as the athletes were introduced and their national anthem blared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC school lunch menu going vegan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-new-york-education-new-york-city-nyc-state-wire-bca2dcfd0dda46cb08160baf6ecfcc86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Forget mystery meat or cheese pizza. Instead, chickpea wraps and veggie tacos will be on the menu for New York City public school students as the nation's largest school district shifts to “Vegan Fridays” in school cafeterias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perth police stop church service to check masks...</title>
      <link>https://7news.com.au/news/wa/community-furore-after-police-stop-st-bernadettes-glendalough-church-service-to-check-masks-c-5567846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;7news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Churchgoers were left stunned when their Thursday night service was halted by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SQUID GAME' VIBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3ab5d8/beijing-olympics-2022-bubble-winter-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those living inside China’s Winter Olympics bubble describe shopping malls for athletes and being served by robot waiters. The only catch—they can’t leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's security men: Elite group who 'fuel anxieties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/04/putin-security-elite-siloviki-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s growing isolation has strengthened the ‘siloviki’ who surround the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside community where pedophiles live surrounded by gator-infested waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4549320/miracle-village-restoration-destination-sex-offender-community-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of sex offenders live in a 24-acre private, isolated community along a miles-long Florida road lined by gator-infested waters and surrounded by thousands of acres of sugar cane. The commun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC votes to censure Cheney, Kinzinger...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/592841-rnc-votes-to-censure-cheney-kinzinger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Committee (RNC) on Friday voted formally to censure both GOP Reps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES USED TO 'WHITEWASH' BRUTAL REGIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4614277/china-winter-olympics-torture-executions-human-rights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has been accused of using the Winter Olympics to try to “whitewash” the regime’s disturbing record of torture and executions. The world’s eyes have descended on Beijin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/discovery-ceo-david-zaslav-reveals-he-sees-cnn-as-the-leader-in-news-to-the-left</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive who is soon to take over CNN made a candid admission about where he sees the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC rapper gunned down hours after signing record contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/rapper-tdott-woo-shot-dead-in-brooklyn-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Tdott Woo was shot and killed on Avenue L in Canarsie, Brooklyn on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How machines stole our privacy...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/how-covid-stole-our-privacy/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have outsourced morality to machines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW BOSS DECLARES: CNN LEADER 'IN NEWS TO THE LEFT'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/discovery-ceo-calls-cnn-leader-in-news-to-the-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery CEO David Zaslav made a frank admission regarding CNN’s ideology on Friday, describing the news network as the leading source for left-leaning viewpoints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Caliph Without a Caliphate...</title>
      <link>https://newlinesmag.com/reportage/a-caliph-without-a-caliphate-the-biography-of-isiss-new-leader/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newlinesmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents and pictures, made public in English by New Lines for the first time, that indicate Qardash was in fact a leading figure among Iraqi jihadist groups over the past two decades who has steadily worked his way up the security and religious hierarchy within the Islamic State group.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
