<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LUCAS 'BETRAYED'</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/george-lucas-felt-betrayed-by-disney-direction-star-wars-sequel-trilogy-bob-iger-2551018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney CEO Bob Iger has recalled how George Lucas "felt betrayed" upon learning of their plans for the 'Star Wars' sequel trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63-vehicle pileup occurs in southeastern Virginia amid fog, ice...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/2-people-sustained-life-threatening-injuries-in-35-vehicle-pileup-on-i-64-amid-ice-fog/649777</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How an 'urgent' tip became 'high crimes'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5a44803c177adf2e1837c9e265972cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The night before the whistleblower complaint that launched President Donald Trump's impeachment was made public, Democrats and Republicans on the House Intelligence Committee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle lines harden... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191222182538-l3b1u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (CORRECTED, UPDATE 1, PIX):REFILE-UPDATE 1-Battle lines harden over Trump impeachment trial witnesses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 predictions for 2020: Here's what people thought would happen by this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/22/2020-predictions-decades-ago-self-driving-cars-mars-voting/2594825001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, academics, futurists and government agencies cast their predictions of what would happen by the year 2020. Here's what happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRANDUS:  Real bias in cable news isn't what you think...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-real-cable-news-bias-isnt-what-you-think-2019-12-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social-media amplification gives cable news greater influence than they deserve, says Paul Brandus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We've just had 'best decade in human history'...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/just-best-decade-human-history-seriously/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CATS' CALAMITY AT BOXOFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/cats-bombs-at-the-box-office-reasons-why-1202813693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The atrocious response from audiences and critics toward the feature adaptation of Andrew Lloyd Webber’s Cats has no doubt upset execs at Universal and Working Title this weekend. The movie w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slams 'unfair' Pelosi delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9960fe3dbd47e87e71c075306f899776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — President Donald Trump complained Saturday about House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's delayed transmission of the articles of impeachment to the Senate, which may delay a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard rescues surfer after terrifying shark attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article238637798.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Socialism Became a Dirty Word -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/socialism-became-dirty-word-again-050152014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It was a bad year to be any kind of socialist in Europe. The decline has been long and agonizing for a once-dominant force, but in 2019 falling popularity reached new depths and raised questions over whether reinvention can lead to a revival.   A decade ago, the prime ministers of Britain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of AMAZON's first employees says company should be broken up...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2019/12/20/21031694/amazon-employee-break-up-paul-barton-davis-marketplace-sellers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos hired Paul Davis to build Amazon’s website. Now Davis wants to break it up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legionaires founder sexually abused 60 boys, religious order's report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-abuse/legionaires-founder-sexually-abused-60-boys-religious-orders-report-says-idUSKBN1YQ02Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexual abuse of minors was rife among superiors of the Legionaires of Christ Cat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide rate rising fast for black youth, report finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/suicide-rate-rising-fast-black-youth-report-finds-n1103956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The gap is narrowing between black and white youth, and we must get at the bottom of why.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New emails give more details on Ukraine aid timeline...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/21/politics/emails-ukraine-aid-timeline/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 90 minutes after President Donald Trump spoke to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on July 25, Trump's political appointees at the White House's budget office were already ordering the Pentagon to freeze security funding for Ukraine, newly released government documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: 7 shot downtown...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-shootings-20191222-5bp26guiizaxdiyvweypicb27e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people, including three teenagers, were shot in downtown Baltimore early Sunday morning, according to Baltimore police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech Could Lose Financial Blessing of Church of England...</title>
      <link>https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/22/12/2019/Big-tech-could-lose-financial-blessing-of-the-Church-of-England</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepeninsulaqatar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church of England has started a review into whether its holdings in big tech firms are compatible with Christian faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN adds non-binary gender booking options...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/american-airlines-adds-non-binary-gender-booking-options/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline has not included the non-binary gender option in their online booking process yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother of 49ERS QB killed in double murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/49ers-quarterback-brother-murdered-casey-beathard-brother-of-backup-quarterback-cj-beathard-killed-in-double-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were stabbed outside The Dogwood bar in Nashville on Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING capsule becomes first to return from orbit, land on ground...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d941852c59a4811603a8ab3611a3cb8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Boeing safely landed its crew capsule in the New Mexico desert Sunday after an aborted flight to the International Space Station that threatened to set back the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandal-plagued city names 3 new police chiefs in 1 week...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/scandal-plagued-vermont-city-names-police-chiefs-week/story?id=67879052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burlington, Vermont, is now hiring a retired former police chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious greenish-yellow liquid gushing onto Detroit highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/oakland/2019/12/21/green-liquid-i-696-lane-closed/2721790001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right lanes will remain closed until Monday after hexavalent chromium oozed from the walls of the I-696 freeway in Madison Heights walls on Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS driver 'worked to death' delivering 240 packages a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/tragic-ups-delivery-driver-worked-21146174</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dad-of-two Paul Crush, 42, collapsed from a suspected heart attack at the end of a 12-hour shift – as workload 'doubled' over Christmas for pressure-hit staff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army to use Kardashian's bottom as new recruiting tool...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7817755/New-campaign-encourages-people-serve-Army-instils-confidence-receiving-likes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mail on Sunday can reveal the concept behind the Army's new advertising campaign is that serving in the Armed Forces instils greater confidence than receiving 'likes' on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba gets first prime minister in over 40 years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuba-gets-first-prime-minister-over-40-years-001102784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba's first prime minister in more than four decades -- long-serving tourism minister Manuel Marrero -- took office Saturday as the country resurrected a post last held by Fidel Castro. The appointment of Marrero, 56, as head of government is part of a process of decentralization and generational</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Us vs. them: President to use to rev up base...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1221d4b055c568daa639663783ffd258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Using stark “us vs. them” language, President Donald Trump and his reelection campaign have begun framing his impeachment not as a judgment on his conduct but as a referendum on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl finds note in Christmas cards from Chinese prison factory 'slave' pleading for help...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10603733/girl-tesco-christmas-cards-note-from-slave-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GIRL aged six discovered a desperate note in her Tesco Christmas cards from caged slaves in China forced to work against their will. Florence Widdicombe, from Tooting, south London, was stunned w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hope for 2-year-old girl's resurrection shifts to memorial service...</title>
      <link>https://www.redding.com/story/news/2019/12/21/hope-girls-resurrection-shifts-bethel-memorial-service/2722748001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.redding.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Facebook post by the Bethel Church on Friday acknowledges an outpouring ofÂ prayers hasn't brought the girl back to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: 13 shot inside memorial party for gunshot victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-englewood-11-wounded-shooting-20191222-mrad2j42ffenpawbh5yo4adzba-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooter opened fire inside a house party early Sunday in the Englewood neighborhood on the South Side, wounding about 11 people, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer plate umps allowed in new MLB labor deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d8760e52b8ced5b8436c60891ea6e877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Computer plate umpires could be called up to the major leagues at some point during the next five seasons. Umpires agreed to cooperate with Major League Baseball in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber attack forces airline to cancel flights in Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/467798874ec33be017978255358e1b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — RavnAir canceled at least a half-dozen flights in Alaska on Saturday — at the peak of holiday travel — following what the company described as “a malicious cyber attack”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 passenger buses engulfed in flames at LAX...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/three-passenger-buses-engulfed-in-flames-at-lax-prompting-traffic-delays/5776402/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three unoccupied passenger buses caught fire Saturday night at Los Angeles International Airport, fire officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soda machine kills 2 MCDONALD's workers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/defective-soda-machine-killed-two-mcdonalds-workers-peru-102255454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defective soda vending machine was responsible for the deaths of two McDonald's cleaners in Peru, the general manager for the Lima franchise told a local news station on Saturday night. Carlos Campos, 19, and Alexandra Porrasa, 18, died late on December 15 as they cleaned the fast food restaurant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's souvenir wine bottle pops up in big-donor debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e14a600779dddcabb8a3a809573285e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On a Saturday evening in June 2018, with temperatures in the 70s and the Red Sox playing at Fenway Park, supporters of Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren gathered at the City...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
