<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dog accused of a HATE CRIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6401779/The-DOG-accused-hate-crime-fouling-outside-home-just-one-2-500-cases-probed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police notes recorded: 'An unknown dog has fouled outside of victim address and victim perceived this to be a racial incident.’ The Met had more than 2,500 complaints for hate crime in 2015 and 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas 'Becoming' a billion-dollar brand...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/17/the-obamas-are-becoming-a-billion-dollar-brand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Obamas are “Becoming” — billionaires. The launch of Michelle Obama’s cross-country book tour for her new memoir, “Becoming,” last week is just the latest marker on the road to fabulous wealth f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1200+ STILL MISSING</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181118030334-ckup2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRES/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 5-Search on for 1,276 now missing after California's deadliest wildfire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS MAKES HIS MOVE?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1046795/brexit-news-theresa-may-confidence-vote-boris-johnson-jacob-rees-mogg-david-davis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SENIOR Brexiteers are in talks to decide who should replace Theresa May with a confidence vote expected this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHOOL WITH 17 CHILDREN CHANGING GENDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6401593/Whistleblower-teacher-makes-shocking-claim-autistic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mail on Sunday can reveal that 17 pupils at a single British school are in the process of changing gender. According to a whistleblower most of the youngsters have autism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CHAOS CONTINUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-46250607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Brexit Secretary Dominic Raab criticises the "lack of will and resolve" in dealing with the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  What has President Trump learned from defeat? </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/What-has-President-Trump-learned-from-defeat-13401267.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All presidents suffer defeats and setbacks, whether through elections, legislative battles, international events or scandals. Most learn from them and adapt. Will President Donald Trump be an exception? That's the question ahead for the president: Will the second two years of his first term be any different from the first two years? His actions and words in the days following the midterm elections indicate things actually could get worse rather than better. He has never been a gracious winner. In defeat, he has shown worse: ill-tempered, withdrawn, even more unpredictable. Trump was elected in 2016 to lead a divided country. The midterm results, however, make clear the degree to which he has widened those divisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing on this page is real': How lies become truth in online America ...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/nothing-on-this-page-is-real-how-lies-become-truth-in-online-america/2018/11/17/edd44cc8-e85a-11e8-bbdb-72fdbf9d4fed_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Facebook, he writes America’s Last Line of Defense. She likes and shares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could you fit in this airplane bathroom? </title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/travel/news/108684430/its-a-struggle-to-fit-into-shrinking-airplane-bathrooms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The toilets on some planes are now so small, an average-size person feels squeezed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With hospitalization losing favor, judges order outpatient mental health treatment...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/with-hospitalization-losing-favor-judges-order-outpatient-mental-health-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every state in the country allows courts to force people with severe mental illnesses into treatment against their will. But critics argue these controversial intervention programs fail to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'has taken the gloves off' in thefts of U.S. tech secrets...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-china-economic-espionage-20181116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the great microchip heist — a stunning Chinese-backed effort that pilfered $8.75 billion in secret American technology. But the real secret is it wasn't unusual. After a lull under President Obama, Chinese economic espionage is soaring again as U.S. relations with Beijing worsen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000+ STILL MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-chokes-toxic-air-wildfires-rage-170430103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump expressed sadness Saturday at the devastation in a California town, as more than 1,000 people remain listed as missing in the worst-ever wildfire to hit the US state. Two huge blazes have created a serious smoke problem across vast areas in the state, and when Trump stepped out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moral panic' targets Indonesia's LGBT community...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/moral-panic-targets-indonesias-lgbt-community-024855676.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesian Budi Ahmad used to live openly as a gay man without fear of becoming a target for violence in the world's biggest Muslim-majority nation. The country of 260 million is in the grip of a moral panic, with critics saying the vulnerable LGBT minority is being used as a political punching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's popularity falls to 25%...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/macrons-popularity-falls-25-percent-poll-231241851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popularity of French President Emmanuel Macron has dropped to just 25 percent, according to a major tracker poll published on Sunday. The poll by research group Ifop was published in the Journal du Dimanche a day after a nationwide "yellow vest" protest against high fuel prices that analysts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL OF ORANGE COUNTY TURNS BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2018-midterms-california-gil-cisneros-young-kim-1542508058-d32b1cf0-8ee8-411d-92d9-209346c2022b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats flip the last remaining Republican seat in Orange County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al-Qaeda Threatens More Infernos...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/having-long-promoted-arson-tactic-al-qaeda-now-touts-california-burning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They will question you about the mountains. Say: 'My Lord will scatter them as ashes,'" says the text citing the Quran, imposed over news photos from the blazes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS FLIP ANOTHER SEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrat-cisneros-nabs-gop-house-seat-southern-california-021426659--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Gil Cisneros captured a Republican-held U.S. House seat in Southern California on Saturday, capping a Democratic rout in which the party picked up six congressional seats in the state. In what had been the last undecided House contest in California, Cisneros beat Republican Young Kim for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See Opportunity in Mississippi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mississippis-gop-senator-is-tripping-all-over-herself-and-dems-are-starting-to-see-an-opportunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the last Senate contest of the cycle with a high degree of uncertainty. Democrats want to help but not mess things up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants get cool reception in Mexican town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cecfafdd898b478b81afb20a1e4f4279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico (AP) — Many of the nearly 3,000 Central American migrants who have reached the Mexican border with California via caravan said Saturday they do not feel welcome in the city of Tijuana, where hundreds more migrants are headed after more than a month on the road. The vast majority were camped at an outdoor sports complex, sleeping on a dirt baseball field and under bleachers with a view of the steel walls topped by barbed wire at the newly reinforced U.S.-Mexico border. The city opened the complex after other shelters were filled to capacity. Church groups provided portable showers, bathrooms and sinks. The federal government estimates the migrant crowd in Tijuana could soon swell to 10,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN FIRE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f52ea34a9f3477e9dc76bd57ab30cad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARADISE, Calif. (AP) — President Donald Trump on Saturday acknowledged Californians suffering from twin tragedies, walking through the ashes of a mobile home and RV park in a small northern town all but destroyed by deadly wildfires and privately consoling people grieving after a mass shooting at a popular college bar outside Los Angeles. "This has been a tough day when you look at all of the death from one place to the next," Trump said before flying back to Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine sub found partially 'imploded' after yearlong search...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-argentina-submarine/argentine-sub-found-partially-imploded-after-yearlong-search-idUSKCN1NM08B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Argentine Navy submarine that went missing a year ago off the country's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN FIRE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8f52ea34a9f3477e9dc76bd57ab30cad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEALE AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — President Donald Trump took a helicopter tour Saturday over the Northern California landscape scorched by a killer wildfire. A full cover of haze and the smell of smoke greeted the president upon his arrival at an Air Force base, as did the governor and his successor. Trump planned to hear from those leaders about the dire situation and talk with first responders, and later was expected to travel several hundred miles south to visit with victims of a recent country music bar shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment of truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-robert-mueller-investigation-questions-888c6956-ea10-40f1-a625-2e8ab092c4ea.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over his decades in public life, Trump has faced scant — if any — serious consequences for saying things that are not true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu heads into cabinet showdown as allies demand early elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netanyahu-heads-cabinet-showdown-allies-174831486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu faces a showdown with his coalition government partners on Sunday as he tries to stop them from forcing early elections in the wake of his unpopular decision to agree to a ceasefire with Hamas.  Three of the smaller parties in the Israeli prime minister’s coalition have demanded elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA building plane that could see return of supersonic passenger travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7763387/nasa-and-defence-giant-lockheed-martin-building-plane-that-could-see-the-return-of-supersonic-passenger-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is joining forces with US defence giant Lockheed Martin to build a state-of-the-art test plane that could pave the way for the return of supersonic passenger travel. It’s hoped the X-59 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA RECOUNTS BY HAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/broward-counts-the-wrong-ballots-as-florida-races-to-finish-manual-recount-ahead-of-sunday-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broward County’s second day of manual recounting stopped about an hour after it began Saturday when lawyers from both political parties pointed out that volunteers were counting the wrong ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN FIRE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6399991/California-searches-1-000-missing-deadliest-fire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll from the catastrophic California wildfires now stands at 71, as more than 1,100 remain missing in and around Paradise. But officials said the missing list could contain duplicate names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL AL diverts flight after religious passengers become violent in Shabbat scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/el-al-diverts-flight-after-religious-passengers-become-violent-in-shabbat-scare/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultra-Orthodox create uproar on two separate planes from New York due to fears they would arrive after sundown Friday, causing one of the flights to detour to Athens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill and Hillary's tour sideshow Dems don't need?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/17/hillary-bill-clinton-speaking-tour-democrats-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid rumours of a possible 2020 run, the Clintons face the possibility of unfavourable comparisons with Michelle Obama’s book tour and of an uncertain reception in the MeToo era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 78: Will Left Get Revenge on Assange?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/17/julian-assange-robert-mueller-222608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious court filing hints the Wikileaks maestro, blamed by many for Hillary’s defeat, has already been secretly charged. But for what?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midwest, Northeast brace for arctic cold...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/snow-moves-northern-plains-midwest-northeast-brace-arctic/story?id=59262423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winter weather alerts are in place across nine states on Saturday as a clipper system will deliver snow from the Rockies through the Central Plains into the Great Lakes. Slick travel conditions are to be expected Saturday morning. Snow associated with a cold front is being pushed to the south by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-ditch laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gop-seeks-last-ditch-laws-states-where-power-161144274--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — With their grip on power set to loosen come January, Republicans in several states are considering last-ditch laws that would weaken existing or incoming Democratic governors and advance their own conservative agendas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores arrested as thousands block London bridges in climate rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/17/thousands-gather-to-block-london-bridges-in-climate-rebellion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters occupied bridges across the Thames over extinction crisis in huge act of peaceful civil disobedience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These pets survived -- now rescuers need help finding owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article221803670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco SPCA and UC Davis vets are working to reunite pets rescued from the Northern CA Camp Fire with their owners. The animals’ burns are mild to severe, and most are unclaimed after the wildfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living together becoming more popular than marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/modern-love-cohabitation-on-rise-in-u-s-demographic-trends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern Love. Cohabitation on Rise in U.S.: Demographic Trends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bans 'expensive' jackets due to 'poverty shaming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/school-bans-expensive-jackets-due-to-poverty-shaming-of-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the public supports the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How human evolution was shaped by pride, guilt and gossip...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/17/how-human-evolution-was-shaped-by-pride-guilt-and-gossip/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early man was a total mean girl. Gossipy, cliquey, exclusionary — these are some of the traits our human ancestors developed to thrive over the last 6 million years, argues psychology professor Wil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA OPENS CUBA 'SPY BASE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/742951/world-war-3-putin-soviet-military-base-cuba-donald-trump-usa-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Sees Oscar Gold in 'ROMA,' but Hollywood Isn't So Sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netflix-sees-oscar-gold-in-roma-but-hollywood-isnt-so-sure-1542464971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has its best shot yet at a major Academy Award with “Roma,” a portrait of a nanny in 1970s Mexico. But first the company must contend with forces within Hollywood that have no interest in helping it win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain storms could bring more misery...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-shelter/rain-storms-could-bring-more-misery-for-california-fire-evacuees-idUSKCN1NM0HA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people displaced by California's most destructive wildfire, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of Witches in USA on Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/number-witches-us-rise-may-outnumber-presbyterians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS: Ousted Gay Councilman Says Blackmailed With Naked Photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/17/us/gay-councilman-election-recall-texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cross Coburn said he was targeted by voters in Grove, Tex., because of his sexuality. Now he’s challenging the validity of signatures on the petition that led to a recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More users delete accounts...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-users-dialing-back-use-latest-scandal-194040754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's latest scandal has left at least some users more disillusioned than ever with the social network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says written responses go to Mueller team next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/695a3c16e9d14073a40f4972d6978119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump says he "very easily" answered written questions from special counsel Robert Mueller, though he speculated that the questions had been "tricked up" to try to catch him in a lie. "They're all done," Trump told reporters at the White House early Saturday before leaving for California, adding that his responses will soon be submitted to Mueller's team. "We do that next week," he said, in what signals a new phase of the inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues hospital for resuscitating her...</title>
      <link>https://www.abqjournal.com/1247179/woman-sues-hospital-for-resuscitating-her-ex-patient-alleges-her-dnr-directive-was-ignored-after-drug-allergy-caused-her-to-have-a-cardiac-arrest-2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abqjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Yellow vest' protests against Macron snarl traffic across France...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181117-yellow-vest-protests-against-macron-snarl-traffic-across-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OF FATHERS AND SONS,' a bleak look at children training for jihad...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181117-fathers-sons-bleak-look-children-training-jihad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumatran elephant found dead with missing tusks in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/sumatran-elephant-found-dead-with-missing-tusks-in-indonesia-10941312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sumatran elephant has been found dead with its tusks removed in an apparent poaching case targeting the critically endangered animal, an ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's 'anti-NETFLIX' law to protect film industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/italys-anti-netflix-law-protect-film-industry-doc-1aw5l42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screams Of Terror Fill Philly Restaurant After Stabbing Prank...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/16/screams-of-terror-fill-philly-restaurant-after-stabbing-prank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrorized patrons took cover and ran for their lives after a man who appeared to be wearing a blood-soaked t-shirt walked into Terakawa Ramen screaming for help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel protege eyes female quota for lawmakers, takes aim at dual citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-politics/merkel-protg-eyes-female-quota-for-lawmakers-takes-aim-at-dual-citizenship-idUSKCN1NM0FC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, leading polls to succeed Angela Merkel as head of Ge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refugees create new town of 'Wallywood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article221775730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How will California find housing for the Camp Fire evacuees and where will they go? As the search continues in Paradise for the dead and missing, CA officials struggle to find homes for victims of the wildfire. Some people are making their own town of “Wallywood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence-Xi Showdown at APEC Shows U.S.-China Divide Only Widening...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/pence-slams-china-says-u-s-offers-countries-better-option</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pence Slams China, Says U.S. Offers Countries `Better Optionâ€™</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teams search for 1000 missing in fire's wake... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181117110124-v0azd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Besides the toll on human life, property losses from the blaze make it the most destructive in California history, posing the additional challenge of providing long-term shelter for displaced residents</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
