<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New 'SAW' Film to Top Box Office as Moviegoing Picks Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-15/new-saw-film-to-top-box-office-as-moviegoing-picks-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Gaetz Snorted Cocaine With Escort Who Had 'No Show' Gov't Job...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rep-matt-gaetz-snorted-cocaine-224503239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos via GettyWhen Rep. Matt Gaetz attended a 2019 GOP fundraiser in Orlando, his date that night was someone he knew well: a paid escort and amateur Instagram model who led a cocaine-fueled party after the event, according to two witnesses.The Florida congressman’s one-time wingman, Joel Greenberg, will identify that escort to investigators as one of more than 15 young women Gaetz paid for sex, according to a source familiar with the investigation.But what distinguishes this woman, Megan Zalonka, is that she turned her relationship with Greenberg into a taxpayer-funded no-show job that earned her an estimated $7,000 to $17,500, according to three sources and corresponding government records obtained by The Daily Beast.On Oct. 26, 2019, Gaetz attended the “Trump Defender Gala” fundraiser as the featured speaker at the Westgate Lake Resort in Orlando. Two witnesses present recalled friends reconvening at Gaetz’s hotel room for an after-party, where Zalonka prepared lines of cocaine on the bathroom counter. One of those witnesses distinctly remembers Zalonka pulling the drugs out of her makeup bag, rolling a bill of cash, and joining Gaetz in snorting the cocaine.While The Daily Beast could not confirm that Gaetz and Zalonka had sex that night, two sources said the pair had an ongoing financial relationship in exchange for sex. "She was just one of the many pieces of arm candy he had,” said one source familiar with the encounters between Gaetz and Zalonka.The congressman—who has declared that he “never paid for sex”—wrote off the stay at the hotel as a campaign expense, with his donors picking up the tab. Handout The U.S. Secret Service, which initiated the Greenberg investigation over allegations that Greenberg used county resources to mine Bitcoin, would not comment on the ongoing probe. Federal prosecutors with the Middle District of Florida would not say if investigators have questioned Zalonka. Greenberg’s attorney declined comment, citing attorney-client privilege.Gaetz’s office did not respond to a request for comment. However, his hired public relations firm, Logan Circle Group, did issue this statement: “Congressman Gaetz won’t be commenting on whether he dated or didn’t date specific women. The privacy of women living private lives should be protected.” Harlan Hill, the president of that firm, did not address questions about cocaine, the party, or the fundraiser.After repeated calls and messages to Zalonka over the last five weeks, her attorney told The Daily Beast on Thursday night that she “is not speaking to any media outlet.” Mark J. O’Brien, a criminal defense lawyer, said the allegations were not “accurate” but would not elaborate further. He did not respond to a list of detailed questions about the fundraiser party, Zalonka’s county contract, or her relationships with Greenberg and the congressman.Federal investigators are exploring Greenberg’s alleged role as the congressman’s go-to contact for arranging paid sexual encounters, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the probe. Greenberg is slated to plead guilty on Monday to six felonies and is expected to cooperate as a witness against his former friend.The Strange Friendship That May Bring Down Matt GaetzZalonka, who is an amateur fashion model and the communications director for the American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association, received $4,000 on Venmo from Greenberg during his first year in office in 2017—mostly in $500 installments. And Greenberg, who is married, listed various explanations for why he paid Zalonka. In the memo fields of his Venmo payments, he paid her $500 for “Stuff,” another $500 for “Orher stuff” [sic], and $1,000 for “Pool.” On a single day in November, he paid her $500 for “Food” and another $500 for “Appetizers.”But Zalonka’s interactions with Greenberg in 2017 morphed into a business relationship with the air of legitimacy. In December of that year, she was in close communication with him as she created her own company, MZ Strategy Group LLC, according to emails between Greenberg and Zalonka that were viewed by The Daily Beast. The next month, Greenberg awarded her a county contract, agreeing to pay her $3,500 a month for “management of digital content” and “production of social media engagements.”Zalonka’s firm received $3,500 installments in Seminole County taxpayer funds in January and April 2018, according to an analysis of Greenberg's government spending obtained via a public records request. Those payments would later be flagged as a “questioned or unaccounted for purchase” by county-contracted auditors with the Florida forensic accounting firm MSL. Even the tax office’s own chief financial officer, who processed the payments, noted in her reports: “do not know what it was for.”Auditors flagged other $3,500 installments in February, March, and May of that year, in the form of suspicious cash advances directly to Greenberg—but Greenberg never specified the purpose of those withdrawals. The charges appear to have ceased after that point.Four people familiar with Zalonka’s arrangement said it was a “no-show” contract. Zalonka never worked at the office, and it was unclear what service she provided, they said. Accountant Daniel J. O'Keefe, who led the forensic audit of Greenberg’s alleged self-dealing, said tax collector employees told him the woman behind the company was a mystery. O’Keefe added that he found no proof Zalonka ever provided the services itemized in her contract with Greenberg.“I have no idea what they were doing. And employees wouldn't know what they were doing. Totally a no-show job,” O’Keefe said. “There's no work product, no evidence work was done. It's just unbelievable.”Zalonka also features prominently in a tranche of Greenberg’s Venmo transactions, which include his payments to more than 40 women. Those women received hundreds of dollars at a time for memo items such as “salad,” “lemons,” and “ass,” according to financial records. The Daily Beast spoke to 12 of those women, who all said the payments were at least in part because Greenberg intended to have sex with them.Three young women paid by Greenberg, who spoke to The Daily Beast under condition of anonymity, placed Zalonka in the room during a 2018 encounter at the Duval Hotel in Tallahassee.One of the women—all of them 19-year-old students attending nearby Florida State University at the time—said Greenberg and a number of “well-connected Republican men” bought them drinks at the hotel bar, knowing how old the students were, then led them to a room furnished with “a huge pile of coke.” The men wanted to have sex with the teens and implied that Zalonka, who was in the room, would join in, one of the women recalled. When the teens refused, Greenberg, Zalonka, and another man went into a connected room to have sex, according to one of the former students and screenshots of a conversation between the three women reviewed by The Daily Beast.Zalonka had signed her marketing contract weeks before the encounter, and financial records show that Greenberg paid for a flight to Tallahassee with Seminole County taxpayer money around that time. American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association Executive Director Savara Hastings (left) and Megan Zalonka with Rep. Matt Gaetz. via Twitter Zalonka’s interactions with Greenberg’s circle extended to Gaetz as well. In mid-2018, Zalonka became a spokesperson for the American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association (AMMPA), a cannabis legalization group with close ties to Gaetz. The congressman was feted as a guest of honor at two of its conferences in 2018, and attended the previous year’s annual conference in October. The 2017 conference, which Greenberg also attended, featured Republican operative and Trump loyalist Roger Stone, who appeared at a Gaetz fundraiser after the congressman’s keynote speech. That day, Oct. 5, Greenberg used Venmo to send Zalonka $500 around midday—for “Rent.”Other AMMPA officials have close ties to Gaetz and Greenberg. In Gaetz’s book, Firebrand, published last September, the congressman singles out executive director Savara Hastings and her boyfriend, AMMPA chairman Jason Pirozzolo, as some of his “best friends.” Gaetz also says he has spent New Years Eve with the couple in the Florida Keys, and he has posted Instagram pictures featuring Hastings in Pirozzolo’s private plane as far back as 2014.Investigators with the Justice Department’s Public Integrity division are now examining Gaetz’s interactions with young women and cannabis industry contacts, CNN reported, as part of a probe into whether Gaetz was provided with sex from escorts in exchange for political favors. The sprawling criminal inquiry that originated with Greenberg has since morphed into an investigation into Gaetz’s role in an alleged prostitution ring that includes potential sex crimes with a 17-year-old girl.The probe could soon have a valuable new asset if Greenberg finalizes a cooperation agreement that could turn him into a government witness against Gaetz and others. While Greenberg was out on release during his final months of the Trump administration, he wrote a confession letter that said he saw acts “occur first hand” involving Gaetz and the underage teen.However, Gaetz has not been charged with a crime, and the government has not publicly acknowledged a case against him. Gaetz has also denied all charges, and told The Daily Beast on March 31 that the last time he had sex with a 17-year-old, he was 17 himself.In August 2020, the month federal prosecutors filed a superseding indictment against Greenberg to include the sex trafficking charges, Zalonka received a grand jury subpoena, according to news reports, as well as a person with knowledge of the subpoena. In a Facebook post the next month, AMMPA canceled its annual October conference for the first time, citing concerns related to COVID. The group hasn’t posted since.Gaetz, however, continued to engage with Zalonka online. As recently as March 11, he commented “Smiling ninjas!” on an Instagram photo of Zalonka. After The Daily Beast published its first report about Greenberg’s mysterious Venmo transactions, Zalonka made her Instagram private. In recent weeks, her account appears to have vanished entirely.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian march to defy Paris ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-paris-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-government-and-politics-e415198646e3752ed63f1c9627b8cafe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Marches in support of Palestinians in the Gaza Strip were being held Saturday in a dozen French cities, but the focus was on Paris, where riot police got ready as organizers said they would defy a ban on the protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish answer to treating mood disorders, addiction?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/uw-researchers-think-a-fish-might-be-the-answer-to-treating-mood-disorders-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protein found in lampreys might be the solution to treating disorders, such as depression and even pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High gas prices, shortages hit trucking, as nation critically needs goods transported...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/high-gas-prices-and-shortages-hit-trucking-industry-as-nation-critically-needs-gasoline-and-goods-transported/ar-BB1gLeWe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent cyberattack on Colonial Pipeline combined with a pandemic-recovering economy have hit the trucking industry, which plays a crucial role in consumer spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bequia: Caribbean island home to world's first Bitcoin community...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/entrepreneur-launches-first-cryptocurrency-community-in-a-carribbean-paradise-b1848070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bequia: The Caribbean island home to world’s first cryptocurrency community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza tower housing AP, AL JAZEERA collapses after missile strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210515112004-163o9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/TOWER-MEDIA (URGENT):Gaza tower housing AP, Al Jazeera collapses after missile strike - witness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Horses Adopted Under Federal Program Going to Slaughter...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/15/wild-horses-adopted-under-a-federal-program-are-going-to-slaughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a lifetime of working with horses, Gary Kidd, 73, had never adopted an untrained wild mustang before. But when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Sharers: The Hidden Ties Between Private Spies and Journalists...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/15/secret-sharers-the-hidden-ties-between-private-spies-and-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some journalists are happy to knock on the doors of strangers. I was never one of them, but Christopher Steele,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest grips Israel, West Bank ahead of large scale demonstrations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/unrest-grips-israel-and-west-bank-ahead-of-large-scale-demonstrations/ar-BB1gKZPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockets launched from Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/jordanian-protestors-passed-police-barrier-on-way-to-israel-border-668187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven Palestinians were killed as over 5,000 people gathered to protest in the West Bank. Over 150 people were injured in the same protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jesus statue toppled, American flag burned in NYC church attack...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/14/jesus-statue-toppled-american-flag-burned-in-brooklyn-church-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Msgr. David Cassato noticed the crime at the Brooklyn church early on Friday. The NYPD Hate Crime Task Force is now investigating further into the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLY LAND HELL</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210515102102-k4xoi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-Israel-Gaza conflict rages on, diplomacy yet to gain traction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Accusers Subpoenaed as State Inquiry Enters Critical Phase...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/15/cuomo-accusers-are-subpoenaed-as-state-inquiry-enters-a-critical-phase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — Four women who have accused Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of sexual harassment have received subpoenas to testify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airstrike in Gaza destroys building with AP bureau...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-west-bank-gaza-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-7974cc0c03897b8b21e5fc2f8c7d8a79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — An Israeli airstrike destroyed a high-rise building in Gaza City that housed offices of The Associated Press and other media outlets on Saturday, the latest step by the military to silence reporting from the territory amid its battle with the militant group Hamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns extremists may strike as virus restrictions ease...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-7788f527ec6c429be2cdf4392f473157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A national terrorism alert issued Friday warns that violent extremists may take advantage of the easing of pandemic restrictions to conduct attacks. The alert does not cite any specific threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOMCBS says ex-CEO Moonves won't get $120M severance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-arts-and-entertainment-537b712842cd122ca6a739eb8f06a27e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — ViacomCBS said Friday that former CBS CEO Les Moonves will not get his $120 million severance package from his firing in 2018, ending a long-running dispute over the money. Moonves was ousted in 2018 after a company investigation into allegations of sexual misconduct spanning three decades found Moonves violated company policy and did not cooperate with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medina Spirit passes drug tests, cleared to run Preakness...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/sports/medina-spirit-passes-drug-tests-cleared-to-run-in-preakness/10634702/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medina Spirit has passed three rounds of prerace drug testing and been cleared to run in the Preakness on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Humane Society's law enforcement investigating Cox's 1,000-lb bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/John-Cox-bear-investigation-California-recall-code-16177548.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Cox may have violated a San Diego city code related to unusual animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted leader says McCarthy 'absolutely' should testify about Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/liz-cheney-regrets-voting-trump-2020/story?id=77695446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Cheney said she regrets voting for Donald Trump in the 2020 election, speaking in a "This Week" interview with ABC Chief Washington Correspondent Jonathan Karl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialed Back On Retail Therapy; Spent More Eating Their Feelings...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/05/14/996806349/americans-are-spending-less-on-things-but-more-on-eating-out-or-getting-a-drink</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail sales were flat in April from a month earlier as Americans spent less on things such as clothes or sporting goods but increased their spending at bars and restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence spreads to West Bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/at-least-six-palestinians-reported-killed-as-violence-spreads-to-west-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians report 500 injured in clashes, including by live fire; IDF says 3,000 participate in violent riots that involve stone-throwing, Molotov cocktails</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVIVOR star 'among honeytraps hired by ex-British spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2885839/survivor-honeytraps-british-expose-enemies-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FORMER ‘Survivor’ contestant was hired for a honeytrap operation to discredit enemies of Donald Trump, it was reported. Anna Khait was reportedly recruited to go on fake dates in an effort to exp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ex-Gaetz Confidant Pleads Guilty and Agrees to Cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-matt-gaetzs-ex-confidant-joel-greenberg-pleads-guilty-admits-to-sex-trafficking-of-a-minor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz’s (R-FL) former confidant Joel Greenberg has admitted to several crimes in court papers on Friday, including sex trafficking of a minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish health system targeted in 'serious' ransomware attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-health-f9478d95ff0f085fa382819e981f4b56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Ireland's health service shut down its IT systems on Friday after being targeted in a ransomware attack by what it called “international criminals.” Appointments and elective surgeries were canceled at several hospitals and Deputy Prime Minister Leo Varadkar said the disruption could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agent charged in cyberstalking plot against ex-lover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-government-and-politics-bb057af1814fc24cd8dbc40928b4f25f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A deputy U.S. marshal was charged in a cyberstalking scheme that authorities said he perpetrated with his ex-wife to have a former lover thrown in jail, the Justice Department said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ex-Gaetz Confidant Pleads Guilty and Agrees to Cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/14/us/politics/joel-greenberg-matt-gaetz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg, a former tax collector in Florida, admitted to sex trafficking a minor and agreed to help in prosecutions of others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can new Podcast Academy break awards show curse?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2021-05-14/podcast-academy-awards-ambies-ceremony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the biggest players in podcasting have created the Podcast Academy and an awards show for podcasts, The Ambies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private firefighters fuel tensions while saving CA vineyards and mansions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/private-firefighters-fuel-tensions-while-saving-california-vineyards-mansions-2021-05-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last October, firefighter Ryan Bellanca and his crew battled to keep the raging Glass Fire from devastating an upmarket Napa Valley vineyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lowrider back: Glorious return of cruising to streets of LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/tripideas/the-lowrider-is-back-the-glorious-return-of-cruising-to-the-streets-of-la/ar-BB1gJRwj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you noticed? Every weekend, caravans of lowriders and custom cars are cruising and hopping in a resurgent ritual. Van Nuys Boulevard is one of the city's oldest sites of this resilient SoCal obsession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamikaze drones and 'skunk water'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14958454/hamas-rockets-kamikaze-drones-skunk-water-israeli/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL and Hamas have been building up a lethal stockpile of weapons that are being unleashed in the escalating conflict.  The warring neighbours’ deadly arsenals threaten to make it the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halston: Almost forgotten icon now getting NETFLIX series...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/may/14/halston-almost-forgotten-icon-netflix-biopic-fashion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designer who dictated American glamour in 1960s and 70s is set to hit radar of younger generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly Discovered Letter Reveals Einstein's Views On Birds and Bees...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/einstein-birds-bees-physics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent discoveries pertaining to migratory birds actually appear to corroborate what Einstein wrote all those years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:   Activists and Ex-Spy Said to Have Plotted to Discredit Trump 'Enemies' in Government...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/05/13/breaking-news/activists-and-ex-spy-said-to-have-plotted-to-discredit-trump-enemies-in-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON &gt;&gt; A network of conservative activists, aided by a British former spy, mounted a campaign during the Trump administration to discredit perceived enemies of President Donald Trump inside the government, according to documents and people involved in the operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar Storms Threaten America...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/05/racing-sun-protect-america/174029/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lessons from the solar storm of May 1921.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat survives 5-story jump from burning building...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cat-fleeing-fire-survives-5-story-jump-walks-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago cat may now have eight lives after jumping out of a fifth-floor window Thursday afternoon to escape an apartment fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: HUSTLER Larry Flynt's Absolutely Wild FBI File...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7evg4/larry-flynt-fbi-file-hustler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 322-page file contains a litany of events from John DeLorean’s cocaine bust to an alleged effort by Flynt to blow himself up in front of the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRIVER HOARDS, CAR CATCHES FIRE DURING POLICE CHASE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/nation-world/national/article251409553.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver told deputies “that she was transporting several containers of fuel that she was hoarding in the trunk.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-year-old closes in on world record for youngest chess grandmaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/may/14/chess-american-12-year-old-closes-in-on-world-record-for-youngest-grandmaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abhimanyu Mishra poised to break Sergey Karjakin’s mark of 12 years seven months mark despite going six months without playing in a tournament due to Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our politics is no uglier or more dysfunctional than in past...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-our-politics-is-no-uglier-or-more-dysfunctional-than-in-the-past/ar-BB1gJdIH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remembering 20th century politics fondly is a distortion of the history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETSMART Workers Criminally Charged After Poodle Dies During Grooming...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/05/13/pittsburgh-petsmart-dog-grooming-death-kobe-aj-ross/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PetSmart says it launched an internal investigation and found “unintended failure to adhere to pet safety processes.” Four workers were fired and criminally charged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLY LAND HELL</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210514115812-k3u1w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 5, TV, PIX):UPDATE 5-Israel pounds Gaza to curb Palestinian militants but rockets still fly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Sentiment Declines; Inflation Fears Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/consumer-sentiment-in-us-declines-as-inflation-fears-mount/ar-BB1gJH4B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer sentiment slumped in early May as Americans grew increasingly concerned about rising prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picasso sells for $103 million!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210514-picasso-painting-sells-for-103-mn-in-new-york-auction-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picasso painting sells for $103 mn in New York: auction house</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising rapper, ill-fated INSTAGRAM post and killing in Hollywood Hills...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/a-rising-rapper-an-ill-fated-instagram-post-and-a-killing-in-the-hollywood-hills/article_1b7617c3-a9bc-5980-924d-45a8b0c0017b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES – At 2 a.m., a black BMW rolled past a house the rapper Pop Smoke was renting in the Hollywood Hills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene Shouted 'Get Rid of Your Diaper' Through AOC's Office Mailbox...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/marjorie-taylor-greene-shouted-get-rid-of-your-diaper-through-aoc-office-mailbox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a 2019 livestream resurfaced by CNN’s KFile, Greene can be seen making a fool of herself outside Ocasio-Cortez’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET Pulls Sports Cards From Shelves After Brawls Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/14/following-parking-lot-brawl-in-wisconsin-target-pulling-trading-cards-from-store-shelves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Target will no longer sell Pokémon and sports trading cards in its physical locations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
