<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Guard Was Substitute...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/in-short-staffed-jail-epstein-was-left-alone-for-hours-guard-was-substitute/ar-AAFHzBc?sf18867990=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO GOES CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/cnns-chris-cuomo-filmed-threatening-heckler-who-called-him-fredo-ill-fcking-ruin-your-sht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video going viral on Twitter tonight shows CNN's Chris Cuomo getting pretty heated with someone who called him "Fredo."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OVER LITTLE BLACK BOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9709564/jeffrey-epstein-british-contacts-mick-jagger-tony-blair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein listed 301 British associates in a “little black book” of society figures uncovered by the FBI, it was revealed last night. Among the contacts were celebrities such as M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMES B. STEWART:  The Day Jeffrey Epstein Told Me He Had Dirt on Powerful People...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/the-day-jeffrey-epstein-told-me-he-had-dirt-on-powerful-people/ar-AAFI7k5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Paul Haggis, Rape Accuser Fight Over Morning-After Texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/paul-haggis-rape-accuser-fight-her-morning-text-messages-1230923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In communications with a friend, Breest writes about "getting a ride home" from Haggis and discusses in graphic terms the physical impact of the encounter: “He was so rough and aggressive never ever again!!!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TEEN CHOICE AWARDS' With Taylor Swift Sinks to All-Time Ratings Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/teen-choice-awards-fox-2019-ratings-all-time-low-big-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox's Teen Choice Awards dropped to an all-time low in both the key adults 18-49 demographic and total viewers with the 2019 show on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Executive Editor Dean Baquet Admits Racism Headline Was 'F*cking Mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-york-times-editor-dean-baquet-trump-unity-headline-was-a-fcking-mess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a lengthy town-hall meeting on Monday, the paper’s top brass addressed a bevy of recent controversies centering around the Times’ coverage of Trump, race, and politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American household debt nears $14 trillion... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/11/bankruptcy-filings-rising-across-the-country-and-it-could-get-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bankruptcies are back — flashing warnings that more Americans are knee-deep in debt in big cities like New York. While total bankruptcy petitions nationwide by consumers and businesses are still we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficit Widens 27%...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-budget-deficit-already-exceeds-180000048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. fiscal deficit has already exceeded the full-year figure for last year, as spending growth outpaces revenue.The gap grew to $866.8 billion in the first 10 months of the fiscal year, up 27% from the same period a year earlier, the Treasury Department said in its monthly budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury yields extend plunge...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-30-yield-drops-fresh-185343178.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The rate on 30-year Treasury bonds approached an all-time low and a closely monitored section of the U.S. yield curve hurtled closer to inversion as investors sought shelter amid a fraught geopolitical backdrop.The yield on the long bond tumbled as much as 14 basis points to 2.12%, closing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala calls out Bingo numbers at old folks home...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-kamala-harris-calls-out-bingo-numbers-at-old-folks-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some candidates will do absolutely ANYTHING for votes. Kamala Harris wrapped up her bus trip across Iowa today by reading off bingo numbers to old folks in Muscatine. h/t ⁦@deepa_shivaram⁩, sending in this magic moment: “B7!” ⁦@KamalaHarris⁩ is calling out #s for bingo in Iowa. She said: “I’m here to answer any questions you might …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British warship sets sail for mission in Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-iran-britain/british-warship-sets-sail-for-tanker-escort-mission-in-gulf-idUSKCN1V21T3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British warship HMS Kent set sail for the Gulf on Monday to join a U.S.-led miss...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER falls to all-time low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/12/uber-stock-falls-to-all-time-low-as-investors-grow-more-skeptical.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Uber continued to sink on Monday, posting its lowest close ever, after the company reported disappointing second-quarter results last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing raises stakes with 'terrorism' warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022508/hong-kong-protesters-cripple-airport-beijing-raises-stakes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands bring Hong Kong International Airport grinding to a halt leaving 180 flights cancelled and travellers stranded, while police play down State Council’s Hong Kong and Macau Affairs Office terrorism comments and say they will treat situation like a ‘violent protest’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guard took bribe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7349603/Security-lapses-jail-Jeffrey-Epstein-hanged-himself.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein's apparent suicide has brought new scrutiny to the federal jail in New York where he was being held given the previous security lapses at the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested After Shooting Outside Chicago VA Medical Center...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/shots-fired-at-jesse-brown-va/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect is in custody after shots were fired outside of Jesse Brown VA Medical Center Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZON sells early social-media darling TUMBLR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4576d270fdf84bc4a90bb30bffafc99c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Verizon is selling Tumblr, a darling of early social media, to the owner of blogging platform WordPress. Tumblr is known for its devoted fan base and has been home to angry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#SHETOO CLAIM: Katy Perry accused of 'exposing male model's genitals at party'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9708212/katy-perry-accused-exposing-male-models-genitals-teenage-dream-actor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MODEL has made astonishing claims that Katy Perry exposed his penis at a party. Josh Kloss, 38, claims he was drinking with the pop princess when she suddenly pulled forward the waistband of his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong cops dress like protesters, infiltrate, start violence -- then beat up protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.hongkongfp.com/2019/08/12/video-hong-kong-police-make-bloody-arrest-assisted-officers-suspected-undercover-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hongkongfp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[Graphic images] Hong Kong police made mass arrests on the streets of Causeway Bay on Sunday night – aided by men who appeared to be undercover officers dressed as protesters. A protester was seen being wrestled to the ground by two men at around 10pm – one was a police officer in riot gear, the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Raids 'Pedophile Island'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7349729/Dozen-FBI-agents-raid-Jeffrey-Epsteins-Pedophile-Island.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents were seen raiding Jeffrey Epstein's US Virgin Island Little St James on Monday morning and afternoon, exclusive DailyMailTV footage shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA alters schedule to solve LeBron problem...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/12/nba-alters-schedule-to-solve-its-lebron-james-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA will experiment with new start times on national TV in an effort to boost ratings in the upcoming season to showcase its biggest stars, led by LeBron James, to as many people as possible. R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Working on Pill for Loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/all-the-lonely-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some, the idea is just another sign of the creeping medicalization of everyday human woes: Is it really the best we can do to fix the loneliness ‘epidemic’?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAKED EXECUTIVE ORDER WOULD LET US GOV CONTROL SOCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/executive-order-us-control-social-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech regulation sounds good in theory, but this executive order might not help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OR Gov Wants President To Release Tax Returns To Get On Ballot...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/huffpost/oregon-governor-kate-brown-trump-tax-returns-ballot-184001717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;We have to hold our elected officials accountable,&amp;quot; Kate Brown said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alliance with Bernie on Brink? Supporters say 'reckoning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article233712817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Baffled After Spotting 'Glitch' In Dying Star...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/astronomers-watched-a-neutron-star-glitch-and-cant-yet-explain-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A glitch in the cosmos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sorcerer's treasure trove' found at Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49325627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The find includes good-luck charms and decorative items thought to have belonged to women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Chants 'F*** Sweden' at A$AP Rocky's First Concert Since Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/asap-rocky-first-concert-real-street-fest-post-swedish-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans could be heard chanting "F--- Sweden!" during the rapper's festival-closing performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi to report for active duty in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tulsi-gabbard-democratic-presidential-candidate-in-2020-campaign-to-report-active-duty-hawaii-national-guard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hawaiian congresswoman spoke with CBSN's Caitlin Huey-Burns on decision to leave the campaign trail and report for duty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  What exactly was being tested in Arctic?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49319160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rocket engine blew up in the Arctic, killing five nuclear experts and sparking a radiation scare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-in sex booths proposed for historic Berlin airport...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/12/europe/berlin-tempelhof-sex-work-sex-booth-intl-scli-grm/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlin's former Tempelhof airport has witnessed some major events in its time -- a Nazi airfield during World War II, it was the site of the Berlin airlift during the Cold War, and most recently an emergency shelter for refugees fleeing Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early study results suggest 2 Ebola drugs saving lives...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec82808c37ac49e08477462c854cd1be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Health authorities in Congo have halted an Ebola treatment study early with good news: Two of the four experimental drugs seem to be saving lives. More than 1,800 people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sadist' priest filmed 'violently baptising' panic-stricken baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9705437/sadist-priest-baptised-baby-russia-church-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “SADISTIC” priest has been suspended for a year after a video went viral of  him “violently” baptising a “panic-stricken” baby. The disturbing footage shows the Russian Orthodox Priest Fotiy Nech…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci says Trump in meltdown mode; Couldn't keep quiet any longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-scaramucci-trump-election-el-paso-meltdown-20190812-rzxcmpgkg5fz3l4wcrnmhixwb4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Onetime Trump-whisperer Anthony Scaramucci said Trump is imploding in front of the country’s eyes and Republicans will have to think about replacing him on the top of the 2020 ticket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He's giving people license to hate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7348809/Scaramucci-compares-Trump-Wicked-Witch-West-suggests-GOP-needs-new-nominee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Remember when the water got thrown on the green witch and she started melting?' Scaramucci asked. 'Let's watch what the soldiers do, which is they'll team up with Dorothy.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> NYPD:  3 Hasidic Jews Attacked By Teens Within Hour...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/hasidic-jews-attacked-in-williamsburg-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the attackers snuck up from behind, punched the victims in the face and then rummaged through their pockets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians killed in missile test blast were working on new weapons... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russians-killed-missile-test-blast-were-working-weapons-154148120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's nuclear agency chief on Monday confirmed that five scientists killed last week were developing "new weapons" and vowed to continue testing despite the explosion. The accident took place at an Arctic military facility on the coast of the White Sea on Thursday, but Russian authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes undermine fragile truce over Jerusalem holy site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/04c82bdb58e24c348a88694637e71a7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — It wasn't inevitable that the overlap of Jewish and Muslim holidays would lead to clashes at a Jerusalem site deeply revered by both faiths. But when rumors circulated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Weakens Protections for Endangered Species...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/aug/12/endangered-species-act-trump-administration-protection-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changes to how Endangered Species Act is implemented come as world scientists warn biodiversity crisis will put humanity at risk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Alarming Rise In Teens Who Need Glasses; Excessive Screen Time Blamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-blames-disturbing-rise-in-teens-who-need-glasses-on-excessive-screen-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is warning parents that all that screen time may be behind a stunning rise in children who need prescription glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIANNE WILLIAMSON: You Can't Just Assume Democracy Is Okay...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/08/12/marianne_williamson_you_cant_just_assume_democracy_is_okay_because_it_was_okay_decades_ago.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FNC's Steve Hilton interviews Democratic presidential hopeful Marianne Williamson during her time at the Iowa State Fair. Williamson said democracy must be tended to like you would your body or your marriage. "You can't just assume that your democracy is okay because it was okay several decades ago. We are learning, and we are learning it the hard way, that our democracy must be tended to," Williamson said in an interview.  WILLIAMSON: The American revolution is an ongoing process. You can't say I was healthy in 1995 so I don't have to take care of my health anymore. You can't say my body was in shape in 2013 so I don't have to work out anymore. And it turns out, and we're experiencing it now. You can't just assume that your democracy is okay because it was okay several decades ago. We are learning, and we are learning it the hard way, that our democracy must be tended to. If you don't take care of your marriage, don't be surprised that you lose your marriage. If you don't take care of your business, don't be surprised if you lose your business. If you don't take care of your health, don't be surprised if you lose your health. And if you don't care and tend to your democracy, don't go being surprised when all these forces that would assault it are at the door. So it's the 11th hour, but it is not midnight yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Serious irregularities'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/jail-where-jeffrey-epstein-died-had-serious-irregularities-ag-barr-n1041421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr's remarks came two days after Epstein was found unresponsive in his cell at the federal detention center in lower Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Man Causes Panic At Houston Mall...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/masked-man-causes-panic-houston-mall-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people rushed out of a Houston mall on Sunday after a masked man jumped on a food court table and said he would kill himself before throwing down an unknown object covered in toilet paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HONG KONG DEFIANT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1131c0f97db34e1293862ca7fa8d4f06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — One of the world's busiest airports canceled all flights after thousands of pro-democracy demonstrators crowded into Hong Kong's main terminal Monday, while the central government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Municipalities nationwide grapple with bans on pet pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Municipalities-nationwide-grapple-with-bans-on-14297855.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knock on Dani Guill's door came in early May. It was a zoning compliance officer, there to investigate a complaint from a neighbor. Word was that a pig lived in her Virginia Beach, Virginia house, he told her.  He wasn't wrong. In fact, 3-year-old, 120-pound Pumpkin has her own bedroom and wardrobe. She loves Honey Nut Cheerios and acts grumpy when she doesn't get as much as she wants.  But unlike Guill's dog, Pumpkin is not allowed to reside in Virginia Beach. City law views her as livestock, though she is a potbellied pig bred to be a pet. Guill said the officer gave her 30 days to relocate the pig.  The eviction is now on hold as two city council members, at Guill's urging, draft a proposal to legalize Pumpkin and other pet pigs in the city. Guill said seven other owners have surfaced since she took up the cause. "Out of the woodwork, here come all the other pig parents," she said.  It's hardly an unusual municipal matter. Across the nation, pet pig owners are forcing cities and towns to grapple with the definition of swine and reassess zoning laws written in eras when the divide between pets and farm animals was far starker.  In the past year, pet pig legalization has been on the agenda in Holland, Michigan; Brookhaven, Georgia; and Chatfield, Minnesota - all of which decided to allow pigs. In Amherst, New York and Eureka Springs, Arkansas, officials did the opposite, upholding bans and calling for the ouster of outlaw pigs. Officials in other places are still mulling what to do.  "This is a growing concern. . . . It's hitting councils all over the country," said Mickey Schneider, a Eureka Springs alderwoman who pushed to change local law so that two potbellies in the Ozarks tourist town could stay. The animals have not been expelled, and Schneider said she's still trying. "These pigs are not stinky. And they are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather app alerts when about to rain, down to minute, all around world!</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/business/article/ClimaCell-weather-app-alerts-when-it-s-about-to-14297708.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if, wherever you're living, working or traveling, you could receive an alert before it's about to rain or snow and when the precipitation is about to end? And it's pretty accurate, too?  ClimaCell, a fledgling weather technology company based in Boston, released a mobile app Monday that provides notifications for exact locations in more than 50 countries. It promises "street-by-street, minute-by-minute short-term forecasts."  The app leverages the company's technology innovations, which are making waves in weather business industries.  ClimaCell, founded in 2015, has developed a global network of weather data that marries traditional observations of pressure, temperature, precipitation and wind with information drawn from wireless signals, satellites, connected cars, airplanes, street cameras, drones and other electronic sources. Millions of pieces of weather data can be derived from these technologies. It's what the company describes as the "weather of things."  This mix of data is fed into ClimaCell's forecast models, operated in Boulder, Colorado. The company created the NowCast model that gives highly specific, minute-by-minute forecasts out to six hours and a longer-term model, known as CBAM, that produces forecasts out to six days.  These models are designed to provide forecasts to help businesses solve problems in which "extra accuracy" is needed, according to Shimon Elkabetz, ClimaCell's chief executive.  Many of the weather companies operating today, spun up in the 1960s and 1970s, just take model forecasts from different governments, blend them and use statistical techniques to try to make them better. But ClimaCell is creating its forecasts from scratch.  Elkabetz said early results on its accuracy are promising. Compared with government forecasts, "we've...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In town called 'Thank God,' Central Americans' pursuit of promised land fades...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-08-11/guatemala-smuggling-hub-quiet-mexico-slows-migration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once bustling with migrants on their way to the United States, Gracias a Dios — whose name translates to 'Thank God' — now feels like a ghost town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE First Look at Witherspoon-Aniston Drama...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/apples-morning-show-teaser-first-look-at-reese-witherspoon-jennifer-aniston-drama-1230792 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teaser brings viewers inside the drama of the fictional TV news show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogfishing: Online daters pose with adorable pets that aren't theirs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/Dogfishing-When-online-daters-pose-with-adorable-14297742.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tinder, Avery Chuang developed a bad habit: She almost always swiped right on guys with a ridiculously adorable dog photo. It's not a high standard to go by, the 25-year-old in Elk Grove, California, admitted, but it helped her find men who are dog owners like herself - presuming that, of course, the featured pup is theirs.  She encountered her fair share of dog-baiters on dating apps (which she no longer uses since they are "addictive and demoralizing"). Most men were upfront in conversation with Chuang, but a few did slip through the cracks until she pieced it together.  There was a guy Chuang found attractive and charming and normal - until he turned around and questioned her for probing about his dog. And there was another who profusely apologized for displaying a friendly corgi that wasn't his (after she called him out) and then ghosted her.  Dogs, notably adorable photos of dogs, are a ubiquitous aspect of dating. They're convenient icebreakers on apps and on first dates. They add a nugget of personality to a profile. On Apple's App Store, Bumble features a photo of a bespectacled man cuddling a goldendoodle to insinuate how likable that is. There's also Dig, a new dating app specifically for dog owners.  This cultural obsession with dogs on the apps has spiraled into another problem: Daters are posting photos of pups they don't own, to attract matches. "Dogfishing" is not exactly a lie - the person did take a photo with that dog - but to some daters, it feels like a veiled form of deception. And things can get awkward fast when a date realizes that the pet in the profile solely exists as bait.  "That's the main thing: Stop borrowing dogs," said Erika Ettin, an online dating coach in Washington. She advises her clients to curate profiles representative of their actual life. "It's just odd when you're using...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Unanswered Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-12/7-unanswered-questions-about-epsteins-death-mainstream-media-not-talking-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocking suspect's hairstyle could get you prosecuted, police warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/08/12/mocking-suspects-hairstyle-could-get-prosecuted-police-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have warned social media users they could face arrest if they &amp;quot;troll&amp;quot; a wanted drug dealer by mocking his distinctive hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BOMBS AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-kitchen-bombs-furthers-hollywoods-identity-crisis-1230760 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only new movie to impress over the Aug. 9-11 weekend was 'Scary Stories We Tell in the Dark,' a parting gift from the disappearing CBS Films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA raises chance of recession to 1-in-3...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/12/bank-of-america-raises-chance-of-a-recession-to-1-in-3-in-the-next-12-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of America said recent data leads it to believe there is a 1-in-3 chance of a recession in the next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine election surprise triggers crash in peso...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/12/argentina-election-macri-suffers-setback-as-analysts-warn-of-peso-depreciation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential primaries were viewed by many as a referendum on Macri's painful economic reforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Satellite Catches Footage of Flying Orb...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/viral/201908111076522269-spacex-satellite-catches-mysterious-object-flying-camera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage posted by YouTube conspiracy theory channel thirdphaseofmoon was apparently taken onboard SpaceX’s Amos 17 satellite, which launched earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 tires slashed in Orthodox Jewish community...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/100-tires-slashed-orthodox-jewish-community-police/story?id=64919973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 tires have been slashed in a predominately Orthodox Jewish community in New Jersey in recent days, according to authorities there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemala election winner sets sights on changing Trump migrant deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-election-migrants/guatemala-election-winner-sets-sights-on-changing-trump-migrant-deal-idUSKCN1V20OE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guatemalan conservative Alejandro Giammattei secured a crushing victory in a pre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals chafe at president's blasphemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/12/trump-evangelicals-blasphemy-profanity-1456178</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Trump-supporting West Virginia state senator who represents many evangelicals got three phone calls from constituents complaining about Trump's profanity after a recent rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellmate transferred hours before...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/jeffrey-epstein-checked-for-hours-apparent-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correctional officers at the New York City prison housing Jeffrey Epstein didn't check in on him for hours leading up to his apparent suicide on Saturday after his cellmate was transferred for reasons that were not immediately clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DONE IT?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-death-investigation-alleged-victims-vow-to-keep-seeking-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As probes are launched over how it happened in a federal lockup known for its tight security, his alleged victims vow to keep seeking justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death shifts focus to alleged co-conspirator Ghislaine Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/epstein-death-britain-alleged-co-conspirator-ghislaine-maxwell-prince-andrew-2019-08-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialite Ghislaine Maxwell has been accused of finding teenage girls for Epstein and his friends, including a British royal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE CRAZY: UNIVERSITY BANS BURGERS TO SAVE PLANET...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/university-bans-burgers-help-save-114859056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beef products are to be removed from sale at Goldsmiths University as part of a plan to become carbon neutral by 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Mystery: Man's Penis Turning To Bone...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/09/doctors-penis-turning-to-bone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bronx doctors say the unidentified man was likely suffering from an “exceedingly rare” case of ossification, or the abnormal formation of bone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay-TV Subscriber Losses More Than Triple in Quarter...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/u-s-pay-tv-subscriber-losses-more-than-triple-to-1-5m-in-q2-report-1202666232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The largest pay-TV providers in the U.S. saw video subscriber losses more than triple to 1.53 million in the second quarter, according to the latest report from Leichtman Research Group. The tally …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Republicans brace for drubbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/12/texas-republicans-2020-elections-1456161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Republicans need to be very concerned,&amp;quot; says a GOP member of the state's congressional delegation of next year's elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury yields extend plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-extend-plunge-as-geopolitical-tensions-heat-up-2019-08-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury prices rise Monday, pushing yields lower, as protests in Hong Kong underline the worsening geopolitical backdrop across the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake-like UFO returns as mystery object seen 'moving like it's alive' over New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/797792/Snake-UFO-return-mystery-object-filmed-New-York-state-Clayville-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeches latest health trend...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/851730/how-leeches-became-latest-health-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient cultures believed leeches had healing powers. Now, the practice is making a modern-day resurgence.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
