<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>They executed people for SC. Nearly destroyed some...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article254201328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of those who helped execute people in South Carolina prisons have never spoken publicly – until now. The closer the 10 men we spoke with were to the act of killing, the more serious the long-term consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man burst into flames after Taser used on him...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/man-burst-flames-taser-police-81000888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say an upstate New York man is in grave condition at a hospital after police used a Taser to subdue him and he burst into flames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROWD OF 50,000 SURGES TOWARD STAGE</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/astroworld-festival-travis-scotts-houston-crowds-trampled/11203827/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight people died Friday night at a concert packed with an estimated 50,000 people at NRG Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China insists will stick to zero tolerance approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3155121/chinese-health-authorities-insist-country-will-stick-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official from the National Health Commission defends the policy as ‘in line with science’ as the country continues to battle sporadic outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got milk? Yes, actually, U.S. has too much...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/06/got-milk-yes-actually-too-much-519775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some parts of the nation have seen localized spikes in milk prices. But most of the nation is facing an oversupply of milk — a challenge policy makers have been struggling to address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President now defends migrant compensation payments he called 'garbage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10172275/Joe-Biden-vigorously-DEFENDS-compensation-payments-families-separated-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden was speaking at a press conference touting the passage of the $1.2trillion infrastructure bill when he was asked about the payments and reiterated that they would not be $450,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture war fight finds mixed success in school board races...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-education-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-school-boards-bed36a1460957cb6be4df9d18583a765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — School board candidates opposing mask mandates and lessons about racism in U.S. history won in red states and some politically divided districts but often came up short in their bids to shape policy for school districts over the newest culture war issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of anti-Covid pills begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211106-the-era-of-anti-covid-pills-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if a simple pill could help heal from Covid-19?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleeing passengers shut down busy Spanish airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59191108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palma de Mallorca Airport closes for four hours after 21 people run from a plane across the tarmac.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Apologize to Arab Royal Families for Leaking Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nw8m/conti-ransomware-hackers-apologize-to-arab-royal-families-for-leaking-their-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Bluntly, UAE sends assassination teams to deal with people they don’t like. [...] Even ransomware groups are subject to political pressure."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety link to irritable bowel syndrome seen in DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-57821848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have been studying more than 50,000 people with IBS to better understand the condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knife attack on German train severely injures 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-germany-nuremberg-2f7cd4d47381d35a515e86ef17849322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A knife attack on a high-speed train in Germany left three people severely wounded, the Bavarian Red Cross said Saturday. Police said a man has been arrested in connection with the morning attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Jan. 6 Rioter Tries to Sell Home on ZILLOW, Inadvertently Reveals Cache of Explosives...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alleged-jan-6-rioter-jeremy-brown-tries-to-sell-home-on-zillow-accidentally-reveals-cache-of-explosives-fbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Green Beret and onetime congressional candidate Jeremy Brown's operational security has apparently gotten a little sloppy of late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan City Council will be all Muslim, likely first in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/11/05/hamtramck-first-muslim-city-council/6288652001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All six members of the Hamtramck City Council will be Muslim starting in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easing of travel restrictions lets loved ones reunite...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-travel-relationships-528d66c448c9b6fc7dd50ac5ddef03fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Erin Tridle and her boyfriend, it was love at first sight. They met while the American was traveling in France in the summer of 2019. They said, “I love you,” on day two. “People tell us it's like something from a movie,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid size of Eiffel Tower heading for Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/asteroid-the-size-of-eiffel-tower-heading-for-earth-in-december-684133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed 4660 Nereus, or 1982 DB, this vaguely egg-shaped asteroid has a size of approximately 330 meters. But while considered potentially hazardous, it also has potential for exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raids PROJECT VERITAS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-searches-project-veritas-personnel-173750571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department conducted two searches on Tuesday in the New York City area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where's Gavin? Newsom disappears from public for 10 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10172023/Wheres-Gavin-California-Governor-Newsom-disappears-public-view-10-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom was last seen in public on October 27, receiving a COVID-19 booster shot in Oakland. He said it was painless and then flexed in celebration, urging others to get boosters as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Politics Rotting Brains, Making Everyone Mad...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/05/politics-is-rotting-brains-and-making-everyone-mad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As exciting as it may sound to grab power and vanquish enemies, the only way to save America is to recommit to its original principles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Dems warn party: Growing Republican wave real...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pennsylvania-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-philadelphia-elections-3420f14ee42f95907b316438585ed4a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW HOPE, Pa. (AP) — The Democrats of Bucks County, Pennsylvania, felt the red wave building over the summer when frustrated parents filled school board meetings to complain about masking requirements and an academic theory on systemic racism that wasn't even taught in local schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA director dispatched to Moscow to warn over troop buildup near Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/05/politics/bill-burns-moscow-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden dispatched CIA Director Bill Burns to Moscow earlier this week to warn the Kremlin that the US is watching its buildup of troops near Ukraine's border closely, and to attempt to determine what is motivating Russia's actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  HALF SAY NOTHING WITH CHANGE MIND...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-unvaccinated-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;18 percent think COVID vaccinations are more dangerous than the virus itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe slams...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/fbi-searches-project-veritas-associates-in-probe-over-diary-purportedly-belonging-to-biden-s-daughter/ar-AAQmUtl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The probe is centered on how a right-wing website ended up with and published contents of the diary just before the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>228-206 vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/congress-approves-12-trillion-infrastructure-bill-sending-measure-to-biden-for-enactment/ar-AAQmcP7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vote marked the final milestone for the first of two pieces in the president’s economic agenda, sending to Biden’s desk a sprawling initiative that grew out of his 2020 campaign pledge to rejuvenate the economy in the aftermath of the coronavirus and “build back better.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Axes Estevez From 'MIGHTY DUCKS' Over Status...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/emilio-estevez-leaving-the-mighty-ducks-game-changers-season-2-gordon-bombay-covid-vaccine-mandate-1234868978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Mighty Ducks franchise will continue without Gordon Bombay. Emilio Estevez, who reprised his role from the 1992 movie and its 1994 and 1996 sequels in Season 1 of The Mighty Ducks: G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 DEAD AT HOUSTON MUSIC FESTIVAL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/8-dead-after-panic-houston-astroworld-music-festival-n1283397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventeen people were transported to the hospital after the crush, and 11 who were taken by ambulance were in cardiac arrest, Houston officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANIC, STAMPEDE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10171759/Multiple-injuries-reported-Astroworld-Festival-Houston.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people are dead and 'hundreds' more injured during a crush and stampede on the opening night of rapper Travis Scott's sold-out Astroworld Festival in Texas on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA developing most powerful laser weapon to blast missiles from sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4007773/us-laser-weapon-missiles-chinas-nuke-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US is developing its most powerful laser weapon yet capable of blasting missiles and drones out of the sky following China’s “round the world” nuke test. Boeing and General At…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Alone Boosts Risk Of Heart Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-alone-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older women eating alone had lower intakes of energy, carbohydrates, dietary fiber, sodium, and potassium in comparison to those eating with others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson accusers detail alleged abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2021-11-05/marilyn-manson-esme-bianco-sexual-abuse-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court records reviewed by The Times and nearly two dozen interviews portray Manson as a transgressive artist who mistreated and isolated women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria bans unjabbed from cafes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211105-austria-bans-those-unvaccinated-against-covid-19-from-caf%C3%A9s-amid-surge-in-new-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria said on Friday it is barring those not fully vaccinated against Covid-19 from cafes, restaurants and hairdressers as infections approach the record set a year ago and the government struggles…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
