<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness divided small Washington town. And then the fighting started...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/homeless/homelessness-divided-a-small-town-in-pierce-county-and-then-the-fighting-started/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When homelessness doubled in a town in Pierce County, a hard-line group on Facebook took an aggressive approach, including posting the photos and license plates of panhandlers, and those that gave money to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab coalition will counter threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-aramco-fire-coalition/arab-coalition-says-it-will-counter-threats-to-saudi-assets-oil-supplies-idUSKBN1VZ0I2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Saudi-led coalition battling Yemen's Houthi group said it was investigati...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7463189/Drone-attacks-spark-huge-fires-two-Saudi-oil-refineries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yemen's Houthi fighters claimed responsibility for the attacks on Abqaiq and Khurais, two major Aramco facilities in eastern Saudi Arabia. It follows a spike in regional tensions with Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe 'record player' just one of his vintage references...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/857ff63c9dbd4ac9988f51a30df00f05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's suggestion that parents leave a record player on to teach their babies better vocabulary was a head-scratching (needle-scratching?) moment in Thursday's debate. But it was hardly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set for PATRIOTS debut?</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/09/14/antonio-brown-makes-the-trip-to-miami/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown is going home. Whether he plays football when he’s in South Florida this weekend remains to be seen. Mike Giardi of the NFL reports that Brown has joined his new teammates for t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Shocking video shows mob pummel man outside Minnesota Target Field...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/13/shocking-video-shows-mob-pummel-man-outside-minnesotas-target-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking surveillance footage shows a senseless beatdown outside the Minnesota Twins stadium, where a group of thugs throw a man to the ground, pummel him, take off his pants and, at one point, run…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid larger than some of world's tallest buildings will zip by Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/14/world/asteroid-flyby-2000-qw7-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, an asteroid will pass by Earth that's larger than some of the tallest buildings on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How clean-cut Eagle Scout became fentanyl drug lord...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ce51cf7c958643629bce76764f71058d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — The photo that flashed onto the courtroom screen showed a young man dead on his bedroom floor, bare feet poking from the cuffs of his rolled up jeans. Lurking on a trash can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far from debate spotlight, Williamson keeps campaigning...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c389914e66b74ceaa98655d1465efa81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Marianne Williamson's voice dropped to a near whisper, then soared preacher-style to the rafters. "There are more lovers than haters in America. But those who hate, hate with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedians Condemn 'SNL' Cast Member Over Slurs...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/comedians-condemn-snl-shane-gillis-over-slurs-1203335929/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Saturday Night Live” showrunner Lorne Michaels has yet to comment on the racist and homophobic remarks made by newly hired cast member Shane Gillis, but comedians and actors are expressing their c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mall brawls and street fights as Hong Kong polarization deepens...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/fights-break-hong-kongs-polarisation-deepens-084035842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fights erupted in Hong Kong on Saturday with political rivals trading blows in a mall and Beijing supporters using Chinese flags to assault opponents on a street, deepening the city's polarisation after months of pro-democracy protests. The once-stable international hub has been convulsed by weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown loses helmet endorsement amid rape allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/14/antonio-brown-loses-helmet-endorsement-amid-rape-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Helmet manufacturer Xenith cut ties with embattled Patriots receiver Antonio Brown this week amid allegations that he raped his former trainer– ending a deal that lasted less than two weeks. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming for AR-15? Beto scrambles Dem gun message...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coming-ar-15-orourke-scrambles-223012589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke's "hell yes" moment at the Democrats' presidential debate is scrambling his party's message on guns. The Democrats have long contended their support of gun control laws does not mean they want to take away law-abiding citizens' firearms. O'Rourke'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude To Hit $100? </title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/massive-fire-after-drone-strike-hits-worlds-largest-oil-processing-facility-saudi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto lashes Bahamas, seen becoming hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-dorian/tropical-storm-humberto-lashes-bahamas-seen-becoming-hurricane-idUSKBN1VZ0CI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Humberto lashed already devastated parts of the Bahamas with heav...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Israel spying? Or was story anti-Bibi sting?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/was-israel-spying-or-was-the-stingray-story-an-anti-bibi-sting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli voters in the “very exciting” Sept. 17 Israeli elections should be skeptical of the weird story in recent days accusing the Israeli government of spying on the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry Bradshaw rips...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27611998/terry-bradshaw-says-stand-guys-ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steelers Hall of Fame quarterback Terry Bradshaw says he "can't stand players" like Antonio Brown and wishes Pittsburgh would have gotten rid of the wide receiver "a long time ago."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's oldest parents' in intensive care after delivering twins...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/14/worlds-oldest-parents-in-intensive-care-after-delivering-twins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s oldest mom and her husband are in intensive care just days after the delivery of their two children. Erramatti Mangayamma, 74, who recently delivered two healthy babies via caesar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set for PATRIOTS debut...</title>
      <link>https://nesn.com/2019/09/patriots-top-wideouts-have-high-hopes-for-absolute-stud-antonio-brown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nesn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Edelman. Josh Gordon. And now, Antonio Brown. Good luck finding a more talented trio of wide receivers anywhere in the NFL. Ahead of what could be Brown’s New England Patriots debut Su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bin Laden son killed in US airstrike, Trump confirms...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9927051/osama-bin-laden-son-hamza-dead-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OSAMA bin Laden’s son and terror heir was killed in a US counter-terrorism operation, Donald Trump has confirmed. Hamza bin Laden, 30, was a high-ranking official in al-Qaeda – the grou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I create fake videos. Here's why people believe even obvious ones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90404007/i-create-fake-videos-heres-why-people-believe-even-the-obvious-ones </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People will accept anything as true if it confirms their beliefs—regardless of whether a video or image has obviously been manipulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solid gold toilet stolen from Winston Churchill birthplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c4c24d249db443fdb33a9fe6405d71ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thieves have stolen a unique solid gold toilet worth up to 1 million pounds ($1.25 million) from the birthplace of British wartime leader Winston Churchill. The toilet, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil supply disrupted...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190914125530-mmsu3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-OIL/FIRE-PRODUCTION (URGENT):Saudi Arabia's oil supply disrupted after drone attacks - sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ringo Starr and Paul McCartney record version of lost Lennon song...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/entertainment/ringo-starr-and-paul-mccartney-record-version-of-lost-lennon-song-950687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grow Old With Me features on Sir Ringo’s 20th solo album, What’s My Name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,246 fetal remains found on property of abortion doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox32chicago.com/news/2246-fetal-remains-found-on-property-of-abortion-doctor-who-recently-died</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox32chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 2,200 medically preserved fetal remains were found Thursday on the property of a deceased doctor in unincoperated Will County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They're Coming! How Joke About Area 51 May Lure Thousands of Partygoers...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/14/theyre-coming-how-a-joke-about-area-51-may-lure-thousands-of-partygoers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - A wildly popular Facebook joke about “storming” Area 51 inspired plans for an enormous alien-themed party in the Nevada desert. Now there are three events</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yemen rebels claim drone attacks on major Saudi oil sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d20f80188e3543bfb36d512df7777cd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Drones claimed by Yemen's Houthi rebels attacked the world's largest oil processing facility in Saudi Arabia and a major oilfield operated by Saudi Aramco early...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats, dolphins and one smart raven: CIA's secret animal spies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cats-dolphins-one-smart-raven-cias-secret-animal-013906580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 1974, Do Da was top in espionage class, on the way to becoming a high-flying CIA agent: he handled himself better in the rough, carried heavier loads, and could brush off attackers. The bird was a central figure in a decade-long US Central Intelligence Agency program to train animals as agents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto targets hurricane-hit Bahamas... </title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bahamas-tropical-storm-warning-areas-devastated-by-hurricane-dorian-track-path-latest-2019-09-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bahamas government has issued a tropical storm warning for its northwestern islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignite huge fire... </title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/business/energy/fire-at-aramco-facility-report-1.1568434597552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fires began after the sites were 'targeted by drones', the Interior Ministry said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones attack oil facilities in Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-saudi-arabia-says-drones-051442143.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia says drones attacked two major oil facilities in the kingdom, sparking fires. One attack struck a major oil facility in Buqyaq, which is near Dammam in the kingdom's Eastern Province. A Saudi-owned satellite news channel is reporting an explosion and fire at a Saudi Aramco facility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKGOOGLE latest efforts to 'save' journalism already getting eye rolls... </title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12267678</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google and Facebook say they are racing to elevate quality journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday the 13th: Full moon 13 years in making...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/09/12/freakish-fun-for-friday-the-13th-a-full-moon-13-years-in-the-making/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September’s curiously-timed full moon — called a “Harvest Moon” because it’s the nearest one to the autumnal equinox Sept. 23 — has many unusual qualities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPhones overpriced and behind the times?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apples-new-iphones-are-overpriced-and-behind-the-times-2019-09-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You pay a premium price for a device that underperforms Android rivals, says Jurica Dujmovic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Smith announces new pronouns of 'they,' 'them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7461739/Sam-Smith-breaks-silence-wanting-use-pronouns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Stay With Me hitmaker, 27, announced their request in a candid statement shared via Twitter on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CRAZY:  Cameron suggests there should be SECOND EU referendum...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7462307/David-Camerons-bombshell-savages-appalling-Boris-Johnson-Michael-Gove.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Cameron said Boris Johnson and Michael Gove 'left the truth at home' with claims that EU membership cost £350million a week and that Turkey would join the bloc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Biden matchup promises epic presidential gaffes contest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-biden-matchup-promises-epic-presidential-gaffes-contest-203408100.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other is a septuagenarian male politician who makes so many slip-ups that the public has almost stopped taking notice. Welcome to Joe Biden vs Donald Trump, the prospective 2020 match-up that, if nothing else, guarantees a lot of puzzlement -- and perhaps laughs. Biden has been making verbal missteps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: Greatest danger lies ahead with refinement of A.I....</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/ng-interactive/2019/sep/13/edward-snowden-interview-whistleblowing-russia-ai-permanent-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man whose state surveillance revelations rocked the world speaks exclusively to the Guardian about his new life and concerns for the future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI FIGHTS FOR POLITICAL LIFE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election-preview/king-bibi-fights-for-his-political-life-in-israeli-election-idUSKCN1VY1TD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty years after Benjamin Netanyahu's first term as Israel's prime m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC: There Are Over 100 Genders...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/education/2019/09/13/bbc-tells-schoolchildren-there-are-over-100-genders/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC tells schoolchildren that there are over 100 genders as part of its “Teach” video series, which has some parents up in arms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. opposes House request for Mueller materials...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf9ee3b20fcd40a393158e56bf648616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department told a judge Friday that the House Judiciary Committee shouldn't get access to secret grand jury material amassed during the special counsel's Russia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBERTY students protest in wake of reports about Falwell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2af299bb899d4d6e8a65dd20d18a99a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students at Liberty University in Virginia gathered Friday to protest in the wake of news reports containing allegations that school president Jerry Falwell Jr. improperly benefited from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar pitches herself to voters tired of 'extremes'...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/amy-klobuchar-pitches-herself-to-voters-tired-of-extremes/560192232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her signature moments came when she offered a message of Democratic unity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Wild police chase tops 130 mph, killing bank robber...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article235071777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Uncovers $1 Billion in Sackler Family Wire Transfers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/new-york-uncovers-dollar1-billion-in-sackler-family-wire-transfers/ar-AAHg8Ni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iger Leaves APPLE Board as DISNEY Rivalry Heats Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/13/bob-iger-resigns-from-apple-board.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's forthcoming Disney+ will compete with Apple's Apple TV+ in the online streaming service market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penthouse, private jets: Inside globe-trotting life of W. Va. Bishop...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-penthouse-limousines-and-private-jets-inside-the-globe-trotting-life-of-bishop-michael-bransfield/ar-AAHcZUB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CULT WOMEN' RUNNING FOR KNESSET...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Cult-women-running-for-Knesset-601372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€˜We wanted to run for the Knesset in the previous election, but we couldnâ€™t, due to procedural obstacles,â€� say A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela 'ready' to defend itself after US invokes defense pact...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-ready-defend-itself-us-invokes-defence-pact-202920955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela is "ready" to defend itself, Foreign Minister Jorge Arreaza said Friday, after Washington invoked a regional defence pact that might justify such a move. "We are ready to protect ourselves, we are ready to react," Arreaza told a news conference after meeting in Geneva with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Inspector General Completes FISA Abuse Probe...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/13/doj-inspector-general-fisa-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department's IG told William Barr on that he has completed his investigation into possible FBI abuse of the FISA during the Trump-Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
