<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>2 Arkansas cops wounded in WALMART shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/arkansas-walmart-shooting-police-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting at an eastern Arkansas Walmart Monday injured at least three people, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire sale: The Iran plant making US flags protesters burn...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/235580c14a77045fc7647562a2ac1d33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KHOMEIN, Iran (AP) — Near the hometown of the late Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini, workers at a small Iranian factory diligently add all 50 stars and 13 red-and-white bars to what are supposed to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirk Douglas' Last Words Were About Bloomberg?</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/2020/02/08/actor-michael-douglas-former-mayor-gary-indiana-stump-bloomberg/4701357002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Michael Douglas helped open Bloomberg's Madison office. Ex-Gary Mayor Karen Freeman-Wilson, in Milwaukee, touted Bloomberg's plan to close the black-white wealth gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greta Thunberg Gets TV Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/greta-thunberg-tv-series-bbc-studios/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Series will follow life of teenage environmental activist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein rape trial appears headed for early conclusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/feb/10/harvey-weinstein-trial-rape-sexual-assault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film producer to call several more witnesses and lawyers could deliver closing arguments this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every voter in Israel just had their data leaked in 'grave' security breach...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90462342/every-voter-in-israel-just-had-their-data-leaked-in-grave-security-breach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s unknown whether anyone actually took advantage of the flaw; however, doing so would take no hacking skills whatsoever. Anyone who knew about the flaw could access the data with a few clicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God and a Glock: Texas churchgoers training to fight off attackers wielding guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2020/02/07/god-and-a-glock-how-churchgoers-are-training-to-fight-off-armed-attackers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HURST — Beneath the Christmas lights still hanging in the church’s fellowship room, Jack Mills pointed a Glock handgun at his enemy’s chest and pulled the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON wants Trump to testify in battle over $10 billion Pentagon contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/10/tech/amazon-trump-defense-contract/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has asked a federal court for permission to get testimony from President Donald Trump and Defense Secretary Mark Esper as part of its ongoing protest over the Defense Department's handling of a multibillion-dollar cloud computing contract, according to a court filing unsealed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of Celebrity is Dead...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/the-age-of-celebrity-is-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super spreaders' could make epidemic harder to contain...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/10/super-spreaders-could-make-coronavirus-epidemic-harder-to-contain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Highly contagious coronavirus carriers known as “super spreaders” could make the new outbreak more unpredictable — and tougher to contain — as its fans out across the globe, experts sai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA charges Chinese military hackers in EQUIFAX breach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/05aa58325be0a85d44c637bd891e668f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Four members of the Chinese military have been charged with breaking into the networks of the Equifax credit reporting agency and stealing the personal information of tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of businesses seek billions in loans...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200210150008-68712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/LENDING (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Hundreds of Chinese businesses seek billions to contend with coronavirus -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Voters Quietly Turning to Bloomberg?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/are-black-voters-quietly-turning-to-mike-bloomberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His belated and convenient stop-and-frisk mea culpa might be good enough for voters concerned with beating Trump, and protecting the fraught gains of the past half-century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKDOWN: DEPRESSION SETTING IN ON CRUISE FROM HELL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7986227/Number-coronavirus-cases-board-Yokohamas-quarantined-cruise-ship-DOUBLES-130-overnight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest batch of test results on the Diamond Princess (pictured in Yokohama today) includes 11 Americans and 45 Japanese nationals who are confirmed to have the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi makes rare visit to meet patients, medics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-stutters-back-virus-deaths-soar-022547215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping donned a face mask and had his temperature checked Monday while visiting medical workers and patients affected by the deadly coronavirus that has killed more than 900 people. Xi has largely kept out of the public eye since the virus outbreak spiralled across the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying Video Shows Suicide Drone Flying Up Armored Vehicle's Ramp...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/32133/help-us-decipher-this-mystery-footage-of-a-suicide-drone-flying-up-an-armored-vehicles-ramp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic video may serve as yet another warning of America's glaring short-range air defense gap and the threat that low-end enemy drones pose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$645 Million Hydrogen-Powered Superyacht; Travels 4,000 Miles Before Refuel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7982765/Bill-Gates-buys-massive-370ft-eco-friendly-superyacht-thats-powered-liquid-hydrogen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates has commissioned the construction of the Aqua superyacht, designed by Dutch studio Sinot. At 370ft long and 50ft wide, it is powered by two tanks of liquid hydrogen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This man says he's stockpiling billions of our photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/10/tech/clearview-ai-ceo-hoan-ton-that/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clearview AI's cofounder Hoan Ton-That claims his company has scraped billions of photos from the internet, including popular sites like Facebook, Twitter and YouTube — all to help law enforcement solve crimes. But what does that mean for your privacy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Bloomberg only Dem ahead of Trump among small business owners...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/284396/small-business-owners-highly-engaged-2020-election.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small-business owners are more likely to say their business would be better off if Donald Trump is reelected than if the Democratic candidate wins, but Michael Bloomberg has crossover appeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not all born in American Samoa want US citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f14d76dad1e8344428135128025dcf3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Growing up in American Samoa, Filipo Ilaoa’s neighbors were his cousins on a plot of land full of banana and breadfruit trees shared by his extended family and overseen by a chief...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB stars walk runway at fashion show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c126d1b2413562a6a66acd717c12efc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fashion label Namilia deconstructed Asian stereotypes in the porn industry, empowering the demure, submissive woman with bold dominatrix looks worn exclusively by Asian models at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of Pelosi brings renewed attention to 'cheapfakes'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12443c46b8cfee5e9659abb31eee5142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The issue of misleading political messages on social media arose again last week, when President Trump tweeted out an edited video showing Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel accused of torturing Palestinians after fatal bombing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/029eb2f122af74621a876ee8b9fbcf00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAMALLAH, West Bank (AP) — One of the men was hospitalized with kidney failure and 11 broken ribs. Another was nearly unrecognizable to his wife when he was wheeled into a courtroom. A third was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV-positive airmen fighting to stay in Air Force in first-of-its kind case...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/hiv-positive-airmen-fighting-stay-air-force-kind/story?id=68276202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two members of the Air Force say they were wrongly discharged due to their HIV status, a lawsuit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Swarms big as cities'...</title>
      <link>https://africa.cgtn.com/2020/02/09/swarms-big-as-cities-un-chief-says-locust-fight-must-intensify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;africa.cgtn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nations (UN) Secretary General Antonio Guterres on Saturday called for intensified international efforts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAMINE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/opinion/editorial/in-the-eye-of-the-swarm-the-growing-threat-of-the-desert-locust-1.975860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need a global united response to this infestation that is jeopardising livelihoods and crops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLOBUCHAR SURGES INTO THIRD...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/amy-klobuchar-third-place-new-hampshire-poll-surge-abc-news-debate-1486472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross appears above Holy Land in 'message from God'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/incredible-moment-cross-appears-above-21466953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious shape was described as a "sign from the heavens", with many viewers claiming it proved that "Jesus was coming"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chances rising for brokered convention...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/482245-democrats-see-chances-rising-for-brokered-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHUA, N.H. — The chance of a contested Democratic convention has increased after the muddle of the Iowa caucuses, raising anxieties ahead of Tuesday’s New Hampshire primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia jails left-wing activists for up to 18 years despite outcry...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200210105344-i9283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-COURT/ACTIVISTS:Russia jails left-wing activists for up to 18 years despite outcry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XFL TICKET PRICES IN WASHINGTON WERE HIGHER THAN SOME REDSKINS TICKETS LAST SEASON...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/sports/xfl-ticket-prices-are-higher-than-some-redskins-tickets/65-0f2cea61-ce87-4f24-a5c8-682e9437cf59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ticket prices were selling for as little as $4 for Redskins games last fall, and the D.C. Defenders' first game was costlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOKER WOKE:  Phoenix rails against cancel culture, cow insemination, MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joaquin-phoenix-rails-against-cancel-culture-cow-insemination-in-wild-oscar-acceptance-speech-for-joker </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘Joker’ actor managed to discuss the selfish nature of humanity, artificial insemination of cows, and his late brother River Phoenix all in one address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRISHMAN' SHUT OUT: THREE STRIKES NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/the-irishman-shutout-at-oscars-what-does-it-mean-for-netflix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is the Oscars’ The Irishman shutout the end of Netflix’s long, costly bid for a Best Picture Oscar? Or just the start? Parasite was Sunday night’s big winner, and was the first foreign-language film ever to win the top prize. Martin Scorsese’s celebrated The Irishman, once seen as a favorite to win Best Picture, somehow didn’t […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICS DOMINATES </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/oscars-2020-ceremonys-political-moments-1277441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Martin made light of the Iowa caucus tech mishap, while best supporting actor winner Pitt nodded to the lack of witnesses at the Senate impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WE'RE ALL PARASITES!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7985453/Brad-Pitt-kicks-political-jokes-Oscars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Academy Awards ceremony was filled with political moments where Joaquin Phoenix ranted about animal rights and Brad Pitt slammed the impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE LECTURE OSCARS</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/joaquin-phoenix-oscar-best-actor-joker-1203497086/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin Phoenix accepted his best actor award for “Joker” at Sunday’s Academy Awards with a lengthy and impassioned speech that touched on racism, animal rights and his own abilit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Lackluster Circus...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/92-academy-awards-show-review-parasite-oscars-eminem-abc-1202855665/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With most of the top categories long since a predictable lock, if there was any real drama in the 92nd Academy Awards tonight it was how well another year of no host would fare. Not so great, turne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg calls for deficit reduction, swiping at Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/pete-buttigieg-calls-deficit-reduction-swiping-bernie-sanders-n1133206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential candidate vowed to focus on the debt even though he says it's "not fashionable in progressive circles."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top candidates turn on one another...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Top-Democrats-turn-on-one-another-after-Iowa-15043098.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. - Democratic leaders have edged toward the brink of open war with each other in recent days after a series of jarring setbacks that could jeopardize the party's chances against President Donald Trump, who continues to solidify his iron-fisted control over the Republican election apparatus.  The infighting focuses largely on the failed caucus process in Iowa, with state and national Democratic leaders at odds over who deserves blame, as well as an increasingly bitter dispute over the rules governing who gets into future nationally televised candidate debates - a process that could allow billionaire Mike Bloomberg to make the stage later this month.  In a particularly stark sign, supporters of Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., have returned to bashing the Democratic National Committee, reviving grievances from the divisive 2016 primary race. In that campaign, Sanders backers said the system had been stacked against the democratic socialist - a view later affirmed when WikiLeaks released hacked internal emails - and supporters of nominee Hillary Clinton blamed Sanders for not sufficiently rally his base on Clinton's behalf in the general election.  Sanders's allies are again charging that the DNC is maneuvering to thwart his anti-establishment movement. They say the DNC's decision last week to call for a "recanvass" in Iowa threatened to undercut Sanders's ability to claim momentum from winning the popular vote there, while changing the rules to benefit Bloomberg reflects the desire among the party elite for a savior to deny Sanders the nomination.  "They can shout unity all they want, but the actions show otherwise," said Nina Turner, a national co-chairman of the Sanders campaign.  The brew of resentment and anxiety represents a sharp turn for a presidential primary race that began last year with a historically...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County In Rural Kansas Jailing People Over Unpaid Medical Debt!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coffeyville-kansas-medical-debt-county-in-rural-kansas-is-jailing-people-over-unpaid-medical-debt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If two court hearings are missed on unpaid medical debt, the judge issues an arrest warrant for contempt of court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMAS' COMPANY WINS ITS FIRST...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/obama-win-oscar-best-documentary-american-factory-1203498032/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s “American Factory,” produced by Michelle and Barack Obama, took home the award for best documentary at the 92nd Oscars. It’s the first Academy Award for the Obamas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O.J. Simpson jumps in...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2020/02/10/oj-simpson-gayle-king-kobe-bryant-controversy-not-right-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gayle King has felt a good amount of pushback after her comments about Kobe Bryant in the wake of [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS ROASTED... </title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/awards/oscars-amazon-jeff-bezos-chris-rock-steve-martin-1203498422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite not having an official host, the 92nd Oscars still featured a mini-monologue from previous hosts Chris Rock and Steve Martin. Following the show’s opening music number from Janelle Mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders and Buttigieg battle in NH...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Sanders-and-Buttigieg-aren-t-competing-for-the-15042512.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. - The two top finishers in last week's Iowa caucuses, 40 years apart in age and representing opposite ends of the Democratic Party's ideological spectrum, are heading for a showdown in Tuesday's primary here - each taking increasingly aggressive swipes at the other.  But there is an unusual twist to the new rivalry between Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg.  The senator from Vermont and former mayor of South Bend, Indiana, are not fighting to win over the same pool of New Hampshire voters, though many likely to vote here remain undecided. Rather, according to strategists in both campaigns, each is trying to energize his supporters by vowing to block the other from winning the Democratic nomination - with Sanders, the democratic socialist, portraying Buttigieg as a captive to his billionaire donors, and the more centrist Buttigieg railing against Sanders as a "my way or the highway" leftist.  That effort burst into full view Sunday, when the candidates hopscotched across the snow-covered state.  At a canvass launch in Plymouth, Sanders accused Buttigieg of being in the pocket of his wealthy donors. "Our views are different," Sanders said, repeating an argument he has made frequently in recent days.  "Pete has raised campaign contributions from over 40 billionaires," he said, adding that those donors are drawn to Buttigieg precisely because he will not, in Sanders's view, take on "the corporate elite."  Buttigieg, meanwhile, continued to paint Sanders as divisive.  "I respect Senator Sanders, but when I hear this message go out that you're either for revolution or you've got to be for the status quo, that's a vision of the country that doesn't have room for most of us," Buttigieg said.  At another event Sunday, he pushed his usual critique further, calling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa's Obama-Trump counties, Dems didn't turn out... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-Iowa-s-Obama-Trump-counties-Democrats-didn-t-15042475.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES - By Tuesday, most of the campaign signs that had been lining the neighborhood streets here for months were gone, pried out of the frozen ground almost instantaneously, as if the election had never happened, as if people were anxious to forget.  The uncertainty over who would emerge victorious from Monday's Iowa caucuses would continue for days - and still does, even as the state Democratic Party announced Thursday it had finally counted all the results after technical and logistical problems prompted chaos and delays in the first nominating contest of the 2020 primary.  Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and former South Bend, Indiana, mayor Pete Buttigieg both claimed victory in a race so tight that the Associated Press announced it could not declare a winner. And amid reports of miscounts and faulty delegate math, there has been enduring drama about what to do. Tom Perez, chairman of the Democratic National Committee, called for a full re-canvass of the results and then dialed that back. The Iowa Democratic Party announced it would review results from 95 problematic precincts and then extended its deadline for candidate re-canvassing requests to Monday. It has all served to extend even further the political hangover of weary Iowans who had labored to make sure the caucuses worked smoothly, only to see it all explode.  "We're actively testing Dante's circles of hell," one local Democratic Party official said just hours after the state party held a Wednesday night conference call with county chairs to divulge even more chaos in the process, including claims that a hotline set up for caucus leaders to phone in results had been swamped by prank calls from supporters of President Donald Trump after the number was posted on social media.  For all the drama, including the concern that the mishandling of the results...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: WINNERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/oscar-winners-2020-updating-live-full-list-1275973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Pitt claimed an early win for 'Once Upon a Time in Hollywood.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lashes out at 'photoshopped' image of face... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-reacts-angrily-image-highlighting-120851207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has described photographs revealing a pale ring around the edge of his distinctly orange face as “more fake news”, after a particularly unflattering image went viral over the weekend.Mr Trump’s eccentric range of facial colourations has been the subject of repeated enquiry by journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after gunman ambushes NYC police twice in 12 hours...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bc2296db89a22c7c313f717ce76ff6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A gunman is in custody after he ambushed police officers in the Bronx twice in 12 hours, wounding two in attacks that ignited outrage from officials who blamed the violence on an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BA flight breaks NY to London speed record as it reaches 825mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/378853/ba-flight-breaks-storm-record-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH Airways jet has today smashed the record for the fastest subsonic New York to London flight – thanks to incredible storm force winds. The Boeing 747-436 reached speeds of 825mph at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county 'ground zero' for 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article239947073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN:  Most devastating plague of locusts in recent history could come within weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/most-devastating-plague-locusts-recent-history-could-come-within-weeks-n1133171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change and al-Shabab extremists contributed to circumstances that could produce crippling swarms of locusts in Somalia and East Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab media accuse Israel of  conspiracy against China...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Arab-media-accuse-US-Israel-of-coronavirus-conspiracy-against-China-617021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One report claimed that it was no coincidence that the coronavirus was largely absent from the US and Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead flesh smells, demon voices and scratches; Possessed teen's exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/dead-flesh-smells-demon-voices-21428694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This woman claims she was exorcised by a Christian pastor as a teenager after an experiment with Wicca magic went wrong and she ended up possessed by a demon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS 7-DAY HELL: DYSFUNCTIONAL DISARRAY, DEFEATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democrats-worst-week-iowa-caucus-1897dc63-341b-4f5d-a274-566c6704cbdb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg Walks Back Gayle King Comments: 'I'm a Non-Violent Person'...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2020/02/09/snoop-dogg-walks-back-gayle-king-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snoop Dogg previously warned Gayle King "back off b--ch before we come get you.” He was upset about her interview on Kobe Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASHES OUT AT 'DOG-FACED' VOTER</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-calls-skeptical-new-hampshire-voter-lying-dog-faced-po</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dust-up came after the voter asked whether he can rebound from Iowa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PREY' Misfires With DC COMICS' Worst Opening in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/birds-of-prey-weekend-box-office-margot-robbie-1202853768/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4th UPDATE, Sunday AM w/final chart: In the wake of hitting highs with Wonder Woman, Aquaman and the highest-grossing R-rated movie of all-time in the 11-time Oscar-nominated and billion-dollar-plu…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
