<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Respect for troops, military sacrifice becomes election friction point...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2020/09/05/respect-for-troops-military-sacrifice-becomes-an-election-friction-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accusations that Trump insulted troops and wounded veterans will be a frequent talking point for election rivals this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postmaster General Accused of Pressuring Employees to Make Political Donations, Then Reimbursing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/06/politics/dejoy-gop-fundraiser-contributions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former employees of the company that US Postmaster General Louis DeJoy previously ran told The Washington Post they were pressured to donate to GOP candidates and then reimbursed through bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA moves on vaccines spark political worries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/515210-fda-moves-on-vaccines-spark-political-worries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health officials are taking aim at the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), warning it should not bow to political pressure and clear a COVID-19 vaccine before one is ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divers pull human remains from Central Park pond...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/07/divers-pull-human-remains-from-central-park-pond/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divers pulled a body out of a pond in Central Park on Labor Day afternoon, FDNY officials said. The human remains were taken out of The Pond around 12:30 p.m. near the park entrance at 59th Street …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Turns Into Furnace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-wildfires-extreme-heat-turns-state-into-a-furnace/ar-BB18NlFZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi killers have death sentences overturned in Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706159/Saudi-Arabia-convicts-eight-people-killing-Jamal-Khashoggi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has convicted eight people of killing Jamal Khashoggi and has jailed them for up to 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy opens competition probe into APPLEGOOGLE cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/07/italy-opens-competition-probe-into-apple-google-and-dropbox.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Competition and Market Authority said it launched six total investigations into the Google Drive service, Apple's iCloud and DropBox.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Journalist Jailed for Christian Persecution Coverage: 'They're Going to Have to Kill Me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/09/07/cuban-journalist-jailed-christian-persecution-coverage-theyre-going-have-kill-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo welcomed the release of Cuban journalist Roberto de Jesús Quiñones Haces from a year in prison on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Soviet Triple Agent Recruited New Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/leaked-kgb-manual-reveals-how-soviet-spies-recruited-in-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A KGB manual, published in English for the first time, reveals how Soviet spies infiltrated Western governments in an elaborate game of cat-and-mouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran shatters 1904 heat record by 8 degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Some-spots-in-San-Francisco-could-break-100-15546642.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a light ocean breeze fails to develop along the Northern California coast on Sunday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black families put trust in Black doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/During-pandemic-Black-families-put-trust-in-15547723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Dr. Janice Bacon was exactly the person Kay McField hoped to talk...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange faces 18 new charges as he appears in court to fight US extradition...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/julian-assange-wikileaks-founder-arrested-over-18-new-allegations-as-he-appears-in-court-to-fight-us-extradition-12065979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new US indictment, filed in June, contains 18 charges and was handed to Assange moments before he appeared at the Old Bailey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bold hopes for antibody tests still unfulfilled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd6b3e37ed51fe770b60c2ec5f8bc293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — At the height of the coronavirus lockdown, President Donald Trump and his top health advisers trumpeted a new test that would help Americans reclaim their lives — one that would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line judge bombarded with death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/tennis/article-8706299/US-Open-line-judge-struck-ball-hit-Novak-Djokovic-bombarded-death-threats-trolls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Open line judge hit in the throat with a ball by Novak Djokovic has been subjected to vile online abuse after fans of the world No 1 discovered her Instagram account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN SURPRISE CASH CRUNCH</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-election-campaign-fundraising-cash-eb9915fc-bbab-410f-8e99-fcca14a68024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of states Trump has to worry about has actually grown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President looms large over campaigns for control of Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ede31313f4988e76dc220bc5302afca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The battle for control of Congress is solidifying into a race about President Donald Trump, as Republicans hitch their fortunes to their party’s leader and Democrats position...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin critic Navalny out of coma, Berlin hospital says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-navalny-hospital/putin-critic-navalny-has-come-out-of-coma-berlin-hospital-says-idUSKBN25Y1E0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny has been removed from a medically induced coma and is responding to speech, Berlin's Charite hospital said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How NETFLIX Reed Hastings Rewrote The Hollywood Script...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dawnchmielewski/2020/09/07/how-netflixs-reed-hastings-rewrote-the-hollywood-script/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant had upended show business long before the pandemic hit. But with a highly unusual management style, its billionaire founder has now positioned his entertainment juggernaut to prosper like few companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'kidnaps' five Indian citizens in disputed border territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706069/China-KIDNAPS-five-Indian-citizens-disputed-border-territory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five missing men are from the Indian state of Arunachal Pradesh, which China claims as South Tibet, and the Indian Army said it had made representations to the People's Liberation Army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest trend in RV'ing: Getting way off the grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/07/success/boondocking-rvs-dry-camping/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational vehicle makers often boast how their RVs and trailers can feel just like home. Besides their cleverly packaged bathrooms and kitchenettes, when you park your rig at a campground you can find something else that will make you feel you never left home: neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organized labor staging political resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/515345-organized-labor-staging-political-resurgence-for-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unions, with only a few exceptions, are going all out for Joe Biden this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCHESTER: Naked protesters demand action after Daniel Prude's killing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e04d590aa95eb033a7e5a50dad3df4e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCHESTER, N.Y. (AP) — Naked except for “spit hoods” in a reference to the killing of Daniel Prude, several protesters sat outside Rochester's police headquarters Monday morning to push for police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Claim DISNEY Covering Up Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/workers-reveal-disney-is-covering-up-its-covid-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers and their worried spouses reveal to The Daily Beast that Disney is not only underreporting its COVID cases but clearing COVID-positive employees to return to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Pardons U.S. Marine Who Killed Trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200907-philippines-president-pardons-us-marine-in-transgender-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines president pardons US marine in transgender killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party voters imperil Trump margins in battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/third-party-voters-were-major-factor-trumps-2016-victory-how-could-they</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a warning sign" for the Trump campaign, said pollster Scott Rasmussen. "Maybe it's a yellow flag as opposed to a red flag. And it is one of many things that could change in the three states that shocked everybody: Pennsylvania Michigan and Wisconsin."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tale of 2 recessions': Rich Americans get richer, bottom half struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/07/income-inequality-wealth-gap-409234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend is on track to exacerbate dramatic wealth and income gaps in the U.S., where divides are already wider than any other nation in the G-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISS cameras capture fast-moving object 'with antennae' hurtling past astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/iss-cameras-capture-fast-moving-22641859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorist Mr MBB333 said the so-called UFO had "legs" or an "antennae-like" attachment coming off the bottom of the craft as it sped past the International Space Station (ISS)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor dies in front of virtual class amid symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/07/professor-dies-in-front-of-virtual-class-amid-covid-19-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A college professor in Argentina who had been suffering from persistent coronavirus symptoms collapsed and died at her home during a lecture in front of her virtual class, according to reports. Pao…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stock 'biggest house of cards'; 'Ready to fold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/06/tesla-could-be-the-most-dangerous-stock-on-wall-street-investment-researcher-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla shares may be up 400% this year, but one investment researcher is sounding the alarm on the stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients May Have Prolonged Gut Infection, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-09-07/covid-19-patients-may-have-prolonged-gut-infection-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and loathing in Hollywood at streamers' stranglehold...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fear-loathing-hollywood-streamers-stranglehold-101859368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood stars and top directors are getting increasingly anxious about the hold streaming giants Netflix and Amazon are exerting over cinema.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crazy 2020 makes for presidential race like no other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crazy-2020-makes-presidential-race-113058743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the campaign heats up post-Labor Day, President Trump emphasizes law and order while Joe Biden seeks to keep focus on the incumbent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters gather for Assange court extradition showdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33036b21539ccfa9d926306ecd41ac4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange appeared in a London court on Monday to fight a U.S. extradition request, at a high-stakes hearing that was delayed by the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming rise of technosexuals...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/alarming-rise-technosexuals-132943318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the pandemic wasn’t a surreal enough experience, a recent study suggests that lockdown has amplified a disturbing trend. Research by sex toy company WeVibe revealed that 14 per cent of men admit to being aroused by their smart-speaker Alexa, which confirms my view that we have been sleepwalking into a different kind of epidemic – one of loneliness and fear of intimacy. I’ve been a practising psychotherapist for 20 years, and never have I worked with so many men and women who are unhappy and scared because their deepest attachments and primary source of arousal are through interacting with their tech. I call these people ‘technosexuals’. Technosexuals are joined – as though surgically – to their favourite gadgets. Whether it’s the ‘ping’ of a message, swiping right, or the seductive, authoritative tones of a cloud-based voice service, their tech fulfils them by mobilising the reward system in the brain and releasing dopamine – the ‘happiness hormone’. The instant activity of using their tech – likes and comments – is like a sexual turn on. This ‘dopamine hit’ happens in all of us but, in technosexuals, something else is at play. For them, the modern digital world influences all their libidinous activity. It dictates who they fancy, and how they present and value themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaze triggered by 'gender reveal firework'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8704833/El-Dorado-wildfire-burned-7-050-acres-California-started-gender-reveal-party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildfire which broke out on Saturday 40 miles from Palm Springs was sparked by a pyrotechnic device at a gender reveal party. The El Dorado fire has burned for 36 hours and is only 5% under control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airplane Cabins Could Look Different the Next Time You Fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/airplane-cabins-could-look-different-the-next-time-you-fly/ar-BB18Ldf3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We Are Not Going to Be Intimidated by the President'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/the-atlantics-jeffrey-goldberg-defends-report-fires-back-at-trump-we-are-not-going-to-be-intimidated-by-the-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic Editor-in-Chief Jeffrey Goldberg used an interview with CNN's Brian Stelter to defend the magazine's reporting on President Donald Trump's disparagement of America's s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald so obsessed with Obama, he made video 'firing' him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-cohens-book-brings-renewed-attention-to-unaired-2012-rnc-video-of-trump-ripping-obama-lookalike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Michael Cohen prepares to release his upcoming autobiography, the former personal lawyer for Donald Trump has rejuvenated public intrigue in the president's hatred for his predecessor: Barack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World No 1 fumes at umpire for decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/tennis/article-8703907/Novak-Djokovic-DISQUALIFIED-Open-accidentally-hitting-ball-line-judge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world No 1, massive favourite for the tournament, was slung out after lengthy deliberations with tournament officials while playing his fourth round against Spaniard Pablo Carreno Busta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>121&amp;#8457;:  Weather service records hottest temperature on record in LA County!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailybulletin.com/2020/09/06/record-heat-sends-more-waves-of-people-to-la-countys-beaches-parks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailybulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic heatwave fueled multiple wildfires, triggered waves of power outages and threatened to return for another searing day on Labor Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN GALATICc plans next test spaceflight as it nears flying founder Richard Branson...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/06/virgin-galactics-next-test-spaceflight-oct-22-as-it-nears-flying-richard-branson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic plans to conducts its next crewed spaceflight test on Oct. 22, according to documents the company filed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  More think Biden trying to calm situation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-trump-wisconsin-opinion-poll-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New CBS News poll finds Biden's margins over Trump are the same nationwide and in battleground state of Wisconsin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Held 'Low Opinions of All Black Folks'... </title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/06/michael-cohens-book-says-trump-held-low-opinions-of-all-black-folks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump routinely referred to Black leaders of foreign nations with racist insults. He had an abiding admiration for President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISH TALK</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/mishtalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mish Talk is a global economics site covering interest rates and central bank policy, gold and precious metals, jobs, and economic reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It is getting better now': Family letters from deadly 1918 flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/It-is-getting-better-now-Family-letters-from-15546748.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobby Clifton never thought of his mother as someone who lived through a pandemic.  Even as the novel coronavirus brought the world to a halt - as it became clear that he, like Annie Donahoe Clifton, would witness a globally catastrophic outbreak of disease - he failed to draw the parallel. It took an emailed suggestion from his niece before Clifton, 75, entered his bedroom, opened the cedar chest at the foot of his bed and paged through the faded letters, exchanged in 1918 between his mother and her brother, then fighting overseas in World War I.  Preserved in paper, he found a teenager troubled by the shutdown of movie theaters, businesses and schools.  "Brother, Norfolk is some dull now," wrote 16-year-old Annie Clifton on Oct. 21, 1918. "All of the moving pictures and theatres are closed on account of the Spanish flu. ... I'm not working now (and) school ... had to close, too."  Bobby Clifton was struck by the similarities. It was late March, and schools, restaurants and shops were just starting to shut down all around his home in Virginia Beach, where he'd been spending a quiet retirement with his wife, Linda Clifton, until the virus hit. Everything had become so uncertain - and now, standing in his bedroom, he gripped the letter a little bit harder.  He hadn't known society shut down in 1918. He hadn't ever thought about it. And he'd never asked his mother, who died of dementia in 1986 without once broaching the pandemic with her son. Annie-of-the-letter spoke to Bobby Clifton in a much younger voice, not the matriarch he knew. But it felt, he said, like his mother was guiding him through the crisis.  "It makes you think, 'OK, we're not the only ones,'" said Valerie Fisher, the niece who recommended he look for the letters.  Americans throughout the country are making...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC editor: Reporting has only just begun ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/06/media/jeffrey-goldberg-atlantic-trump-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Goldberg, editor-in-chief of The Atlantic, said his magazine's story about Trump calling Americans who died in battle "losers" and "suckers," was just the tip of the iceberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No evidence of foul play'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-boat-parade-sinking-sheriff-2ca8cc05-e01b-4661-ba63-d77393dcb55f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"All the distress calls were resolved without injury or loss of life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy says trashing mail-in voting will hurt Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republicans-mail-in-voting-trump-a75b7b58-6405-4840-a48f-e26caf72b0fc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's particularly worried about deterring senior citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver swing from 101-degrees to SNOW!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/drastic-denver-temperature-plunge-yet-to-come-could-set-historic-record/808470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic turns summer into European tourism's leanest season...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fb7c50340a69f586dfb62835f23ef489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUGES, Belgium (AP) — Bruges mayor Dirk De fauw first realized something was desperately wrong with European tourism when on a brisk March morning he crossed the Burg square in front of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel announces curfews in cities, towns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2e05fd7e8c8831c5fcccfb551c2db42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia — Australia’s hot spot Victoria state on Monday recorded its lowest count of new COVID-19 cases in more than 10 weeks. The state reported 41 news cases and nine deaths...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen memoir casts him as star witness against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b388f843a13507ac83671494defcd100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michael Cohen's tell-all memoir makes the case that President Donald Trump is “guilty of the same crimes” that landed his former fixer in federal prison, offering a blow-by-blow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic out of US Open after hitting judge with ball...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b58237780cf41d7a375acfbd12e9c6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Novak Djokovic was kicked out of the U.S. Open for accidentally hitting a line judge in the throat with a tennis ball after dropping a game in his fourth-round match Sunday, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala warns suppression, interference could alter election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/79be8d5f69b1bfbcc55dbaec3ca001e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic vice presidential nominee Kamala Harris says foreign interference, doubt cast about the election by President Donald Trump and voter suppression could potentially cost...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine-weary Brazilians head to beaches despite warnings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45d940e61731d4dd6b369118055639ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Suellen de Souza could no longer endure the confinement. After six months of precautions, the Brazilian nursing technician decided that Sunday would be her first day at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans divided about reports Trump disparaged military...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3e3403f65ff186e557f94ae4ce52b3f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAYETTEVILLE, N.C. (AP) — In this soldier's city and across the country, veterans and military families are divided about reports that President Donald Trump made disparaging comments toward the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
