<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LIFE IN THE BUBBLE</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-patients-apocalypse-ward-gasp-21723273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients are seen lining walls throughout a Bergamo hospital in bubble helmets as medics desperately plea for the UK to lock down or face the same horrors they have - with the Italy death toll having surpassed China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELAY REPORTING NUMBERS?</title>
      <link>https://www.fxstreet.com/analysis/trump-asks-states-to-hide-unemployment-claim-data-202003200202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fxstreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKMAN:  We need to get Fed out of way. We need higher interest rates not lower...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/stockman-coronavirus-sparking-financial-crisis-wall-street-is-toast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former OMB director David Stockman believes Main Street is better equipped to deal with a recession than Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE-WIDE LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/california-governor-issues-statewide-order-to-stay-at-home-effective-thursday-evening.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Governor Gavin Newsom on Thursday issued a statewide order for all residents to 'stay at home' amid a coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia deploys innovative, if invasive, tech to curb virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asia-deploys-innovative-invasive-tech-curb-virus-015625449.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Electronic bracelets and phones that report your whereabouts, text messages if you stray too far from quarantine and digital detectives tracking where you've been -- Asian countries have embraced innovative, if somewhat invasive, tech to counter the coronavirus pandemic. When Hong Kong stylist Declan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  2nd Republican senator dumped millions after briefing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sen-kelly-loeffler-dumped-millions-in-stock-after-coronavirus-briefing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Georgia Republican is the second senator who has gotten rid of their holdings right as the stock market went bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP URGES DELAY OF NUMBERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/19/business/economy/coronavirus-employers-unemployment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New filings for unemployment benefits rose 30 percent last week amid cutbacks and shutdowns over the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak: A Cascade of Warnings, Heard but Unheeded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/coronavirus-outbreak-a-cascade-of-warnings-heard-but-unheeded/ar-BB11pYY1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Vice President Candidates? Party Leaders Favor Former Rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/biden-vice-president-candidates-party-leaders-favor-former-rivals/ar-BB11qB8I?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus killing far more men than women...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/The-coronavirus-is-killing-far-more-men-than-women-15143405.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 200,000 coronavirus cases worldwide and thousands of deaths, a striking pattern is appearing in the hardest-hit countries: More men are dying than women.  No where is this trend more pronounced than in Italy. Men make up nearly 60% of people with confirmed cases of the virus and more than 70% of those who have died from covid-19, according to the country's main public health research agency.  On the other end of the spectrum is South Korea, where about 61% of confirmed infections have been in women. Though far fewer patients have died, the majority of fatalities - 54% -- were again in men.  As the pandemic escalates, epidemiologists and public health authorities are scrambling to understand who is most vulnerable and how to protect them. The data from countries such as Italy and South Korea show that the disease can take wildly different paths.  Exactly what makes a group vulnerable - and how to protect them - has experts "mystified," said Carlos del Rio, chair of the department of global health at Emory University. "This difference in mortality is creating a lot of anxiety," he added.  The outbreak of covid-19 in Italy is the deadliest in the world. As of March 17, more than 40,000 people there have been sickened with the virus, and 3,405 have died. That means that, based on these current and unavoidably incomplete figures, 8.2 percent of people infected in the country have died. That is more than double the global figure presented recently by the WHO.  Italy's aging population is probably particularly susceptible to the disease, researchers say. With a median age of 46.5, according to the CIA World Factbook, it is the fifth oldest country in the world. And these elderly citizens are those who have become the sickest: People over the age of 70 represent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Flocking to the Safety of Comfort Foods...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/americans-are-flocking-to-the-safety-of-comfort-foods/ar-BB11qK7U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With low test rates, COVID-19 spreads in shadows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/low-test-rates-covid-19-spreads-shadows-173039467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of available tests for COVID-19 means the world is effectively fighting the pandemic blind and may not know the true extent of infection for months if not years, experts said Thursday. Because COVID-19 is so infectious -- roughly 2.5 times that of the common cold -- but not everyone presents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA, UNITED sending largest planes to desert for storage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-united-other-airlines-sending-195832455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marana, Arizona is where aircraft go to retire but some airlines are sending their jets there to ride out the COVID-19 crisis affecting the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES grounds 55,000 flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241345821.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA:  56% WILL BE INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/488547-california-projects-56-percent-of-the-population-will-be-infected-over-8-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly unemployed grapple with fallout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319221637-13fyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-JOBS (PIX):'How did things end up like this?' America's newly unemployed grapple with coronavirus fallout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. jobless claims could top record 1.5 million next week...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319190408-erroj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-LAYOFFS (GRAPHIC):U.S. jobless claims could top record 1.5 million next week - economists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Chief Sees 'Tens of Thousands' Deployed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319171102-vnw4m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-NATIONALGUARD (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-'Tens of thousands' of National Guard troops could be used to assist with coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro strives to regain leadership...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d74123a2ddeed5e5ef845f180ff2a637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — After questioning the seriousness of COVID-19, defying his own health ministry's recommendations and denouncing a “certain hysteria,” Brazil's president is now projecting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gathering bans raise religious freedom questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6198ba98ea6d26b128044ea59b9b4da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — On the first Sunday after the coronavirus began upending American life, some religious institutions – including two churches whose pastors are close to President Donald Trump –...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis accuse Netanyahu of exploiting virus to keep power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9023e2a54c5d5b6b28969292cd55aeba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel appeared to be barreling toward a constitutional crisis Thursday as opponents took to the streets and turned to the Supreme Court to fight a series of unprecedented steps...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept tells citizens not to travel; Return home if overseas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c7a28aae24ec5f4bb8a79022ac92e5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration has upgraded its already dire warning to Americans against all international travel as the coronavirus outbreak spreads. The State Department on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Found Oil on Mars. Or Truffles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/scientists-found-oil-on-mars-or-truffles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two astrobiologists say they’ve found “thiophenes” in dried-up mud on Mars. The presence of these organic compounds on the Red Planet could be a sign of life—or something else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Dumped Up to $1.6 Million of Stock After Reassuring Public About Coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/senator-dumped-up-to-1-6-million-of-stock-after-reassuring-public-about-coronavirus-preparedness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence Chair Richard Burr’s selloff came around the time he was receiving daily briefings on the health threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating Gets Complicated: 'Things Going Alright Until I Sneezed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/weird/dating-gets-complicated-in-the-time-of-coronavirus-things-were-going-alright-until-i-sneezed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thing about social distancing in our lives under the coronavirus pandemic is it runs counter to a timeless human enterprise: dating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell stimulus plan would provide $1,200 per person...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mcconnell-coronavirus-stimulus-plan-payments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saying lawmakers "need to take bold and swift action as soon as possible," Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell on Thursday introduced legislation to provide as much as $1,200 per person and $2,400 per couple in the U.S. amid the coronavirus outbreak and skyrocketing jobless claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY: Death toll overtakes China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/540510ba224feb84c7044024119323ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy's death toll from the coronavirus outbreak eclipsed China’s on Thursday as the scourge extended its march across the West, where the United States and other countries...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.H. residents sue over gatherings ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/19/new-hampshire-coronavirus-gatherings-ban-prompts-l/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people who planned to attend political and religious events in the next few weeks are challenging New Hampshire’s statewide emergency ban on gatherings of 50 people or more to prevent spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FEMA Chief Calls 'Bullsh*t!', Storms Off MSNBC Set...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-former-fema-chief-rips-out-earpiece-calls-bullsht-and-walks-off-interview-on-msnbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FEMA Chief Craig Fugate ripped out his earpiece and walked off during an interview with Katy Tur on MSNBC on Thursday. "I don't have time to listen to bullshit, people," Fugate m</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival hit with car during argument over social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/19/man-hits-rival-with-car-during-argument-over-social-distancing-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man angered over a neighbor’s social distancing practices rammed the guy with his car outside of a Brooklyn synagogue, cops said Thursday. The 31-year-old victim was arguing with the man ou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 members of same NJ family die...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/19/fourth-person-in-nj-family-has-died-from-the-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey family has lost a fourth member to the coronavirus, according to a report Thursday. Vincent Fusco died at CentraState Medical Center in Freehold, cousin and Fusco family lawyer Roseann…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA  to announce Mexico border restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319193745-vecoi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO-USA (URGENT):U.S. expected to announce restrictions on travel across Mexico border - sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Wall Street Tsunami Get Worse?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/03/could-wall-streets-coronavirus-tsunami-get-worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the current crisis, private equity, with its mountains of debt, could be the weak link, said a very senior Wall Street banker. If limited partners don’t kick in cash when asked, things could get very bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Total annihilation': May just be end for many alt-weeklies...</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2020/03/total-annihilation-coronavirus-may-just-be-the-end-for-many-alt-weeklies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 is "a nearly perfect weapon against alternative weeklies." In dozens of cities, papers are asking for donations, laying off staff, or abandoning print as social distancing dries up their revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Of Coronavirus Patients Have Digestive Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-digestive-symptoms-diarrhea-almost-half-of-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests respiratory symptoms aren't the only thing doctors and patients should be looking out for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>96% of small business owners already feeling impact...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/small-business-owners-coronavirus-survey-06e04322-7788-4de4-8216-42b875a39e53.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half say their business won't be able to last more than three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento County Issues Legal Order To Stay Inside...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/03/19/sacramento-stay-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just before midnight tonight, residents of Sacramento County will be under the order to stay inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested After Telling People On Public Bus He Had Coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/coronavirus-lebanon-nh-david-ladeau-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Vermont man is accused of trying to scare people by telling them he had the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No soap, no water: Billions lack basic protection...</title>
      <link>http://www.rfi.fr/en/wires/20200319-no-soap-no-water-billions-lack-basic-protection-against-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rfi.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No soap, no water: billions lack basic protection against virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Who Hid Symptoms to Fly to China Faces Criminal Charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/coronavirus/woman-who-hid-coronavirus-symptoms-to-fly-to-china-faces-criminal-charges/2093876/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcboston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who allegedly flew from Massachusetts to Los Angeles to China and then tested positive for COVID-19 is under investigation for concealing her symptoms and putting fellow travelers at risk of infections, the Los Angeles Times reports. According to the L.A. Times, the woman, a Chinese citizen living in Massachusetts, became ill with coronavirus symptoms and when she went…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE will STOP immigration enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8129105/ICE-delay-illegal-immigrant-arrests-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration officials said it will delay the majority of its arrests of illegal immigrants due to the coronavirus pandemic except for those who pose a risk or have committed serious criminal acts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 pillars of Trump's case for reelection collapsing all at once...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/coronavirus-crisis-trumps-argument-for-reelection-is-collapsing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is rising. Markets are falling. Coronavirus is spreading. And Trump's reelection campaign will need a new message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweeping new emergency laws in UK include power to arrest sick people...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11208831/coronavirus-emergency-laws-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINISTERS have today revealed sweeping new coronavirus laws – with the powers to arrest sick people and even shut down airports. Boris Johnson will try and push through the emergency legislat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY: Death toll overtakes China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/coronavirus-death-toll-italys-is-now-higher-than-chinas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people who have died from the coronavirus in Italy has hit 3,405, according to Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIDEMIC OF DESPAIR: Looming psychological crisis...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/903343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the coming epidemic of despair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weddings limited to 2 guests, says Church of England...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-weddings-should-be-limited-to-two-guests-says-church-of-england-11960420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apart from the couple themselves, all other people at weddings should practice social distancing, the Church of England says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Quarantine shaming': Radical new social norms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0714c8c609d604579d00ab93cd6df12c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of Arizona's Asian Chamber of Commerce didn't see much downside to attending a small dinner at a local restaurant to bolster the business and bring together other leaders to discuss...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Younger Adults Comprise Big Portion of Hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/younger-adults-comprise-big-portion-of-coronavirus-hospitalizations-in-us/ar-BB11nGEB?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France may extend lockdown as 'idiots' flout rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-may-extend-lockdown-many-flout-rules-132356654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's two-week lockdown to try to stem the coronavirus is likely to be extended, officials said Thursday as the interior minister blasted "idiots" flouting the home confinement rules. President Emmanuel Macron ordered French residents to stay at home from Tuesday except for essential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Chief Sees 'Tens of Thousands' Deployed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319150729-4df6k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-NATIONALGUARD (URGENT):"Tens of thousands" of National Guard troops could be called up to help with coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept to tell Americans not to travel; Return home if overseas...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/561689/coronavirus-state-department-travel-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE STATE Department is set to tell Americans ‘not to travel and to return home if overseas’ due to coronavirus pandemic. If announced, the advisory will be the most serious warning yet…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY CASES DOUBLE OVERNIGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ny-cases-jump-to-4000-overnight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York has confirmed more than 4,000 cases statewide, which Cuomo said was driven by a dramatic increase in testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAY HOME FOR 18 MONTHS?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-not-going-stay-home-143016960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Remember a week and a half ago when CNBC’s Rick Santelli said that “maybe we’d just be better off” if we just infected everybody with the coronavirus now? His reasoning:Then in a month it would be over because the mortality rate of this probably isn’t going to be any different</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India activist arrested for selling cow urine to combat virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-political-activist-arrested-selling-cow-urine-combat-194235262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An activist with India's ruling party has been arrested after a volunteer fell ill from drinking cow urine at a party to combat the novel coronavirus, police said Wednesday, as interest grows in home remedies amid the pandemic. Narayan Chatterjee, a Bharatiya Janata Party activist, was arrested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Out May Never Be the Same...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eating-may-never-same-u-140041187.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Coronavirus is sending Americans back home for dinner, creating a crisis for a restaurant industry that was already slowing down.The viral outbreak is wreaking havoc as diners isolate themselves at home and states restrict operations to carryout and delivery only. Large swaths of the industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX asked to slow streaming so Internet doesn't buckle...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/netflix-coronavirus-speed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In what could be a harbinger of things to come in the United States, the European Union has asked Netflix to tap the breaks on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House mulls new 50-year bonds...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/white-house-mulls-50-25-130627864.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Trump administration is revisiting the idea of issuing ultra-long bonds as it grapples with how to finance a $1.3 trillion fiscal stimulus plan, according to people familiar with the matter.President Donald Trump’s advisers are considering, among other options, issuing both 50-year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How long will this last?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67ac94d1cf08a84ff7c6bbeec2b167fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a matter of days, millions of Americans have seen their lives upended by measures to curb the spread of the new coronavirus. Normally bustling streets are deserted as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christ the Redeemer statue debuts gripping tribute to COVID-19-stricken countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.theblaze.com/news/brazils-christ-the-redeemer-statue-debuts-gripping-tribute-to-covid-19-stricken-countries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants break into farm in self-isolation and get drunk on whisky...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/coronavirus-elephants-break-farm-self-21719583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the world there are now 200,000 confirmed cases of COVID-19 - but a herd of elephants in China found a very fun way to make the most of people putting themselves in self-isoltion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as cluster of red lights move 'in formation' over Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-cluster-red-lights-move-21720173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorists have ruled out the lights being Chinese lanterns, given their positioning and that they're "not flickering"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone, Rome's seniors live in silence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/alone-romes-seniors-live-lockdown-silence-130546784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks desperately empty, again, and Roberto Fichera could easily not see another human being today -- a growing problem in Europe's oldest country. "I am a homebody and I like to take care of myself," says Fichera, who might come across the odd stranger at the pharmacy, should he decide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot Sales Jump...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pot-sales-jump-more-people-123245158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- More people stuck at home has led to a higher demand for cannabis, and Aphria Inc. is one of the best-positioned companies to take advantage of that trend, an analyst at Bank of America said.“Our checks across North America were consistent: regardless of region, cannabis purchases have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everything out of our control': Inside first major U.S. city on lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/everything-out-our-control-san-francisco-eases-lockdown-n1163376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco is two days into a lockdown that has no definite end. What happens next is anyone's guess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even most isolated corners of country not safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-19/coronavirus-wyoming-covid-19-casper-idaho</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even Wyoming, the least populated state in the U.S., isn't safe from coronavirus. Only three states have no confirmed cases. You can't run from COVID-19. You can't hide from the infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo's sons vs. 'El Mencho': Mexico sees rising cartel bloodshed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mexico-cartels-landscape-rising-violence-el-chapo-sons-el-mencho-sinaloa-jalisco-new-generation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another year, another homicide total unseen before in Mexico's modern history as the country struggles to check rising violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three members of same NJ family die...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/19/three-members-of-the-same-new-jersey-family-die-after-contracting-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two family members of a New Jersey woman who died from the coronavirus last week also reportedly lost their lives from the illness on Wednesday. Grace Fusco, 73, a mother of 11 from Freehold, died …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHASE to close 1,000 branches...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/19/chase-to-temporarily-close-1000-branches-over-coronavirus-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan Chase is closing about a fifth of its bank branches to help contain the spread of COVID-19. The finance giant will shutter about 1,000 Chase bank locations temporarily, according to a memo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World wages 'war' on virus as China offers ray of hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.outlookindia.com/newsscroll/world-wages-war-on-virus-as-china-offers-ray-of-hope/1773230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outlookindia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans must relearn to sacrifice...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Americans-must-relearn-to-sacrifice-in-the-time-15142319.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past few days, federal and state governments have intensified anti-coronavirus measures, closing schools and imposing restrictions on business activity and socializing. Although Americans are waking up to this peril, there has been significant resistance to disruptions of normal life despite the dire warnings of health experts.  One NBC News poll conducted from March 11-13 showed that only 56 percent of Democrats and 26 percent of Republicans thought their daily lives would change significantly in the near future, and more recently a poll showed that more than three out of four Republicans believe the media has exaggerated the risk of the virus. Only 61 percent of Democrats and a paltry 30 percent of Republicans planned to stop attending large public gatherings. Business owners in Washington, D.C., Illinois, Nashville and Philadelphia have pledged to defy government orders to shut down. The Republican governor of Oklahoma, Kevin Stitt, notoriously tweeted a photo of himself and his children at a restaurant on Saturday, proclaiming "Eating with my kids and all my fellow Oklahomans . . . It's packed tonight!" These divides leave Democrats especially furious that their political opponents aren't taking the crisis seriously.  While further mandatory restrictions will hopefully change this outlook, we must understand why it has been so difficult mobilizing Americans to slow the spread of the virus through social distancing. One could point to a host of causes: the death of expertise, the stovepiping of information sources, the rise of post-truth politics, the lack of paid leave for many workers and the Trump administration's failure of leadership.  Yet, another factor is at play. For the past three-quarters of a century, Americans have largely not been asked to sacrifice across the board for the good of the country....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY: Dozens of army trucks carry corpses as morgues fill up...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/dozens-army-trucks-carry-coronavirus-21717762</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trucks were pictured driving through the city of Bergamo in the country’s Lombardy region, one of the worst-hit by the virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disinfectant Wipes Being Flushed Down Toilets Causing Major Pipe Problems...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/coronavirus-disinfecting-wipes-being-flushed-down-toilets-causing-major-pipe-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the coronavirus scare, sterilizing cleaning wipes are flying off of store shelves. Unfortunately, many of those wipes are ending up in sewer systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fever dream' of invincibility...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/youth-warned-against-fever-dream-coronavirus-invicibility-055907018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before shutdowns swept the globe and many were urged -- or mandated -- to stay indoors to stymie coronavirus's spread, Divya Sonti sensed the worst was yet to come. Deborah Birx, the White House taskforce coronavirus administrator, said "the millennial generation" could include many more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai hospitals deploy 'ninja robots' to aid battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thai-hospitals-deploy-ninja-robots-aid-virus-battle-073032208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thai hospitals are deploying "ninja robots" to measure fevers and protect the health of overburdened medical workers on the frontlines of the coronavirus outbreak. First built to monitor recovering stroke patients, the machines have been quickly repurposed to help fight the disease, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Jerusalem's Old City, virus 'worse than war'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jerusalems-old-city-virus-worse-war-025115789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Munib Abu Assab, a tour operator in Jerusalem's Old City, has seen deserted streets before, but he said not even past conflicts over the contested land compare to the impact of coronavirus. The 56-year-old Palestinian has lived though the 1967 Six Day War, the 1973 Yom Kippur War, the threat of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There are no funerals:' Death in quarantine leaves nowhere to grieve...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319112258-bkfu7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RITES (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-"There are no funerals:" Death in quarantine leaves nowhere to grieve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every 10 mins person dies in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319111156-9ccig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/IRAN-DEATH (URGENT):In Iran, every 10 minutes one person dies from the coronavirus - health official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From trickle to steady flow: Caseload tests military...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200319092230-4c0pj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-PENTAGON (PIX):From a trickle to a steady flow: Coronavirus caseload tests U.S. military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Index Slumps Most on Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/manufacturing-philadelphia-fed-region-drops-123809299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia’s survey of factories showed conditions in the area deteriorated in March by the most on record, showing the heavy toll on demand from the novel coronavirus battle is extending to more of the nation’s producers.The general activity index slumped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We Are Not Prepared': ER Doctor Says Hospital Supplies Being Rationed...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/colorado-doctor-supplies-rationed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jane Jenab, a Denver-based emergency room physician, warned of area hospitals already rationing vital medical equipment for health care workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON warehouse closes after first worker tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2020/03/amazon-warehouse-employee-has-coronavirus/608341/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers at the Queens, New York, facility say employees were expected to come in for their night shift after the case was identified. Amazon denies this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk offers to make ventilators amid shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-musk/teslas-musk-offers-to-make-ventilators-amid-shortage-in-coronavirus-battle-idUSKBN2160PM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Twitter users welcomed on Thursday an offer by Tesla's chief ex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKHEED MARTIN simulates US strike on Russian forces in promo...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/lockheed-martin-appears-simulate-airstrike-21719077</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockheed Martin has offered a teaser of its future Skunk Works autonomous planes by simulating a battle with Russian-made weapons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London braced for lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/coronavirus-london-will-12-hour-21719143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency legislation could be used to close down streets completely, restrict public transport networks and ban large public gatherings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah quake damages temple, iconic angel statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/18/us/earthquake-salt-lake-temple-moroni/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 5.7-magnitude earthquake that shook Utah Wednesday morning also dislodged a symbolic part of Salt Lake City's iconic Mormon temple: the trumpet of an angel statue atop its highest spire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famed AIDS Researcher Racing to Find Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/this-famous-aids-researcher-wants-to-find-a-coronavirus-cure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed AIDS Researcher Is Racing to Find a Coronavirus Treatment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
The RV Gets a Makeover: Head for the Hills in Six-Figure Winnebago on Steroids...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/earthroamer-lti-head-for-the-hills-in-luxury-overlanding-vehicle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head for the Hills in a Six-FigureÂ Winnebago on Steroids</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Extravagance of Less...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/19/th...-extravagance-of-less/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“IT’S NOT SO easy to live in my houses,” says the Italian artist and architect Vincenzo De Cotiis. Known as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced Quarantines Spark Confusion and Worries About Precedent...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/19/forced-quarantines-spark-confusion-and-worries-about-precedent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day after Bill Roberts’s oldest daughter Christina drove to their hospital in Westchester County to be tested for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New York Doctor's Warning: The Sky Is Falling...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/19/a-new-york-doctors-coronavirus-warning-the-sky-is-falling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve had hard conversations this week. “Look me in the eye,” I said to my neighbor Karen, who was spiraling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man beaten to death by mob 'for having coronavirus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8129791/Kenyan-man-beaten-death-mob-youths-suspected-having-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim, named as George Kotini Hezron (not pictured), was going home after visiting a bar in his village of Msambweni, Kenya, when he was attacked by a vigilante group and stoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient on hellish ordeal: 'I was screaming for mercy and praying to God'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/18/coronavirus-patient-on-hellish-ordeal-i-was-screaming-for-mercy-and-praying-to-god/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It started out as a tickle in his throat before bed, but by the next morning, it felt like the worst flu ever. And by the time Kevin Harris was admitted to a hospital in Ohio five days later, he th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX plans first manned flight to space station...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spacex-plans-first-manned-flight-space-station-may-090626539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's SpaceX will send astronauts to the International Space Station for the first time in May, NASA said, announcing the first crewed launch from the United States to the platform since 2011. The tech entrepreneur's company will launch a Falcon 9 rocket to transport NASA astronauts Bob</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
