<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New Marine Corps maternity uniforms coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2021/04/10/new-marine-corps-maternity-uniforms-available-in-april/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Corps also will make maternity and nursing undershirts available by the end of April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Up to 80 percent' in Sicily refuse AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210411-up-to-80-percent-in-sicily-refuse-az-vaccine-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Up to 80 percent' in Sicily refuse AZ vaccine: president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power cuts after another 'explosive event' on Caribbean island...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-56707956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitors report another "explosive event" at a volcano on the now ash-covered Caribbean island of St Vincent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court leaves major conservative cases waiting, from abortion to guns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-leaves-major-conservative-090011022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rather than handing conservatives a string of wins, the Supreme Court has left advocates on the right grasping for answers about high-profile cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER CAN'T STOP SAFRICA STRAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/real-world-israeli-data-shows-south-african-variant-better-at-bypassing-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strain is more effective than original COVID and the British variant at bypassing the shot, Israeli scientists find, in first-of-its-kind, real-world study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For years, Boston Police kept secret: Union prez was alleged child molester...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/04/10/metro/years-boston-police-kept-secret-union-president-was-an-alleged-child-molester/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite 1995 evidence, Patrick Rose kept his badge, worked on child sexual assault cases, and ascended to power in the police union. He went on to allegedly molest five other children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims key to Republican success is more Trumpism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-8e31fdc2b54f9d61e4d317449507c7be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Staking his claim to the Republican Party, former President Donald Trump is casting his populist policies and attack-dog politics as the key to future GOP success. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As left and right protesters target public servants at home, city pushes back...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/protesters-left-target-public-servants-120040948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After protesters in Sacramento vandalized the mayor's house and threatened the city manager, a broad coalition is urging "Sactivists" to cool it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland ICE building set on fire during protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/portland-ice-building-set-on-fire-during-saturday-night-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters in Portland, Oregon, allegedly set fire to a U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) building late Saturday night, according to videos posted on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci 'not sure' why Texas doesn't have uptick after nixing masks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/10/fauci-not-sure-why-texas-doesnt-have-covid-uptick-after-nixing-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been some five weeks since Texas lifted its mask mandate, and there has yet to be an explosion of COVID-19 cases. It’s something Dr. Anthony Fauci can’t quite explain. &amp;#8220…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding in Polls, Erdogan Kicks Up New Storm...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/10/sliding-in-the-polls-erdogan-kicks-up-a-new-storm-over-the-bosporus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL — The unpredictable roller coaster that has become Turkish politics was on full display this past week after 104</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 dog tags found in belly of monster gator...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/10/five-dog-tags-found-in-belly-of-south-carolina-monster-gator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Carolina hunter got the shock of his life when he killed a monster “nuisance gator” along the Edisto River in the alligator-laden ACE Basin estuary in Beaufort, Colleton and Charleston coun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Boogaloo' extremists destroyed evidence in probe of officer's murder, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/boogaloo-extremists-destroyed-evidence-in-probe-of-officer-s-murder-feds-say/ar-BB1fw5CH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury indictment says members of the Northern California-based Grizzly Scouts tried to cover for one of their own by deleting chat histories that included a message reading, “Dudes i offed a fed.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German conservatives mull Merkel succession...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210411-german-conservatives-mull-merkel-succession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German conservatives mull Merkel succession</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother Detained After 3 Kids Stabbed to Death in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9457549/3-children-fatally-stabbed-Los-Angeles-apartment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California mom suspected of killing her three children before fleeing in a stolen car once had a 'Blog for Good' filled with inspirational messages while slamming Teen Mom stars in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's Hidden Toll Is Open Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/you-cant-trust-anyone-russias-hidden-covid-toll-is-an-open-secret/ar-BB1fvubF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olga Kagarlitskaya’s father had been hospitalized weeks earlier in a coronavirus ward. Now he was gone, cause of death: “viral pneumonia, unspecified.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside BLM co-founder's real-estate buying binge...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/10/inside-blm-co-founder-patrisse-khan-cullors-real-estate-buying-binge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As protests broke out across the country in the name of Black Lives Matter, the group’s co-founder went on a real estate-buying binge, snagging four high-end homes for $3.2 million in the US …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Suspicious' blackout strikes Iran nuke site
...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/official-accident-strikes-irans-natanz-nuclear-facility-77002407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s underground Natanz nuclear facility has lost power just hours after starting up new advanced centrifuges capable of enriching uranium faster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rips McConnell at Mar-a-Lago: 'Dumb son of a b*tch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/11/trump-mcconnell-dumb-son-of-a-bitch-rnc-480748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president spoke at an RNC donor retreat Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unloads on Fauci: 'Ever seen anybody that so full of crap?'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-slashes-at-mcconnell-as-he-reiterates-election-falsehoods-at-republican-event/ar-BB1fwuyf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president used most of a speech to GOP leaders to fling familiar grievances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAVE DAMAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/incident-reported-in-iranian-natanz-nuclear-facility-664792</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natanz has in the past been targeted by Israeli cyber operations. In 2010, Stuxnet attacked the facility, destroying 1,000 centrifuges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER less effective in SAfrican variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pfizer-less-effective-african-variant-052046553.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study in Israel found Pfizer/BioNTech's COVID-19 vaccine to be less effective on the variant found in South Africa.However, the variant's occurrence in the country is low, and the research has also not been peer-reviewed. The study, released on Saturday, compared almost 400 people who tested positive at least two weeks after receiving one or two doses of the vaccine against the same number who had tested positive but were unvaccinated. It also matched age and gender, among other characteristics. South Africa's variant was found to make up 1% of all cases in the study, according to Tel Aviv University, and the country's largest healthcare provider, Clalit. They found that the variant was eight times more prevalent in patients who had received two doses of the vaccine, compared to those who were unvaccinated. According to Tel Aviv University professor Adi Stern, the data suggests that the South African variant is able to break through the vaccine's protection to some extent. The researchers cautioned that the data was not intended to deduce overall vaccine effectiveness against other variants, since it only looked at people who had already tested positive for COVID-19, instead of overall infection rates. Pfizer and BioNTech could not be immediately reached for comment outside business hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electrical problem 'strikes' Iran nuke facility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-358384f03b1ef6b65f4264bf9a59a458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's Natanz nuclear site suffered a problem Sunday involving its electrical distribution grid just hours after starting up new advanced centrifuges that more quickly enrich...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official admits Chinese shot's effectiveness low...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/beijing-immunizations-chengdu-coronavirus-pandemic-china-675bcb6b5710c7329823148ffbff6ef9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — In a rare admission of the weakness of Chinese coronavirus vaccines, the country's top disease control official says their effectiveness is low and the government is considering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry and William will reunite to walk behind coffin...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2677223/harry-walk-behind-prince-philips-coffin-with-harry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry and brother William will walk behind the  Duke of Edinburgh’s coffin at his funeral next Saturday. Harry’s pregnant wife Meghan will not go for medical reasons. 🔵 Read our live bl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Vaccinated Can Be Evacuated, Says Prime Minister!</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/only-vaccinated-people-can-be-evacuated-from-island-to-escape-volcano-says-prime-minister/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unvaccinated people in Caribbean already being treated as second-class citizens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying robot army...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/vladimir-putin-deploy-fearsome-russian-23890805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defence Minister Sergei Shoigu has paid a trip to the 766th Production and Technological Enterprise in Nakhabino, to get a glimpse of Russia's unmanned robots in action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE:  TRUMP SEARCHES AT LOWEST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-television-media-social-media-mar-a-lago-15475effad776332890300bcb2b35bde</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Donald Trump insists he's enjoying his life off Twitter. The press releases his aides fire off on an increasingly frequent basis are more “elegant,” he says....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Bowl Sets July Reopening!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/hollywood-bowl-reopening-july-covid-concerts-1234731070/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For fans of the Hollywood Bowl, the lack-of-shell shock is nearly over. After being closed for more than a year, the storied venue said today that it will reopen in July for 14 weeks of concerts wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel drafts law for nationwide lockdown rule, curfews...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/germanys-merkel-drafts-law-for-nationwide-lockdown-rule-curfews/article_48075c86-cdc6-554d-af6e-2c30c66ef5da.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — German Chancellor Angela Merkel’s coalition has drafted legislation that would shift the power to impose COVID-19 restrictions to the federal government from regional leaders to combat a surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KKK fliers, White Lives Matter rally: Huntington Beach confronts 'storm of hate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/kkk-fliers-white-lives-matter-rally-huntington-beach-confronts-storm-of-hate/article_8c8746cf-ddcc-55cc-92f8-c9c750bf7128.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. — For years, Huntington Beach has tried to push back against its reputation as a magnet for extremist hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan will skip funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9457035/Prince-Philips-funeral-Saturday-Meghan-advised-doctors-not-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckingham Palace today announced that Philip's ceremonial royal funeral will take place on April 17 in St George's Chapel, Windsor Castle, and a national minute's silence will be observed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA DELAYS MARS COPTER FLIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/10/22377299/nasa-ingenuity-mars-helicopter-flight-delayed-wednesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from Ingenuity’s pre-flight preps showed a minor glitch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST FOR SPACE FUTURE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/nasa-is-preparing-to-fly-the-ingenuity-helicopter-on-mars-in-an-otherworldly-wright-brothers-moment/ar-BB1fvlDo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flight of a tiny helicopter called Ingenuity, perhaps as early as April 11, would mark a first in interplanetary travel, demonstrate a new technology, and pave the way for future scientists and explorers to more quickly traverse the surface of the Red Planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon builds 'physics-bending weapon' for wars with UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/military-paid-scientist-build-physics-23870808</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon chiefs, concerned that China may already have advanced UFO technology, commissioned Dr Salvatore Pais to build a new kind of aircraft that can travel at incredible speeds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Police Held Black Lieutenant at Gunpoint, Pepper Sprayed Him Over Traffic Stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/virginia-police-held-black-lieutenant-caron-nazario-at-gunpoint-and-pepper-sprayed-him-over-a-traffic-stop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caron Nazario has sued, alleging the officers racially profiled him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Calls James Franco 'Predatory;' Seth Rogen 'Enabler'...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/04/charlyne-yi-james-franco-allegations-disaster-artist-1234629255/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yi also called out producer Seth Rogen in an Instagram post detailing how the filmmakers tried to bribe her into staying in the movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN: Truce Proposal In Trans Wars...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/a-truce-proposal-in-the-trans-wars-c49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a compromise available. Here's one version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramsey Clark, attorney general who became critic of U.S. policies, dies at 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ramsey-clark-attorney-general-who-became-a-critic-of-us-policies-dies-at-93/ar-BB1fvTOe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He served as LBJ’s attorney general, then later questioned U.S. foreign policy and defended an international rogues’ gallery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands evacuated -- return unsure...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/saint-vincent-evacuating-thousands-after-eruption-their-return-unsure-3178138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saint Vincent evacuating thousands after eruption, their return unsure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://voranda.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;voranda.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
