<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Five years after death, is Castro revolution floundering?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/five-years-after-his-death-is-castro-s-revolution-floundering/ar-AAR6gsQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five years after Fidel Castro's death, the revolution he started in 1959 appears to be at an impasse, with Cuba's economy battered and an ever-larger part of its population clamoring for change. The communist island has seen unprecedented protests in the last year as more and more citizens blame the one-party state for a variety of social and economic ills. A younger generation of Cubans, the so-called "grandchildren" of the revolution, are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany death toll passes 100,000 as virus surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211125-germany-s-death-toll-from-covid-19-passes-100-000-as-virus-surges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100,000 people have died of Covid-19 in Germany since the start of the pandemic, a public health agency announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moving forces to Crimea in Ukraine buildup, analysts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2021/11/24/russia-s-military-build-up-near-ukraine-is-different-this-time-say-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What we see is a significant, large Russian military build-up. We see an unusual concentration of troops."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS LOWEST SINCE 1969...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/24/us-jobless-claims-fall-to-just-199000-the-lowest-level-since-1969.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial jobless claims totaled 199,000 last week, the lowest since 1969, easily beating Dow Jones estimates for 260,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungarian Tycoon Who Made Fortune in Porn Weighs Election Challenge to Orban...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/hungarian-tycoon-who-made-fortune-in-porn-mulls-taking-on-orban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungarian Tycoon Who Made Fortune in Porn Weighs Election Challenge to Orban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran nuke work mystery to global monitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/iranian-nuclear-work-is-becoming-a-black-box-to-global-monitors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian Nuclear Work Is Becoming a Mystery to Global Monitors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA law allows trans inmates in women's prisons. Now, female inmates suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/california-law-allows-transgender-inmates-in-womens-prisons-now-female-inmates-are-suing/article_5380a9d5-fd54-5fc4-abeb-daed3e5e1eef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — A woman's rights group is suing the state to overturn a new law that requires prisons to place transgender and gender nonbinary inmates in facilities that correspond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers clears up COVID toe claims by showing off bare, fractured toe...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nfl-packers-aaron-rodgers-covid-toe-actually-fractured-toe-injury-212044250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers was quick to show his legion-less toes and explain he has a fractured one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron gets fans ejected in return from suspension...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/24/returning-lebron-james-gets-pacers-fans-ejected-in-lakers-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James just can’t stop getting people ejected from games — this time two fans. The Lakers star — in his first game back from his one-game suspension for bloodying Pistons forward Isaiah Stewa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU to recommend passes last for nine months after full vaccination...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211125105135-iu7n4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/EU-TRAVEL (URGENT):EU to recommend COVID passes last for nine months after full vaccination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. lawmakers coming to Taiwan on military-focused trip...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211125101633-sc8h9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-USA/VISIT:U.S. lawmakers coming to Taiwan on military-focused trip -report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Psychedelic Retreats...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/25/the-rise-of-psychedelic-retreats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night in 2019, while strangers vomited around her, Lynn Cohen had a vision. After being tipped off by a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Pagans and Smartphone Witches: Where Tech Meets Mysticism...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/space-pagans-and-smartphone-witches-where-tech-meets-mysticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DORTMUND, Germany — “Let’s use smartphones and tarot cards to connect to spirits,” reads the writing on the wall, illuminated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Christmas markets warily open as COVID cases rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-travel-business-b5dd27e7e01b1c94f458662ef7768f62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The holiday tree is towering over the main square in this central German city, the chestnuts and sugared almonds are roasted, and kids are clambering aboard the merry-go-round just like they did before the pandemic .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia sending troops to Solomon Islands as unrest grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/australia-solomon-islands-honiara-a87d6b12d46642bf58c35aabd616ae0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia announced Thursday it is sending police, troops and diplomats to the Solomon Islands to help after anti-government demonstrators defied lockdown orders and took to the streets for a second day in violent protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden restarting 'Remain in Mexico' policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-restart-trump-remain-mexico-49d43ad0-41d3-4e09-8fe5-a90dd62b78ea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The program will force asylum seekers to stay in Mexico while awaiting court hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorean sentenced to death after students caught watching 'SQUID GAME'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rfa.org/english/news/korea/squidgame-11232021180155.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rfa.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locals say rich parents were able to bribe authorities to spare a student from punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to prioritize prosecuting violence on flights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-merrick-garland-c3b947f81b4281266f9f97eb279db3ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General Merrick Garland directed U.S. attorneys across the country to swiftly prioritize prosecution of federal crimes that happen on commercial flights as federal officials face a historic number of investigations into passenger behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New covid variant with 32 'horrific' mutations most evolved strain ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10238113/New-Botswana-variant-32-horrific-mutations-evolved-Covid-strain-EVER.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only 10 cases of the strain, which could be named 'Nu', have been detected so far but it has been spotted in Botswana, South Africa and Hong Kong, suggesting it's more widespread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers' 'Covid toe' saga reaches new levels of weird...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/24/aaron-rodgers-covid-toe-saga-has-reached-new-levels-of-weird/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers’ foot injury has reached new heights of weirdness. After rumors floated around the internet that Rodgers’ mysterious toe injury was a symptom of his COVID diagnosis, the P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Investigation Enters Crucial Phase as Prosecutor's Term Nears End...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/trump-investigation-enters-crucial-phase-as-prosecutors-term-nears-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long-running criminal investigation into Donald J. Trump and his family business is reaching a critical phase as Cyrus R. Vance Jr.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Spent Final Days In Fear of MS-13, Struggling With Constipation...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dgb78/jeffrey-epstein-spent-final-days-in-fear-of-ms-13-struggling-with-constipation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bureau of Prisons records described the infamous abuser as "optimistic" and "psychologically stable," and not a risk to himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typewriters Making Big Comeback; 'Busiest In 41 Years'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/23/cambridge-typewriter-arlington-business-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of people are yearning for life to be more simple. That has made a low tech machine wildly popular again: the typewriter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquitted and in demand, Kyle ponders what's next...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kyle-rittenhouse-donald-trump-entertainment-tucker-carlson-mar-a-lago-a852da724d4e06438da0cef6d02fc8f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — When he was acquitted of murder in shootings during unrest in Wisconsin, Kyle Rittenhouse went from staring at possible life behind bars to red-hot star of the right: an exclusive interview with Tucker Carlson and a visit with Donald Trump at Mar-a-Lago capped by a photo of both men smiling and snapping a thumbs-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortions inching up after decades of decline...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-8fe14b7608c105c67c1d1ee1021423b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. abortions appear to be inching up after a long decline, though officials are cautious about calling it an upward trend because a government report issued Wednesday is incomplete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military will help treat Michigan patients amid surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-detroit-veterans-gretchen-whitmer-667a8fa4437d330af8a178437739636f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — The federal government will send 44 military medical personnel to Michigan to help beleaguered hospitals treat COVID-19 patients amid a fourth surge that is the worst in the country, state health officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden's first female prime minister resigns hours after appointment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/swedens-first-female-prime-minister-resigns-hours-appointment-rcna6628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden's first female prime minister Magdalena Andersson resigned on her first day of the job on Wednesday after suffering a budget defeat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Apache' Artist Faked Native Heritage to Sell His Work, Feds Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/apache-artist-faked-native-heritage-to-sell-his-work-feds-say/ar-AAR5KAI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO in Fight For Survival...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/hbo-book-tinderbox-game-of-thrones-lovecraft-country-att-james-miller-interview-1234879610/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOILER ALERT: This post contain details about James Andrew Miller’s book Tinderbox, an oral history of HBO, which was published today.  On the eve of yet another corporate reframing, HBO has…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says changing definition of fully vaxxed to include boosters on table...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/582962-fauci-says-changing-definition-of-fully-vaccinated-to-include-boosters-is</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top infectious diseases expert Anthony Fauci said changing the definition of what</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Daily Power Walk Wards Off Alzheimer's, Slows Mental Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/physical-activity-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have found that physical activity dampens inflammation in the brain, protecting against mental decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruel or cute? Monkey jockey show at Florida county fair sparks outcry from animal activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/cruel-or-cute-monkey-jockey-show-at-florida-county-fair-sparks-outcry-from-animal-activists/article_fe49534a-4474-57c2-82b7-1f862d6525d5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARGATE, Fla. —These jockeys weigh only 6 pounds and they’re not riding horses — they’re riding dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany mulls full lockdown, shot mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/582954-germany-mulls-full-lockdown-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German officials are mulling the possibility of enacting stricter coronavirus restrictions across the country amid a surge in daily infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans moving less than ever...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/582904-americans-moving-less-than-ever-before</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer Americans are moving to new homes than at any time since the government began keeping track, as demographic trends collide with a hot housing market in which prices are rising over lack of supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Public Being Primed for War...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/will-putin-invade-ukraine-russians-are-being-told-to-get-used-to-the-idea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin’s propaganda campaign at home is getting people ready for a ‘reluctant’ move into Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Pandemic Star Loses Some Luster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/11/vermont-covid-19-coronavirus-surge/620792/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont’s COVID-19 surge could point the way toward an uncertain endemic future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON: 82-Year-Old Motorist Surrounded, Assaulted By Gang Of 40 Dirt Bike Riders...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/24/brookline-man-attacked-dirt-bike-atvs-boston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 82-year-old man was surrounded and assaulted by a group of people riding dirt bikes and ATVs in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz frontrunner in PA Senate race?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/dr-oz-equipped-to-fill-void-in-pennsylvania-senate-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity surgeon Mehmet Oz is poised to shake up the Pennsylvania Senate race, bolstered by a vast personal fortune to invest in a 2022 campaign and enviable poll numbers that suggest the Republican would be an immediate front-runner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rittenhouse Meets With Trump at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rittenhouse-mar-a-lago-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president revealed the meeting himself during an interview with Fox News' Sean Hannity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden heir? Buttigieg presidential buzz has penetrated White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/24/pete-buttigieg-presidential-buzz-white-house-523281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 39, he is the most recognizable and powerful transportation secretary in modern memory. And he wants you to believe his eye isn’t on the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for ET looks at nearest galactic neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/search-extraterrestrial-life-going-look-nearest-galactic-neighbor-rcna6313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are starting to look for life in our galactic backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havana Syndrome Hits FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fbi-acknowledges-agents-may-havana-syndrome-symptoms-rcna6504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an internal email, the FBI told a former agent reporting symptoms of Havana syndrome that there were "no medical programs in place" to help him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to keep borders closed another five months...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/582938-new-zealand-planning-to-keep-borders-closed-for-another-five-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's borders will remain closed to most international travelers over the next five months as the country takes precautions to fight the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy to restrict access of unjabbed to indoor venues...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211124132922-751o9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-CURBS (PIX):Italy to restrict access of unvaccinated to indoor venues - sources</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
