<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump Castigates Mueller Investigation as 'Disgrace to Nation'; Probe 'Total Mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-castigates-mueller-investigation-as-disgrace-to-nation-says-probe-is-total-mess-1542292248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump asserted that special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election is in complete disarray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMCAST fires employee who is allegedly 'Proud Boys' member...</title>
      <link>https://www.phillymag.com/news/2018/11/14/comcast-fires-proud-boys-employee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.phillymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The YSL Documentary Pierre Berge Did Not Want Anyone to See...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/fashion/yves-saint-laurent-celebration-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Bergé, the partner of Yves Saint Laurent, suppressed the film for years, but it is finally reaching theaters this month. Here’s what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA restricts sales of most flavored e-cigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/fda-restricts-most-flavored-e-cigarette-sales-pursues-menthol-ban.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Food and Drug Administration Commissioner Scott Gottlieb outlined a slew of policies, including restrictions on sales of flavored e-cigarettes, and essentially threatened to pull products from the market if manufacturers do not follow them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands without power...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/15/winter-storm-moves-midwest-east-coast-bringing-power-outages-school-closings/2009881002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pre-winter storm is blamed for five deaths. It's also leaving a trail of closed schools, traffic headaches and power outages across much of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why Are Young People Having So Little Sex?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2018/12/the-sex-recession/573949/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the easing of taboos and the rise of hookup apps, Americans are in the midst of a sex recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Burton's Live-Action 'DUMBO' Trailer Introduces Rest of Circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/dumbo-trailer-disney-releases-new-glimpse-tim-burton-movie-1161378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though plot details are being kept closely under wraps, early descriptions of the film suggest that it's following some plot points of the original.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE SCENARIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Dump-May-Approve-her-plan-Some-scenarios-for-13394680.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - Theresa May's premiership has been declared dead before. After her election losses last year, the British Prime Minister appeared to be on the brink of resigning. As she left 10 Downing Street on Thursday morning, members of her own party once again wondered: How long can she last? In the early morning hours, several British ministers resigned over May's deal to leave the European Union, which was released on Wednesday. Theresa May likely expected some resignations, but one came unexpectedly: Dominic Raab, her second Brexit minister. With the official who negotiated May's Brexit deal writing that he "cannot support the proposed deal," the British government was suddenly thrown into jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ARGUES: CAN BAN ALL REPORTERS FROM WHITE HOUSE!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/white-house-trump-has-broad-discretion-to-regulate-journalists-access-989916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'If the president wants to exclude all reporters from the White House grounds, he has the authority to do that,' a lawyer for the administration said during a hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana breaks records...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwltv.com/article/weather/parts-of-louisiana-breaks-records-with-early-snow/289-614431369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists say Wednesday's snowfall of as much as a half-inch across northeastern Louisiana broke the previous record set on Nov. 24, 1950.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Will Behead Khashoggi Killers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6392951/Jamal-Khashoggis-accused-killers-face-death-penalty-Saudi-prosecutor-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's public prosecutor is seeking the death penalty against five suspects the regime accuses of murdering journalist Jamal Khashoggi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The drag queen Eagle Scout who dances on mountaintops...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/14/pattie-gonia-drag-queen-mountaineer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balancing on cliffs in 6in heels, the ‘world’s first backpacking queen’ amassed 30,000 Instagram followers in a month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUP!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/politics/742629/theresa-may-brexit-statement-parliament-resignations-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Database To Use Loyalty Rewards To Identify Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-14/national-facial-recognition-database-use-loyalty-rewards-identify-american-shoppers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 million in path...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/14/winter-storm-roar-deep-south-new-england/2002785002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deadly winter storm will bring a messy mix of snow, sleet and freezing rain to portions of the central and eastern U.S. over the next two days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN: Money-making hypocrisy laughable...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/michelle-obamas-money-making-hypocrisy-is-laughable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — To read the worshipful press coverage you’d never know that, for Democrats, the unthinkable has happened: Michelle Obama has revealed herself as just another guru for sale. On Tuesday nig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI CAN FAKE FINGERPRINT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/15/fake-fingerprints-can-imitate-real-fingerprints-in-biometric-systems-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeepMasterPrints created by a machine learning technique have error rate of only one in five</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER ON CARIBBEAN CRUISE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6390117/Husband-arrested-Aruba-choking-wife-throwing-cruise-ship-severing-leg.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American man was hauled off the Royal Princess cruise ship by investigators in Aruba on Wednesday morning on suspicion of killing the 52-year-old woman. They had departed from Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norovirus outbreak at shelter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/norovirus-outbreak-confirmed-at-california-wildfire-shelter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say there has been an outbreak of norovirus at a shelter housing people who evacuated their homes to escape the massive wildfire in Northern California. Butte County public health spokesw…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm animals may soon get new features through gene editing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f628e7c65c794995b19977b7c1cdc10c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKFIELD, N.Y. (AP) — Cows that can withstand hotter temperatures. Cows born without pesky horns. Pigs that never reach puberty. A company wants to alter farm animals by adding and subtracting genetic traits in a lab. It sounds like science fiction, but Recombinetics sees opportunity for its technology in the livestock industry. But first, it needs to convince regulators that gene-edited animals are no different than conventionally bred ones. To make the technology appealing and to ease any fears that it may be creating Franken-animals, Recombinetics isn't starting with productivity. Instead, it's introducing gene-edited traits as a way to ease animal suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadlines looming in pivotal, rancorous Florida recounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/058c5f727bab45be9372110fbba9c07a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida's bumpy election recount reaches a pivotal point Thursday as most counties across the state complete reviews that could determine the next senator and governor in one of America's top political battlegrounds. Barring a dramatic last minute court-mandated extension, Florida counties face a 3 p.m. deadline to wrap up their machine recounts. Some counties, such as the Democratic stronghold of Palm Beach County, have warned that they may not be able to make the deadline. Lawsuits that could spur further delays are still swirling, including one filed by U.S. Sen. Bill Nelson and Democrats that seeks to set aside the looming deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUTER HELL: Transit riders, drivers brace for influx of AMAZON employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/transit-riders-drivers-brace-influx-060126549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commuters beware: New York and Washington's clogged streets and creaky subway systems are about to feel more pain as 50,000 more people descend on the two metro areas where Amazon will open new headquarters. An expansion of that scope in a city such as New York — where the regional subway, bus and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record tick diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/record-number-of-tickborne-diseases-lyme-disease-reported-in-us-2017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the CDC shows that tickborne diseases like Lyme and Rocky Mountain spotted fever continue to rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSURGENTS SEEK FEMALE</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/416836-insurgents-seek-female-challenger-to-replace-pelosi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anti-Pelosi insurgents are coalescing around a new strategy in their quest to deny Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) the Speaker's gavel: recruit a woman to run against her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The looming threat to Trump boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/15/trump-economy-federal-reserve-tax-cuts-deficit-trade-967501</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sugar high — from tax cuts and other stimulus — is expected to wear off in the coming year, constricting economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia to Seek Death Penalty for Khashoggi Killers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/saudi-prosecutor-seeks-death-penalty-in-jamal-khashoggi-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death penalty sought for five out of 11 suspects charged with the journalist’s murder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meal of 50 Courses Over 6 Hours. Future of Dining?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/a-meal-of-50-courses-over-6-hours-is-this-the-future-of-dining#gs.tH0Yoo8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Meal of 50 Courses Over 6 Hours. Is This the Future of Dining?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rest easy: No link between insomnia and early death...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/no-link-between-insomnia-and-early-death-according-to-largest-study-r577335n9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is one less thing to worry about in the small hours. There is no link between insomnia and an early death, according to the largest study of its kind. The analysis of 37 million people found...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Supervolcano Headed For 'Large Volume Eruption'; Magma Building...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/campi-flegrei-magma-building-beneath-dangerous-supervolcano-could-signal-huge-1213424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
POUND PLUNGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-46219038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sterling loses about 1% against both dollar and the euro after Dominic Raab and Esther McVey quit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181115103419-avfed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-British PM May suffers severe blow over Brexit as ministers quit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginkgo Supplement Was Ginkgo-Free, Watchdog Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ginkgo-supplement-was-ginkgo-free-u-s-watchdog-finds-1542239276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two dietary supplements promoted as improving memory using Ginkgo biloba contained either none of the ingredient or a lower amount than advertised, a federal watchdog said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>68% of Americans quit or taken break from socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/bailey-richardson-decided-to-quit-instagram-this-year-she-also-helped-create-the-social-media-app-1947551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the evening of Sept. 26, Bailey Richardson logged in to Instagram for the last time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MORE GAVEL?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/pelosi-faces-daunting-challenge-in-speakers-bid-as-democratic-foes-stand-firm/2018/11/14/29c1e018-e83a-11e8-a939-9469f1166f9d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an electoral year marked by a record number of women joining the House, incoming female Democrats may help decide Nancy Pelosi’s fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lawyers, CNN square off in federal court in Jim Acosta case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/media/cnn-trump-lawsuit-hearing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first hearing in CNN and Jim Acosta's federal lawsuit against President Trump and several top White House aides ended with the judge saying that he would rule on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell Says Fed Deserves Credit for Economic Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/powell-credits-fed-policy-for-the-us-economy-being-in-a-good-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell expressed confidence in U.S. economic strength Wednesday and said markets will have to get used to the idea that the central bank could raise rates at any time starting in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Sees Uptick In Travelers Packing Turkeys Into Bags...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/tsa-expecting-record-setting-crowds-during-thanksgiving-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines and the TSA are not just expecting big crowds, but record setting crowds during this year's Thanksgiving travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI ON THE BRINK?	</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pelosi-challenges-unhappy-dems-block-her-bid-speaker-175012347--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As a steadfast Rep. Nancy Pelosi all but dared potential rivals for the gavel to come forward, a group of restive House Democrats vowed Wednesday to produce enough votes to block her from becoming the House's new speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earliest Houston snowfall ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/snow-vember-the-earliest-houston-snowfall-ever-just-happened/285-614153347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your eyes didn't deceive you -- it snowed in Houston today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-breathing premature baby revived by police officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/11/14/non-breathing-premature-born-boy-revived-by-oakland-police-officer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oakland police officer is being credited with saving the life of an infant boy, who he revived when the child stopped breathing after being born prematurely inside a car Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant sues AMERICAN AIRLINES, says she was dragged down aisle mid-flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/american-airlines-flight-attendant-suing-scarf-assault-drag-down-aisle-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight attendant is suing the Fort Worth, Texas-based airline over a 2016 altercation with another crew member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE wants virtual assistant in every room of house...</title>
      <link>http://www.weny.com/story/39479577/google-wants-its-virtual-assistant-in-every-room-of-your-house </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Heather Kelly, CNN Business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold San Antonio 'shatters' 102-year-old record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/weather/article/Icy-San-Antonio-weather-shatters-102-year-old-13391345.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Antonio reached a low of 23 degrees at the International Airport this morning, which ties for the fourth coldest November low temperature on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK TURNS BEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-bellwether-for-technology-stocks-falls-into-a-bear-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple dipped into a bear market on Wednesday as shares added to a 20 percent decline from recent all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 Buses with 900 More Near Border... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/14/22-buses-with-900-caravan-migrants-nears-u-s-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 900 Central Americans in 22 buses arrived in the northern border state of Sonora, escorted by state and federal police on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast, South brace for winter storm...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-11-14-winter-storm-avery-snow-ice-east-midwest-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With cold air in place, a wintry mess is moving in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flake vows to oppose judges unless Mueller protection bill gets vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/28c5f8d772fd4b3097e152c025336fd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Republican Sen. Jeff Flake said Wednesday that he won't vote to confirm judicial nominees unless GOP leaders hold a vote on legislation to protect special counsel Robert Mueller from being fired. Flake of Arizona and Democratic Sen. Chris Coons of Delaware went to the Senate floor on Wednesday and tried to bring the legislation up for a vote. But Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell objected. McConnell has said that the legislation is unnecessary because he believes Mueller won't be fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE downgraded, more iPhone estimates cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-gets-downgraded-more-iphone-estimates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guggenheim downgraded Apple to neutral from buy and removed its prior $245 price target. UBS cut its 12-month price target on Apple to $225 from $240 and lowered iPhone unit sales estimates for the current quarter to 73.5 million from 75 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/michael-avenatti-denies-alleged-domestic-violence-ive-never-been-physically-abusive-in-my-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVENATTI ARRESTED FOR DOMESTIC VIOLENCE...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/14/official-michael-avenatti-in-los-angeles-police-custody-on-domestic-violence-allegation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti, who skyrocketed to fame as a critic of President Donald Trump and the lawyer for porn actress Stormy Daniels, was released on bail after being arrested Wednesday and booked on a felony domestic violence charge, Los Angeles police said. The victim in the case had visible injuries, according to Officer Tony Im, a police spokesman. But Avenatti slammed the allegation as "completely bogus" in a statement released by his law firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She hit me first!'</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/14/michael-avenatti-arrested-domestic-violence-stormy-daniels-attorney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti was arrested for felony domestic violence against a woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crypto civil war' slams bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/bkcm-brian-kelly-crypto-civil-war-slams-bitcoin-but-not-for-long.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin had been coasting in recent months on fairly low volatility until "things exploded," says the cryptocurrency fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic bishops leave conference without acting on abuse reforms...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/catholic-bishops-baltimore-sex-abuse-cardinal-theodore-mccarrick-20181114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the prospect of leaving their most closely watched gathering in years with no consensus response to the sex abuse crisis that has gripped their church since summer, the nation's Catholic bishops pushed Wednesday for something – anything – they might approve to show they were taking the problem seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER ON CRUISE SHIP SAILING IN CARIBBEAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2018/11/14/princess-cruises-woman-dies-fall-ship-royal-princess/2001881002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American woman aboard a Princess Cruises ship died Tuesday in what authorities are treating as a possible murder case, according to several news outlets in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBC votes no confidence in DNC Perez...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/congressional-black-caucus-tom-perez-991270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedric Richmond said members “felt that the DNC pitted them against their constituents.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Thanksgiving nears, mystery of drug-resistant Salmonella in turkey persists...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/as-thanksgiving-nears-regulators-food-processors-grapple-with-ongoing-salmonella-threat-in-turkey/500506282/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota has reported 17 cases, the most of any state. With Thanksgiving a week away, federal officials aren't telling consumers to stop eating turkey, but they are stressing the importance of proper handling and cooking techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock-Market Supercomputer to Launch With Glitches...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stock-market-supercomputer-to-launch-with-glitches-1542236446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A data warehouse created to track all U.S. stock market orders is expected to launch on Thursday with limited functionality because the contractor in charge of it hasn’t been able to make it reliably searchable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Dems 'Dog Whistle' Tactics Against Clyburn...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article221666375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after Rep. Jim Clyburn, D-South Carolina, accused detractors of using racially-motivated “dog whistle” tactics to undermine his bid to be House majority whip, Rep. Steny Hoyer, D-Maryland, came to his defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi battle for Speakership votes...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-pelosi-speaker-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi is whipping votes to try to regain the gavel as House speaker. More than a dozen Democrats have come out against her, and the result remains uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Filing confirms investigation will extend into next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-isnt-done-former-trump-campaign-aide-gates-222015853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Robert Mueller isn't done with former Trump campaign aide Rick Gates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafty crook fished $400K  out of PO boxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/crafty-crook-fished-400k-in-checks-out-of-postal-boxes-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queens is a great spot to go fishing — for checks, that is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putino MILITARY CHURCH to bolster patriotism, spirituality...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1045323/russia-news-military-church-vladimir-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has unveiled plans to build a military church as Moscow seeks to reinforce the value of “patriotism, love, and devotion to our Motherland” into troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service loss TRIPLES as package deliveries rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-postal-service-results/u-s-postal-service-loss-triples-even-as-package-deliveries-rise-idUSKCN1NJ2HS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Postal Service lost almost $4 billion in 2018 even as package deliverie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'War on Terror' price tag to top $6,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2018/11/14/price-tag-of-the-war-on-terror-will-top-6-trillion-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The figure is several times higher than official Pentagon reports on war spending because it includes VA benefits and other related expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidance overhaul on college sex assault gives new rights to accused...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-betsy-devos-college-sexual-assaults-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education Secretary Betsy DeVos is set to release a sweeping overhaul of how colleges and universities must handle allegations of sexual assault and harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. says defendant in political fundraiser hacking case has diplomatic immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/u-s-says-defendant-elliott-broidy-hacking-case-has-diplomatic-n935456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-diplomat accused of helping steal and distribute GOP fundraiser Elliot Broidy's emails is entitled to immunity, the U.S. government tells NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER loses $1 Billion, bookings slow...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-posts-1-billion-loss-210213496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber Technologies Inc said on Wednesday that growth in bookings for its ride-hailing and delivery services rose 6 percent in the latest quarter, the third quarter in a row that growth has remained in the single digits after double-digit growth for all of last year. As a private company, Uber is not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorite crater bigger than Paris found under Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/meteorite-crater-meteor-greenland-ice-sheet-hiawatha-glacier-scientists-a8633826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 contenders say Republicans 'stealing' Georgia race...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/2020-democratic-contenders-georgia-gop-stealing-governors-race-abrams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two potential 2020 Democratic White House contenders are accusing Georgia Republicans of stealing the governor's race from Democrat Stacey Abrams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delay, Deny and Deflect: Inside FACEBOOK's Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/technology/facebook-data-russia-election-racism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian meddling, data sharing, hate speech — the social network faced one scandal after another. This is how Mark Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg responded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES tool warns if articles quote too many men...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/nov/14/financial-times-tool-warns-if-articles-quote-too-many-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paper develops bot in attempt to force writers to look to include more expert women in pieces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER NYC cab driver deep in debt kills self...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/another-nyc-cab-driver-deep-in-debt-kills-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another debt-burdened New York City cabbie has committed suicide — the eighth for-hire driver to kill himself in the past year, Taxi and Limousine Commission officials confirmed on Wednesday.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsa paying $10,000 just to move there...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-us-city-is-paying-people-more-than-10000-just-to-move-there-2018-11-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The package for newcomers to this Oklahoma city includes a free membership at a co-working space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Staggering' raccoons acting rabid just drunk, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/article221652130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two raccoons in Milton, West Virginia, appear to have gotten drunk on crab apples, the Police Department said. One of the creatures is named Dallas. People thought they had rabies, but they’re not rabid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH:  44 dogs in freezers, 130 more living in squalor...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/pets-animals/44-dogs-found-in-freezers-130-more-living-in-filth-in-nj-home/4688017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey State Police have arrested a 65-year-old woman after they say dozens of dogs were found dead in freezers and more than 100 more living in filth inside her home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Looters Arrested For Stealing Motor Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221651485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Butte County Sheriff’s Office has reported six arrests this week relating to incidents in areas under mandatory evacuation orders due to the Camp Fire, with suspected crimes ranging from drug possession to looting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ:  Mueller Probes Possible Witness Intimidation by Roger Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-probes-possible-witness-intimidation-by-roger-stone-1542222284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller’s office is exploring whether longtime Trump adviser Roger Stone tried to intimidate and discredit a witness who is contradicting Mr. Stone’s version of events about his contacts with WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls Acosta 'Bad For Country'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/14/trump-cnn-lawsuit-bad-for-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We’ll see how the court rules'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden, Bernie lead early primary states...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/democrats-not-ready-hillary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Likely Democratic voters in primary states are not eager for a third White House run by Hillary Clinton, according to a new poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super-Earth' discovered orbiting Sun's nearest star...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/super-earth-discovered-orbiting-suns-nearest-star-180125151.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "super-Earth" has been discovered orbiting the closest single star to our Sun, scientists said Wednesday in a breakthrough that could shine a light on Earth's nearest planetary neighbours. Astronomers studied Barnard's Star, a red dwarf just six light years away -- practically in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neanderthal life not especially risky, skull analysis shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/neanderthal-life-not-especially-risky-skull-analysis-shows-180255654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Life as a Neanderthal was no picnic, but a new analysis says it was no more dangerous than what our own species faced in ancient times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Best US Airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-best-of-the-biggest-u-s-airports-1542204004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first WSJ U.S. airport rankings uses 15 metrics to decide which of the 20 largest airports treat travelers better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Claims Fires Are Retribution, Vows More...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-group-claims-california-wildfires-are-retribution-vows-you-will-see-more-fires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terror group has previously suggested both wildland and commercial or residential arson as an attack tactic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Collect Record Taxes in October...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/feds-collect-record-taxes-october-still-run-100b-deficit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Paul Ryan, Sept. 6, 2018. (Getty Images/Mark Wilson)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious purple glow lights up night sky in Eastern Wash...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/mysterious-purple-glow-lights-up-eastern-wash-night-sky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINLEY, Wash. - It looked like something out of The X-Files - a pink and purple glow filled the night sky near the Tri-Cities in Eastern Washington. Was it caused by a UFO? Or emissions from the Hanford nuclear facility? Or a top-secret military experiment? â€œWe thought maybe the bar that's out there was having some kind of party,â€� said local resident Alisha Dickenson. Purple lights illuminated the sky Sunday night, but it wasn't from a party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN JUMPS BORDER FENCE; NO TROOPS...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2018/11/13/video-shows-group-climbing-on-border-fence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People on the Mexican side of the border could be seen climbing the fence near Friendship Park Tuesday afternoon after part of the Central American migrant caravan arrived in Tijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY'S BREXIT D-DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/13/theresa-may-can-no-longer-delay-her-bunfight-with-tory-brexiters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May hopes to secure support for the ‘product’, but tougher challenges await</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN WHO COULD BE CHIEF</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/13/nick-ayers-replace-john-kelly-987654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Ayers, Pence’s chief of staff, was initially seen as a potential Kelly successor this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beekeeper therapist uses venom to heal patients...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181113201908-97opo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EGYPT-HEALTH/BEES (TV, PIX):Beekeeper therapist uses venom to heal his patients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How GOOGLEAMAZON Got Away with Not Being Regulated...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/book-excerpt-curse-of-bigness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet companies used to grow big and die—fast. But now a few of them are huge and entrenched, because regulators didn't foresee their dominance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Evacuation fatigue'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/13/california-wildfires-evacuation-fatigue-paradise-camp-danger </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How  World's First Male Supermodel Escaped Abusive Doomsday Cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-the-worlds-first-male-supermodel-escaped-an-abusive-doomsday-cult</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hoyt Richards was dubbed the “world’s first male supermodel,” pulling in a minimum of $15,000 a day. But little did the world know that he was deeply involved in a terrifying cult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Police Escort 400 from Migrant Caravan to U.S. Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/13/watch-mexican-police-escort-400-from-migrant-caravan-to-u-s-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A caravan of nearly 400 migrants in eight buses arrived in Sonora, escorted by state and federal police on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Men with beards more attractive...</title>
      <link>https://fox8.com/2018/11/14/study-men-with-beards-are-more-attractive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study shows men who have full beards are more attractive than men who are clean-shaven. The study was published in the Journal of Evolutionary Biology. Researched asked more than 8,500 women to rate men on their attractiveness as a long-term romantic partner, Yahoo News reported. Here's how the facial hair rated:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ Troops Converge...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/1000-troops-converge-on-border-awaiting-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 troops are on the U.S. Mexico border preparing for the possible arrival of a migrant caravan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parties barrel toward clash over border wall... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/13/government-shut-down-congress-mueller-border-wall-trump-988159</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the two sides can't come to terms on special counsel Mueller and the border wall, part of the government will shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great for ratings!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/13/donald-trump-jim-acosta-222463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fakest news in town is that the president is mad at a preening TV reporter who’s great for ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O:  Yes, I'm black...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-michelle-obama-united-center-chicago-20181113-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long before former first lady Michelle Obama was to take the stage at United Center on Tuesday night to kick off her much-anticipated book tour, the crowds had gathered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX BACKS CNN IN ACOSTA LAWSUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fox-news-cnn-lawsuit-trump-jim-acosta-press-pass-81bc6dd3-4590-4f66-9197-6d1ff92676b6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We do support a free press, access and open exchanges for the American people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: ISIS Suggested Arson and Devastation of California...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-details-devastation-california-wildfires-caliphate-newsletter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terror group has encouraged followers to try arson as a terror tactic, yet has not taken credit for starting any of the blazes still under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>250+ CASES...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/officials-investigating-252-cases-polio-illness-afm/story?id=59163987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are now investigating 252 cases of possible acute flaccid myelitis (AFM) including 90 confirmed cases in 27 states, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>878,000 MILLIONAIRES ADDED IN YEAR </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/america-first-878-000-millionaires-added-in-last-12-months-trump-effect-relentless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The booming U.S. economy, jump started by the 2017 GOP tax cut, has created 878,000 more millionaires in just the last 12 months, according to an international wealth report from Credit Suisse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE:  Number of US citizens seeking asylum in Canada reaches record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/14/us-citizens-seeking-asylum-canada-increases-immigration-refugees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans, Haitians and Nigerians were the largest groups seeking asylum, spurred by fears they would be deported by the Trump administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIN!!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/return-of-moisture-to-aid-firefighting-efforts-in-californias-wildfire-disaster-next-week/70006616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA's secret 'truth serum' to bust terror plots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7736660/cia-truth-serum-drug-al-qaeda-911-suspects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE CIA contemplated giving Al-Qaeda terror suspects a “truth serum” to force them into revealing information about potential attacks, in the wake of 9/11. Newly declassified documents show interro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne's husband launches new anti-Trump group...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6389209/Kellyanne-Conways-husband-founds-new-group-anti-Trump-conservative-lawyers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missing from the mission statement of 'Checks and balances' is any mention of Conway's wife, who helmed Trump's White House campaign and is now one of his most trusted advisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob That Stalked Tucker Carlson Back On TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/14/smash-racism-dc-back-twitter-tucker-carlson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how they got around their suspension</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire death toll 48; Search for missing continues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2144d7d18c2144d09ce31eec69515441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — A message board at a shelter for the many people who fled California's deadliest wildfire is filled with photos of the missing, as well as pleas for any information about relatives and friends. "I hope you are okay," reads one hand written note on the board filled with white and yellow sheets of notebook paper. Another had a picture of a missing man: "If seen, please have him call." Authorities on Tuesday reported six more fatalities from the Northern California blaze, bringing the total number of dead so far to 48. They haven't disclosed the total number still missing, but earlier in the week that figure was more than 200.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polluting air more than 100 miles away...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/california-wildfires-fouling-air-100-miles/story?id=59162108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two massive California wildfires are creating bad air more than 100 miles away.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
