<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Socialism Boom: Emboldened Leftists Agitate for Radical Change...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywoods-socialism-reboot-1234982568/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chants are beginning in front of the Chateau Marmont. It’s the evening of June 25 and masked protesters are marching on the sidewalk outside the legendary Hollywood hangout, which has bee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK's $1.6 Billion Bid to 'Save Journalism': Secret Deals, Favored Partners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/inside-facebooks-1-6b-bid-to-save-journalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside Facebook's $1.6 billion bid to save journalism: Secret deals, favored partners but few actual details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMASK NYC?</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-councilman-wants-mask-mandate-reinstated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿With COVID-19 cases climbing in all 50 states, New York City Councilman Mark Levine, who chairs the Health Committee, is calling for the indoor mask mandate to be reinstated even for the vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leyna Bloom is SPORTS ILLUSTRATED SWIMSUIT first trans cover star...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/19/leyna-bloom-is-sports-illustrated-swims-first-transgender-cover-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The world is changing and people need to see the fact that, wow, this is the beginning of it,” she told us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti acting PM to step down amid post-assassination leadership dispute...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haitis-acting-prime-minister-step-140646239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti's acting Prime Minister Claude Joseph told the Washington Post on Monday that he will step down from the role, which had seen him serve as de facto leader of Haiti in the wake of President Jovenel Moïse's assassination earlier this month.Why it matters: Joseph's decision to step down, which he said was “for the good of the nation," may resolve the leadership crisis set off by Moïse's death.Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free.Joseph will be succeeded b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is aging disease? Treating it like one could be worth trillions, study says...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/life-culture/2021/07/13/is-aging-a-disease-treating-it-like-one-could-save-us-trillions-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investing in healthy aging — rather than fighting specific diseases — could have an economic value worth trillions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five people shot, including ambulance crew, in AZ attack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/563652-five-people-shot-including-ambulance-crew-in-arizona-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of attacks on paramedics, firefighters and police on Sunday left 5 people shot, several children missing and one person dead in Tucson, Ariz.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA spike hits alarming levels, with 10,000 infected in week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-county-coronavirus-spike-hits-120023795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County coronavirus spike hits alarming levels as the Delta variant hits the unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Levitating' hyperloop will travel 670mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3308608/hyperloop-commuters-cities-minutes-levitation-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HYPERLOOP systems will move as many people as a 30-lane highway between cities in minutes, according to Virgin Hyperloop’s chief. Speaking to Reuters on Monday, Josh Giegel said the upcoming …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tornado' of mosquitos blot out sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3309746/mosquitoes-swarm-in-east-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“TORNADOES” of sex-starved mosquitoes have blotted out the sun in east Russia as they gather for mating season. The swarm is one of the worst yet in the region. Fast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China threatens to nuke Japan if intervenes in Taiwan conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3308916/china-threatens-to-nuke-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA is threatening to NUKE Japan on the eve of the Olympics if it intervenes in conflict with Taiwan, it has been revealed in a new video. The communist republic said that it would declare “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Iran launched stealth missile boat?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/has-iran-launched-a-new-stealthy-missile-boat-674310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Iranian ship is one of several under construction that will be called the Shahed Soleimani class of stealth ships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS REBOUND SPOOKS STOCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/18/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks dropped aggressively on Monday amid concerns about a flare-up in Covid cases slowing economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drag Queens Navigating One of Most Dangerous Culture Wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvz5ed/the-drag-queens-navigating-one-of-europes-most-dangerous-culture-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drag scene in Hungary is popular and vibrant. But animosity whipped up by the nationalist government and a supportive press is taking its toll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths up 25% from two weeks ago; Cases rising in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/07/19/covid-vaccine-variant-mask-restrictions-hospitalizations/8008947002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More experts are calling for vaccinated people to mask up as COVID surges around the country. Live COVID news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branding the left: AOC makes push into political merch...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/branding-us-left-aoc-makes-push-into-political-merchandise-2021-07-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez became one of America's most prominent progressive Democrats with her calls to tax the wealthy and spend heavily to fight climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing buying up American farms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/19/china-buying-us-farms-foreign-purchase-499893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bipartisan pressure is building to stop foreign nationals from purchasing American farm operations and receiving taxpayer subsidies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Kristof Exploring Run for Oregon Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.wweek.com/news/state/2021/07/18/new-york-times-columnist-nicholas-kristof-is-exploring-a-run-for-oregon-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says successfully tested hypersonic missile praised by Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-conducts-ship-based-hypersonic-missile-test-ifax-cites-defence-ministry-2021-07-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia said on Monday it had successfully tested a Tsirkon(Zircon) hypersonic cruise missile, a weapon President Vladimir Putin has touted as part of a new generation of missile systems without equal in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiet and secretive BLUE ORIGIN hopes to start new chapter with flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/quiet-and-secretive-blue-origin-hopes-to-start-new-chapter-with-jeff-bezos-s-space-flight/ar-AAMiims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos has said Blue Origin is "the most important work I am doing." Tuesday, he'll launch to space on the company's New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Agrees With Critics of 'Joyrides'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jeff-bezos-agrees-with-critics-of-billionaire-joyrides-to-space-theyre-largely-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos defended himself from critics who argue that billionaire tycoons would be better off focusing on Earth's problems, rather than traveling to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMORROW: SPACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9796123/Jeff-Bezos-fly-space-TOMORROW-Blue-Origin-New-Shepherd-rocket.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This will be the first human flight launched by Jeff Bezos owned space company, Blue Origin, and will take place out of their spaceport Launch Site One in Van Horn, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador 'House of Horrors' killings shock nation numbed to violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210719094736-vc7av</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL SALVADOR-VIOLENCE/ (PIX):El Salvador 'House of Horrors' killings shock nation numbed to violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive and mysterious, 100-pound fish washes ashore. Scientists hope to learn secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/massive-and-mysterious-a-100-pound-fish-washed-ashore-scientists-hope-to-learn-its-secrets/ar-AAMiDBz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Seaside Aquarium official said the 3½-foot, 100-pound opah is the first she’s seen on local beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US GYMNAST POSITIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9802439/US-womens-gymnast-tests-positive-Covid-training-four-days-Tokyo-opening-ceremony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of the US women's gymnastics team tested positive for the coronavirus while training for the 2021 Olympics in Narita, 35 miles east of Tokyo. She is between the ages of 10 and 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales of Vegan Bacon on Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/as-more-vegan-bacon-brands-hit-the-market-sales-are-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of Vegan Bacon Are On the Rise as More Brands Hit the Market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Challenges Chinese Warship in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/philippines-challenges-chinese-warship-in-south-china-sea-083314946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philippines Coast Guard said it drove away a Chinese warship in the South China Sea, in another sign of tension between the two nations in the disputed waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Allies Blame Chinese Govt for MICROSOFT Hack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/microsoft-exchange-hack-biden-china-d533f5361cbc3374fdea58d3fb059f35</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Monday blamed China for a hack of Microsoft Exchange email server software that compromised tens of thousands of computers around the world earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone, considered to be gold standard for security, shown to be vulnerable...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/07/19/apple-iphone-nso/?itid=hp_alert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An international investigation found 23 Apple devices that were successfully hacked. “Zero-click” attacks, as they are called within the surveillance industry, can work on even the newest generations of iPhones, even after years of effort in which Apple attempted to close the door against unauthorized surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden transfers first detainee from Gitmo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/biden-administration-transfers-its-first-detainee-guant-namo-bay-n1274333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transfer comes after NBC News reported in June that President Joe Biden had quietly begun efforts to close the detention facility at the U.S. enclave on the southeast coast of Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Trump Org Money Man's Interview With Investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-the-trump-org-money-mans-interview-with-investigators/ar-AAMjmKK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff McConney, a high-ranking accountant at the Trump Organization, has reportedly already testified before the special grand jury in New York that yielded a criminal indictment against the company. But as prosecutors look at additional charges, never-before-seen testimony from McConney during an earlier civil case four years ago shows that while this Trump insider quickly acknowledges when the company runs afoul of the law, he does his best to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $8 Billion Question: Which Towns Will Cash In on Marijuana?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/19/the-8-billion-question-which-towns-will-cash-in-on-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational adult use of marijuana is now the law of the land in one of the most crowded corners of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID AT OLYMPIC VILLAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-tokyo-soccer-coronavirus-pandemic-1ae8177bef505404d4cc495fbc8b2c93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A third athlete at the Olympic Village in Tokyo has tested positive for COVID-19 with the Czech Republic team reporting the latest case Monday. Beach volleyball player Ondřej Perušič's opening game in seven days' time is now at risk after a PCR test confirmed his infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOYOTA PULLS ADS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-5eb0e254b9a0cac7ad57005677eebe66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Toyota won’t be airing any Olympic-themed advertisements on Japanese television during the Tokyo Games despite being one of the IOC’s top corporate sponsors. The extraordinary decision by the country’s top automaker underlines how polarizing the Games have become in Japan as COVID-19 infections rise ahead of Friday’s opening ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man faces 1st sentencing for felony in riot at US Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-government-and-politics-capitol-siege-sentencing-785d865e0be2bc912614821768cf95b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A Florida man who breached the U.S. Senate chamber carrying a Trump campaign flag is scheduled to become the first Jan. 6 rioter sentenced for a felony, in a hearing that will help set a benchmark for punishment in similar cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger as French protesters compare vaccines to Nazi horrors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-race-and-ethnicity-e3757c1c51abd7ce56473c455f6f880d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A French Holocaust survivor has denounced anti-vaccination protesters comparing themselves to Jews who were persecuted by Nazi Germany during World War II. French officials and anti-racism groups joined the 94-year-old in expressing indignation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia deports commentator Hopkins for quarantine boast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-business-health-arts-and-entertainment-australia-fed94e65c6012afce3a3b6ce20e14c0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Far-right British commentator Katie Hopkins was deported from Australia on Monday after she boasted on social media that she planned to breach the country's quarantine rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWISTED CANNES:  Movie where woman has sex with car takes Palme d'Or ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3303541/titane-sex-cars-cannes-film-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shock-fest Titane – a film about a woman having sex with cars – took home the top prize  Palme d’Or at Cannes last night. The news was revealed early at the closing ceremony in an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  20% of Americans believe microchips inside covid vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/omg/20-percent-of-americans-believe-microchips-are-inside-covid-19-vaccine-study-674272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;False content has been published on social media regarding the microchip theory, with many conspiracy theorists saying that COVID-19 is just a coverup to track people using the vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaotic scene after shots outside baseball stadium...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-baseball-mlb-washington-nationals-san-diego-padres-4ef44d26efc5499bcd96986c68e1a4ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the gunshots started to echo all around Nationals Park, San Diego Padres star shortstop Fernando Tatis Jr. quickly thought about the team's family members and friends in the seats. Tatis bolted from the bench down the left field line Saturday night, helped open a gate to the stands and began ushering a group back to the dugout to shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Jews visit contested holy site in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-jerusalem-b87218462ca854370b216798f62803a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Hundreds of Jewish pilgrims visited a contested Jerusalem holy site under heavy police guard on Sunday, shortly after Muslim worshippers briefly clashed with Israeli security forces at the flashpoint shrine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak uncovers global abuse of cyber-surveillance weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/18/revealed-leak-uncovers-global-abuse-of-cyber-surveillance-weapon-nso-group-pegasus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spyware sold to authoritarian regimes used to target activists, politicians and journalists, data suggests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>180 reporters identified...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/18/ft-editor-roula-khalaf-among-180-journalists-targeted-nso-spyware</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data leak and forensics suggest NSO’s surveillance tool used against journalists at some of world’s top media companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatters lie that innocent need not fear surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/jul/18/huge-data-leak-shatters-lie-innocent-need-not-fear-surveillance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our investigation shows how repressive regimes can buy and use the kind of spying tools Edward Snowden warned us about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiet and secretive BLUE ORIGIN hopes to start new chapter with  Bezos space flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/quiet-and-secretive-blue-origin-hopes-to-start-new-chapter-with-jeff-bezos-s-space-flight/ar-AAMiims?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos has said Blue Origin is "the most important work I am doing." Tuesday, he'll launch to space on the company's New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW NORMAL:  Real estate values have surged by 25% since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/the-new-real-estate-normal/ar-AAMir6k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the fracturing American economy, any property can inspire a bidding war — and shut some people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takeaways from 'Pegasus Project'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Takeaways-from-the-Pegasus-Project-16322652.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military-grade spyware leased by the Israeli firm NSO Group to governments for tracking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Responses from nations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Responses-from-countries-to-the-Pegasus-Project-16322662.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forbidden Stories, a Paris-based journalism nonprofit, and Amnesty International had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spyware sold to authoritarian regimes used to target activists, politicians and journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Private-Israeli-spyware-used-to-hack-cellphones-16322695.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military-grade spyware licensed by an Israeli firm to governments for tracking terrorists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak closes Boy Scouts camp, another hits retirement home...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article252863438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boy Scouts camp canceled its scheduled activities in response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys and Antifa clash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9799077/LAPD-orders-crowd-disperse-protests-transgender-rights-Koreatown-spa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles police arrested dozens of people during a transgender rights protest and fired non-lethal projectiles to disperse the unruly mob that turned violent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers seize ONLYFANS account to stream ISIS beheadings...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3303817/hackers-seized-onlyfans-model-account-isis-beheadings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ONLYFANS model’s account has been seized by hackers who are using it to stream “terrifying” ISIS beheadings. Tina Bean, 22, has lost almost all of her followers and has lost thousands of pounds …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Conservative pornstar' derails TURNING POINT USA's youth gathering...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/18/conservative-pornstar-derails-turning-point-usas-right-wing-youth-gathering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The adult entertainer Brandi Love was banned from a right-wing gathering after mounting pressure online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rebuffs DeSantis over CDC cruise rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/18/appeals-court-cdc-cruises-desantis-499987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11th Circuit's stay order puts on hold a courtroom victory that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis won last month.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
