<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN MARY in danger of sinking. Can it be saved?</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-06-01/queen-mary-could-capsize-without-urgent-repairs-report-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of court documents and inspection reports released last month reveal the extent of the Queen Mary’s disrepair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's greatest cardsharp reveals all...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/the-worlds-greatest-cardsharp-reveals-all/ar-AAKBf4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Vegas legend, Steve Forte is revered by magicians and gambling experts as the most skilled person ever to deal, shuffle and manipulate a deck of cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent pool 100ft above ground making people sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/viral/london-embassy-gardens-swimming-pool-b1857576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transparent swimming pool built more than 100ft above the ground is making people feel queasy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors Fear Bear-Themed Compound Will Be Next Ruby Ridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/neighbors-fear-bear-themed-compound-will-be-next-ruby-ridge/ar-AAKAD30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alt-right comedian’s plans for a remote patch of land in Idaho have terrified his neighbors, who fear it could become a hostile compound or mark the start of a new Ruby Ridge-style standoff. Comedian Owen Benjamin once had a moderately successful Hollywood career, landing roles in movies and TV shows and briefly becoming engaged to actress Christina Ricci. After moving to the right, he appeared on podcasts hosted by Joe Rogan, Steven Crowder,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Reportedly Telling People He Will Be Reinstated By August...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-is-reportedly-telling-people-he-will-be-reinstated-as-president-by-august/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump is reportedly telling people that he expects to get reinstated by August, according to New York Times reporter Maggie Haberman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living On Busy Road Could Trigger Parkinson's?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/living-on-busy-road-could-trigger-parkinsons-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In experiments on mice, exposure to ambient toxic particles were found to damage neurons that make dopamine, a hallmark of Parkinson's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Police Chief in Wyoming Lost War on Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-a-police-chief-in-wyoming-s-ranchlands-lost-her-war-on-drugs/ar-AAKzpKI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUERNSEY, Wyo. — It was a few days before New Year’s Eve 2019, and Terri VanDam, the chief of Guernsey, Wyo.’s three-person Police Department, had run out of options. For more than a year, Ms. VanDam and her sergeant, Misty Clevenger, had tried and failed to get to the bottom of the drug and alcohol problem in Guernsey, population 1,124. Methamphetamine use was rampant, and much of it was bought and sold right at the bars, they were told, but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close encounters: Dems, Republicans unified in taking UFOs seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/close-encounters-democrats-and-republicans-unified-in-taking-ufos-seriously/ar-AAKADYm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sightings — also known as Unidentified Aerial Phenomena, or UAPs, in official parlance — are having their moment in politics, and a bipartisan one at that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaken by virus, Americans try 'manifesting' positive result...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/shaken-by-covid-some-americans-try-manifesting-a-positive-result-01622511313 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: NATO war games; Russia to send troops west...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/31/us-nato-wage-war-games-europe-russia-send-troops-w/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and its NATO allies on Monday conducted a set of major war games across Europe, while Russia responded by announcing plans to send at least 20 new military units to its western border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian doctors protest 'yoga-beats-Covid' guru...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210601-indian-doctors-protest-yoga-beats-covid-guru</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian doctors protest 'yoga-beats-Covid' guru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tackled after running onto court at WIZARDS-76ERS game...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/556230-man-tackled-after-running-onto-court-at-wizards-76ers-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been banned from Capitol One Arena and could face charges after running onto the court during an NBA playoff game Monday night between the Washington Wizards and Philadelphia 76ers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Tensions Set to Rise as Inspectors Lay Bare Violations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-tension-set-rise-inspectors-095042101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A bleak assessment of Iran’s nuclear transparency cast a pall over months of arduous diplomacy aimed at restoring its atomic accord with world powers that has major implications for Middle Eastern security, global business and oil markets.Despite recent statements of optimism from Iranian and European officials, significant differences at the talks in Vienna remain over how to deal with Iranian enrichment advances and the removal of U.S. sanctions.On Tuesday, less than a day after International Atomic Energy Agency inspectors circulated two confidential reports in the Austrian capital that paint a far from rosy picture of Iran’s willingness to address concerns over its past and present nuclear activities, a top official in Tehran conceded that an agreement could take another two months.The IAEA’s conclusions circulated late Monday among diplomats in Vienna will feed into a parallel diplomatic track at an meeting next week, where the Persian Gulf nation could be subject to formal censure by the agency’s 35-nation board of governors.If Iran considers any condemnation to be especially harsh, the spat could introduce greater acrimony into the Vienna talks. They aim to reintroduce caps on Iran’s nuclear activities in exchange for relief from the sanctions imposed by former President Donald Trump, who all but collapsed the six-year-old accord by withdrawing U.S. participation.Ali Rabiei, spokesman for Iran’s government, said Tuesday that while there were “no obstacles” in the way to restoring the beleaguered agreement, President Hassan Rouhani may now need to use all the remaining time available to his administration to strike a deal.“We’re close to an understanding over principal, nuclear issues,” Rabiei told reporters in a televised news conference, adding “some differences such as Trump’s sanctions and Iran’s measures need to be worked out.”As a two-term president, Rouhani can’t contest Iran’s June 18 election. He’ll remain in office until early August but is widely expected to be succeeded by a conservative hardliner more hostile to the U.S. and the nuclear deal.IAEA Director General Rafael Mariano Grossi reported that Iran has continued to stonewall diplomats investigating decades-old traces of uranium found at undeclared sites, according to a copy of a 6-page document seen by Bloomberg.The Argentine diplomat’s suggestion that Iran could be providing incomplete information has potentially serious consequences. The entire international apparatus of rules that the IAEA enforces is based on verifying nations’ declared nuclear material and nuclear-related activities. Failures can result in referrals to the UN Security Council.“The lack of progress in clarifying the agency’s questions concerning the correctness and completeness of Iran’s safeguards declarations seriously affects the ability of the Agency to provide assurance of the peaceful nature of Iran’s nuclear program,” reads the document.Potentially more worrying, Iranian restrictions imposed on IAEA monitors are undercutting international safeguards, even as the country dramatically ramps up its nuclear activities. Monitors listed 15 areas in Iran where they can no longer do their job, including the verification of centrifuge machine shops and some parts of the uranium fuel cycle. Investigators no longer have daily access to key Iranian enrichment facilities at Fordow or Natanz.“The agency’s verification and monitoring activities have been affected as a result of Iran’s decision to stop the implementation of its nuclear-related commitments,” Grossi told diplomats in a second 13-page report.Historically, such conclusions would result in diplomatic censure of Iran in the form of an IAEA resolution. The country has been subject more than a dozen such motions since 2003, including the consequential 2006 referral to the Security Council that set off the subsequent waves of international sanctions that still linger.But with nuclear talks still in high gear and Iran’s election nearing, IAEA envoys may exercise more caution when they convene June 7. Iran had threatened to rip up a provisional monitoring arrangement if it faced censure at the last IAEA board meeting.Envoys will have to decide whether reconstituting intrusive nuclear inspections -- widely seen by world powers as the most important element of the 2015 nuclear deal -- requires diplomatic coercion or dialog.Success in Vienna could see significant quantities of Iranian oil flow into global markets, and ease tensions in the Persian Gulf that spiraled during the confrontation between the Trump administration and Tehran.(Adds Iranian spokesman in the second and sixth paragraphs,)More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Croatia yacht holidays in demand once again...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601103914-cgu99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CROATIA-LEISURE (TV, PIX): Escaping the crowds: Croatia yacht holidays in demand once again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow ready to stop 'unfriendly' foreign action...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531130429-gzqsb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-SECURITY/PATRUSHEV (URGENT):Russia says it is ready to use force to stop 'unfriendly' foreign action - Ifax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports human case of H10N3 bird flu, a possible first...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-bird-flu-flu-health-b5862e1d9892b25fdb470abf30432289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A man in eastern China has contracted what might be the world’s first human case of the H10N3 strain of bird flu, but the risk of large-scale spread is low, the government said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 years after Tulsa race massacre, Black residents await Biden, and reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210601-100-years-after-tulsa-race-massacre-black-residents-await-biden-and-reparations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;100 years after Tulsa race massacre, Black residents await Biden, and reparations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist tricks high-profile Republicans into retweeting pic of Lee Harvey Oswald...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/journalist-tricked-high-profile-republicans-013611320.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candace Owens claimed the portraits were photoshopped, despite Oswald being a former military member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osaka crisis throws light on stars' mental health and media 'voyeurism'...</title>
      <link>https://au.sports.yahoo.com/osaka-crisis-throws-light-stars-103642095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naomi Osaka's decision to withdraw from the French Open, after revealing her battle with depression and anxiety, has thrown the tournament into turmoil and cast a harsh light on the mental health of the sport's superstars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning ship covered beautiful beaches in plastic 'snow.' Now Sri Lanka faces environmental disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-burning-ship-covered-beautiful-beaches-in-plastic-e2-80-98snow-e2-80-99-now-sri-lanka-faces-an-environmental-disaster/ar-AAKADrb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists fear the plastic pellets could travel as far as the other side of Sri Lanka, killing wildlife and damaging sensitive ecosystems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He bashed police on FACEBOOK. Then chief threatened fake charges unless he deleted it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-bashed-a-police-chief-on-facebook-then-the-chief-threatened-fake-charges-unless-he-deleted-it-feds-say/ar-AAKAx5z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Hazleton Police Chief Brian Buglio was charged with threatening a man with fake criminal charges in retaliation for critical Facebook posts, federal prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Tech's Golden Child, APPLE Loses Luster as Scrutiny Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-01/apple-aapl-is-getting-the-same-big-tech-scrutiny-as-google-amazon-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressured over its App Store and its handling of customer data, Apple can no longer sidestep the criticism directed at peers like Amazon and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany lowers risk level...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601092401-onwi8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Germany lowers coronavirus risk level as cases ease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major rulings loom for Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601085129-r2jzo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/RULINGS (PIX):Major rulings including Obamacare loom for U.S. Supreme Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something Bothering You? Tell Woebot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/something-bothering-you-tell-it-to-woebot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I understand that you’re experiencing a relationship problem, is that right?” Yes. “Okay, I’m delighted that you want to work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World Ran Out of Everything...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/how-the-world-ran-out-of-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the story of how the modern world was constructed, Toyota stands out as the mastermind of a monumental advance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variants to be given Greek alphabet names to avoid stigma...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/01/covid-19-variants-to-be-given-greek-alphabet-names-to-avoid-stigma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO unveils new names for variants of concern to replace ones linked to where they were discovered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peru leads global mortality rate after adjusting Covid toll...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/peru-leads-global-mortality-rate-183952477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peru on Monday more than doubled its official coronavirus death toll, becoming the country with the highest Covid-19 mortality per capita anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In time for summer, Europe sees dramatic fall in cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-music-travel-premier-league-d4982700d81ae5a7cfc58c14a7d145eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — When Italy won the Eurovision Song Contest with an over-the-top glam-rock performance, the victory signaled more than just a psychological boost for one of the countries hardest hit by COVID-19: Held before a live, indoor audience of 3,500, the annual kitsch fest confirmed that Europe was returning to a semblance of normalcy that was unthinkable even a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correctional officers who slept while Epstein hanged himself planned to slam federal prison system at trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-mcc-epstein-suicide-correctional-officers-sleeping-20210531-mj2ifnsefzbj7g3zjltj7e747a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two federal correctional officers who neglected their duties while Jeffrey Epstein killed himself inside a troubled lower Manhattan jail planned to defend themselves as scapegoats for a deeply dysfunctional system had they gone on trial, sources told the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief slams Ted Cruz for claiming 'woke' policies turning military into 'pansies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/05/31/pentagon-chief-slams-ted-cruz-for-abetting-russia-and-china-with-claim-that-woke-policies-are-turning-army-into-pansies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin slammed Sen. Ted Cruz on Monday for accusing the Army of projecting an image of “pansies” because of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado man seriously injured by bear attack -- inside his home...</title>
      <link>https://www.coloradoan.com/story/news/2021/05/31/colorado-bear-attack-injures-man-near-steamboat-springs/5281453001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.coloradoan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man encountered a sow and two cubs in his garage in unincorporated Routt County near Steamboat Springs when we went to close the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  USA Covid cases near  low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/post-pandemic-40-percent-americans-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-day average for new COVID-19 cases has fallen to about 12,000 per day, numbers not seen since March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday still subdued by pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531205350-bzcmw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HOLIDAY/MEMORIALDAY (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Americans hit the road on Memorial Day holiday, a year after pandemic slammed travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat latest cyber victim as hackers hit top supplier...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meat-latest-cyber-victim-hackers-214130697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The world’s biggest meat supplier was the target of a cybersecurity attack Sunday in the latest threat to global food supply chains that have been rattled by the pandemic.JBS SA shut its North American and Australian computer networks after an organized assault on servers, the company said by email Monday. Without commenting on operations at its plants, JBS said the incident may delay certain transactions with customers and suppliers.The attack sidelined two shifts and halted processing at one of Canada’s largest meatpacking plants, while the Australian Financial Review earlier reported that cattle and sheep slaughtering had been suspended at JBS’s operations in Australia, citing country manager Brent Eastwood. There were no immediate reports of plant disruptions in the U.S.Hackers have the commodities complex in their crosshairs with the JBS attack coming just three weeks after the operator of the biggest U.S. gasoline pipeline was targeted. It comes as the meat industry battles lingering Covid-19 absenteeism after recovering from mass outbreaks last year that saw plants shut and supplies disrupted.JBS’s incident affected a Canadian beef plant in Brooks, Alberta, about 190 kilometers (118 miles) east of Calgary, on Monday, according to Scott Payne, spokesman for United Food and Commercial Workers Canada Union Local 401.“There are no unionized workers there,” Payne said in a phone interview. “That means effectively the plant’s operations have shut for the day.”JBS didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment on the Canadian closure.A JBS packaging facility in Belleville, Ontario, where beef, pork and salmon are prepared for grocery stores, was operating normally, said Tim Deelstra, a spokesman for UFCW Canada Local 175. Dakar Lanzino, an external UFCW representative, said he had no information on whether the attack had disrupted plants in the U.S. Monday, a public holiday.Sao Paulo-based JBS owns facilities in 20 countries. Australia and New Zealand account for 4% of the company’s revenue, while the U.S. represents 50% and Canada 3%, according to company fillings.A ransom-ware attack forced Colonial Pipeline Co. to stop the flow of fuel for several days earlier this month, causing severe gasoline shortages in some areas.(Updates with Ontario plant operating normally)More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico raids building project next to pyramids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-travel-lifestyle-science-c251a6dc3289adc3d64b50c5cd253a2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico sent in 250 National Guard troops and 60 police officers Monday to seize land next to the pre-Hispanic ruins of Teotihuacán where authorities have said bulldozers were destroying outlying parts of the archeological site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, NEW HAMPSHIRE!  Nevada OKs bill in try for 1st presidential nominating state...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ia-state-wire-nevada-bills-election-2020-government-and-politics-f2a8771919ea6d6f66e6b4ea54a80fb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Nevada lawmakers passed a bill on Monday that aims to make the state the first to weigh in on the 2024 presidential primary contests. The move upends decades of political tradition and is likely to prompt pushback from other early states that want to retain their places in the calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn Backtracks on Calling For Coup...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/mike-flynn-tries-to-backtrack-on-apparent-call-for-military-coup-in-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Flynn, the first national security adviser to President Donald Trump, has backtracked on comments apparently endorsing a violent coup in the United States. Flynn, the retired general who was hired, fired and then pardoned by Trump, made the alarming comment in an appearance at a conference organized by supporters of the QAnon conspiracy theory. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge American flag stolen from veterans cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-lifestyle-veterans-f7d3182c1f7786c39d2c8d006e8c49cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Authorities said a huge American flag and several smaller flags were stolen from a Southern California veterans cemetery over the Memorial Day weekend. Les' Melnyk, a spokesperson for the Department of Veterans Affairs' National Cemetery Administration, said the garrison flag at Los Angeles National Cemetery was reported stolen sometime late Sunday or early Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon monitoring warships that may be headed to Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/29/iranian-warships-venezuela-491414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran's intent in sending the vessels in the direction of the Western Hemisphere remains a mystery, as does their cargo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn's Comment That Coup 'Should Happen' in USA Sets Off Uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/this-is-sedition-pure-and-simple-mike-flynns-comment-that-a-myanmar-style-coup-should-happen-in-the-u-s-sets-off-an-uproar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former National Security Adviser Michael Flynn set off a firestorm with comments over the weekend at a conference in Dallas organized by QAnon supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Under Renewed Pressure Following Mafia Boss Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/europe/turkeys-erdogan-under-renewed-pressure-following-mafia-boss-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Turkish government is facing accusations of arming and funding jihadists in Syria. The allegations are just the latest by an exiled mafia boss in a weekly YouTube broadcast that are putting the Turkish president in an increasingly tight spot.     Among the many allegations being spread by Sedat Peker on YouTube is one that allegedly implicates the Turkish government of arming and buying oil from Syrian jihadists. In one of his broadcasts Peker explains in detail how key aides of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan ran the scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA eyes shuttered malls, stores for new housing...</title>
      <link>https://wnyt.com/money/california-eyes-shuttered-malls-stores-for-new-housing-/6126952/?cat=12987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wnyt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LeBron's Agent Is Transforming the Business of Basketball...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/06/07/lebron-james-agent-is-transforming-the-business-of-basketball</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Paul is known for driving hard bargains for star clients, giving them new power in the N.B.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov plans to strip Legislature's pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/texas-governor-strip-legislative-branch-of-pay-2021-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"No pay for those who abandon their responsibilities," Texas Gov. Greg Abbott wrote on Twitter when announcing his plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In post-pandemic Europe, migrants will face digital fortress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-europe-migration-technology-health-c23251bec65ba45205a0851fab07e9b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEPLO, Greece (AP) — As the world begins to travel again, Europe is sending migrants a loud message: Stay away! Greek border police are firing bursts of deafening noise from an armored truck over the frontier into Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals 'bouts of depression' after shock move...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210531-osaka-reveals-bouts-of-depression-after-shock-french-open-withdrawal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Osaka reveals 'bouts of depression' after shock French Open withdrawal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds arrest man who received controversial pardon from KY gov in slaying...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2021/05/31/feds-arrest-patrick-baker-who-was-pardoned-by-bevin/5280052001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Baker, whose family hosted a fundraiser for Gov. Bevin before Bevin later pardoned him in 2019, faces new charges over Donald MIlls' murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal escorted off high school after graduation speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/education/article/stagg-high-ben-nakamura-principal-stockton-16213580.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An impassioned speech by a Stockton high school principal resulted in him being escorted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New data triples Peru death toll to over 180,000...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/peru-health-coronavirus-pandemic-64aa6bf464e40f384c5e4f108a8e75a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — Peru on Monday announced a sharp increase in its COVID-19 death toll, saying there have been more than 180,000 fatalities since the pandemic hit the country early last year. The announcement was made in the presidential palace during the presentation of a report by a working group commissioned to analyze and update the death toll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-chief of opposition group detained in St. Petersburg...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531172744-44dfy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/OPEN RUSSIA-ARREST:Russia detains ex-chief of opposition group Open Russia - report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance video shows gunmen approach Miami rap concert before shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/video-shows-gunmen-prior-to-mass-shooting-at-florida-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trio of gunmen, wearing masks and hoods, emerge from the front passenger-side door, as well as the back seat, and run toward the crowd, the footage shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise lines, DeSantis square off over vaccine passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/cruise-lines-florida-gov-desantis-square-over-vaccine-passports-n1269029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise lines are eager to set sail, but a new law championed by Gov. Ron DeSantis banning so-called vaccine passports may keep them anchored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naomi Osaka WITHDRAWS from French Open in wake of media boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-9637725/Naomi-Osaka-WITHDRAWS-French-Open-media-boycott-world-No-2-opens-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world number two won her opening match against Patricia Maria Tig on Sunday but her decision not to take part in press conferences or interviews has been the biggest talking point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Locked Men Up For Drugs. Now Site Will Grow Marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2021/may/31/mostly-death-fills-memoriesof-war-for-101-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Strickland's lasting memories of World War II aren't of battles or parades but of camaraderie and suffering the war brought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants raise prices amid soaring costs, labor shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/restaurants-raise-prices-amid-soaring-costs-labor-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising costs of ingredients and basic supplies as well as a nationwide labor shortage are throttling restaurants just as they begin to fully reopen and ramp up for a bustling summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ bringing back gas chamber with chemical favored by Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/arizona-bringing-back-gas-chamber-with-chemical-favored-by-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Arizona is reportedly preparing to execute death row inmates using hydrogen cyanide — and has “refurbished” a mothballed gas chamber using primitive techniques. The Republican-co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos in African parliament after 'I'll kill you' threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/africa-c2b1ae2e673a3327c898143a59ba6b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE TOWN, South Africa (AP) — There was mayhem at a meeting of the African Union's parliament Monday as lawmakers scuffled over a ballot box and a man appeared to aim a head-high kick at a female colleague amid shouts that there were people armed with guns in the room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN &amp; JERRY'S ice cream with CBD?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ben-jerry-s-with-cbd/ar-AAKzgsN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben &amp; Jerry’s made a bold new flavor announcement in May 2019: CBD ice cream was coming ... “as soon as it’s legalized at the federal level.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Covid cases near  low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/30/us-covid-cases-lowest-in-a-year-as-memorial-day-travel-picks-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11,976 new Covid-19 cases reported on May 29 were the lowest since March 23, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-limits-travel-most-populous-094613554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities imposed fresh travel limits, cancelled flights and tested thousands of residents in Guangdong Monday after the Indian variant of the coronavirus was reported in the country's most populous province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday still subdued by pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531140733-3ksl5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HOLIDAY/MEMORIALDAY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. travelers on the road again with Memorial Day holiday still subdued by pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES FINAL CURTAIN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531104812-din11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/NETANYAHU (TV, PIX):Israel's 'magician' Netanyahu faces final curtain after record run</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
