<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Deadly parasitic worm set to invade Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6743224/parasitic-worm-schistosomiasis-lays-eggs-human-organs-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S the second most deadly parasitic disease – only malaria is more lethal. And schistosomiasis – also known as snail fever – could be set to invade Europe’s shores. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti trying to bring down president  -- one cable hit at a time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/10/magazine/michael-avenatti-stormy-daniels-donald-trump-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In representing the porn star Stormy Daniels, the lawyer thinks he can bring down a president — one cable-news hit at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INDIANA JONES 5' Delayed Again -- Harrison Ford to Turn 79 When Released in 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/indiana-jones-5-release-date-pushed-again-2021-1125975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwayne Johnson's 'Jungle Cruise' will swim into theaters in fall 2019, while Angelina Jolie's 'Maleficent 2' will open in summer 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Braces For Protests After Vice Mayor Calls For 'Straight Pride Month'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/10/dixon-ted-hickman-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some residents are planning to protest the Dixon’s vice mayor during a council meeting Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texan arrested for having sex with neighbor's dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.wacotrib.com/news/police/police-man-arrested-on-bestiality-charge/article_58744e08-cf58-588e-ad2f-84301e01d40e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wacotrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bellmead man who ran from police after he allegedly sexually assaulted a neighbor's dog was arrested early Saturday morning on a charge of bestiality, Bellmead police Lt. Kory Martin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues UNITED after waking to find pilot 'rubbing her crotch while masturbating'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5935373/Woman-sues-United-Airlines-claiming-drunken-passenger-sexually-assaulted-her.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anne Dowling, from Denver, Colorado, is seeking $75,000 in damages claiming passenger Monte Wedl molested her on a United Airlines flight from Hong Kong to San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge again delays sentencing for Michael Flynn...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-mike-flynn-court-20180710-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former national security advisor, Michael T. Flynn, appeared in federal court Tuesday for a hearing about his eventual sentencing for lying to the FBI in the Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crabber hit by flesh-eating bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/news/weird/2018/07/10/nj-man-could-lose-his-limbs-flesh-eating-bacteria/770523002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After going crabbing in New Jersey, this man caught a flesh-eating bacteria that is threatening his life and limbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hail Satan' carved into church porch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article214618710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After someone carved "Hail Satan" into the floor of an Upstate baptist church, deputies are investigating. The phrase was found on the front porch of Welcome Baptist Church's Family Life Center, cut into the floor, WSPA reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo leaving REAL MADRID to join Italian club ...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ronaldo-leaving-real-madrid-join-italian-club-juventus-155916649--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURIN, Italy (AP) — Cristiano Ronaldo is leaving Real Madrid to join Italian club Juventus, bringing to an end a hugely successful nine-year spell in Spain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Furious Over Nomination of [Insert Name Here]...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/blog/liberals-are-furious-over-the-nomination-of-insert-name-here-to-supreme-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Behold the rallying cry of a new generation of manufactured outrage: "Stop [blank]!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves swipe $27K worth of gadgets in brazen APPLE Store heist...</title>
      <link>http://abc7news.com/thieves-steal-from-fresno-apple-store-in-seconds/3734642/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crystal clear surveillance video shows how a group of young men made off with a small fortune worth of Apple products at Fashion Fair in Fresno.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA to Build Auto Factory in Shanghai...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tesla-to-build-auto-factory-in-shanghai-1531230784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The electric-car maker will build a factory in Shanghai capable of producing 500,000 vehicles a year in a move expected to boost sales in the world’s largest auto market but one that could also draw fire in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons Oregon ranchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-pardons-oregon-ranchers-whose-case-led-refuge-145552833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday pardoned Oregon cattle ranchers Dwight Hammond and his son after both were convicted on arson charges, sparking the 2016 occupation of a wildlife refuge, according to a White House statement. Dwight Hammond, 76, and his son, Steven, 49, were convicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing augmented reality ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/facebook-tests-augmented-reality-ads-news-feed-u-150906502--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ads will let users virtually interact with different products - from trying on Michael Kors sunglasses and accessories to visualizing furniture in a room. Facebook said Sephora, Bobbi Brown, Pottery Barn, Wayfair and some other brands will start testing the new ad concept later this summer. Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in 'angry clown mask' WAFFLE HOUSE, shoots customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/breaking-customer-shot-northwest-atlanta-waffle-house/4wSPV6QEP36EYgZVKLeuFL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman in an angry clown mask is on the run after shooting a customer early Tuesday at a northwes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Allies on Edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-leaves-for-nato-gathering-with-european-allies-on-edge-1531215000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is beginning a seven-day tour through Europe that will start with him confronting allies over military spending and end with a summit with President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli company will attempt to become first private entity to land spacecraft on moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a691690a583d47bc86ecc44cc16c662a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEHUD, Israel (AP) — An Israeli organization said Tuesday that it hopes to become the first non-governmental entity to land a spacecraft on the moon when it attempts to launch a m</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Tweet About Nicki Minaj Spiraled Into Internet Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/10/arts/music/nicki-minaj-wanna-thompson-twitter-stans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hip-hop writer became the target of superfan ire — and the rapper’s own fury — after she posted a message about Ms. Minaj’s musical direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb Freakout...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/07/10/hollywood-resistance-freaks-over-kavanaugh-nomination-will-cement-the-first-american-dictatorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrities predict "Shariah Law" and "dictatorship" reacting to President Trump's selection of Judge Brett Kavanaugh for the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 11 retailers may not survive '18...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/retail/2018/07/10/shopping-struggles-11-retailers-may-not-survive-2018/36720811/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retail apocalypse, which began nine years ago, isn’t over yet. Let’s examine eleven retailers which could struggle to remain relevant this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pop-Up Protests, Liberal Meltdown Erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-07-10/pop-protests-erupt-after-trump-picks-kavanaugh-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Kennels': Venezuela's dangerous answer to transport chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kennels-venezuelas-dangerous-answer-transport-chaos-061608296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Packed inside a barred pick-up truck that looks like a mobile cage, passengers are risking their lives in Venezuela's perilous solution to a public transport crisis. In the Libertador municipality hometown of President Nicolas Maduro, himself a former bus driver, the words "Loving Caracas"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidding War Brews Over Bankrupt IHEART Radio...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-bidding-war-brews-over-bankrupt-iheartmedia-1531174295 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Malone’s Liberty Media and buyout firm Silver Lake are circling the nation’s No. 1 radio broadcaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orcas of Pacific Northwest Starving and Disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/starvation-and-habitat-threats-stalk-killer-whales/17685419/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — For the last three years, not one calf has been born to the dwindling pods of black-and-white killer whales spouting geysers of mist off the coast in the Pacific Northwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying Organs Restored to Life in Novel Experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/dying-organs-restored-to-life-in-novel-experiments/17685654/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Georgia Bowen was born by emergency cesarean on May 18, she took a breath, threw her arms in the air, cried twice, and went into cardiac arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE to Promote 'Authoritative News'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/youtube-debuts-plan-to-promote-fund-authoritative-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video platform is less focused on getting rid of conspiracy theorists than on trying to elevate journalism it considers valuable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump advisers face taunts from hecklers around DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/dc-politics/viciousness-trump-aides-endure-public-fury-toward-presidents-policies/2018/07/09/23d3b9a2-8051-11e8-b0ef-fffcabeff946_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Bannon is just the latest target. From Kellyanne Conway to Stephen Miller, Trump’s advisers face taunts from hecklers and protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Older immigrants 'crowding out' U.S. teens for summer jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/older-immigrants-crowding-out-u-s-teens-for-summer-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal and illegal immigrants are “crowding out” American teens looking for summer jobs, and the impact of higher teen unemployment could be a drag on them for years, according to a new analysis of the seasonal workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFLer says TSA spilled mother's ashes in baggage inspection...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/giants/2018/07/10/ny-giants-aj-francis-tsa-spilled-mothers-ashes-nfl/770611002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Giants defensive lineman A.J. Francis slammed the TSA on Twitter Monday when he said agents spilled his mother’s ashes while doing a baggage inspection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp Accused of Punching Film Crew Member in New Lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/johnny-depp-accused-of-punching-film-crew-member-in-new-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gregg "Rocky" Brooks says he was working as a location manager last year when Johnny Depp got physical with him at a downtown Los Angeles hotel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first floating city will have 'own government and currency by 2022'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6711865/floating-city-cryptocurrency-varyon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE WORLD’S first floating city will boast its own government and cryptocurrency when it lays roots in the South Pacific in 2022, claim its backers. Building work on this isolated “utop…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby survives nine hours buried under debris in Montana woods...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/09/montana-baby-found-woods-debris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five-month-old boy found safe and well after being abandoned in western Montana forest wearing wet clothes in cold weather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOD TESTS REVEAL LIFE EXPECTANCY?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/jul/09/scientists-yale-life-expectancy-test-biological-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yale scientists develop measure to calculate biological age with greater accuracy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover world's oldest color: Bright pink...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/09/scientists-discover-worlds-oldest-colour-bright-pink-sahara</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pigments found in 1.1bn-year-old rocks beneath the Sahara desert shed light on ‘major puzzle’ about early life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University works to reduce number of white people on campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/post/46633/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cal Poly San Luis Obispo works on massive diversity and inclusion effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB TRAFFIC RACE:  CNN TOP NEWS; PORN SITES DOMINATE; DRUDGE RISES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even casual ties to others can better health...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Even-casual-ties-to-others-can-better-your-health-13060656.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close relationships with family and friends, we know, are important for our health and well-being. But what about the people who make up our broader social networks: the parents at school drop-off, the neighbor down the street or that colleague in another department who always makes you laugh? While research on the benefits of social connections has generally focused on the importance of "strong ties," or the intimate relationships we have with family and close friends, a growing body of research is shedding light on the hidden benefits of casual acquaintances, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash building to cashless movement... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Backlash-building-to-cashless-movement-13060811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global cashless movement has reached Washington, where a growing number of fast-casual and other establishments are saying no to greenbacks in favor of plastic and mobile payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Blasts 'Controversial' Nominee -- Before Announced!</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2018/07/09/nightline-deems-supreme-court-pick-controversial-hes-even-named</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Supreme Court pick is very “controversial,” whoever he or she turned out to be. That’s the consensus of ABC’s Nightline. About 90 minutes before Donald Trump announced the name of Judge Brett Kavanaugh, Nightline’s Twitter page blasted:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC DANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/curtis-houck/2018/07/09/left-foxs-shannon-bream-forced-bail-scotus-set-after-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late Monday night, Fox News @ Night host and Supreme Court correspondent Shannon Bream tweeted that she had to flee her live shot from outside the Supreme Court after having “felt threatened” by the “very volatile” “mood” by the far-left protesters having conniptions over President Trump’s nomination of Brett Kavanaugh for the nation’s high Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVISIONTELEMUNDO Ignore Lowest Ever Hispanic Unemployment...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/latino/ken-oliver/2018/07/08/lowest-ever-hispanic-unemployment-ignored-univision-telemundo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the morning of July 6, the U.S. Department of Labor’s Bureau of Labor Statistics announced that Hispanic unemployment in the United States had reached its lowest level, 4.6%, in the 45 years since the agency first started keeping records on the statistic, back in 1973. One would think such a historic achievement would be news that night on the nation’s leading Spanish-language television news programs, but that was not the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python found in hard drive at Miami airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article214596115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSA officers found a python inside luggage at Miami International Airport on Sunday. It did not board the plane to Barbados. Nor did the passenger connected to the reptile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-sacha-baron-cohen-gets-dick-cheney-to-sign-a-waterboarding-kit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Host Cancels Live Show Over Volatile Protests: I Felt 'Threatened'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/fox-news-host-cancels-live-show-from-scotus-steps-due-to-volatile-protests-i-felt-threatened/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Waiting for Man to Die!!!' Inside Fall of Sumner Redstone's Girlfriends...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/bookmark/inside-fall-sumner-redstones-girlfriends-book-excerpt-1125811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Sydney Holland and Manuela Herzer ruled the aging Viacom-CBS mogul's L.A. mansion, until a medical crisis, a secret fiance and some frantic texts gave Shari Redstone a path to regain control of her father’s empire, reveals this exclusive excerpt from Wall Street Journal reporter Keach Hagey's new biography of the media mogul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Deficit With China Hits New Record... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/152237500000-merchandise-trade-deficit-china-hit-record-through-may </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Airs Star-Spangled 'Salute to Abortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/netflix-airs-salute-abortion-host-declares-god-bless-abortions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiment wipes out over 80% of disease-carrying mosquitoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/10/australia/australia-mosquito-disease-experiment-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an experiment with global implications, Australian scientists have successfully wiped out more than 80% of disease-carrying mosquitoes in trial locations across north Queensland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowners sitting on record amount of cash -- $5.8 trillion!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/09/homeowners-sitting-on-record-amount-of-cash-and-not-tapping-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeowners are gaining thousands of dollars in available equity to tap, but they are taking out very little. It may be that they don't know how much they have or that they are generally more conservative after the last housing crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Top State for Business...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/29/texas-rebounds-to-become-americas-top-state-for-business-in-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas claims the top spot in CNBC's 2018 America’s Top States for Business rankings. The energy sector is turbocharging the state's $1.6 trillion economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti 'just completely blew up,' pastor says of stranded mission team...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214554250.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen members of a North Carolina church in Stanly County are among mission teams stranded in Haiti, where violent protests erupted when sharp increases in fuel prices were announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall of dust, powerful monsoon storms slam Phoenix area...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/phoenix-arizona-monsoon-dust-storm-flights-cancelled-power-out-mesa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flights cancelled, property damage reported and many without power as monsoon storm slams central Ariz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAVANAUGH: Judges Must Interpret, Not Make Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/07/09/kavanaugh-judges-must-interpret-not-make-law-interpret-statues-and-constitution-as-written/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the announcement of his nomination to the Supreme Court, Judge Brett Kavanaugh stated, "A judge must be independent and must interpret the law, not | Breitbart TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Seeing Putin Will Be Easier Than Meeting May...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/10/trump-says-seeing-putin-will-be-easier-than-meeting-theresa-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Says Seeing Putin Will Be Easier Than Meeting Theresa May</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Court Pick to Cement Conservative Majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/09/trump-making-supreme-court-pick-to-cement-conservative-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has decided who he’ll nominate to the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline Restrooms Getting Smaller...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/09/it-s-not-your-imagination-airline-restrooms-are-getting-smaller </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the restroom on your next flight seems a bit snug, don’t assume you’ve picked up a few pounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Antitrust Critic Joins FTC as Agency Sets Sights on Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/09/amazon-antitrust-critic-joins-ftc-as-agency-sets-sights-on-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lina Khan, a prominent critic of Amazon.com Inc.’s business practices, is joining the office of FTC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-Priced $16M Colt Euthanized After Career Earnings Of $10,440...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloodhorse.com/horse-racing/articles/228451/world-record-priced-colt-the-green-monkey-euthanized</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloodhorse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Green Monkey, who'll forever be etched in Thoroughbred history books as a result of his world-record $16 million price tag as a 2-year-old, was euthanized at Hartley/DeRenzo Thoroughbreds in May due to the effects of laminitis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminists Clash with Transgenders at Pride Parade...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/lesbians-blame-transgenderism-for-conversion-therapy-and-rape-culture-at-london-pride-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feminism and transgenderism are fundamentally incompatible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: ICE Protesters chant 'F--- the police' at officers...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/ice-protestors-in-ohio-chant-fck-the-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Forgets McConnell's Name, Aide Forced to Prompt...</title>
      <link>https://ijr.com/2018/07/1108419-nancy-pelosi-forgets-mitch-mcconnell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ijr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Has anyone asked whatshisname, the one who's the head of the Senate?&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise Of Smaller Screen? Top Cable Drama Gets More Viewers On App Than TV...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/power-ratings-season-5-app-tv-1202423349/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The power was certainly on for the Season 5 premiere of Power but it was surging on a much smaller screen than before. Laying track to the future in the present, the July 1 airing of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Threatens To Shoot Up Newspaper Office For Not Publishing Article...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/07/09/woman-threat-shooting-walpole-times-journalist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walpole newspaper office is temporarily shut down after one of its journalists received a specific threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSTICE BRETT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae9330694da8476e82a97b4cd472d8e2/The-Latest:-Trump-nominates-Brett-Kavanaugh-to-Supreme-Court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump's nomination of a Supreme Court justice (all times local):        10:30 p.m.        Democratic lawmakers and l</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long DC history gives Senate much to review...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/9/brett-kavanaughs-long-washington-history-gives-sen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Brett M. Kavanaugh has perhaps the longest Washington pedigree of any of the people who were on President Trump’s short list for the Supreme Court, having worked at the highest levels of the White House under President George W. Bush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill and Hill fly commercial...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-bill-and-hillary-clinton-spotted-flying-on-commercial-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Hillary attempting to fashion herself as just one of the people in preparation for a 2020 presidential run? Bill and Hillary Clinton were forced to fly with the unwashed masses recently, according to video posted on Twitter. The video shows the pair apparently sitting in the First Class section, captured across the aisle peons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES:  TRAM TO HOLLYWOOD SIGN?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-hollywood-sign-sky-tram-20180710-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The studio would foot the bill for the project, which it hopes will relieve traffic congestion in the neighborhoods near the sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious giant sarcophagus discovered in Egypt...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/07/09/mysterious-giant-sarcophagus-discovered-in-egypt.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious ancient black granite sarcophagus has been discovered in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clooney injured in scooter crash in Italy...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-5937207/George-Clooney-injured-bike-accident-Sardinia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source told MailOnline the US star, 57, was riding his scooter from his house in Puntaldia, Sardinia, to the set of his new TV show, Catch 22, which is in Capo Ceraso, on the sea in Olbia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Being rich, successful in your DNA...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5934673/Being-rich-successful-really-genes-study-suggests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts from Duke University, North Carolina, found that men and women with a certain combinations of genes are more likely to be socially mobile, regardless of their background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest family in world? 87-year-old has 346 living descendants...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5937965/Largest-family-87-year-old-346-living-descendants-including-203-great-grandchildren.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Semenyuk family in Ukraine consists of 346 living relatives. There is a party for every birthday and wedding, and for each newlywed couple a house is built in the village of Dobroslav by the family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents of California city set to get monthly $500 stipend...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5936339/Residents-Stockton-set-500-month-no-strings-attached-bid-boost-economy.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stockton, California will become the first city in the country to participate in a test of Universal Basic Income, where 100 residents will be given $500-dollars-a-month with no strings attached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS GOES IN FOR THE KILL...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5935751/Jacob-Rees-Mogg-says-former-Foreign-Secretary-make-excellent-Prime-Minister.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May has been left fighting for her political life after Boris Johnson accused her of killing Brexit in his resignation letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLINTON EYES 20/20...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5931169/Talk-emerges-Hillary-Clinton-plotting-2020-comeback-prepping-Trump-rematch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton has ramped her public presence and her fundraising appeals in recent weeks, leading to speculation she's plotting her 2020 comeback and preparing for a rematch with Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming 'labor shortage' in America is great news for workers...</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/labor-shortage-good-news-workers-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opinion: For now, the coming "labor shortage" is good news for workers. We should root for it to continue. It's undoubtedly a headache for some owners and managers. But it's one they should, hopefully, be made to live with for a few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Chinese govt startup developing AI that recognizes anyone, anywhere...</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/china-facial-recognition-tech-company-megvii-faceplusplus-2018-5?op=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the creepy and impressive startup funded by the Chinese government that is developing AI that can recognize anyone, anywhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of 'victims' grows...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/396163-drudge-warns-sacha-baron-cohen-at-it-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drudge Report chief Matt Drudge tweeted a warning on Monday that comedian Sacha Baron Cohen "is at it again," a day after the "Borat" star</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems doubt Warren can take on Trump...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/396204-dems-mull-whether-warren-is-the-one-to-take-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Elizabeth Warren win back blue-collar Democrats from President Trump in Michigan, Wisconsin and Pennsylvania?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez to visit Capitol Hill next week...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/396195-ocasio-cortez-to-visit-capitol-hill-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York congressional candidate Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D) will meet with a handful of her early supporters in Washington, D.C., next week, making her first trek to Capitol Hill since her stunning primary victory over Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Launches New Stunt Series...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/09/sacha-baron-cohen-showtime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-gx70yWboTs&amp;feature=youtu.be It's official: Sacha Baron Cohen is returning to TV — and a lot sooner than you might think. Showtime announced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  LA's record heat wave was 'compromised' and likely wrong...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/09/record-temperature-los-angeles-compromised/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The data from these stations is worthless'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
