<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee faces unprecedented choice of whether to call Republican lawmakers to testify...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-committee-faces-unprecedented-choice-of-whether-to-call-republican-lawmakers-to-testify/ar-AAMMF4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reports pressure drop in space station service module...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-reports-pressure-drop-space-station-service-module-2021-07-31/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of Russia's Roscosmos space agency said on Saturday that pressure in a Russian service module on the International Space Station had dropped as a result of an air leak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti police identify former top judge as suspect in ex-president's killing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/565763-haiti-police-identify-former-top-judge-as-suspect-in-ex-presidents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haitian police are investigating what role a former Supreme Court judge may have played in the assassination of Haiti’s president following new developments announced on Friday, Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammunition shelves bare as gun sales continue to soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-gun-politics-86e61939eb4ae1230e110ed6d7576b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — The COVID-19 pandemic, coupled with record sales of firearms, has fueled a shortage of ammunition in the United States that’s impacting law enforcement agencies, people seeking personal protection, recreational shooters and hunters -- and could deny new gun owners the practice they need to handle their weapons safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacon may disappear in California as pig rules take effect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-california-coronavirus-pandemic-5ebe70407fcd94ef712c16410f32c4b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Thanks to a reworked menu and long hours, Jeannie Kim managed to keep her San Francisco restaurant alive during the coronavirus pandemic. That makes it all the more frustrating that she fears her breakfast-focused diner could be ruined within months by new rules that could make one of her top menu items — bacon — hard to get in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Spreader Sex Houses to Nude Beach Fistfights, Vaxxed Partying Not All Cracked Up to Be...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/super-spreader-sex-houses-nude-102827164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ilan Deutsch/Paris Match via Getty ImagesAfter being woken up by the sound of a little dog below me humping his favorite teddy bear, I crawl down the ladder of a kid bunk bed and head downstairs to assess the damage of last night’s debauchery. Cigarette butts, empty wine bottles, and half eaten baguettes litter the kitchen and pool area of this mini French mansion my friend Jackie is currently dog sitting at. There’s puke around the toilet in the “cave” downstairs, a hot Frenchie sashaying throu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula 2022? Brazil poised for sensational political comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/30/lula-2022-brazil-poised-for-sensational-political-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With former president’s political rights restored, polls suggest he would thrash Jair Bolsonaro if he stands for election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS prepares for bloody showdown after littering streets with headless corpses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-jihadis-prepare-bloody-showdown-24653728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrorists affiliated to ISIS have wreaked havoc in Mozambique in recent years, leaving thousands dead. However, a new fighting force is now aiming to halt their advances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths rise 300%...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9846441/Deltas-deadly-surge-Daily-deaths-rise-nearly-300-891-number-new-cases-doubles-190k.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday there were 321 deaths from COVID-19 reported. Twenty four hours later, the figure had risen to 891. The shocking surge suggests that the United States is feeling the full force of Delta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer hoped history books would help her Capitol riot clients grow. She was called traitor -- and worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-lawyer-hoped-history-books-would-help-her-capitol-riot-clients-grow-she-was-called-a-traitor-e2-80-94-and-worse/ar-AAMMoRF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shaner’s method seemed unconventional to the public, but not to her. She’s been giving her clients books for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden eagle populations struggling in West...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-science-health-utah-ca29dab560179148f4d2be8208093862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNOWVILLE, Utah (AP) — Dustin Maloney is in sagebrush country in remote northern Utah west of Snowville on a grueling hiking trip full of dust and heat and sweat. He’s got one eye looking for snakes and the other on the ground so he doesn’t lose his step and take a perilous fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE BRACED FOR PROTESTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-256bbfd835e6388219390cacb536eaba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France braced for more protests on Saturday against the upcoming special virus passes that will be needed to enter restaurants, as police took up posts along Paris’ Champs-Elysees to guard against an invasion of the famed avenue by rowdy demonstrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Tenants Nationwide, Scramble to Pay Months of Rent or Face Eviction...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/31/for-tenants-nationwide-a-scramble-to-pay-months-of-rent-or-face-eviction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For almost a year, a federal moratorium on evictions allowed tenants who suffered economic losses from the coronavirus pandemic to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA CASES JUMP 50% IN WEEK</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/565740-florida-coronavirus-cases-jump-50-percent-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of coronavirus cases in Florida has jumped 50 percent over the past week, officials said Friday, as the state that already makes up a large chunk of the nation's total cases sees a surge in new infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much info will become public?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/07/30/justice-department-tells-treasury-to-turn-over-trump-tax-records-to-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOJ told the Treasury Department it must turn over former President Donald Trump’s tax returns to the House Ways and Means Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sues TX over Abbott's order restricting transport of migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-sues-texas-over-abbott-s-order-restricting-transport-of-migrants/ar-AAMLoay?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Justice filed suit Friday afternoon to stop an order by Texas Gov. Greg Abbott to restrict the transportation of migrants who had previously been detained by the federal immigration authorities. The suit, filed in El Paso in the U.S. District Court for the Western District, is the latest in an escalating battle between Abbott and the administration of President Joe ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA drought: Dozens of communities at risk of running out of water...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-drought-dozens-of-communities-are-at-risk-of-running-out-of-water/ar-AAMLz4v?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dry wells, low rivers and other problems are creating emergencies across Northern California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just say was corrupt + leave the rest to me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-to-acting-ag-according-to-aide-e2-80-99s-notes-e2-80-98just-say-the-election-was-corrupt-2b-leave-the-rest-to-me-e2-80-99/ar-AAMKRjt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump bluntly urged acting attorney general Jeffrey Rosen to back claims of voter fraud, which senior Justice officials told him were false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Ed Buck's victims, being believed was first mountain to climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/he-was-a-white-man-who-had-money-ed-bucks-black-victims-fought-to-be-believed/ar-AAMKcMs?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victims of Ed Buck, who was convicted in the overdose deaths of two Black men, say it felt like no one believed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald pressed officals to declare election was illegal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-urged-justice-department-to-declare-election-corrupt-0edf178869f33ddcf72d4c739bd18a5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump urged senior Justice Department officials to declare the results of the 2020 election “corrupt” in a December phone call, according to handwritten notes from one of the participants in the conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Vaccinated people can carry as much virus as others...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-d9504519a8ae081f785ca012b5ef84d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another dispiriting setback for the nation’s efforts to stamp out the coronavirus, scientists who studied a big COVID-19 outbreak in Massachusetts concluded that vaccinated people who got so-called breakthrough infections carried about the same amount of the coronavirus as those who did not get the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95% of Brits still wearing mask when out...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/30/95-of-british-adults-still-wearing-a-mask-outdoors-says-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Figure same as before legal requirement relaxed, while most still feel that complying with other Covid safety measures is important</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Viewership Down 42% From Rio...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-rio-2016-suni-lee-simone-biles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the most-watched and least-watched nights of the Tokyo Olympics so far -- and how viewership stacks up to the 2016 Rio Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  How I Learned To Stop Worrying And Live With The Virus...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/let-it-rip-f9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How I Learned To Stop Worrying And Live With The Virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Black woman to run St. Louis shaking up city with war on normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-first-black-woman-to-run-st-louis-is-shaking-up-the-city-with-a-war-on-normal/ar-AAMKmaB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tishaura Jones is among a wave of progressive leaders aiming to turn around struggling cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY making all employees...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/30/disney-employees-vaccinated-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Walt Disney Co. announced Friday it will require all salaried and non-union hourly employees at all of its U.S. sites to be fully vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Images Show New Tunnel At Test Site...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/30/1022209337/a-new-tunnel-is-spotted-at-a-chinese-nuclear-test-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite imagery showing a new tunnel comes just weeks after the discovery of two new nuclear missile fields in other parts of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125,682 'BREAKTHROUGH' CASES</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/breakthrough-covid-cases-least-125-000-fully-vaccinated-americans-have-n1275500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 125,682 "breakthrough" cases in 38 states represent less than .08 percent of the 164.2 million-plus people fully vaccinated since January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets Cuba crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-readies-new-Cuba-sanctions-as-Biden-meets-16352270.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration announced new sanctions on Friday against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Privacy Battle APPLE Isn't Fighting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/global-privacy-control-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has begun enforcing a browser-level privacy setting, but you still can’t find that option in Safari or iOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only half of Israelis want 3rd jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/only-half-of-israelis-want-a-third-covid-19-vaccine-shot-survey-675419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli belief in the effectiveness of the Pfizer vaccine appears to be on the decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA plans 'sprint' to accelerate PFIZER review...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/07/30/fda-under-pressure-plans-sprint-to-accelerate-review-of-pfizers-covid-19-vaccine-for-full-approval/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers and prominent health experts have urged the FDA to expedite full approval of Pfizer’s vaccine, citing various potential benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART mandates -- for home workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Walmart-mandates-masks-for-all-workers-in-some-16352108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Walmart is requiring that all home office workers as well as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74% of infected were fully dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/cdc-study-shows-74percent-of-people-infected-in-massachusetts-covid-outbreak-were-fully-vaccinated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC data published Friday was based on 469 cases of Covid associated with multiple summer events and large public gatherings in July in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bin Laden Bel Air estate listed for $28M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/30/osama-bin-ladens-bel-air-estate-is-on-sale-for-28m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The home was abandoned after the September 11 attacks. “Ready for redoing, owner has not been here for over 20 years,” the listing states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sir, there is something on your chin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9844869/Staffer-passes-Biden-note-saying-Sir-chin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden was speaking on Zoom about the responses to raging wildfires throughout the country when an aide passed him a card, alerting him there was a spot on his face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China battles worst outbreak since Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-58021911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 200 people have been infected since the virus was first detected at Nanjing airport on 20 July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can masturbating beat Covid?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3381486/can-masturbating-boost-your-immune-system-fight-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH a deadly virus circulating the past year and a half, many people have been wondering how they can boost their immunity. Masturbating is sometimes touted as a way to give the immune system a ki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt denies BLUE ORIGIN protest of human moon lander contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/07/30/government-denies-blue-origins-protest-of-nasas-human-moon-lander-contract/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GAO sided with NASA Friday denying protests submitted by Blue Origin and Dynetics of the agency's decision to pick only SpaceX's Starship for the first human moon lander contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYDNEY DEPLOYS ARMY</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-58021718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say the deployment is needed, but critics argue it will "pick on" marginalised groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military warns China building more nuclear missile silos...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/07/30/us-military-warns-china-is-building-more-nuclear-missile-silos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The underground missile silo field in the Xinjiang region is the second one reported this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax returns can be released to Congress, DOJ says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/trump-tax-returns-can-be-released-to-congress-doj-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump has refused for years to voluntarily disclose his income tax returns. Congress can now see them, the Justice Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed Dog Grooming Alarms Local News Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/29/unlicensed-dog-grooming-alarms-local-news-reporter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do we really need the state to step in over an unfortunate tragedy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Mouthwash Test Just As Effective As Nasal Swabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mouthwash-tests-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both the nasal and mouthwash tests are of the polymerase chain reaction variety, which are highly sensitive and capable of producing a result in real-time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
