<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The scandals we don't know about...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/donald-trump/1001454/doj-subpoenas-scandals-we-dont-know-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest revelation of administration abuses won't be the last</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists demanding more action against online harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-journalists-racial-injustice-business-race-and-ethnicity-d986426b7211a67fffb621f0a2414001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Associated Press' recent firing of a young reporter for what she said on Twitter has somewhat unexpectedly turned company and industry attention to the flip side of social media engagement — the online abuse that many journalists face routinely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers hit Teamsters -- but they refused to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/ransomware-attack-hit-teamsters-2019-they-refused-pay-n1270461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI advised the union to "just pay" the ransom, according to sources. Union officials chose to rebuild their computer network instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobster Diver Survives After Nearly Swallowed Off Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/11/lobster-diver-swallowed-by-whale-cape-cod-michael-packard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lobster diver says he was nearly swallowed by a whale in a terrifying encounter off Cape Cod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star who posed nude pic at George Floyd mural found dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/11/porn-star-who-posed-nude-pic-at-george-floyd-mural-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 27-year-old was discovered dead in her Los Angeles motorhome by her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders agree to keep money taps open...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611180646-8xykl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/ECONOMY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-G7 leaders agreed to keep the money taps open -source</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gives Biden framed Frederick Douglass photo printed from WIKIPEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/newsletter/london-playbook/politico-g7-playbook-carbis-bay-fitness-regime-hug-and-walk-turbot-charged-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's driving the day in Westminster. Politics and policymaking in the UK capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress, Justice Dept. probing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-donald-trump-ca-state-wire-europe-business-76af370a04c6d80613c9e9ba1e54c8c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department's internal watchdog launched an investigation Friday after revelations that former President Donald Trump's administration secretly seized phone data from at least two House Democrats as part of an aggressive leaks probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists sent freeze-dried mouse sperm to ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/11/space-radiation-sperm-international-space-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists sent freeze-dried mouse sperm to the International Space Station to study the effects of space radiation on reproduction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Doge' meme NFT breaks record, selling for $4 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/iconic-doge-meme-nft-breaks-records-selling-roughly-4-million-n1270161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meme of an excited Shiba Inu named Kabosu is officially the most expensive meme NFT ever sold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN to drop in-flight magazine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-a990ef02a12b6a4681613e12b7258c70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas (AP) — After more than half a century in airplane seatback pockets, the American Airlines in-flight magazine American Way is going away. An airline spokeswoman said Friday that American will retire the magazine and its online version at the end of June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will yoga classes in public school lead kids to convert?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-lifestyle-yoga-6596351665214b0f271da3ca8c2808db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — As soon as Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey signed a bill lifting the state’s 30-year ban on teaching yoga in public schools last month, the critics began weighing in. Christian conservatives said yoga classes might lead students to convert to Hinduism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocking man's manhood spurs reverse #MeToo in SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2021-06-11/whats-size-got-to-do-with-it-the-pinching-hand-anti-feminist-backlash-drive-up-the-fever-pitch-of-south-koreas-gender-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pinching hand symbol has become a point of contention in a charged battle over gender and anti-feminist backlash by men's rights groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How hedge funds took over struggling industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/11/how-hedge-funds-took-over-americas-struggling-newspaper-industry-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the largest U.S. newspaper groups — like Tribune, McClatchy and Media News Group — are owned, controlled by or in debt to hedge funds or private equity groups. CNBC looks at how this happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate threat to subpoena Barr, Sessions... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/trump-justice-department-democrats-congress/2021/06/11/7c2b1aa8-cace-11eb-a11b-6c6191ccd599_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer and Judiciary Committee Chairman Richard J. Durbin called the secret subpoenas “a gross abuse of power.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bled red as pandemic hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/money/other/rupert-murdoch-slashes-value-of-the-sun-newspaper-to-zero/ar-AAKWHqN?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch slashes value of the Sun newspaper to zero</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris tells G7 to build 'more gender neutral, feminine' world...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/15244060/pm-urges-g7-to-build-gender-neutral-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson today called on G7 leaders to build a “more gender neutral, more feminine” world after the pandemic. The PM’s odd rallying cry came as he opened the weekend summit i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  UK's Biggest Paper for Decades -- Now Worth Zero?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jun/11/rupert-murdoch-writes-down-value-of-sun-newspapers-to-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move follows £200m loss caused by Covid-19 pandemic and one-off charges related to phone hacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When will pandemic end? Where we'll be in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/when-will-the-pandemic-end-and-will-you-need-a-booster-shot-where-we-ll-be-in-2022/ar-AAKUqXG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — It’s 2022. And people have learned to live surrounded by the novel coronavirus and its many variants moving across the world that cause COVID-19. Employees are back in the office using a staggered schedule. Kids are in the classroom again. Live theater, concerts and sporting events are playing to audiences across South Florida. And people no longer need to wear a mask to enter a store ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST HOURS OF 'THE KING'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-israel-religion-a8e8517989213286c206d709b212dada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — If all goes according to plan, Israel will swear in a new government on Sunday, ending Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's record 12-year rule and a political crisis that inflicted four elections on the country in less than two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON ordered to throw out 60 MILLION vaccine doses... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3061480/johnson-covid-vaccine-throw-out-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHNSON &amp; Johnson has been ordered by the FDA to throw out 60million Covid jab doses. The discarded shots were made at a facility in Baltimore where there were several violations. The issues le…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inflation storm coming for housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/an-inflation-storm-is-coming-for-the-u-s-housing-market-11623419869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some economists suggest the government may be misunderstanding the size of the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district strips all holiday names to avoid offending anyone!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-jersey-school-district-removes-names-of-all-holidays-from-school-calendar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an outcry at a raucous public meeting over a previous decision to rename Columbus Day as Indigenous Peoples Day, the board of education at a New Jersey school district decided to strip all holiday names off of the school calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets all-time record low tornado activity...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/may-snaps-long-standing-us-streak-for-ef3-tornadoes/955116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been eight years since an EF5 tornado touched down in the U.S., and May ended another streak for strong tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He 'won lottery' of Israeli politics. But Naftali Bennett remains enigma...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/won-lottery-israeli-politics-naftali-180258953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naftali Bennett, a right-wing Israeli politician, now stands somewhat surprisingly on the cusp of supplanting Benjamin Netanyahu as prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV employees blamed for theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/11/italian-tv-employees-blamed-for-theft-of-dozens-of-works-of-art-rai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Priceless’ pieces removed from Rai’s offices by employees and replaced with fakes, police believe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drug That Could Break American Health Care...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/06/aduhelm-drug-alzheimers-cost-medicare/619169/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aduhelm, the first new Alzheimer’s drug in 18 years, may not work. But states and Medicare might pay billions of dollars for it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch's SUN, UK's Biggest Paper for Decades, Now Worth Zero...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/murdoch-s-sun-u-k-s-biggest-paper-for-decades-now-worth-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp. wrote down the value of its once high-flying Sun title to zero, underscoring the dramatic decline in Britain’s newspaper industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400,000 without power in Puerto Rico after fire, cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/557957-400000-without-power-in-puerto-rico-after-fire-cyberattack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were at least 400,000 people without power in Puerto Rico on Thursday night as the company that took over the island’s power transmissions has been faced with fire and cyberattack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details of torture, cover-ups in China internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/new-details-torture-cover-ups-china-s-internment-camps-revealed-n1270014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese officials spent days burning documents after government information leaked to global media exposed conditions in the camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motor neurone disease linked to 'vigorous exercise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-57431412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular and strenuous exercise can increase the risk of MND in people who are vulnerable, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden wants world to know America back. But has everyone moved on?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/g-7-summit-biden-looks-reassert-american-leadership-wary-weary-n1270278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's election has seen "a dramatic shift in America's international image," Pew said, with public opinion rebounding in a dozen key countries since he became president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-thirds of millennials have homebuyer regrets, new survey says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2021/06/11/millennials-facing-financial-and-physical-regrets-after-buying-homes/7594826002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent Bankrate survey found that 64% of millennials are facing regrets after buying a home, with the main factors being financial and physical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Op-eds in Chinese state tabloid slammed U.S. policy. Author works at Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/op-eds-in-a-chinese-state-tabloid-slammed-us-policy-the-author-works-at-the-pentagon/ar-AAKWfp2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Franz Gayl, a celebrated whistleblower and former Marine, is being investigated after attacking American policy on Taiwan in a Chinese government mouthpiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC to hold 'emergency meeting' on heart inflammation after vax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/557944-cdc-to-hold-emergency-meeting-on-heart-inflammation-after-covid-19-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An advisory panel of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention will hold an emergency meeting on June 18 to discuss rare reports of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of delta variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611100743-8vhsc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SWEDEN-VACCINE:Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of COVID delta variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowout Year for CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/11/behold-the-highest-paid-c-e-o-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to get the DealBook newsletter in your inbox each day? Sign up here. Paying (a lot) for performance Six</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 inmates escape federal lockups in 18 months; Half not caught...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-prisons-prison-breaks-business-c1979d6ad6e7b3531968dab0e61eb22d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Over the past 18 months, 29 prisoners have escaped from federal lockups across the U.S. — and nearly half still have not been caught. At some of the institutions, doors are left unlocked, security cameras are broken and officials sometimes don't notice an inmate is missing for hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars to Cans Getting Pricey as Aluminum Costs Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/cars-to-cans-risk-getting-pricey-as-japan-s-aluminum-costs-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything from a can of beer to an electric vehicle is likely to get pricier with negotiations over aluminum fees in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At El Salvador Bitcoin Beach, glimpse of crypto economy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-el-salvador-bitcoin-lifestyle-technology-d30c52b39e16ef49e4b6342fdc885c92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL ZONTE, El Salvador (AP) — After El Salvador’s congress made the bitcoin legal tender this week, eyes turned to this rural fishing village on the Pacific coast. Known to surfers for its pounding waves, El Zonte has had the cryptocurrency in its economy for the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: LAMBORGHINI Sells Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/lamborghini-is-almost-sold-out-this-year-as-pandemic-gloom-lifts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lamborghini said it’s almost sold out for the year as an easing pandemic unleashes a free-spending attitude among consumers confined to their homes for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer Young Men in Labor Force. More Living at Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/fewer-young-men-are-in-the-labor-force-more-are-living-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 25- to 34-year-olds, the two trends add up to a failure to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law enforcement struggles to recruit since killing of Floyd...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-george-floyd-racial-injustice-only-on-ap-coronavirus-pandemic-d434cc8023875ddb996abb7df0a7bc44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement agencies across the country experienced a wave of retirements and departures and are struggling to recruit the next generation of police officers in the year since George Floyd was killed by a cop .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records of aides and family members also shared...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-donald-trump-politics-ap-top-news-ca-state-wire-5b6f6bf0daf8bccf106a90d2ff52686c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department under former President Donald Trump seized data from the accounts of at least two members of the House Intelligence Committee in 2018 as part of an aggressive crackdown on leaks related to the Russia investigation and other national security matters, according to a committee official and two people familiar with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidenomics not working?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/latest-economic-figures-shows-bidenomics-is-not-working/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden Administration keeps insisting inflation is “transient,” but there are now real signs inflation is here and possibly for the long haul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas will build its own border barriers, governor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/10/greg-abbott-texas-will-build-its-own-border-barrie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If President Biden won’t build a border wall, then Texas will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of his era draws near...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-israel-middle-east-government-and-politics-9785d2410bf55bce06b893b19b3e6234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — In what appear to be the final days of his historic 12-year rule, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is not leaving the political stage quietly. The longtime leader is accusing his opponents of betraying their voters, and some have needed special security protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Bitcoin Gathering Was Hot Spot, Attendees Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/miami-bitcoin-gathering-was-a-covid-hot-spot-attendees-say/ar-AAKVjQ3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency podcaster Luke Martin said he caught Covid-19 during the Bitcoin 2021 conference in Miami last week, one of the biggest events to take place in the U.S. since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Richest Face Squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/worlds-richest-face-tax-squeeze-after-40percent-run-up-in-fortunes/ar-AAKTlik</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos has the resources to launch himself into space. Elon Musk does, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rates of anxiety and depression among college students soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Rates-of-anxiety-and-depression-among-college-16239104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College students are feeling more anxious and depressed as they sleep less and spend more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER GIVES SECOND CHANCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-toobin-returns-to-cnn-gets-grilled-about-masturbating-on-zoom-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Toobin’s had been aggressively lobbying CNN boss Jeff Zucker to allow the legal analyst back on-air, two people familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  Two passengers on first 100% vaccinated cruise in North America test positivefor Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3057850/celebrity-millennium-passengers-vaccinated-america-covid-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO passengers onboard the first fully-vaccinated cruise ship in North America have tested positive for coronavirus. The passengers, who shared a room on the Celebrity Millennium, tested positive d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Ford, 78, begins filming fifth 'INDIANA JONES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3043909/harrison-ford-indiana-jones-films-fifth-blockbuster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISON Ford has still got it as Indiana Jones aged 78 — as he begins filming the fifth blockbuster in the series. He wore the familiar fedora and leather jacket on set in Grosmont, North Yorks. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos rocket mocked for looking like giant penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3043422/amazon-jeff-bezos-space-mission-todger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON billionaire Jeff Bezos’ space mission was met with ridicule yesterday — because people think his rocket is shaped like a giant todger. Online jokers poked fun at the Blue Origin New Shepard …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man going to prison for beheading bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-gets-prison-sentence-for-beheading-bear-on-reservation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has sentenced a man to 15 months in prison for killing and then beheading a 700-pound black bear on an Indian reservation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans picking your nose...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-bans-nose-picking-spanking-24279936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hugely popular Chinese social media platform WeChat, which is heavily regulated by state authorities, has published a list of more than 70 "common violations" and "indecency," including nose picking and "spanking games"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD Federal Taxes, Spending and Deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-spending-and-deficit-all-set-records-through-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set new records in the taxes it collected, the spending it engaged in and the deficit it ran through the first eight months of fiscal 2021 (October through May), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida city bans gambling amid prospects of casino...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/557824-florida-city-bans-gambling-amid-prospects-of-trump-owned-casino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Doral in Florida’s Miami-Dade County voted unanimously on Wednesday to officially ban gambling and casinos in the city, potentially putting in jeopardy reported plans for former President Trump's Do</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL OR ARMS?</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/06/10/iranian-warship-could-be-bringing-millions-of-gallons-of-oil-to-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former oil-tanker the Iranian Navy converted into a warship could be carrying millions of gallons of fuel to Venezuela in a ploy to get around U.S. sanctions, according to photos that emerged on Persian social media. On Thursday, undated photos of IRIN Makran show the ship, designed to carry around 3 million of gallons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Giant IHEART: 'We Are Looking at Only Diverse Hires'...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/business/rob-shimshock/media-giant-iheart-we-are-looking-only-diverse-hires-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An executive producer at America's largest owner of radio stations advertised a job Thursday by stating "we are looking at only diverse hires at this time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah's Ark replica faces dilemma of biblical proportions...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/noahs-ark-replica-faces-costly-dilemma-of-biblical-proportions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This ark might need a miracle to get back home. A replica of Noah’s Ark has been stranded in the United Kingdom for a year and a half and his facing $700-a-day fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms 1st Muslim American federal judge in US history...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-confirms-1st-muslim-american-federal-judge-us/story?id=78206834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zahid Quraish is the first Muslim American federal judge to be confirmed by the United States Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Detects Suicidal Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/app-suicide-risk-sound-of-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Carol Espy-Wilson says the coordination of someone's speech gestures reflects their mental health status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNGER GAMES:  Zuckerberg goes wild boar hunting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9674091/Zuckerberg-seen-camo-carrying-bow-arrows-Hawaii-danger-hike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg and his wife Priscilla own property in Hawaii and have plans to expand on it to create a compound-like home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd FDA expert resigns over controversial Alzheimer's drug decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/10/third-member-of-fda-expert-committee-resigns-over-controversial-alzheimers-therapy-decision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kesselheim wrote that the approval of Biogen’s Aduhelm “was probably the worst drug approval decision in recent U.S. history.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unanswered 'JEOPARDY!' question: Who's the new host?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-b15ea28c004f905a24c0a8936f7797df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — “Jeopardy!” needed a host, and Lucille Ball had an enthusiastic suggestion for creator Merv Griffin: The smooth-voiced, debonair emcee of the “High Rollers” game show. That was 1984.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
