<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AI bias: How tech determines if land job, get loan or end up in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2019/10/02/how-artificial-intelligence-bias-can-work-against-you/2417711001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI helpsÂ determineÂ whether you qualify for a loan or get to be considered for a job. How can it be fair when human bias gets programmed in?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrupt Chinese mayor had 13 tons of gold and $37 BILLION in cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10049059/corrupt-chinese-mayor-300million-stash-gold-bars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OFFICIALS found a stash of gold bars and $20billion (£16.34bn) in cash in the basement of an allegedly corrupt Chinese mayor. The former mayor of Haikou City, 58-year-old Zhang Qi, allegedly also h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD BUST: Ari Emanuel IPO Dreams Fade...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-ari-emanuel-s-outsized-ipo-dreams-were-dashed-1244772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with the potential for its stock to fall below $20 on the first day — stripping hundreds of millions from its valuation — top execs pulled the plug as its headstrong CEO declares, "We’re not willing to undervalue our company."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM STRIKE BEGINS TO BITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/gm-michigan-economy-2020-4f755651-c7c4-46cd-bc5a-8a425bdc3a76.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longer the strike lasts, the worse Michigan's fragile economy becomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Declines to Share Opinion of Trump's Call with Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/bolton-declines-to-share-his-opinion-of-trumps-call-with-ukraines-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Former National Security Advisor John Bolton declined to comment on President Donald Trump's phone conversation with Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelensky, which is at the center of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's impeachment inquiry. "Did the president abuse his power with the Ukraine ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beheaded Alligator Found Alongside Florida Highway...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/10/02/beheaded-alligator-discovered-alongside-florida-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission wants to find the person responsible for beheading an alligator found on the side of a road in Sarasota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater chain warns parents not to take kids...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/10/02/joker-parents-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One theater chain is getting pretty candid about Joker. Posting a rare critical-sounding assessment of an upcoming film on its…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF: 'We're not fooling around'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fooling-house-democrat-leading-impeachment-probe/story?id=66004383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam Schiff, the Democrat leading the House impeachment effort, said sday that any efforts to interfere with their investigation would be "obstruction of justice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 'sub-launched ballistic missile' toward Japan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191002090948-4ut6o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (EXPLAINER):EXPLAINER-N.Korea's suspected submarine missile 'pushes the envelope'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid larger than bus to fly closer to Earth than Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10049076/nasa-alert-large-asteroid-close-approach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE asteroid is about to pass so close to our planet that it will actually be closer to us than the Moon. The “potentially hazardous” space rock is called 2019 SP3 and it will be zoo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October heat wave breaks records, closes schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/weather/october-heat-wave-breaks-records-closes-schools-n1061106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scorching heat is expected to continue Wednesday with temperatures from the South to the Mid-Atlantic forecast to be 10 to 20 degrees above average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much does ticket to space cost? Meet people ready to fly....</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-much-does-a-ticket-to-space-cost-Meet-the-14485562.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Lori Fraleigh unwrapped the present her husband had given her for her 38th birthday, she found a curious surprise: a model of a spaceship. It was cool, sure, but a toy would be better suited for her young children, then 5 and 1, not her.  Then she noticed the ticket. It took Fraleigh, a Silicon Valley executive, a moment to realize what her husband had purchased for her: a trip to space with Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic. "I went through a lot of crazy emotions, like, 'Did you really buy this?'" she recalled of the moment in 2011. " 'Do we still have enough money to remodel the kitchen?'"  Today, her children are 13 and 9. The kitchen remodel has long since been completed. But Fraleigh is still waiting for her trip to space.  For years, Branson has been pushing a quixotic vision for the future, where his spacecraft would ferry passengers off Earth as frequently as airplanes. But for all the talk about a new Space Age full of citizen astronauts, the journey has been fitful, and filled with setbacks, including the death of a test pilot in 2014 after a harrowing crash.  But now, 15 years after Branson founded Virgin Galactic, space tourism could be tantalizingly close to becoming a reality. The company has flown to the edge of space twice and says its first paying customers could reach space next year. Another space venture, Blue Origin, founded by Amazon founder and chief executive Jeff Bezos almost 20 years ago, hopes to conduct its first test flight with people this year, though it hasn't announced prices or sold any tickets. (Bezos owns The Washington Post.)  And NASA recently announced that it would allow private citizens to fly to the International Space Station on spacecraft built by SpaceX and Boeing.  Which means that Fraleigh may soon finally get her five minutes of weightlessness, a view that promises to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan housing prices in near 'free fall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-housing-prices-in-near-free-fall-conditions-mirror-recession-era-following-tax-hikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan real estate market stumbled in the third quarter of 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of mass shooter at 'JOKER' opening put cops across country on alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7529241/Fears-incel-mass-shooter-Joker-opening-weekend-cops-country-high-alert.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationwide, police departments and even the Army have issued security alerts and planned stepped up patrols for Joker's theatrical release on Thursday afternoon, as theater chains also prep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House will subpoena White House for Ukraine documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/02/house-will-subpoena-white-house-ukraine-documents-in-trump-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of a leading House committee on Wednesday said he plans to issue a subpoena to the White House for documents related to Ukraine as part of an ongoing impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump. The subpoena will be issued Friday, said Rep. Elijah Cummings, D-Maryland, the head of the House Oversight and Reform Commmittee, in a memo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren passes Biden in weekly national poll...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/463997-warren-passes-biden-to-lead-field-by-4-points-nationally-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  29% of Republicans say Trump 'DID NOT' mention Biden on call...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/463948-poll-just-40-percent-of-republicans-say-trump-probably-mentioned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 4 in 10 Republicans say they think President Trump discussed an investigation into Democratic presidential rival Joe Biden during a phone call with Ukraine's president, despite Trump acknowledging having done so,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joaquin 'Embarrassed' By Expletive-Laden Outtake Clip...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/joker-joaquin-phoenix-jimmy-kimmel-outtake-embarrassed-expletive-laden-clip-1202750039/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin Phoenix seemed to get a surprise last night on the Jimmy Kimmel Live! show when he was confronted with a behind-the-scenes Joker clip capturing him in an expletive-laden rant…Or did h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Frightening Videos Surface Of TESLA 'Smart' Summon Feature...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/technology/frightening-videos-surface-teslas-smart-summon-feature</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hotel mystery: Giant reservations followed by empty rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/02/trump-hotel-empty-rooms-016763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTOROLA becoming major player in govt surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/motorola-company-known-cellphones-fast-becoming-major-player-government-surveillance-n1059551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motorola Solutions is among the tech firms racing to deliver new ways of monitoring the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre deaths of bulls baffle Oregon police and residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-10-01/oregon-bizarre-deaths-bulls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mutilated Hereford bull carcasses have been turning up. So far, authorities are at a loss for an explanation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rebirth of Celine Dion: 'Life is short. Can we just have a good time?'</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2019-10-02/celine-dion-courage-tour-dionaissance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years after the death of her husband-manager, and rebranded as an avant-garde style icon, the balladeer has returned with a new album and world tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren continues attack after Zuckerberg warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/elizabeth-warren-attack-facebook-mark-zuckerberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren continued her attack on Facebook after audio comments from CEO Mark Zuckerberg were leaked, with Warren stating the company "won't even do the bare minimum to improve transparency."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's first cannabis cafe lights up West Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7528167/Marijuana-enthusiasts-queue-block-Americas-cannabis-cafe-Lowell-Farms-opens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's first cannabis cafe offering guests farm-to-table cuisine alongside vaping, joints, bongs and prepackaged edibles has opened in West Hollywood on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest mall owner -- going online...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/02/the-biggest-mall-owner-in-the-us-is-going-online.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest mall owner in the U.S., Simon Property Group, is teaming up with online shopping company Rue La La's owner to launch a new kind of website. Simon has been testing a site in beta for the past few months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SPOOKED... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/02/dow-futures-trump-trade-manufacturing-data-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Wednesday, adding to Wall Street's poor start to the final quarter of 2019 as investors grapple with fears of an economic recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring slows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/02/adp-jobs-report-private-payrolls-grow-but-hiring-slows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies hired 135,000 more workers in the month, ahead of the 125,000 that economists surveyed by Dow Jones had expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final home designed by Frank Lloyd Wright set for auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/photos-final-home-designed-by-frank-lloyd-wright-to-go-up-for-auction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary Norman Lykes house, designed by architect Frank Lloyd Wright, will be sold at auction on Oct. 16. It was the last residence designed by Wright, who also designed the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 millennials keeping money secret from partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/1-in-4-millennials-is-keeping-a-money-secret-from-their-partner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One-third of millennials would consider breaking up with their partner because of a financial secret, such as hidden debt or a bad credit score. Yet, a quarter of those polled admitted that they're also hiding something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Earthquake Swarms Hit Texas, Oklahoma, San Francisco...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/signs-of-the-times-earthquake-swarms-hit-texas-oklahoma-san-francisco-and-the-new-madrid-fault-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a whole lotta shaking going on in America right now, and many people are concerned about what that could potentially mean.  Could it be possible that the U.S. is entering a more seismically active time?  This week alone, we have seen earthquake swarms in Texas, Oklahoma, San Francisco and t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Americans who think monarchy would solve political problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2019/oct/01/the-rise-of-monarchism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are searching for a return to tradition, some are yearning for stability, while for others the rise of Trump is the spur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Must Pass Facial Recognition Test to Surf Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/beijing-launches-new-rule-residents-must-pass-facial-recognition-test-to-surf-internet_3099181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theepochtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese regime announced a new rule which requires residents to pass a facial recognition test in order ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro-backed highway targets heart of Brazil's Amazon...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-environment-highway-insight/bolsonaro-backed-highway-targets-heart-of-brazils-amazon-idUSKBN1WH0Z3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deforestation in Brazil is the story of highways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Changing Delegate Rules to Prevent Discord at Convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/02/republicans-changing-delegate-rules-to-prevent-discord-at-convention/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - President Trump’s political advisers have concluded a monthslong effort to tighten the rules for choosing delegates to the Republican National Convention,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore 'fake news' law takes effect as critics sound alarm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/singapores-fake-news-law-takes-effect-critics-sound-053322467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore's new law to combat "fake news" came into effect Wednesday despite criticism from tech giants and activists, who labelled the tough rules a "chilling" attempt to stifle dissent. The law gives government ministers powers to order social media sites to put warnings next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu tries to avert indictment as he fights for political life...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-netanyahu/netanyahu-tries-to-avert-indictment-as-he-fights-for-political-life-idUSKBN1WH0U3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu began his final attempt to fend off a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Food shortages, hyperinflation in Venezuela forcing thousands to leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b4eb44ddd03747eb83b9b216951b91c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO, Venezuela (AP) — Midday is approaching and the bus terminal in this border town is in a frenzy. Merchants heading for the center of Venezuela hop on buses and load them with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'House of torture' puts focus on Islamic schools...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-torture-puts-focus-nigeria-islamic-schools-031319157.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrific revelations of torture and abuse at a compound billing itself as a Koranic reform school in northern Nigeria have shone a spotlight on Islamic institutes unregulated by the authorities. Last week police in the city of Kaduna raided a building to find hundreds of men and boys -- some reportedly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protests Set to Escalate as Shooting Stirs Anger...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-protests-set-escalate-104146570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A Hong Kong police officer who fired a bullet into the chest of an 18-year-old protester may have inadvertently given new life to the months-long movement challenging Beijing’s authority.Demonstrators hit the streets again on Wednesday following the release of videos showing the man getting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece struggles to cope as migrant arrivals soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greece-struggles-cope-migrant-arrivals-soar-094539041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hulking Greek coastguard officer gazed intently as another group of migrants, the fifth of the day, boarded a minibus after landing on a beach on the island of Lesbos. "We're taking it day by day," he sighed, amid talk of a new refugee crisis, four years after nearly one million asylum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's first cannabis cafe lights up West Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americas-first-cannabis-cafe-opens-hollywood-084416643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's first cannabis restaurant has opened in West Hollywood, offering diners an array of weed products and hoping to rival Amsterdam's famed coffee shops. Called Lowell Farms: A Cannabis Cafe, the much-hyped 240-seat establishment is open to people 21 and over, who can order from a cannabis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Spend More on Taxes Than Food, Clothing, Health Care -- Combined!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/americans-spent-more-taxes-2018-food-clothing-and-health-care-combined</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grocery shopper in Los Angeles on July 24, 2019. (Photo by Mark RALSTON/AFP/Getty Images) Americans on average spent more on taxes in 2018 than they did on the basic necessities of food, clothing and health care combined, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics Consumer Expenditure Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This robot can make 300 pizzas in hour...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/business/technology/this-robot-can-make-300-pizzas-in-an-hour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch out pizza world: this pizza robot could shake things up. Seattle startup Picnic announced Tuesday that it has a developed a unit that can make 300 12-inch pizzas per hour and 180 18-inch pizzas per hour. We are excited to unveil our first-of-its-kind intelligent food assembly platform. See us</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLY AND THE BEAST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0c0b700b58048838a70906979f93b83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Setting a defiant tone, the Trump administration resisted Congress' access to impeachment witnesses, even as House Democrats warned such efforts themselves could amount to an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipwrecked drug smugglers survive shark-infested waters by clinging to cocaine bails...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191001-shipwrecked-colombians-clung-to-cocaine-bales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipwrecked Colombians clung to cocaine bales</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watergate Prosecutor to Represent Rudy...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/01/rudy-giuliani-taps-watergate-prosecutor-jon-sale-to-represent-him-in-ukraine-impeachment-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani has tapped Watergate prosecutor Jon Sale to represent him in the ongoing Democrat-led impeachment probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD TO DEPLOY UNDERCOVER OFFICERS FOR 'JOKER' OPENING...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/joker-movie-theaters-new-york-police-plan-opening-weekend-undercover-1202749565/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Amid concerns about potential violent situations, the opening weekend of Warner Bros’ controversial Joker in New York City will see an increased police presence both in and out of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaking classified information is 'thievery, not protected speech,' Justice Dept says... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Leaking-classified-information-is-thievery-not-14484074.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. - A contractor accused of leaking classified information engaged in "thievery, not protected speech," and has no First Amendment grounds to challenge his Espionage Act prosecutions, the Justice Department said in an Alexandria federal court filing.  Former intelligence analyst Daniel Hale shared National Security Agency details of drone warfare with the website The Intercept, according to an indictment filed in May. His defense attorneys argued last month that the law was designed to deal with spies, not leakers, and that the prosecution runs afoul of the First Amendment by chilling newsgathering and implicating the reporter who received the information.  It's an argument that probably will resurface if Julian Assange, facing prosecution in the same courthouse for publishing classified information, is ever extradited. The government rarely prosecuted leakers until President Barack Obama's tenure, and the Trump administration is the first president to prosecute the publisher of classified information along with the leaker.  Prosecutors pushed back in their own motion Monday, saying Hale signed nondisclosure agreements that made the law clear.  "Hale expressly waived in writing his right to disclose the national security information he obtained while in his government position," Assistant U.S. Attorney Alexander Berrang wrote.  Whether Congress intended the Espionage Act to cover leaks when the law was drafted during World War I, Berrang says, "may be interesting thought exercises but are irrelevant to the case at hand."  He also called it "dubious" to suggest there should be any legal distinction between leakers and spies.  "While spies typically pass classified national defense information to a specific foreign government, leakers, through the internet,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any challenge to his presidency is attack on America... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-Trump-s-telling-a-challenge-to-his-presidency-14484365.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - For President Donald Trump, the impeachment case being built by Democrats over his alleged effort to recruit foreign help for his reelection effort isn't just a "WITCH HUNT," though he calls it that, too; it's "treason." It isn't just "presidential harassment," though he also makes that charge; it's an invitation to "Civil War."  The president is bringing the rhetorical heavy artillery to the most serious challenge to his presidency in nearly three tumultuous, norm-busting, warp-speed years in office.  Expanding on the lexicon of outrage and victimhood honed during the probe into Russian interference in the last election, Trump is invoking the muskets-and-ramparts idioms of the country's beginnings.  The ratcheting up of his rhetoric is also indicative of Trump's tendency to interpret any criticism of him as an attack on the government, worrying critics and scholars who warn of the dangers posed by his l'état, c'est moi call to arms.  "Charging anyone with treason is a most unusual act in American history. It's an incendiary charge which relates to the ultimate crime: overthrow of the state," said Michael Glennon, an international law professor at the Fletcher School at Tufts University.  In setting out a definition and consequences for treason in the Constitution, including death, the Founders were guarding against the "danger that the charge of treason could be made irresponsibly against political opponents," he said, adding that cavalierly throwing around words like treason and civil war belies their unique meaning in American history.  "I suppose it has an incendiary effect on some supporters, but we are dealing with dynamite here," Glennon said.  Trump has focused his most pointed comments on Rep. Adam Schiff, a California Democrat and chairman of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower protections tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-disregards-whistleblower-protections-as-polls-turn-against-him-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump wants to interview the whistleblower who prompted an impeachment inquiry. And polls suggest he's losing public support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rules Say Senate Must Act, but Its Act Might Be a Swift Dismissal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/01/us/politics/senate-trump-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As both sides prepare for a potential Senate impeachment showdown, the focus is on how quickly Republicans might move to jettison the accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT'S A COUP!'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-calls-impeachment-inquiry-coup-n1061036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump tweet came about 12 hours after Trump adviser Peter Navarro called the impeachment inquiry an "attempted coup d'etat'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Nunes lawsuit: Congressman sues magazine over story about family's Iowa farm...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article235667107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Impeachment Moves Forward, Trump's Language Turns Darker...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/02/as-impeachment-moves-forward-trumps-language-turns-darker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — President Trump’s language has changed in the days since House Democrats began their impeachment inquiry. The presidential Twitter feed still</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems vow obstruction charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/state-nation-world/democrats-may-consider-obstruction-charges-against-trump-in-impeachment-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald Trump, desperate to undermine a fast-moving impeachment probe, could be adding to his troubles. House Democrats say Trump’s stonewalling and threats to unmask a whistleblower could lead to obstruction charges if articles of impeachment are drafted over the president’s r</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HONG KONG TURNS WARZONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7523839/Hong-Kong-protesters-throw-eggs-Chinas-President-Xi-Jinpings-portrait-National-Day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police have urged the public to stay indoors after an 18-year-old protester was shot in the chest by an anti-riot officer during a clash. The young activist was said to be in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI: NO FORCE CAN STOP CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7523145/Chinas-70-year-parade-economic-military-might.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China held a massive celebration in Beijing Tuesday to mark the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People's Republic, featuring a huge military display and a civilian parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANUFACTURING INDEX LOWEST IN DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/us-manufacturing-economy-contracts-to-worst-level-in-a-decade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A monthly gauge of U.S. manufacturing showed its worst reading in more than 10 years in September as exports dived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Movie way too full of itself'...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/arts/film-tv/2019/10/01/review-joaquin-phoenix-is-a-vivid-operatic-joker-but-the-movie-is-way-too-full-of-itself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Joker” is a flagrantly seedy movie. Welcome to Gotham City, where the weak are killed and eaten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoot Them in the Legs, Trump Suggested: Inside His Border War...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/463928-trump-suggested-shooting-migrants-in-the-legs-nyt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump suggested having migrants shot in their legs during a March meeting with White House advisers in the Oval Office,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump be impeached and reelected?</title>
      <link>https://theconversation.com/could-president-trump-be-impeached-and-convicted-but-also-reelected-124384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theconversation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known provision of the Constitution might allow Trump to be reelected president in 2020 even if he is removed from office through the impeachment process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2019/10/01/video-riot-cop-shoots-hong-kong-protester-in-chest-with-live-round/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic escalation in force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appear to be ballistic missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/north-korea-launches-apparent-missile-japans-coast-guard-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea has launched what appeared to be a missile, Japan's coast guard said in a statement on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THURSDAY:  Former Ukraine envoy to testify...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/former-ukraine-envoy-volker-testify-impeachment-inquiry-thursday-n1061001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volker will be deposed before members of the House Intel, Foreign Affairs and Oversight Committees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff has dossier of insider information from DEUTSCHE BANK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7526427/Adam-Schiff-dossier-insider-information-Donald-Trumps-main-lender-Deutsche-bank.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drug-using whistleblower gained access to a trove of information about Deutsche Bank after the death of his bank exec father, and the House Intelligence Committee has obtained it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Urgent' State Dept IG Briefing on Hill...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/state-dept-inspector-general-expected-urgent-ukraine-briefing/story?id=65991911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department 's inspector general was expected to give an 'urgent' briefing on Capitol Hill Wednesday on documents related to Ukraine and the State Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With liberal bloc aging, Trump may get more Supreme Court appointments...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-justices/with-liberal-bloc-aging-trump-may-get-more-supreme-court-appointments-idUSKBN1WG3PB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 86-year-old liberal Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg enduring a series of health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making paper out of stone -- and saving lots of trees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/01/success/stone-paper-karst-entrepreneurs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian entrepreneurs Kevin Garcia and Jon Tse are on a mission to save trees by producing paper products from stone waste</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President, RNC raise $125 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3b5b5d61556f4ca49402477de9d28bdb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's reelection campaign and the Republican National Committee raised $125 million in the third quarter of the year, a presidential fundraising...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philadelphia First Major City To Ban Cashless Stores...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/01/philadelphia-becomes-1st-major-us-city-to-ban-cashless-stores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill prevents most retail locations from refusing to take cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House ordered top-secret system upgraded to prevent leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/01/white-house-trump-leaks-code-015194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY LAWYERS UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/01/politics/giuliani-hires-watergate-prosecutor/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida attorney Jon Sale, who worked as an assistant prosecutor on the legal team investigating the Watergate scandal, is representing Rudy Giuliani in the matter of the congressional impeachment inquiry, Giuliani and Sale both confirmed to CNN on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLPHINS Stadium Vendor Charges Fan $724 For 2 Beers...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/10/01/hard-rock-stadium-beer-vendor-accused-of-using-personal-card-reader-to-charge-fan-724-for-2-beers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A football fan who went to see the Los Angeles Chargers beat the Miami Dolphins at Hard Rock Stadium on Sunday was shocked when he received a message from his credit card company saying he had just been charged $724 for two beers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARTIAN SOUNDS CAPTURED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0c9f5e3d9a2240a69ea73dcf317b7b89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA's InSight lander on Mars has captured the low rumble of marsquakes and a symphony of other otherworldly sounds. Scientists released an audio sampling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer banned 3 years for obscene gesture...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2019/10/01/bio-kim-korean-tour-obscene-gesture/40229311/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Korean Professional Golfers Association suspended Bio Kim for three years for making an obscene gesture towards the gallery during a final round.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runner killed by lightning as he finishes 50k race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/runner-killed-by-lightning-while-finishing-50k-race-in-southeast-kansas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A runner has been killed by lightning as he was about to finish a 50 kilometer (31.07 miles) race in southeast Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian alcohol consumption down 43%...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49892339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 43% decline follows a series of alcohol-control measures implemented by the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters: Trump should be 'imprisoned &amp; placed in solitary confinement'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/463859-maxine-waters-trump-should-be-imprisoned-and-placed-in-solitary-confinement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan, Harry sue MAIL ON SUNDAY over publication of private letter...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/meghan-and-harry-to-sue-mail-on-sunday-over-publication-of-private-letter-11824783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry issued a powerful statement criticising some of the press for "continual misrepresentations" of his wife, Meghan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sword-wielding student kills 1, wounds 9 at Finland school...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5048f34db7a408295d543c35e2fb5b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — A man wielding a sword and a firearm killed a woman and wounded nine others Tuesday at a vocational school inside a shopping center in central Finland, police said. The attacker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In memorializing Khashoggi, WASH POST gives platform to top jailer of reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/1/memorializing-jamal-khashoggi-washington-post-give/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been a year since the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in Istanbul. Mr. Khashoggi wore many professional hats throughout his career, one of which was as a freelance online blogger for Washington’s other newspaper — I believe it’s called the “Post?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When NASA finds life on Mars, world may not be ready, agency chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/30/us/nasa-life-on-mars-jim-green-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's next mission to Mars will be its most advanced yet. But if scientists discover there was once life -- or there is life -- on the Red Planet, will the public be able to handle such an extraterrestrial concept?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Now Offering Degrees In Esports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/college-esports-universities-launch-degrees-in-esports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shenandoah University and The Ohio State University are among training students to enter the growing esports field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH!</title>
      <link>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/woman-enters-exhibit-dances-front-lion-bronx-zoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;1010wins.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (1010 WINS) -- A woman that climbed over the safety barrier and entered the African lion exhibit at the Bronx Zoo over the weekend can be seen waving and dancing in front of one of the lions in a video posted to Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar after research claims red meat poses no health risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2019/sep/30/research-red-meat-poses-no-health-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One expert says findings by international experts represent ‘egregious abuse of evidence’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark trends in American society call for 'spiritual warfare'?</title>
      <link>https://www.patheos.com/blogs/thefreethinker/2019/10/dark-trends-in-american-society-call-for-greater-spiritual-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.patheos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Oregon exorcist, who claims he has had the ability to conquer satanic forces since he was four, warned last week that modern American society, with its interest in things such as drugs and ouija boards, needs to take demonic possession more seriously. "Archbishop" James Cloud, above, insisted that, "as the years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Woman climbs into Bronx Zoo exhibit, taunts lion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Bronx-Zoo-Lion-561880561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman climbed over a visitor safety barrier at the Bronx Zoo's African lion exhibit over the weekend, according to the zoo and video of the encounter that was posted online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Congratulates Communist China on Its 70th Anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/while-trump-congratulates-communist-china-on-its-70th-anniversary-senate-republicans-condemn-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy years ago today, Mao Zedong declared the People’s Republic of China after his Communist forces had conquered most of the mainland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRASSLEY: Whistleblower Followed Law and Should Be Heard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/grassley-whistleblower-followed-the-law-and-should-be-heard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal policy wasn’t secretly changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Robots hurting your pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-01/robots-are-hurting-u-s-workers-wages-regional-fed-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Sets Second American Civil War TV Series For 2020...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/ava-duvernay-hbo-max-pilot-dmz-roberto-patino-1202749125/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hot off a big Emmy win for When They See Us, Ava DuVernay is set to launch her second project based on a DC Comics property Already primed to directed a big-screen adaptation of Jack Kirby’s New Go…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE FIRES BACK!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/elizabeth-warren-tears-into-facebook-over-leaked-mark-zuckerberg-audio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO railed against the presidential candidate’s plan to break up big tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Raises Massive $25 Million, Largest Of Cycle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-raises-massive-dollar253-million-in-third-quarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quarter is among his best in both presidential campaigns he’s run and perhaps the largest of the 2020 cycle thus far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four earthquakes in 13 hours rattle Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article235663322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quake swarm hits San Francisco area with 5 shakes in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/california/article235664912.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani's Ukraine ally leaves trail of debts:  'He conned us from day one'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article235626327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St starting to believe she may win nomination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/elizabeth-warrens-rise-has-some-analysts-uneasy-on-health-care-tech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raymond James says Wall Street is underestimating Elizabeth Warren's odds of winning the White House in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Captured After 17 Years Living in Cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/crime/2019/09/30/chinese-fugitive-captured-after-17-years-living-cave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted human trafficker Song Jiang was apprehended on September 19, after 17 years spent hiding alone in a remote cave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAT FALLS FROM WHITE HOUSE CEILING!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/463815-reporters-scramble-after-mouse-falls-from-white-house-ceiling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House reporters were sent into a panic Tuesday morning after a mouse fell from the ceiling of the press booth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodel confronts prankster who stormed Paris runway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/01/gigi-hadid-confronts-crasher-who-stormed-chanel-runway-at-paris-fashion-week/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gigi Hadid escorted her off the stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon fired official trying to cut billions in waste...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-promised-to-save-billions-of-dollars-on-military-contracts-then-the-pentagon-pushed-out-the-official-responsible-for-doing-that-090005221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shay Assad was known as the Defense Department’s toughest contract negotiator and was praised for saving the government billions. Yet within two years of Donald Trump’s entrance into the White House, Assad would be removed from his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French ex-president Sarkozy to face trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-ex-president-sarkozy-face-campaign-finance-trial-135003150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French court on Tuesday ordered Nicolas Sarkozy to stand trial for illicit campaign financing, adding to the ex-president's legal woes as he also prepares to answer charges of exerting pressure on a judge. Sarkozy, 64, lost his final appeal to France's highest criminal court, and risks a year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Audience Chants 'Lock HIM Up'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-colbert-crowd-chants-lock-him-hillary-begins-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I created a monster — I apologize’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Gas Prices Soar Past $4...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/09/30/southern-california-los-angeles-4-dollar-gas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks of daily price hikes have sent the average price of a gallon of self-serve regular gasoline well over the $4 mark across the region, even in outlying areas where prices are usually cheaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Sentences U.S. Spies to Death...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-issues-death-prison-sentences-for-accused-u-s-spies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has issued a death sentence for an individual it has accused of spying for the United States, according to the Islamic Republic's judiciary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Pompeo accuses Dems of bullying; Rejects subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d98be4ffbaa4462b9454cca0a8a7e88a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Secretary of State Mike Pompeo on Tuesday declared that House Democrats are trying to "intimidate, bully and treat improperly" five current and former career officials in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off message: A Republican takes heat for impeachment remarks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8f2925fda234310b0eb3e795e6d076f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — GOP Rep. Mark Amodei's comment seemed harmless enough. Asked what he thought of the Democrats' impeachment probe into President Donald Trump, the Nevada Republican gave reporters...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
