<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Will This Warhol Become Most Expensive Artwork Ever Sold?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2022/04/will-this-warhol-become-the-most-expensive-artwork-ever-sold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When one of the pop artist’s famed portraits of Marilyn Monroe goes to auction next month, some observers think it could fetch up to half a billion dollars. What is it about this particular work that gives it such potential to break the market?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China holds drills around Taiwan as U.S. lawmakers visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/15/china-holds-military-drills-around-taiwan-as-us-delegation-visits.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China said it conducted military drills around Taiwan on Friday, as a U.S. Congressional delegation visited the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Memo Deepens Mystery of Possible Interstellar Visitor to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/military-memo-deepens-mystery-of-possible-interstellar-visitor-to-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2014, a dishwasher-size meteor dashed over the shores of Papua New Guinea before sunrise as it burned up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France election, meaty issue unites Jews, Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-france-europe-paris-marine-le-pen-d77606f09df17415b94c273eb71be489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — As she cooks lunch and talks politics, Jewish voter Sarah Gutmann has a nasty feeling — of would-be French president Marine Le Pen invading the privacy of her home, reaching directly into her life and the plates of chicken and kosher sausages that she is frying for her husband and their eldest son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Arizona man stuffed 183 animals in freezer, some alive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-lizards-animals-turtles-snakes-20039b4f1dea6cfa24613f11f9d477f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLDEN VALLEY, Ariz. (AP) — An Arizona man faces animal cruelty charges after 183 dead dogs, rabbits, birds and other animals were found in a freezer, including some that were apparently frozen while alive, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS COLLECT RECORD TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/2121987000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $2,121,987,000,000 in total taxes through the first six months of fiscal 2022 (October through March), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wolf of Crypto: Belfort Marketing Self as Digital Currency Guru...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/the-wolf-of-crypto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, Fla. — Jordan Belfort was lounging by the pool on a sunny April morning, sipping Red Bull and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Director Airs Concern He Might Turn to Nukes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/14/c-i-a-director-airs-concern-that-putin-might-turn-to-nuclear-weapons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The director of the C.I.A. said on Thursday that Russian President Vladimir V. Putin’s “potential desperation” to extract</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS POLICE VICIOUS IN SHANGHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718709/Video-shows-cops-pin-arrest-Shanghai-locals-resist-homes-isolation-hubs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shanghai cops and health officials pinned down residents as they fought attempts to turn their homes into quarantine hubs. Videos circulated on Weibo before being deleted show scuffles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESISTANCE AT COVID CAMPS</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/jenniferatntd/status/1514619855340814337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Shooter Worked for AMAZON, DOORDASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gjgv/frank-james-nyc-subwayshooter-amazon-doordash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank James, accused of opening fire on a New York subway car, railed about working at Amazon in at least one of his hundreds of videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA astronauts not ready for deep space...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/14/nasa-artemis-moon-explorer-astronauts-00025099</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space agency still hasn't developed the training or equipment — even the space suits — needed to live and work on the moon and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To find out where pandemic is headed, look in sewer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/to-find-out-where-the-covid-pandemic-is-headed-look-here-the-sewer/ar-AAWe4eY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan finally reunite with Queen amid family feud...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/04/14/prince-harry-meghan-markle-reunite-with-queen-prince-charles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sussexes have seen the Queen — and Prince Charles — together for the first time in more than 2 years, Page Six can confirm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense minister has 'massive heart attack not from natural causes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718247/Putins-defence-minister-Sergei-Shoigu-massive-heart-attack-not-natural-causes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoigu, Putin's right hand man and leader of the Russian army for a decade, was a mainstay in the early weeks of the war in Ukraine but recently disappeared from Kremlin briefings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor injected 2 men with fatal doses of drugs in sexually deviant pattern...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ed-buck-face-judgment-injecting-120014614.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Buck, once a fixture of West Hollywood's political scene, was sentenced to 30 years for drug and sex crimes that led to the deaths of two men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social-Media Campaign to Label Bucha Massacre 'Hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-wages-social-media-campaign-to-label-bucha-massacre-a-hoax/ar-AAWeCvR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Lies, and UFOs: Pentagon Head of Counterintelligence and Security Ousted...</title>
      <link>https://thedebrief.org/sex-lies-and-ufos-pentagons-head-of-counterintelligence-and-security-ousted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedebrief.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Debrief's two year investigation into the Pentagon's recently ousted chief of counterintelligence, Afghan refugee evacuations, and UAP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Buck sentenced to 30 years for injecting two men with fatal doses of drugs in sexually deviant pattern...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/ed-buck-sentencing-west-hollywood-political-donor/11748027/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Democratic donor Ed Buck was sentenced to 30 years in prison in connection with the overdose deaths of two men in West Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Rose Back: Scores Major Interview with Warren Buffett...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/04/14/charlie-rose-is-back-former-cbs-pbs-newscaster-posts-in-depth-interview-with-warren-buffett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver repeatedly runs over woman in road rage attack...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/14/driver-repeatedly-runs-over-woman-in-shocking-road-rage-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The harrowing footage captured Tuesday by a witness in Elizabeth shows the moment Vincent Jean, 56, drove his silver Mitsubishi SUV over the 23-year-old victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money for nothing: Receipt for 'invisible art' sells for $1.2M...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2022/apr/14/receipt-for-invisible-art-auction-yves-klein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A receipt written by the French artist Yves Klein auctioned by Sotheby’s in Paris has been hailed as a precursor to NFTs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare on N Train: Inside terrifying Brooklyn subway shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nightmare-on-the-n-train-inside-the-terrifying-moments-during-the-brooklyn-subway-shooting/ar-AAWdoFu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida pastors seek salvation in real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/14/miami-church-real-estate-first-presbyterian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As membership plummets, church leaders are looking for new ways to make ends meet. Some congregants say they’re selling out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds cold-blooded execution of MICROSOFT exec...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718831/Florida-widow-begs-help-finding-husbands-killer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police still have no leads after Jared Bridegan, 33, was gunned down on February 16 when he got out of his family's black Volkswagen Atlas in Jacksonville Beach to move a tire in the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Newsom already running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/Gavin-Newsom-needs-a-reality-check-17078264.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's painfully obvious Newsom wants to run for president one day."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Vegan Diets Healthiest For Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-health-go-vegan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings suggest that "nutritionally sound" vegan diets may be healthier and less hazardous than conventional or raw meat-based diets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Director: Nuke threat not taken 'lightly'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-04-14-22/h_312213803972ddfd3de6696c16f4d172</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US and EU have pledged a combined $1.3 billion more in military aid for Ukraine as Russia prepares to launch an eastern offensive. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tall can Mount Everest grow?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220407-how-tall-will-mount-everest-get-before-it-stops-growing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arching over 8,849 metres (29,032ft) into the sky, Everest is the world’s tallest mountain. But will it always be? 8,848.86</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eextremist Jews arrested for planning animal sacrifice atop Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/four-extremist-jews-arrested-for-planning-animal-sacrifice-atop-temple-mount/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goat found at suspect's home, following Facebook post offering cash prize for animal sacrifices at locale; police vow to work 24/7 against anyone violating order at flashpoint site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Hit by missiles traveling 650mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5123349/russian-warship-ukraine-disaster-general-belgrano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINIAN forces used some of their newest missiles to blow up an ageing Soviet-era Russian warship in the biggest naval loss sink Britain sunk the General Belgrano. Slava-class missile cruiser Mos…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest woman to get inked; 105 year old flaunts multiple tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/gran-105-becomes-oldest-tattooed-26714802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epifania Maria de Jesus Mendes, 105, from Brazil, has become the oldest woman to get inked as she showed off her collection of tattoos in a bid for a Guinness World Record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Bury the Race of Murderers -- If They're Not White?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/yes-the-media-bury-the-race-of-murderers-if-theyre-not-white/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank James, the man arrested for Tuesday's New York City subway shooting, is a black nationalist and outspoken racist who railed against whites, Jews, and Hispanics. A careful reader of the New York Times could be forgiven for overlooking that. In a nearly-2,000 word article on the attack, James's race is not mentioned. The same is true for the coverage offered up by ABC News and Reuters; the Washington Post only mentioned James's race in relation to his condemnation of training programs for "low-income Black youths."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  BIDEN APPROVAL CRASHES TO 33%</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10716929/Bidens-approval-craters-33.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's approval rating stands at 33 per cent among American adults in a Quinnipiac University Poll released Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump teases health issues for 2024 race withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/3267190-will-trump-practice-the-art-of-withdrawal-ahead-of-2024-presidential-primaries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Trump, 2016-like numbers of primary opponents are the polar opposite of what he expects — more reasons a crowded primary might prompt the face-saving medical card</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli laser defense system able to intercept drones, missiles in test...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-14/israeli-laser-defense-system-able-to-intercept-drones-missiles-in-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cronenberg Returns to Body Horror in 'CRIMES OF THE FUTURE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/movies/movie-news/david-cronenberg-crimes-of-the-future-trailer-1337622/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film will premiere at the Cannes Film Festival in May</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes 2022: 15 Surprises and Snubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2022/04/cannes-selection-announcement-2022-surprises-snubs-1234716816/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s lineup may be far from finished, but it already offers a grab bag of global cinema ripe for exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Candidate Who Could Crush Dem Dreams in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meet-candidate-could-crush-dem-003108436.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast/Betsy JohnsonDemocrats in Oregon have long enjoyed party dominance and an absence of viable opposition. The governor’s mansion especially has been blue for decades, with party outsiders seemingly unable to change its hue no matter the year.But in 2022, former state Sen. Betsy Johnson might force that to change.She’s well-funded, with millions in her coffers and no need to spend money on winning a party nomination. She’s drawing endorsements fr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador president's mass arrests 'punitive populism'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-nayib-bukele-el-salvador-gangs-crime-a4fe92cb4125fa67679310e6d88b9307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA TECLA, El Salvador (AP) — A day after the bloodletting -- 62 gang killings that convulsed El Salvador -- the crackdown began. Before dawn on Sunday, March 27, just hours after congress approved a state of emergency, heavily armed police and soldiers entered the packed, gang-controlled neighborhood of San Jose El Pino.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit fighter captured...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5124015/brit-fighter-captured-ukraine-first-pictures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HERO Brit captured by Russian forces while fighting for Ukraine has been pictured in captivity for the first time. Aiden Aslin’s picture was shared by a pro-Donetsk People’s Republic …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cholesterol Protects Against Alzheimer's?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/good-cholesterol-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with more small HDL particles in their cerebrospinal fluid show two key signs that they have more protection against Alzheimer’s disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Buck to face judgment for injecting two men with fatal doses of drugs in sexually deviant pattern...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/ed-buck-face-judgment-injecting-120014072.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted of injecting two men with fatal doses of drugs, Ed Buck will be sentenced Thursday. Prosecutors have asked a judge to send Buck to prison for life, while his lawyers have requested a sentence that would one day allow him to rejoin society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Sales Show Impact of Surging Gas Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/markets/retail-sales-slow-in-march-as-gas-prices-inflation-trim-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high gas prices and the fastest inflation in forty years continue to hold back consumer spending, with March retail sales slowing from their February levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youth voter drive battles apathy -- and could help Lula...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-youth-voter-drive-battles-apathy-and-could-help-lula/ar-AAWdxh2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Supreme Court weighs abortion, Christians challenge what it means to be 'pro-life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-weighs-abortion-christians-090036279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican Party, evangelical Christianity and the antiabortion movement have long been inextricably linked. Some Christians want to change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Talk of race, sex in schools divides Americans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-only-on-ap-lifestyle-education-dcf725bafd7d6852a9377c9cdeba700d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Americans are deeply divided over how much children in K-12 schools should be taught about racism and sexuality, according to a new poll released as Republicans across the country aim to make parental involvement in education a central campaign theme this election year .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleagues worry Feinstein mentally unfit to serve, citing recent interactions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/dianne-feinstein-senate-17079487.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four U.S. senators, including three Democrats, as well as three former staffers and a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad Losing Control of His Own Spiraling Minions...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/lonely-putin-losing-control-own-085725849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyAfter a series of embarrassing setbacks in trying to capture Ukraine’s capital, Kyiv, over the past 40-odd days, Russian President Vladimir Putin has ultimately decided to have his forces retreat, and regroup to go after eastern Ukraine. But his cronies can’t seem to get the picture straight.Putin loyalist Ramzan Kadyrov, the head of the Chechen Republic—also known as Putin’s “foot soldier”—said on his Telegram account this week that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German protesters accused of plot to kidnap health minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.record-eagle.com/nation_world/4-germans-arrested-over-extremist-blackout-kidnapping-plan/article_f6521be1-b4e1-5faa-830b-5313c579c232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.record-eagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Four people were arrested in Germany and weapons were seized in an investigation into suspected anti-government extremists who allegedly planned to cause a long nationwide blackout and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking small: Biden scrounges for ways to break through...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-barack-obama-europe-77d3c6ba4b761b979f30092b836295aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With his sweeping domestic agenda on hold and images of horror in Ukraine dominating headlines, President Joe Biden is scrounging for ways to demonstrate that he’s still making progress for Americans at a time when many feel the country is heading in the wrong direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crackdown silences war protests, from benign to bold...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-moscow-347cf5d867eb34b1e8469f942685b673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former police officer who discussed Russia's invasion on the phone. A priest who preached to his congregation about the suffering of Ukrainians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOP GUN' to star at Cannes film fest under Ukraine shadow...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-entertainment-business-jerry-lee-lewis-baz-luhrmann-8356effc4705102e50b70881c3c51a81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — With tensions around the war in Ukraine as a backdrop, the Cannes Film Festival plans a special honor for Tom Cruise’s “Top Gun” comeback and to host some 35,000 people as the movie industry looks to reclaim its pre-pandemic allure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
