<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CDC projects 'sharp decline' in summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/cdc-projects-a-surge-in-us-covid-cases-through-may-due-to-bpoint1point1point7-variant-before-a-sharp-decline-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Covid cases are expected to increase this month, hospitalizations and deaths will likely remain low nationally, the U.S. agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Seagal gifts Maduro samurai sword...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210505161808-4tulk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-MADURO/SEAGAL (PIX, TV):Venezuela's Maduro receives samurai sword gift from actor Steven Seagal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal staffers offered free yoga class led by Sophie Grégoire Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/eyes-roll-as-stressed-liberal-staffers-offered-free-virtual-yoga-class-led-by-sophie-gregoire-trudeau</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In boring Biden era, NYTIMES growth coming from NON-NEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/new-york-times-subscription-gains-non-news-products-0690d5ea-9d7f-4225-97ce-9822200da996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Times now has nearly 8 million paid subscribers — far ahead of even its closest news competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle accused of plagiarizing book...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/05/markle-accused-of-plagiarizing-2018-kids-book-but-defended-by-author/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online critics are accusing Meghan Markle of ripping-off of another author with her new children’s book. The author of the original work disagrees that Markle copied the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPID GETS A SHOT...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/rivlin-to-meet-lapid-bennett-as-consultations-begin-667245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yamina leader Naftali Bennett: Wide emergency government to be formed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Amy Coney Barrett has changed Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/05/politics/barrett-supreme-court-kavanaugh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett has aligned most often with Clarence Thomas and Neil Gorsuch in her first months on the bench. Yet as the court enters the final weeks of its annual session, Barrett is also separating herself from brethren on the right with a lower key, attention-deflecting manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Told Their Therapists Everything. Hackers Leaked It All...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/vastaamo-psychotherapy-patients-hack-data-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mental health startup built its business on easy-to-use technology. Patients joined in droves. Then came a catastrophic data breach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  'Proud Boys' saw wave of contributions from Chinese before Capitol attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/05/04/proud-boys-chinese-americans-community-support-donations/7343111002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Proud Boys enjoy support from some Chinese Americans and the broader Chinese diaspora, attracted by the group's claim to be fighting communism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The art detective who hunts stolen Picassos and lost Matisses...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2021/may/05/pitbulls-art-detective-christopher-marinello-mobsters-stolen-picassos-lost-matisses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Marinello has spent three decades finding missing masterpieces, recovering half a billion dollars’ worth of art. He talks about threats from mobsters, tricky negotiations – and bungling thieves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Iran releases horrifying video of U.S. Capitol blowing up...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2824464/iran-video-blow-up-us-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HORRIFYING fake footage of the US Capitol being blown up was released by Iran as Joe Biden comes under increasing pressure to take action from a GOP senator. The video leaked on state-controlled Ir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre new trend of eating ROTTEN meat to get high...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/2827943/trend-eat-raw-rotten-meat-get-high-explosive-incontinence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE are forcing down chunks of rotten, raw meat in a bid to get high in the latest bizarre social media trend. Coronavirus lockdowns have driven some people to attempt strange challenges but doc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sleeping 6-7 Hours Best For Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sleeping-six-to-seven-hours-best-for-heart-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that people who manage less -- or more -- than 6-7 hours of sleep each night are more prone to cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area market so hot houses selling $1M over asking price...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/realestate/article/2021-05-east-bay-real-estate-overbids-hot-market-16151227.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Especially in the East Bay, this type of sale isn’t an anomaly anymore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN opens up ticket sales for suborbital sightseeing trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/blue-origin-begin-space-tourism-ticket-sales-wednesday-2021-05-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin, billionaire Jeff Bezos' rocket company, said on Wednesday it is targeting July 20 for its first suborbital sightseeing trip on its New Shepard spacecraft, a landmark moment in a competition to usher in a new era of private commercial space travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STICKS TO BELIEFS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/05/cheney-isnt-fighting-mccarthy-push-to-replace-her-in-leadership-485430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian Caught Up In Ancient Roman Statue Smuggling Row...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/kim-kardashian-caught-up-in-ancient-roman-statue-smuggling-row-2428113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian found herself caught up in an unlikely international art smuggling row Tuesday involving an ancient Roman sculpture that was imported to California under her name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN HERD?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/herd-immunity-us-san-francisco-offers-reasons-optimism-rcna815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's low case numbers and high vaccination rates are signaling to experts that the city may have already reached herd immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another top Republican backs ousting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/another-top-republican-publicly-backs-ousting-cheney-gop-conference-chair-n1266376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Whip Steve Scalise is calling for New York Rep. Elise Stefanik to take over the leadership role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He faked virus certificate to fly to Argentina, officials say. He was infected all along...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-faked-a-coronavirus-certificate-to-fly-to-argentina-officials-say-he-was-infected-all-along/ar-BB1gnGg4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santiago Solans Portillo had traveled to Miami to get vaccinated, but likely exposed more than 200 people to the virus on his flight back to Buenos Aires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Tribe to Buy Palms Casino in Vegas for $650 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/california-tribe-to-buy-palms-casino-in-vegas-for-24650-million/ar-BB1gm4AI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Manuel Band of Mission Indians agreed to buy the Palms Casino Resort in Las Vegas from Red Rock Resorts Inc. for $650 million, the biggest purchase by a Native-Indian tribe in the U.S. gambling capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy trashes her on hot mic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/listen-kevin-mccarthy-caught-on-fox-news-hot-mic-bashing-liz-cheney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McCarthy — prior to hitting the air on Fox News Tuesday morning — spoke candidly on his feelings about Cheney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of expensive koi mysteriously die in Florida neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/05/01/mysterious-situation-in-coconut-grove-as-thousands-of-expensive-fish-suddenly-die-outside-several-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The common denominator is that all the ponds source their water from wells connected to the aquifer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind WARNER BROS. Search for Black Superman...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/black-superman-ta-nehisi-coates-warner-bros-movie-1234947599/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While promoting his Amazon Prime film Tom Clancy’s Without Remorse in late April, Michael B. Jordan put a Kryptonite pin in any rumors that he might suit up as Warner Bros.’ next Superman. “I’m fla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She told followers she was 'Mother God.' Her mummified body was found wrapped in Christmas lights...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/She-told-followers-she-was-Mother-God-Her-16152659.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Carlson's body was mummified in a sleeping bag and wrapped in a cloth adorned with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM fuels rise in black-market sales of maids into Persian Gulf servitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Instagram-fuels-rise-in-black-market-sales-of-16152644.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates - The advent of Instagram in recent years has helped create...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210505-israel-president-eyes-new-candidate-to-form-government-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel president eyes new candidate to form government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana paying bonuses to people willing to work...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/montana-to-end-extra-unemployment-pay-due-to-worker-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana, facing a shortage of workers, will now give bonuses to people who start working instead of extra unemployment pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite green light, Broadway to stay dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/despite-green-light-broadway-to-remain-dark-until-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor is giving the go-ahead to performance venues to reopen later this month. But the reality is that the lights won't go up on Broadway until the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pentagon tracking out of control Chinese rocket expected to crash into Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/the-pentagon-is-tracking-an-out-of-control-chinese-rocket-expected-to-crash-into-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese Long March 5B rocket is expected to reenter Earth's atmosphere around May 8. No one knows where. But don't panic!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELETON recalling all treadmills after injuries, death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/peloton-recalling-all-treadmills-after-reports-of-injuries-one-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a major reversal, Peloton announced Wednesday voluntary recalls of both its Tread+ and Tread treadmill machines over safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK: TRUMP STAYS BANNED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/facebook-will-keep-trump-ban-in-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's oversight board effectively punted the decision on the length of the suspension back to the social media company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butt Implants Up, Botox and Hair Transplants Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-05/cosmetic-surgery-2020-data-butt-implants-up-botox-and-hair-transplants-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair transplants, not so much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious brain disease baffles doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-56910393</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of people in New Brunswick are showing symptoms of the devastating new condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia raided across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/ndrangheta-mafia-raided-across-europe-01620204012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy led a Europe-wide police operation Wednesday against the 'Ndrangheta organised crime group, seizing cocaine and millions of euros in assets in early morning raids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untold Story of How Bezos Beat Tabloids...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-4ecfbfe6-4640-428e-9c78-e9a609b4f76b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Stone has all the details in his new book "Amazon Unbound."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to more babies than expected -- 9...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/africa/2021/05/a-woman-from-mali-gives-birth-to-9-babies-in-morocco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Malian woman has given birth to nine babies after only expecting seven, Mali’s Ministry of Health said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani allies press Trump to help foot his growing legal bills...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/551787-giuliani-allies-press-trump-team-to-help-foot-his-growing-legal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani’s allies are reportedly pressing former President Trump’s team to help the embattled lawyer pay for his growing legal bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Global tax deal 'urgently needed'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/551793-imf-warns-global-tax-deal-urgently-needed-to-avoid-potential-trade-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Monetary Fund (IMF) warned Tuesday that a global tax deal is “urgently needed” in order to avoid a potential trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure increases for USA to send covid vaccines to Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/551810-pressure-increases-for-us-to-send-vaccines-to-latin-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising rates of COVID-19 infections in Brazil and other countries in Latin America are posing a risk to the U.S. in its own battle to overcome the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney defends: She 'refuses to lie'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/551761-romney-defends-cheney-she-refuses-to-lie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney (R-Utah) is coming to the defense of Rep. Liz Cheney (R-Wyo.) amid a high-profile feud with House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) that is sparking fresh questions about her future in GOP leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to flex clemency powers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/551842-biden-set-to-flex-clemency-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials are signaling that President Biden is prepared to flex his clemency powers as officials wade through a large backlog of requests behind the scenes, according to advocates with whom the White House has consulted on criminal justice reform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Equity Mess...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/05/02/the-equity-mess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite their professed goals, Democrats' pandemic policies have widened disparities between races, classes, and genders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman missing for 6 months found living in tent in Utah, eating moss and grass...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/04/woman-missing-since-2020-found-living-utah-canyon-eating-grass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who went missing nearly six months ago was found living in a tent in a national forest in Utah, subsisting on a diet including grass and moss -- after a drone that was searching for her crashed nearby, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists see path for virus to invade brain...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-see-path-coronavirus-invade-130011296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An up-close view of how the coronavirus infects cells in the brain and spinal cord helps explain the neurological symptoms of some COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA RECALL CIRCUS: 1,000-pound bear and Hollywood-worthy campaign video...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/day-california-recall-1-000-002151477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Republican opponent posed for photos with a bear and another sought to leverage her celebrity status on national television. These events woke up what has so far been a quiet march toward a historic election to recall Gov. Gavin Newsom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chauvin Attorney Files Motion For New Trial On Grounds Of Juror Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/04/derek-chauvins-attorney-files-motion-for-new-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Eric Nelson has filed a motion for a new trial for former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin, who was convicted of murdering George Floyd last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Intensifies With Supply Shortages Multiplying...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-risk-intensifies-supply-shortages-210000287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Discover what’s driving the global economy and what it means for policy makers, businesses, investors and you with The New Economy Daily. Sign up hereSigns of inflation are picking up, with a mounting number of consumer-facing companies warning in recent days that supply shortages and logistical logjams may force them to raise prices.Tight inventories of materials as varied as semiconductors, steel, lumber and cotton are showing up in survey data, with manufacturers in Europe and the U.S. this week flagging record backlogs and higher input prices as they scramble to replenish stockpiles and keep up with accelerating consumer demand.As commodities become increasingly expensive, whether faster inflation proves transitory -- or not -- is the biggest question for policy makers and markets. Rising prices and the potential for a response from central banks topped the list of concerns for money managers surveyed by Bank of America Corp.Many economists and central bankers, from the Federal Reserve on down, maintain that price gains are temporary and will be curbed by forces such as virus worries and unemployment. Investors remain skeptical, with businesses including Nestle SA and Colgate-Palmolive Co. already announcing they’ll need to raise prices.U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, a former Fed chair, entered the debate on Tuesday when she ruffled markets with the observation that rates will likely rise as government spending ramps up. She later clarified she was neither predicting nor recommending an increase.The Bloomberg Commodity Spot Index, which tracks 23 raw materials, has risen to its highest level in almost a decade. That has pushed a gauge of global manufacturing output prices to its highest point since 2009, and U.S. producer prices to levels not seen since 2008, according to data from JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. and IHS Markit. JPMorgan analysts also estimate non-food and energy import prices in the biggest economies rose almost 4% in the first quarter, the most in three years.“Risk clearly leans to the upside in the current environment,” said John Mothersole, pricing and purchasing research director at IHS Markit. “The surge in commodity prices over the past year now guarantees higher goods-price inflation this summer.”The IHS Markit analysis across oil, chemicals, steel, copper, zinc, lumber, pulp and rubber expects the price boosts to fade closer to the end of the year. Meanwhile, strategists at Blackrock Investment Institute wrote Monday that they see U.S. consumer-price increases averaging just under 3% from 2025-2030, though that pace is “still under-priced by markets.”The case for higher-for-longer inflation into 2022 often rests on the trillions of dollars being pumped into infrastructure projects globally in a low-interest rate atmosphere, most notably in the U.S. That has supercharged a rally across raw materials, as major economies recover from the pandemic amid growing signs of shortage across several markets.Some businesses have found they can’t afford to wait for “temporary” increases to pass. That means consumers can expect to deal with higher costs for a range of daily items, including garbage bags and children’s clothes.“Straight price increases will continue to be an important element as we look at the back half of the year,” Colgate-Palmolive Chief Executive Officer Noel Wallace said late last month when the company announced earnings. “I anticipate that you’ll see more price increases across the sector, given the headwinds that everyone has faced in this space.”Higher cotton prices from Chinese producers are pushing clothes-maker Carter’s Inc. to consider how much of the increase it can pass along.“We’re beginning to see signs of inflation in product input costs, particularly those related to fabric,” Chief Executive Officer Michael Casey said on an April 30 earnings call. The company will offer “fewer promotions” this year, he said, amid a return of resilient shoppers buoyed by stimulus payments.Corn, too, is on the growing list of commodities seeing price boosts. Futures surged this week above $7 a bushel for the first time in more than eight years on the Chicago Board of Trade, alongside increases for soybeans and wheat.The underlying materials shortage has spooked Greg Sharenow, who manages a portfolio focused on energy and commodities at Pacific Investment Management Co.The premium on near-term deliveries over future deliveries for commodities tracked by the Bloomberg Commodity Index has jumped to the highest in more than 15 years, signaling immediate physical shortages across different markets, Sharenow said. He sees the price surge this time as more organic, rather than the kind of anticipatory demand seen from 2005 to 2008.Edward Robinson, deputy managing director and chief economist at Singapore’s central bank, said in a speech last week that he’s watching Chinese producer prices closely as an “important upside risk” to his baseline call that inflation should stay in check, helped by labor-market slack.A surge in copper is crippling some Chinese manufacturers, who have idled units, delayed deliveries and even defaulted on bank loans, data from a Shanghai Metals Market survey show. That’s already rippled through the production chain, delaying projects by power grids and property developers.Lumber has been in the spotlight as red-hot housing markets, especially in advanced economies, are driving up costs for the commodity.Fed Chairman Jerome Powell said last week the central bank was watching that market closely, even though he doesn’t currently have financial stability concerns around housing. Still, the sector has been emblematic of the K-shaped recovery, with cost surges pricing out middle-income buyers while homeowners reap gains.Markets have responded more calmly of late to the Fed’s mantra, with bond yields little changed after Powell last week doubled down on his inflation read and still-easy policy stance. The inflation run across so many materials, though, could break that patience, as pressure builds on businesses and officials to ward off price increases for consumers.“One always has to be careful not to overplay a few anecdotes, and project that onto the broader economy,” Douglas Porter, chief economist at BMO Capital Markets, said in a May 1 report. “But as the anecdotes accumulate, they eventually become data.”Porter pointed to a sampling of 10 recent datasets, including U.S. employment costs, Canadian wages and still-soaring shipping costs.“As rising inflation risks suggest,” he said, “when you run things hot, you risk getting burned.”(Updates with additional detail on corn prices in second paragraph after cotton price chart.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Were Promised Socialist Paradise, and Ended Up in 'Hell'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/05/they-were-promised-a-socialist-paradise-and-ended-up-in-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL — On a bright August morning in 1960, after two days of sailing from Japan, hundreds of passengers rushed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury will employ measures to avoid unprecedented default on national debt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-national-debt-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-a95665cfc7fbd8504fc91fdb2a6eb861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Treasury Department says it will employ measures to avoid an unprecedented default on the national debt this summer, but officials say those measures could be exhausted “much more quickly” than normal given the unusual circumstances of the global pandemic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of DOJ memo justifying not prosecuting Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/04/trump-obstruction-justice-doj-485360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. District Court Judge Amy Berman Jackson blasts former Attorney General William Barr's spin on the Mueller report as "disingenuous."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC getting rid of snow days; Virtual school instead...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-york-city-is-getting-rid-of-snow-days-for-next-school-year/ar-BB1glZW2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students will be asked to sit through remote learning days, following a policy instituted this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The love Bill Gates never forgot: Weekends alone with ex-girlfriend EVERY YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9541957/How-Bill-Gates-dated-venture-capitalist-Ann-Winblad-80s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates dated venture capitalist Ann Winblad, 70, in the 80s but broke up in 1987, the same year he met future wife Melinda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Incredibly intoxicated' man shot, barbecued his dog...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/04/incredibly-intoxicated-man-shot-and-barbecued-his-dog-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nikolay Lukyanchikov was dousing $100 bills with lighter fluid and burning them in the metal fire pit — which was topped with a barbecue grate where his pooch was cooked, the affidavit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The Liberals Who Can't Quit Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/05/liberals-covid-19-science-denial-lockdown/618780/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive communities have been home to some of the fiercest battles over COVID-19 policies, and some liberal policy makers have left scientific evidence behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Beast, YOUTUBE Star, Wants to Take Over Business World...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/04/mr-beast-youtube-star-wants-to-take-over-the-business-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Donaldson, 22, a YouTube megastar better known as Mr. Beast, operates six YouTube channels with names like MrBeast, MrBeast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual leader's mummified remains found in Colorado home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/colorado-business-lifestyle-religion-d829b1be1564dcf83c90a4c462a11376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Authorities have arrested several people after the mummified body of the leader of the spiritual group “Love Has Won” was found wrapped in a sleeping bag and decorated with Christmas lights in a southern Colorado home. Amy Carlson, 45, who was known as “Mother God” by her followers, was found dead in a home in the tiny, rural town of Moffat on Wednesday, April 28, according to arrest affidavits for seven people, who are each charged with abuse of a corpse. A follower told investigators he knew the woman as Lia Carlson, and a Saguache County sheriff's corporal wrote in the affidavits that Carlson is believed to be the leader of the group. It's unclear why the follower provided the name Lia.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
