<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Family finds unknown woman in mother's clothes in casket...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/family-finds-unknown-woman-in-mothers-casket</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of grieving sisters opened their mother’s casket and found someone they didn’t recognize dressed in their mom’s clothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Online Daters Decide Whether To Swipe Right In Less Than Second...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/online-daters-swipe-right-second/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online dating apps like Match.com, Tinder, and OK Cupid are responsible for 10% of the long-lasting adult relationships in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZ Police Goes Door to Door: 'Are You Aware Of Any Planned Protests Or Events?'</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/09/23/australia_police_goes_door_to_door_are_you_aware_of_any_planned_protests_or_events_coming_up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of Australian police officers visited a man claiming they are doing "welfare checks" to ask residents if they plan on participating in the ongoing protests against COVID-19 mitigation efforts. The man in this video was asked if he has plans or if he knows anyone who has plans to protest and if he has participated in protests in the past. "I'd like to know how you got this address, actually," the man told the police. "Anything else you might want to tell us to help ensure the public safety?" an officer asked after a barrage of questions about his "plans." "No, as long as you aren't going around shooting people with rubber bullets like in Victoria," the man said. How is this real? pic.twitter.com/5G9ElM1uPU-- Echo Chamber (@echo_chamberz) September 23, 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  FOXNEWS BANS RUDY...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2021/09/24/scoop-fox-to-rudy-youre-banned-494458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Chuck Grassley is running for reelection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Defense Bill Includes New Permanent UFO Office at Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/09/house-ndaa-proposes-permanent-ufo-studying-office-within-pentagon/185569/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the legislation clears the Senate as is, the new office would investigate military reports of unexplained incidents—and whether they’re linked to foreign threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack reveals MAGA websites under subpoena investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/epik-hack-subpoenas-data-preservation-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data leaked online from the hack of web hosting company Epik reveals numerous domains have been issued subpoenas as part of investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREEDOM:  Sweden won the argument on Covid?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/anders-tegnell-sweden-won-the-argument-on-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the celebrities that have been created during the course of the Covid-19 pandemic, Swedish State Epidemiologist Anders Tegnell is perhaps the most surprising. A softly-spoken official within the Swedish Health Agency, he has quietly been going about his work monitoring infectious diseases for years. But his decision, when Covid hit, to stick to [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani vanishes from network...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/chris-cuomo/1005301/cnns-chris-cuomo-accused-of-sexual-harassment-by-his-former-boss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodel Evangelista Reveals Cosmetic Procedure Left Her Deformed...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/model-linda-evangelista-cosmetic-procedure-left-deformed-destroyed-career/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linda Evangelista says a cosmetic procedure she had more than five years ago left her 'deformed.' [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless Man Opens Fire On SHAKE SHACK After Being Asked To Leave...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/09/24/no-injuries-after-gunman-opens-fire-at-shake-shack-in-canoga-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect, a homeless man, had been asked to leave the restaurant just prior to the shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE CRYPTO PAIN AFTER CHINA DECLARES ALL TRANSACTIONS ILLEGAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/24/bitcoin-ethereum-sink-as-china-intensifies-crypto-crackdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin and ethereum tumbled Friday, with traders rattled by tough talk out of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa senator announces reelection bid; Would be 95 at end of next term!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/grassley-announces-2022-reelection-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iowa Republican Sen. Chuck Grassley said on Friday he is running for reelection in 2022, announcing plans to hold a series of public events over the weekend to spearhead his pursuit for an eighth term in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKINSTAGRAM threatened with ban from iPhone after secret slave market uncovered on apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/3724188/facebook-instagram-ban-iphone-slave-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE threatened to ban Facebook from the iPhone after an investigation found that its apps were used for human trafficking. The discovery led to warnings from Apple that it would remove Facebook a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTTEST NEW SILICON VALLEY PERK: EVERYONE TAKES WEEK OFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/workplace/lessonly-hubspot-bumble-burnout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech companies like Lessonly, Bumble, Google and HubSpot are giving their workers more time off to address burnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Cuomo accused of sexual harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/chris-cuomos-former-boss-accuses-him-of-grabbing-her-butt-offering-bizarre-email-apology-afterwards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Cuomo's former boss Shelley Ross has accused him of sexual harassment in a New York Times op-ed published Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  1 DEAD, 13 INJURED AT SUPERMARKET RAMPAGE IN TN..</title>
      <link>https://www.fox13memphis.com/news/local/active-shooter-reported-collierville-kroger-officials-say/K4VFTTAFN5GMRBFAHRULX25KUM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13memphis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos unfolded at the Collierville Kroger following the deadly mass shooting early Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Opened Fire As Soon As He Walked Into Store'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/kroger-shooting-colliervile-tennessee-today-2021-09-23/#post-update-75ff2cd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe the shooter died of a self-inflicted gunshot wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  JETBLUE Passenger Restrained With Neckties, Seat Belts After Choking Flight Attendant...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/23/khalil-el-dahr-passenger-attack-flight-attendant-cockpit-jetblue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a flight from Boston to San Juan, Puerto Rico was arrested after he allegedly choked a flight attendant and tried to enter the cockpit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas shock families with oral sex show at Bronx zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3723437/hilarious-moment-randy-gorillas-shock-oral-sex-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE AWKWARD moment a pair of randy gorillas shocked families with an X-rated sex show at a zoo was caught on camera. The videographer captured the raunchy exchange during a visit to the Bronx zoo w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK GAS CHAOS: Gas stations blocked, huge lines due to 'shortage fears'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3723165/petrol-stations-blocked-fuel-shortage-panic-buying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUGE queues are blocking access to petrol stations across the country amid fuel shortage fears. Panic-buyers have been lining up from the early hours to fill their tanks – despite the governm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Get COVID' Party Helped Overrun Alberta's ICUs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvzq73/a-get-covid-party-helped-overrun-albertas-icus-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partygoers were reportedly trying to “build up natural immunity” rather than get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrests after French soccer rocked by violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210923-arrests-after-french-football-rocked-by-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arrests after French football rocked by violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas shock onlookers with sex show at Bronx Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/gorillas-shock-onlookers-with-oral-sex-at-bronx-zoo-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say it’s quite common: Primates can be caught “performing every position and variation one can imagine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When 'Ask app not to track,' some iPhone apps keep snooping anyway...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ask-app-not-track-iphone-161340829.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On your iPhone, you can now tap a button that says, "Ask app not to track." But behind the scenes, some apps keep snooping anyway. Say you open the app Subway Surfers, listed as one of the App Store's "must-play" games. It asks if you're OK with the app "tracking" you, a question iPhones started displaying in April as part of a privacy crackdown by Apple. Saying no is supposed to stop apps such as Subway Surfers and Facebook from learning about what you do in other apps and websites.Subscribe to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN BRINGS BACK HAND AMPUTATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/taliban-afghanistan-executions-punishments-ae174220-c2ec-41e4-8b40-6e3f06cec9ad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Quran will be the foundation of laws in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU pummeled for altering RBG abortion quote, replaces 'woman' with 'person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/aclu-ruth-bader-ginsburg-abortion-quote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) is raising eyebrows for altering a quote from the late Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg in order to be more inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLM Leader Promises National 'Uprising' Over 'Racist' Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/new-york-blm-leader-promises-national-uprising-over-racist-vaccine-mandates-similar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses In Short Supply. Vax Mandate Could Make It Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/23/1039228806/nurses-are-in-short-supply-employers-worry-vaccine-mandate-could-make-it-worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has ordered more than 17 million health care workers to get a COVID-19 vaccine. Some health care employers fear losing large numbers of workers who don't want the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of horses in Del Rio suspended...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/use-of-horses-along-border-in-texas-suspended-white-house-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The use of horses among Border Patrol officials in Del Rio, Texas, has been suspended in the aftermath of images being shared that showed mounted Border Patrol agents using their horses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy roils Kennedys after killer's release recommended...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/rfk-jr-bobby-kennedy-sirhan-sirhan-parole-16474192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recommendation for parole has sent shock waves through the Kennedy family, already...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both vaccinated? Oregon health officials say you can kiss on dates again...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/coronavirus/2021/09/both-vaccinated-oregon-health-officials-say-you-can-kiss-on-dates-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oregon Health Authority says "intimacy" is back on, if you're vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Legalizes Breakthrough Treatment: Magic Mushrooms...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/09/23/magic-mushrooms-oregon-legalizes-breakthrough-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon will license and regulate psilocybin-assisted therapy by 2023. Some health care professionals aren't willing to wait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warrant issued for ex-NETFLIX exec accused of raping wife...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/diego-bunuel-former-netflix-exec-accused-of-assaulting-wife-wanted-by-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Post has confirmed a warrant is still active for former Netflix executive Diego Bunuel as the 46-year-old allegedly assaulted his wife Maggie Kim in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA 1st state to set quota limits for retailers like AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/newsom-signs-law-making-california-1st-state-to-set-quota-limits-for-retailers-like-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California on Wednesday became the first state to bar mega-retailers from firing warehouse workers for missing quotas that interfere with bathroom and rest breaks under a new law signed by Gov. Gav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tears in the Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm/2021/09/23/scoop-tears-in-the-oval-office-494448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Democrats announce a reconciliation revenue framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader mass grave in Lebanon sheds light on cruelty of medieval warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/crusader-mass-grave-in-lebanon-sheds-light-on-cruelty-of-medieval-warfare-680138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists managed to reconstruct the rest of 25 individuals, all men, and analyzed their wounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPP SPEAKS:  No one is safe from cancel culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/johnny-depp-blasts-cancel-culture-from-literal-platform-more-strike-talk-r-i-p-melvin-van-peebles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp criticizes cancel culture as reporters hang on his every word; a strike by IATSE’s 150,000 members looks increasingly possible; R.I.P. to Melvin Van Peebles, an icon, revolutionary, and baadasssss. Cancelled: Johnny Depp bemoaned yesterday that “no one is safe” from cancel culture, while speaking into a microphone to a room filled with journalists.  “It […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen says Trump bluffing about running for office again...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com.au/michael-cohen-trump-bluffing-about-running-for-president-2024-2021-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen told Insider that Trump wants to keep raising money and retain some "semblance of power, importance, and relevance, none of which he has."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-coded tickets are key to escape...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haitians-color-coded-tickets-key-033002097.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities are allowing Haitian migrants at a massive camp in Texas who hold blue and yellow numbered tickets to remain in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At overrun ICU in Montana, 'problem is we're running out of hallways'...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/montana-icu-overrun-with-covid-patients-staffing-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billings Clinic in Montana is past the tipping point as it looks for places to add intensive care unit beds and is on the cusp of rationing care to deal with the surge of sick covid patients in a s…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
