<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tense Hill Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/strzoks-house-judiciary-hearing-plunges-into-absolute-chaos-as-lawmakers-exchange-heated-barbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok Swears:  My work never tainted by political bias...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fbi-agent-never-tainted-political-bias-080213902--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An FBI agent whose anti-Trump text messages fueled suspicions of partisan bias told lawmakers Thursday that his work has never been tainted by politics and that the intense scrutiny he is facing represents "just another victory notch in Putin's belt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't kiss the queen!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/royal-etiquette-trumps-visit-dont-kiss-queen-151224009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — President Donald Trump is coming to Britain fresh from a confrontational NATO summit that featured stinging criticism of America's closest allies, but he's likely to tone down that stance when he takes tea Friday with Britain's Queen Elizabeth II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STORMS LONDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6760773/donald-trump-slams-theresa-mays-chequers-plan-for-brexit-saying-i-dont-know-if-thats-what-they-voted-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has landed in Britain for his first official visit – and declared that the people of the UK “like me a lot”. The President arrived at Stansted Airport near London on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMMY Nominations: The List...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2018-emmy-nominations-live-updating-1110785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The Handmaid's Tale's' Samira Wiley and 'New Amsterdam's' Ryan Eggold are set to make the announcement starting at 8:25 a.m. PT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems struggle with unity... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/396589-dems-struggle-with-unity-amid-leadership-tensions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are struggling to show a united front as the shocking ouster of their Caucus chairman rekindles tensions about the future of the party — and who is best suited to lead it into the crucial 2020 cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL FOR MUSK...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2018-07-12/how-tesla-s-model-3-became-elon-musk-s-version-of-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can he deliver?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ocasio-Cortez drama; Accuses rival of pushing 3rd party...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/784415/alexandria-ocasiocortez-accuses-defeated-democratic-primary-opponent-stubbornly-running-thirdparty-challenge-against</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Joseph Crowley (D-N.Y.) was stunningly defeated in last month's Democratic primary in New York by progressive phenom Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez. At the time, he put on a good face, even playing "Born to Run" for her after she'd sealed the spot. But things might not be so friendly beyond the Bruce Springsteen covers, and now Ocasio-Cortez is accusing Crowley of mounting a third-party challenge against her: .@repjoecrowley stated on live TV that he would absolutely support my candidacy.Instead, he’s stood me up for all 3 scheduled concession calls.Now, he’s mounting a 3rd party challenge against me and the Democratic Party- and against the will of @NYWFP.https://t.co/Xvb6Jk8N8q — Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (@Ocasio2018) July 12, 2018 New York has a quirky third-party system, which can allow unsuccessful major party candidates like Crowley to be the nominee for a smaller party and therefore still appear on the general election ballot. This was most recently highlighted by Ocasio-Cortez winning a district she didn't even run in as a write-in for the Reform Party. Likewise, Crowley won the Working Families Party line in New York's 14th District, where he lost the Democratic nomination to Ocasio-Cortez. It had been expected that Crowley would vacate the spot and support his fellow Democrat in the race: Bill Lipton, state director of the Working Families Party, said he immediately reached out to Mr. Crowley's campaign to request that he vacate the line. To Mr. Lipton's chagrin, his campaign declined; Mr. Crowley will remain on the ballot in November. "You'd think that given the moment we're in," said Mr. Lipton, "that Democratic leaders would want to help progressive forces to unite." [The New York Times] Crowley's campaign sidestepped a question about why they are remaining on the ballot. "Joe Crowley is a Democrat," a spokeswoman told the Times. "He's made clear he is not running for Congress and supports the Democratic nominee in NY-14." Update 9:51: Crowley responded to Ocasio-Cortez's accusation on Twitter, writing: "Alexandria, the race is over and Democrats need to come together. I've made my support for you clear and the fact that I'm not running. We've scheduled phone calls and your team has not followed through. I'd like to connect but I'm not willing to air grievances on Twitter." Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY DROIDS:  Sex robot makers blasted over sick 'family friendly' love doll designs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6760656/sex-robots-family-friendly-dolls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SEX robot with a “family mode” that dials down her dirty talk has been blasted as “profoundly damaging” for kids by academics. The controversial droid named Samantha went …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The World Needs More Cowboys' slogan for University of Wyoming called SEXIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article214680825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Wyoming is drawing criticism after school staff thought the new $500,000 UW slogan — "The World Needs More Cowboys" — was sexist. Women and Twitter users are defending the college and say the word "cowboy" is inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump as popular as Obama in middle of first term...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article214749845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A poll from Pew Research Center found 44 percent of people say Obama has done the best or second best job, with Clinton in second with 33 percent and Reagan third with 32 percent. Trump, at 19 percent, matches Obama in middle of first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuba diver finds iPhone lost at sea -- after text lights it up...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/scuba-diver-finds-iphone-lost-12898742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incredibly the device still had more than 80% of its charge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University moving desecrated US flag to art museum...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Kansas has moved a paint-spattered American flag from a prominent flagpole to a publicly-funded art museum on the same campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Could Dems Nominate Maxine Waters for President?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2018/07/11/could-democrats-nominate-maxine-waters-for-president-answer-yes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Democratic side of the aisle, I challenge you to find a politician or media personality who has better expressed the anger, frustration and rage of the “Resistance” better than Maxine Waters…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posed as Trump Voter with 'Bullet' Necklace and 'INFOWARS' Stickers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/07/12/exclusive-sacha-baron-cohen-posed-as-disabled-veteran-trump-voter-with-bullet-necklace-and-infowars-stickers-in-palin-prank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen "pretended to be a disabled veteran from Kentucky" in a disguise "meant to mock Trump voters by making them seem ignorant and offensive," a source close to Palin told Breitbart News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Peter Strzok Breaks Silence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5cd36c766cf14f548bdaf050d1393d98/FBI-agent:-My-work-has-never-been-tainted-by-political-bias</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An FBI agent whose anti-Trump text messages fueled suspicions of partisan bias will tell lawmakers Thursday that his work has never been tainted by politics and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complications and controversy of Nick Loeb's pro-life 'ROE v. WADE' movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/movies/ny-ent-nick-loeb-roe-v-wade-20180710-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Loeb’s polarizing, pro-life “Roe v. Wade” movie faced an onslaught of challenges practically from the get-go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Joy Reid ratings drop 20% after blog hacking controversy?</title>
      <link>http://contemptor.com/2018/07/11/msnbcs-am-joy-has-lost-over-20-percent-of-its-audience-following-blog-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;contemptor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been almost three months since a slew of homophobic and culturally insensitive posts from MSNBC host Joy Reid's old blog were unearthed, resulting in a lengthy controversy that embroiled the Re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'exotic' tick clones self; 'Aggressive biter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214748110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A species of East Asian tick has found its way to N.C. The U.S. Department of Agriculture reports it found the Longhorned tick on an opossum in Polk County and fears the bug will spread quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaginal Rejuvenation  Latest Cosmetic Trend to Hit Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/vaginal-rejuvenation-is-latest-cosmetic-trend-hit-hollywood-1126442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data is in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump arrives in 'hot spot' Britain, questioning May's Brexit plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-arrives-hot-spot-britain-questioning-mays-brexit-130316893--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump arrived in "hot spot" Britain on Thursday after casting doubt on Prime Minister Theresa May's plans for leaving the European Union and with protests planned across the country where he says the people like him a lot. After a NATO summit where he provoked a crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever color X-ray on human...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-ever-colour-x-ray-human-005837590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand scientists have performed the first-ever 3-D, colour X-ray on a human, using a technique that promises to improve the field of medical diagnostics, said Europe's CERN physics lab which contributed imaging technology. The new device, based on the traditional black-and-white X-ray, incorporates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans are starving, but the country still sends crude to Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article214635335.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan oil production is dropping rapidly and the government has no money to buy food, medicines or consumer goods, but there's one item the socialist regime of Nicolas Maduro does not appear willing to sacrifice at all: oil subsidies to Cuba</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN LOBBIES FACEBOOK TO SHUT DOWN ALEX JONES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/cnn-lobbies-facebook-to-shut-down-infowars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media giant admits it down ranks Infowars content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/economy/jobless-claims-plunge-to-214-000-lowest-since-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New applications for unemployment insurance benefits dropped 18,000 to 214,000 in the first week of July, the Department of Labor reported Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Lopez uses water bottle to pretend to urinate on Trump's star in Hollywood...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/07/12/george-lopez-uses-water-bottle-to-pretend-to-urinate-on-trumps-star-in-hollywood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian George Lopez was recently seen in a TMZ video emptying a small water bottle onto President Donald Trump’s star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame, acting as though he was urinating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FONDLED UNDERCOVER OFFICERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.10tv.com/article/police-stormy-daniels-grabbed-backside-undercover-columbus-officer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult film actress Stormy Daniels was arrested in Columbus, Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Tebow get called to Majors?</title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/sports/baseball/2018/07/11/improving-tim-tebow-its-now-never/764001002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow's recent play has opened many eyes as the 30-year-old could see a call-up this season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash piles up in USA as China closes door to recycling...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/trash-piles-us-china-closes-door-recycling-doc-17h4mx1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto raises $10.4M, keeping flush his bid to upset Cruz...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/orourke-raises-10-4m-keeping-flush-bid-upset-024154414--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Democratic U.S. Rep. Beto O'Rourke says he raised more than $10.4 million over the past three months, putting him on track to again outpace U.S. Sen. Ted Cruz, whom he's trying to upset in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masquerade As Vet Felony?</title>
      <link>http://www.kxl.com/listen-karen-straughan-was-sacha-baron-cohens-masquerade-as-a-vet-funny-or-a-felony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen, the comedian and actor known for “Borat” and other roles in Hollywood …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The online battle for truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/online-battle-truth-doc-17h6381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World oil supply risks being 'stretched to limit'...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180712-world-oil-supply-risks-being-stretched-limit-iea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riding migration backlash, Sweden's political pariah looks to end isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sweden-election-swedendemocrats-newsm/riding-migration-backlash-swedens-political-pariah-looks-to-end-isolation-idUSKBN1K20HJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM/VISBY, Sweden - Once denounced as neo-fascists, Jimmie Akesson's Sweden Democrats look poised to translate more voter-friendly nationalist policies into big electoral gains in a country long famed for liberal tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF OF AMERICANS TRYING TO LOSE WEIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/12/nearly-half-of-americans-trying-to-lose-weight-cdc-data-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly Half of Americans Trying to Lose Weight, CDC Data Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Peter Strzok to Break Silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fbis-peter-strzok-to-break-his-silence-1531387800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent censured for sending anti-Trump text messages while he helped lead investigations into Hillary Clinton and President Trump will break his public silence Thursday in testimony before Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO ALLIES AGREE TO INCREASE DEFENSE SPENDING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/trump-says-nato-allies-have-agreed-to-increase-their-defense-spending-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGED WITH SEX OFFENSES...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/stormy-daniels-arrested-strip-club-charged-sex-offenses-n890791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Michael Avenatti says the adult film star was arrested after a customer touched her in a non-sexual manner during a performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
RARELY ENFORCED LAW?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/07/12/columbus-has-rarely-used-2007-bill-that-protects-strippers-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was unclear early Thursday exactly what charges, if any, porn star Stormy Daniels may face following her arrest at an Ohio strip club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMY DANIELS ARRESTED IN OHIO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/stormy-daniels-arrested-in-columbus-ohio-while-performing-avenatti.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels, the porn star who has made headlines for an alleged affair with Donald Trump, was arrested in Columbus, Ohio, according to her attorney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPA JOHN'S chairman resigns after using racial slur...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/10/papa-johns-founder-john-schnatter-resigns-as-chairman-of-company-boar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papa John's founder John Schnatter has resigned as chairman of his company's board after admitting and apologizing for using the N-word during a May conference call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADIO HOST DUPED...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/11/joe-walsh-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former congressman and radio host claims Sacha Baron Cohen duped him with fake award ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Thailand cave rescue to be turned into Hollywood movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/thailand-cave-rescue-turned-hollywood-movie-003908190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission to rescue 12 boys and their soccer coach from a Thai cave is to get the Hollywood treatment in a movie announced by faith-based production house Pure Flix. Managing partner Michael Scott, who lives in Thailand and was at the rescue site in Chiang Rai as the boys were being pulled to safety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Battling Fake Accounts, TWITTER to Slash Millions of Followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/11/technology/twitter-fake-followers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter will begin removing tens of millions of suspicious accounts from follower numbers, signaling a major new effort to fight fraud and restore trust on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CBSSHOWTIME SERIES CREATES CHAOS...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/sarah-palin-dick-cheney-bernie-sanders-duped-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin, who is enraged that Sacha Baron Cohen “duped” her on his new show, is apparently not the only politician who's fallen prey to the comedian's humor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA BARON COHEN PROBES CHELSEA CLINTON'S 'SEX CHANGE' OPERATION!</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/11/sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen-interview-chelsea-clinton-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin recently revealed she was “duped” by actor Sacha Baron Cohen, who disguised himself as a disabled U.S. veteran to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEF OF IRRITATION</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/onpolitics/2018/07/11/john-kelly-upset-breakfast/777505002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of news outlets, including the Post, speculated that Kelly's body language was related to the remarks Trump was making at the time about Germany being "totally controlled by Russia."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great white shark makes U-turn off Carolinas coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/technology/article214731770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A great white shark made a sharp U-turn off the coast of the Carolinas and is headed south again in deeper water. OCEARCH researchers have seen this before, and think they might know why why sharks behave this way: They're pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Spends Evening Feeding Homeless...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/11/kavanaugh-feeds-homeless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is really touching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED snubs mediation, sends anti-Trump dossier lawsuit to trial...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/11/buzzfeeds-ben-smith-mediation-snub-sends-dossier-l/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first face-to-face encounter between anti-Trump dossier publisher Ben Smith and one of its targets, Russian entrepreneur Aleksej Gubarev, was set to happen last month in a New York City law office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY, COMCAST Raise Stakes in Battle for FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/disneys-71-billion-bid-for-fox-is-now-worth-90-billion-1531316559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official: The battle for 21st Century Fox assets moved across the Atlantic with dueling bids for satellite-TV provider Sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese urged to 'eat a bug, save a tree' as cicada threaten greenery...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2154855/chinese-citizens-urged-eat-bug-and-save-tree-summer-cicada-glut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An official is hoping to start a trend for chomping on chirpy insects in a bid to stop them devastating willow and cherry blossom trees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest Tools Outside Africa Found, Rewriting Human Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-china-human-tools-africa-shangchen-hominin-paleoanthropology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New evidence suggests that our ancient cousins left the continent much earlier than thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA-Bron: NBA Star In Talks to Star In Comedy...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/lebron-james-new-movie-body-swapping-comedy-1202863347/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James, scribe Steve Mallory, and James’ SpringHill Entertainment have sold an untitled comedy pitch to Paramount Players, with the NBA icon in early talks to star. SpringHill and Mallo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Armless Artist Stabs Tourist in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article214692415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Crenshaw, a homeless man with no arms who paints with his feet on South Beach's Lincoln Road Mall, is accused by Miami Beach police of stabbing a tourist from Chicago on Collins Avenue Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Threats at Home and Abroad, Rouhani Takes Harder Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facing-threats-at-home-and-abroad-irans-president-takes-a-harder-line-1531301400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he forged diplomatic ties with the West, Iran’s President Hassan Rouhani has been at loggerheads with the military and conservative establishment. Now, with his political survival in question, Mr. Rouhani is sounding a lot like Iran’s hard-liners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Puts eSports Competition in Primetime...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/gaming/news/espn-disney-abc-overwatch-league-1202870413/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Overwatch League quarterfinals start Wednesday, July 11 at 8 p.m. ET and fans can now watch all of the action on ESPN, Disney, and ABC networks, “Overwatch” developer Blizzard Enter…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies parental request to change trans teen's name...</title>
      <link>https://local12.com/news/local/parents-appeal-after-judge-denies-transgender-teen-name-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;local12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON, Ohio (WKRC) - The parents of a transgender teenager claim a Warren Co. probate judge violated their constitutional rights when he denied their request to legally change their son's name.Leigh and Kylen Whitaker filed the request to change their so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge charged for dropping gun in Chicago courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/cook-county-judge-drops-gun-video-487836311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cook County judge dropped a gun as he walked through a courthouse on Chicago’s South Side last week, video shows—and now he faces a misdemeanor charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dem Sanchez digs Pelosi with 'generational change' call...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/onpolitics/2018/07/11/linda-sanchez-generational-change-democratic-leadership-nancy-pelosi/775977002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Linda Sanchez, the highest-ranking Latina in the House, called for new leadership at a time when Democrats are increasingly dissatisfied with Nancy Pelosi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feinstein scramble to stave off party endorsement loss...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/10/dianne-feinstein-california-kevin-de-leon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dianne Feinstein’s Democratic opponent, Kevin de León, is closing in on a party endorsement. So now she’s calling for party unity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: KYLIE JENNER VERGE OF BEING YOUNGEST 'SELF-MADE' BILLIONAIRE EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesdigitalcovers/2018/07/11/how-20-year-old-kylie-jenner-built-a-900-million-fortune-in-less-than-3-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What her half-sister Kim Kardashian West did for booty, Jenner has done for full lips. Like Kardashian West, she has leveraged her assets to gain both fame and money. But while her sister is best-known for the former, Kylie Jenner has proved adept at the latter. In historic fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA model attacked by shark during photo shoot...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/world/ny-news-instragram-model-shark-attack-20180711-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram model was attacked while swimming with sharks for a photo shoot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTY OVER  FOR UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6755687/england-croatia-world-cup-2018-fans-celebrations-uk-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENGLAND fans have been left heartbroken after Croatia won 2-1 in extra time of the World Cup semi-final tonight. The hopes of a nation were dashed as it became clear England’s years of hurt w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROATIA MAKES WORLD CUP FINAL!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/croatia-stuns-england-in-extra-time-to-advance-to-world-cup-final-1531341455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mario Mandzukic’s 109th-minute shot into the left corner of the net sealed a 2-1 comeback win for Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama out of hiding; Enters 2018 campaign...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/11/obama-campaign-congress-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of hiding?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE TV Outage in Middle of Game...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/youtube-tv-outage-world-cup-england-croatia-1202870724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube TV, Google’s internet-delivered subscription TV service, was hit with nationwide outages — right in the middle of the 2018 World Cup semifinal match between England and Croatia.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When GOOGLE was young: Sex, drugs and rock n' roll...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/11/when-google-was-young-oral-history-from-new-book-has-sex-street-view-and-how-it-all-began/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All this was back when the “don’t be evil” mantra wasn’t quite as complicated for Google as it is nowadays — and way before the “Me Too” movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Claims Autism, Arthritis Treatable By Pot...</title>
      <link>http://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/michigan-medical-marijuana-autism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan has added several medical conditions to the state's list of ailments which qualify for a medical marijuana prescription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPA JOHN'S shares skid after report founder used N-word...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/11/papa-johns-shares-crater-after-report-that-founder-used-a-n-word.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Papa John's skidded on Wednesday after a report surfaced alleging that founder John Schnatter has used the N-word during a conference call in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump protest in Brussels expected THOUSANDS, got DOZENS...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/anti-trump-protest-at-nato-draws-only-a-couple-dozen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs Urge City Citizens To Report 'Illegal Aliens' To ICE...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/signs-report-illegal-aliens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some residents in Omaha have been pulling the homemade flyers down, calling them hateful and offensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Blitzer's airtime trimmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/brianna-keilar-will-anchor-cnns-1-p-m-timeslot-beginning-this-fall/369804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolf Blitzer will continue to anchor The Situation Room weekdays from 5 - 7 p.m. ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: Inside Mueller's New Army...</title>
      <link>'https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/11/papa-johns-shares-crater-after-report-that-founder-used-a-n-word.html&gt;PAPA JOHN'S shares skid after report founder used N-word...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player attacked by employee at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nfl-player-pacman-jones-attacked-employee-airport-162700741--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Police say former Cincinnati Bengals cornerback Adam "Pacman" Jones was attacked during a run-in with a facility-service employee at the airport in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tells NATO leaders to increase defense spending to 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-tells-nato-leaders-military-spending-4-percent-155939755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump told NATO leaders on Wednesday they should increase their defense spending to 4 percent of their country's economic output, double the group's current goal of two percent. NATO allies shrugged off the demand as part and parcel of Trump's brash push for allies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals attack Brett Kavanaugh for 'frat boy' name...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/11/liberals-attack-brett-kavanaugh-for-frat-boy-name.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest line of attack from liberals against Brett Kavanaugh, President Trump’s nominee for the Supreme Court, is knocking the judge for his “frat boy”-sounding first name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tom Petty Song Drops...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/music/news/tom-petty-an-american-treasure-boxed-set-track-list-revealed-new-song-drops-1202870299/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As announced on SiriusXM yesterday, on September 28, Reprise Records will release “An American Treasure” — a career-spanning Tom Petty box set containing dozens of previously unreleased recordings,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK WORLD CUP MANIA RAMPS UP AGAIN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6751746/england-world-cup-2018-party-kicks-off-russia-moscow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENGLAND’s World Cup party kicked-off in style as thousands of fans gathered in bars around Moscow’s iconic Red Square today before the big game – and the Wags joined in too. Jamie Vardy’s wif…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
