<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>US, NKorea Rocketing Toward NYE Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-12-26/5-things-to-watch-for-from-north-korea-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDIAN ANGELS OUT IN FORCE; PATROLLING NEIGHBORHOODS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/amp/ncna1108251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're a visual deterrence," said Curtis Sliwa, who founded the unarmed crime prevention group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie warns against religious bigotry hours after Hasidic Jews are stabbed in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Bernie-Sanders-warns-against-religious-bigotry-14938755.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa - Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., who had relatives killed by Nazis during the Holocaust, responded Sunday to the latest incident of anti-Semitic terror by wearing a kippah and lifting a blowtorch to light a public menorah on the final night of Hanukkah.  And less than 24 hours after an intruder stabbed five Hasidic Jews at a rabbi's home in New York, the Democratic presidential candidate delivered an urgent speech on a frigid evening in Des Moines, decrying recent attacks against Jews and other minorities.  "We're seeing people being stabbed yesterday in New York City because they were Jewish," Sanders said, calling the assault part of an alarming rise in anti-Semitism, both in the United States and globally.  Sanders added, "If there was ever a time in American history where we say no to religious bigotry, this is the time. If there was ever a time when we say no to divisiveness, this is that moment."  The bundled-up crowd, gathered around a menorah at Brenton Skating Plaza, listened intently as the 78-year-old son of a Jewish immigrant spoke and cheered when he called for unity.  The latest attack in New York, which officials said began after 10 p.m. Saturday in the suburb of Monsey, was called an act of "domestic terrorism" by New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, who linked it to the spate of violence against Jewish people.  Sunday's lighting event was scheduled before the Monsey attack- and was planned to be a low-key stop following a day of campaigning in two states. But it became a rare charged moment for Sanders, who often resists departing from his core stump speech.  Sanders - who has long noted that the family of his late father, Eli Sanders, was "wiped out" during the Nazi occupation of Poland during World War II - mentioned his father, who, he said, "came...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEWORK Lays Off 2,400  -- Bosses Get $18 Million Exit Package...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90448185/wework-laid-off-2400-employees-but-its-execs-just-got-a-potential-extra-18-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of layoffs and a cash crunch has not deterred WeWork from generous exit packages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Scientist Who Gene-Edited Babies Is Sent to Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/30/china/gene-scientist-china-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese scientist who helped create the world's first gene-edited babies has been sentenced to three years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Public School Students Barred From Returning Until They Get Vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-vaccinations-seattle-public-school-students-required-to-be-vaccinated-after-outbreaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle Public Schools said roughly 2,000 students need to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIM COY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be887e8a0bd1c3fc4a6f67bdaa65e492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korean leader Kim Jong Un called for his military and diplomats to prepare unspecified “offensive measures” to protect the country’s security and sovereignty, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin weighs future options as he marks 20 years in power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0dc36e0cdf7e6fa3c5e0d735b4c55197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — As Russian President Vladimir Putin marks two decades in power , he boasts about his achievements but remains coy about his political future — a reticence that fuels wild...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Warns USA Its Middle East Dominance Is Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/iran-warns-us-middle-east-dominance-over-naval-drills-russia-china-1479628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messy primary finally meets election year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4d2857515d8664d24c5419197d9d327</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The presidential politics calendar turned to 2020 nearly a year ago. This week, the actual date catches up. What we’re watching as the preseason closes and election year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Could 'CATS' Lose? $100 Million?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cats-box-office-hairball-how-much-money-could-tom-hoopers-musical-lose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adaptation of Andrew Lloyd Webber's musical will make a quarter of what "La La Land" and "The Greatest Showman" grossed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In strategic Djibouti, a microcosm of China's growing foothold in Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-strategic-Djibouti-a-microcosm-of-China-s-14938761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DJIBOUTI - Above ground in this tiny but strategically located country, signs of China's presence are everywhere.  Chinese entities have financed and built Africa's biggest port, a railway to Ethiopia and the country's first overseas naval base here. Under the sea, they are building a cable that will transmit data across a region that spans from Kenya to Yemen. The cable will connect to an Internet hub housing servers mostly run by China's state-owned telecom companies.  Beijing's extensive investments in Djibouti are a microcosm of how China has rapidly gained a strategic foothold across the continent. Western countries, including Africa's former colonizers, for decades have used hefty aid packages to leverage trade and security deals, but Chinese-financed projects have brought huge infrastructural development in less than a generation.  The construction is fueled mostly by lending from China's state-run banks. Spindles of Chinese-paved roads have unfurled across the continent, along with huge bridges, new airports, dams and power plants as part of Chinese President Xi Jinping's 152-country Belt and Road Initiative.  Overall, Chinese companies have invested twice as much money between 2014 and 2018 in African countries as American companies, spending $72.2 billion, according to an analysis by Ernst &amp; Young.  "The Chinese are thinking far into the long-term in Djibouti and Africa in general," said David Shinn, a former U.S. ambassador to Ethiopia who was also the State Department's desk officer for Djibouti as far back as the late 1960s. "Djibouti is one node in an economic chain that stretches across the northern rim of the Indian Ocean, from ports in Cambodia to Sri Lanka to Pakistan. They have a grand, strategic plan. We don't."  In Djibouti, that strategic plan is all the more evident because of the country's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hecklers derail Biden event...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hecklers-biden-quid-pro-joe-new-hampshire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden was interrupted by hecklers calling him "creepy" and a "pervert" during a campaign event in Milford, NH, Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Worst ever' hoarder house found with 19 dead cats buried under piles of trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worst-ever-hoarder-house-found-21186351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tamara Bender and her husband Jeremy travel with a team of helpers who specialise in cleaning out homes in the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg campaign moves offices into Times Square as staff tops 300...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/476211-bloomberg-campaign-moves-offices-into-times-square-as-staff-grows-above-300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg’s campaign is set to move to a new location in Times Square as the campaign swells to more than 300 staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun, dynamic, frivolous...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/12/27/whos-up-for-a-roaring-20s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France waits on Macron as pension strike stretches on...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-waits-macron-pension-strike-stretches-142058122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French union leaders upped their calls on Monday for President Emmanuel Macron to give ground on a planned pension overhaul, despite signs that support is flagging for a gruelling transport strike now in its 26th day. Macron will address the nation Tuesday in his annual New Year's Eve address, having</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Obama, Trump Tie as Most Admired Man...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/273125/obama-trump-tie-admired-man-2019.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama and Donald Trump tie as the most admired man this year. Michelle Obama remains the most admired woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Of Americans Had Best Sex Of Their Lives In 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fireworks-nearly-half-of-americans-had-best-sex-of-their-lives-in-2019-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 adults asked respondents to recount their sexual experiences in 2019, and found that about half had the best sex of their lives this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight against facial recognition hits wall across West...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/30/facial-recognition-privacy-089881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The result is an impasse that has left tech companies largely in control of where and how to deploy facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi arrests hundreds for 'wearing inappropriate clothes', 'indecency'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nst.com.my/world/world/2019/12/551861/saudi-arabia-arrests-hundreds-wearing-inappropriate-clothes-indecency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nst.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIYADH: Saudi Arabia has arrested more than 200 people for violating “public decency” – including by wearing immodest clothing – and “harassment“, police said, in the first such crackdown since the ultra-conservative kingdom began easing social norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garoppolo Shines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/bayarea/49ers/where-jimmy-garoppolo-ranks-among-49ers-qb-leaders-after-great-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Garoppolo joined some 49ers legends with his epic 2019 regular season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Decade of Debt: Big deals, bigger risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets-decade-credit/the-decade-of-debt-big-deals-bigger-risk-idUSKBN1YY09Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever nickname ultimately gets attached to the now-ending Twenty-tens, on Wal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge-Fund Purge Continues With More Closures Than Launches...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hedge-funds-to-record-more-closures-than-launches-for-fifth-straight-year-1.1367459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pain kept coming for hedge funds in 2019: if they weren’t being killed off, they were bleeding cash or wringing out dismal returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade of very poor and super-rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-09455429-a788-43d0-8c0f-a6ad3d882e86.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELIN restaurant bible faces ruling in French chef's protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/michelin-restaurant-bible-faces-ruling-french-chefs-protest-115123105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French court will rule Tuesday if the authoritative Michelin restaurant guide must hand over its secret reasonings for stripping a chef of his third Michelin star, just a year after the coveted award was won. Marc Veyrat launched the unprecedented lawsuit after his Maison des Bois restaurant in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on 'new way' in Kim Jong Un's New Year speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eyes-way-kim-jong-uns-speech-040614958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has called for "offensive measures" to strengthen security ahead of a New Year speech that could flesh out the nuclear-armed nation’s threat to seek a "new way" forward after the expiration of its year-end deadline for US sanctions relief. Kim’s latest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex toy an electronics show award finalist after controversy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1143b874fe71199db7772f09c38ccdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A sex toy that can be controlled through a mobile app is a finalist for the Last Gadget Standing award at CES 2020, an electronics show in Las Vegas. The Las Vegas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Political Predictions of 2019...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/30/worst-political-predictions-of-2019-089874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one knows what the future holds, but these pundits and politicians knew even less than the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China jails scientist who created world's first 'gene-edited' babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/china-jails-scientist-who-created-21184026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr He Jiankui was charged with illegally practicing medicine in China as he faced a backlash from fellow scientists following his claims that he had changed the genes of twin girls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steep rise in pets needing treatment for anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/steep-rise-pets-needing-treatment-21184637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of insurance claims to treat anxiety, depression and OCD in pets has rocketed, with some owners forking out £1,000 a day for behaviour and hormone treatments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acts of anti-Semitism on rise in New York and elsewhere, rattling communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Acts-of-anti-Semitism-are-on-the-rise-in-New-York-14938238.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Hours after a knife-wielding man barged into a Hannukah party in a New York suburb, stabbing five people, top officials condemned the crime as part of a disturbing trend. New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo called it "domestic terrorism," linking it to the recent spate of violence against Jewish people in New York.  Anti-Semitic attacks are on the rise around the country, leaving Jews and their communities feeling frightened and unsafe. In New York City, anti-Semitic crimes have jumped 21% in the past year. According to the Anti-Defamation League, there were 1,879 incidents of anti-Semitism in the United States in 2018, including more than 1,000 instances of harassment. The 2019 figures are expected to meet or exceed that number.  "This is a national phenomenon that we are seeing, and it's frightening and it's disturbing," Cuomo said at a news conference Sunday. "If anyone thinks that something poisonous is not going on in this country, then they're in denial."  Experts say anti-Semitic violence has been rising for years. In 2018, a gunman stormed the Tree of Life synagogue in Pittsburgh, killing 11 congregants, and wounding six others. It was the deadliest anti-Semitic attack in the history of the United States.  In April, during the observance of Passover, a gunman killed a Jewish worshiper at a Poway, California, house of worship and injured three others.  And a string of attacks in recent weeks has left the Jewish community in the New York area particularly unsettled.  This month, David Anderson and Francine Graham went on a violent rampage at a kosher supermarket in Jersey City, New Jersey, killing three people inside the store. The pair have been linked to the Black Hebrew Israelites, a hate group that traffics in anti-Semitic tropes. Authorities said they also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Year Flying Saucers Became Legit...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/technology/2019/12/2019-year-in-aliens-ufos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The truth is out there, but it’s fuzzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Trial Tests Incumbents Key to Senate Control...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-trial-tests-incumbents-090000264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Senate’s historic impeachment trial of President Donald Trump will be especially momentous for a small group of vulnerable incumbent senators whose 2020 re-election bids are central to determining control of the chamber.Trump is all but certain to be acquitted on two articles of impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garoppolo  Shines...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/game/_/gameId/401128040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get a summary of the San Francisco 49ers vs. Seattle Seahawks football game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  PUT AWAY YOUR PHONES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10637721/pope-francis-encourages-people-to-put-phones-away-mealtimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE Francis has called for people to spend less time on their phones at mealtimes and to get talking, citing Jesus, Mary and Joseph as examples. Francis told a gathering in St Peter’s Square…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Giuliani held phone call with Maduro amid crisis... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-s-lawyer-and-the-Venezuelan-president-How-14937863.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international call came in September 2018, after months of rising tension between the United States and Venezuela, a key strategic player in South America.  On one end of the line was Venezuela's socialist president, the pariah leader of a disintegrating economy whom President Donald Trump's administration was seeking to isolate.  On the other end: the U.S. president's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani and then-Rep. Pete Sessions, R-Texas.  Both were part of a shadow diplomatic effort, backed in part by private interests, aimed at engineering a negotiated exit to ease President Nicolás Maduro from power and reopen resource-rich Venezuela to business, according to people familiar with the endeavor.  Sessions had served as emissary in the back-channel effort, visiting Maduro in Caracas that spring. The phone call, which Giuliani joined, was a follow-up to that visit, Sessions' spokesman Matt Mackowiak told The Washington Post.  The phone conversation involving the Venezuelan president and Trump's personal lawyer, which has not been previously reported, provides another example of how Giuliani used his private role to insert himself into foreign diplomacy, alarming administration officials confused about whose interests he was representing.  Giuliani operated a similar campaign this year in Ukraine, where he pressured officials to announce investigations to benefit Trump - an endeavor that led to the president's impeachment this month.  The impeachment inquiry pushed into the spotlight consulting work Giuliani has undertaken around the globe even as he has been representing Trump at no charge. His freelancing has triggered concerns among White House officials that his intercessions have muddied and at times undercut official U.S. policy, according to people familiar with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS LOSE LAST GAME OF REG SEASON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/268b264f5cbb631ff80d0d75dcd69621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — The New England Patriots of Tom Brady and Bill Belichick never have made the Super Bowl while playing in the wild-card playoff round. They'll have to make some more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER blames 'outage' after Trump whistleblower tweet temporarily disappears...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191229215046-jklx6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/TWITTER:Twitter system 'outage' briefly blocked Trump whistleblower tweet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman Shot Dead By Church Member... </title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/12/29/2-dead-1-critically-injured-shooting-white-settlement-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people are dead and another person is critically injured after a shooting at a church in the Tarrant County city of White Settlement, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Giuliani said to have taken part in 2018 call with Venezuela's president as part of shadow effort to ease him from power... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trumps-lawyer-and-the-venezuelan-president-how-giuliani-got-involved-in-back-channel-talks-with-maduro/2019/12/29/289dc6aa-235f-11ea-86f3-3b5019d451db_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudolph W. Giuliani participated in a September 2018 phone call with Venezuelan President NicolÃ¡s Maduro that was part of a shadow effort to ease him from power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS LOSE LAST GAME OF REG SEASON... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/12/29/game-day-live-sony-michel-questionable-for-patriots-regular-season-finale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest from Gillette Stadium, where the Pats are hoping to secure their 10th straight first-round playoff bye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California newspaper ends print publication after 161 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b56662573647af12c6d7d9c9c4a10c6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARTINEZ, Calif. (AP) — One of the longest-running newspapers in California printed its final edition on Sunday, ending 161 years of publishing news about the city of Martinez east of San...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:   All 7 killed in Hawaii tour helicopter crash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b15500d19b19291a42cba21b6dee65f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Tour helicopter operations in Hawaii have come under increased scrutiny after the deadly crash this week, one of several recent accidents in the state, with a congressman calling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRUBHUB driver attacks BURGER KING workers when order not ready for pickup...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/grubhub-battery-bust-278560</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 29--Two Burger King employees were attacked yesterday by a Grubhub deliveryman who “became agitated when informed that his order was not ready for pick up,” according to police reports. Inve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOOTING AT CHURCH IN TEXAS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/12/29/2-dead-1-in-critical-condition-after-reported-shooting-at-church-in-white-settlement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story and will be updated. Two people are dead and another is in critical condition after a shooting at a church in White Settlement,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANUKKAH HORROR</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2846e752d621824a9c2c75a89271c71e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONSEY, N.Y. (AP) — A knife-wielding man stormed into a rabbi's home and stabbed five people as they celebrated Hanukkah in an Orthodox Jewish community north of New York City, an ambush the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg's personal wealth rose by $27 billion this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10631458/facebook-chief-mark-zuckerbergs-personal-wealth-rose-27-3-billion-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK boss Mark Zuckerberg’s personal wealth rose by a mind-boggling $27.3 BILLION in 2019, says a report. The giant leap comes despite hostility from both users and lawmakers over the soc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans man has baby with sperm donated by trans woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/transgender-man-gives-birth-non-21177808</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Proud dad Reuben Sharpe has revealed how he gave birth to miracle baby Jamie with partner Jay in Britain’s most modern family - and even the couple's doctor was transgender</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete calls for decriminalization of all drugs...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/pete-buttigieg-calls-for-decriminalization-of-all-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 candidate Pete Buttigieg said in a Friday interview that he would decriminalize all drugs, not just marijuana.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
