<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City marks fall of Aztec capital 500 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-mexico-caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-21d75936dc02a995797612be69133eb6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Walking for hours through the gritty streets in the center of Mexico City, you can hear the daily urban soundtrack: Car engines, the call of the man who buys scrap metal and the handbells that announce the passing of a garbage truck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX deploys 2,500 out-of-state medical workers as younger, healthy patients crowd hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/texas-covid-abbott-deploys-2500-out-of-state-medical-workers-as-younger-patients-crowd-hospitals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said the state was bringing in 2,500 out-of-state medical personnel to relieve exhausted doctors and nurses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>440 Palm Beach Students Forced To Quarantine 2 Days Into School Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/440-students-palm-beach-county-quarantine-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Thursday, there are a total 131 confirmed cases of COVID-19 across more than 50 K-12 schools in the district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Florida Teachers Die In 24 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/13/broward-educators-lose-battle-with-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vicious virus, in less than one day this week, between Tuesday and Wednesday, claimed the lives of three Broward County school teachers and one of its assistant teachers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornel West on Why the Left Needs Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/cornel-west-jesus-progressives/619741/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The famous professor has found himself out of step with cancel culture and the search for political purity among progressives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Dems threaten mutiny over Pelosi budget plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/13/9-dems-threaten-mutiny-over-pelosis-budget-plan-504408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi can afford to lose only three votes in the House and will need near unanimity among Democrats to pass the budget resolution, which is slated for a vote when the House returns the week of Aug. 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouses getting booked by wealthy travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/where-to-rent-treehouses-in-us-japan-australia-and-costa-rica.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern treehouses are in demand by travelers who want a five-star, outdoor experience with a dose of childhood nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Toddler fatally shoots mother during work video call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/shootings-c6fca7d62ef3225327e111b760ee897a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, Fla. (AP) — A toddler found an unsecured, loaded handgun inside an apartment and fatally shot a woman while she was on a work-related video call, police in central Florida said. According to news outlets, the woman was the mother of the toddler who shot her in the head Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Sydney outbreak prompts new borders inside Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210813-growing-sydney-outbreak-prompts-new-borders-inside-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growing Sydney outbreak prompts new borders inside Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra shot OK'd for those with weak immune systems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-283298fb55b0556dbd9e45a62b782095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. regulators say transplant recipients and others with severely weakened immune systems can get an extra dose of the Pfizer or Moderna COVID-19 vaccines to better protect them as the delta variant continues to surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27 people aboard CARNIVAL cruise test positive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-travel-caribbean-4dd34f14b6a6365f48b3375c57ba4fb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELIZE CITY (AP) — Twenty-seven people aboard a Carnival cruise tested positive for COVID-19 just before the ship made a stop in Belize City this week, according to the Belize Tourism Board. The positive cases were among 26 crew members and one passenger on the Carnival Vista, which is carrying over 1,400 crew and nearly 3,000 passengers, the board said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Pioneer SONOS Fighting GOOGLE in 'Golden Age of Audio'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/speaker-pioneer-sonos-fighting-google-in-e2-80-98golden-age-of-audio-e2-80-99/ar-AANgPV8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonos Inc. became a favorite with audiophiles by selling sleek, wireless speakers for streaming music long before technology titans such as Alphabet Inc.’s Google entered the market with cheaper, internet-connected models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Billionaires Stir Alarm With Absence of Safety Oversight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/space-billionaires-stir-alarm-with-absence-of-safety-oversight/ar-AANgXh0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaires who blasted into space in recent weeks did so with style. Blue Origin’s Jeff Bezos sported a cowboy hat after landing and Richard Branson wore a blue Virgin Galactic jumpsuit he’d called “sexy.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem moderates threaten Pelosi strategy; Demand vote on infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/13/politics/house-moderate-democrats-infrastructure-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine Democratic House moderates are threatening to withhold their support for their party's must-pass budget resolution until Speaker Nancy Pelosi changes course and instead allows their chamber to first vote on the $1.2 trillion bipartisan infrastructure plan the Senate approved this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touchless TACO BELL could be future of drive-thrus...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/touchless-taco-bell-could-be-the-future-of-drive-thrus-b9468c0b-a215-4c6c-a022-b1aa40ac54dc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scan a QR code, and your order is lowered down from the kitchen above</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great American dog shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-great-american-dog-shortage-63218738-4472-47be-9428-76b1d9299a77.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the U.S. imports more than 1 million dogs a year, the annual demand is 8 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Humanitarian catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210813101141-av7xb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/UN (UPDATE 1, TV):UPDATE 1-Afghanistan on brink of 'humanitarian catastrophe', UN agencies say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan crisis intensifying...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-taliban-c6c8d4a41c554f36031a8131538d1402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban captured another three provincial capitals in Afghanistan on Friday, completing their sweep of the country's south in a lightning offensive that is gradually encircling Kabul, just weeks before the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators want answers about AMAZON biometric data collection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/567628-senators-want-answers-about-amazons-biometric-data-collection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bipartisan group of senators sent a letter to Amazon Friday raising questions about its collection of biometric data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Port Shutdown Raises Fears of Closures Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/massive-china-port-shutdown-raises-210441619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Supply Lines is a daily newsletter that tracks trade and supply chains disrupted by the pandemic. Sign up here.A Covid outbreak that has partially shut one of the world’s busiest container ports is heightening concerns that the rapid spread of the delta variant will lead to a repeat of last year’s shipping nightmares.The Port of Los Angeles, which saw its volumes dip because of a June Covid outbreak at the Yantian port in China, is bracing for another potential decline because of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human sperm mutations that cause disease identified...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-08-human-sperm-mutations-disease-children.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout development, life and the processes of aging, all human cells accumulate mutations, resulting in what is called mosaicism, a condition in which different cells in the same person have different DNA sequences or genetic makeup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overheated Real Estate Market Begins to Cool...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/13/overheated-real-estate-market-begins-to-cool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic created a frenzied real estate market in much of the United States that has yet to let up,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUMBLE, a YOUTUBE rival popular with conservatives, will pay creators who 'challenge the status quo'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/rumble-youtube-rival-popular-conservatives-173004776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-growing YouTube rival popular with conservative influencers has a new strategy to expand its online audience: Paying hundreds of thousands of dollars to well-known media personalities it says work to "challenge the status quo." The Toronto-based upstart Rumble said Thursday that it has struck deals with former U.S. congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard, the journalist firebrand Glenn Greenwald and others who had committed to posting their videos first to the site.Subscribe to The Post Most newslett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Preparing to Recognize Taliban if Kabul Falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-08-12/china-prepared-to-recognize-taliban-if-kabul-falls-sources-say-undermining-us-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes at the expense of the U.S., which has held up the Taliban’s international legitimacy as its remaining source of leverage while the militant group storms across Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children born during pandemic 'have lower IQs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/12/children-born-during-pandemic-have-lower-iqs-us-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers blame lack of stimulation as parents balanced childcare with working from home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow Seriously Considers Leaving MSNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rachel-maddow-considers-leaving-msnbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As her contract draws to a close, sources told The Daily Beast, the MSNBC icon has been weighing taking her brand elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears father agrees to step down as conservator 'when time is right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3463967/britney-spears-dad-jamie-steps-down-conservator-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ dad Jamie has agreed to STEP DOWN as conservator of her estate, court documents obtained by The Sun state.  The move comes after years of the singer BEGGING for the patriarch to be …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July busiest month for illegal border crossings in 21 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/july-was-busiest-month-for-illegal-border-crossings-in-21-years-cbp-data-show/ar-AANfIrr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is encountering “an unprecedented number of migrants,” DHS Secretary Mayorkas said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Plant-based diet best way to avoid heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/nutrition/a-plant-based-diet-is-the-best-way-to-avoid-heart-disease-according-to-a-new-report/ar-AANf1jj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers advise consuming whole foods and avoiding red and processed meat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 Marines Deployed to Evacuate Embassy Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/12/afghanistan-us-urges-citizens-to-leave-immediately-as-taliban-nears-kabul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Embassy warned its ability to assist Americans is "extremely limited even within Kabul" due to deteriorating security and reduced staffing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants seize Kandahar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-afghanistan-taliban-26d485963b7a0d9f2107afcbc38f239a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban captured two major Afghan cities, the country's second- and third-largest after Kabul, and a strategic provincial capital on Thursday, further squeezing the embattled government just weeks before the end of the American military mission in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  More Dem voters favor socialism than capitalism in major shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/democrats-favor-socialism-capitalism-shift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have grown considerably more accepting of socialism since the coronavirus pandemic began, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan crisis intensifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taliban-on-the-verge-of-capturing-two-of-afghanistan-s-largest-cities-after-taking-11th-provincial-capital/ar-AANeMF2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clashes pushed into the center of both Kandahar and Herat as Taliban fighters took control of some of the main government buildings in the two cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court won't block Indiana University vaccine mandate as Justice Barrett rejects student plea...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-won-e2-80-99t-block-indiana-university-vaccine-mandate-as-justice-barrett-rejects-student-plea/ar-AANg9rj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first case about mandatory coronavirus vaccinations to reach the Supreme Court, but Justice Amy Coney Barrett gave no reason for rejecting the request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7JXGQVvhCNc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner avoids talk of book, TV deals tied to recall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-caitlyn-jenner-6ce79bd7d97b417c6780a36dca89aa93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Caitlyn Jenner kicked off a monthlong campaign tour Thursday in her bid to become California’s next governor, but she also raised fresh questions about her motive for entering the contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jersey Town Became Magnet for Media Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/08/how-one-new-jersey-town-became-a-magnet-for-the-media-elite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Montclair, where a large swath of The New York Times is working from home and the local paper’s advisory board resembles “the Pulitzer committee,” as one resident put it. Amid such suburban splendor, will they ever want to commute back to the newsroom?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Strategist Arrested for Underage Sex Trafficking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gop-strategist-anton-lazzaro-arrested-for-underage-sex-trafficking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feds just arrested wealthy Republican strategist and occasional Fox News guest Anton Lazzaro on five counts of underage sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECLINE IN CHILDREN; GROWTH IN AGING BOOMERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/census-2020-five-takeaways-f313d5d43eb90e4f1b5d69bd163597d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau on Thursday issued its long-awaited portrait of how the U.S. has changed over the past decade, releasing a trove of demographic data that will be used to redraw political maps across an increasingly diverse country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Amy Coney Barrett rejects challenge to university's requirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-rejects-challenge-indiana-university-s-vaccination-requirement-n1276714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight students asked the court for an emergency order, arguing the risks of vaccination outweigh potential benefits to those in their age group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindell says he was 'attacked' at hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3463247/mike-lindell-attacked-hotel-cyber-symposium-dominion-lawsuit-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MyPILLOW CEO Mike Lindell has claimed he was ‘attacked’ in a hotel lobby in South Dakota. Lindell, a devoted supporter of former President Donald Trump, was in the state for a “cy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi raises House aide pay to almost $200K...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/pelosi-announces-house-staff-can-now-make-almost-200g-n1276683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The maximum salary last year was $173,900, according to the Congressional Research Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Weighs Creating Mission Center for China in Bid to Out-Spy Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/cia-weighs-creating-special-china-unit-in-bid-to-out-spy-beijing/ar-AANfDTD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Central Intelligence Agency is weighing proposals to create an independent “Mission Center for China” in an escalation of its efforts to gain greater insight into the U.S.’s top strategic rival, according to people familiar with the deliberations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police monitor death threats to judge in Spears conservatorship case...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/britney-spears-judge-death-threats-police-1235040519/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are monitoring death threats being made to Judge Brenda Penny, who’s overseeing Britney Spears’ conservatorship case. “LASD continues to monitor the social media chatter re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People flock to big cities...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/567613-census-rural-america-shrinks-as-people-flock-to-big-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans who live in rural areas continued to shrink in the last decade while the nation’s largest cities grew substantially, according to new data released Thursday by the U.S. Census Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem child, 19, comes out as non-binary...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3462095/eminem-child-comes-non-binary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMINEM’S 19-year-old child has quietly come out as non-binary and now goes by the name Stevie Laine – as family have shown their support, The Sun can reveal. The rapper legally adopted …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Hawaii visitors arrested for falsifying papers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/hawaii-visitors-arrested-false-vaccination-cards/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two visitors to Hawaii from the United States mainland were arrested Sunday for falsifying vaccination cards, the governor posted on social media Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Metabolism in adulthood does not slow as commonly believed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/metabolism-adulthood-does-not-slow-commonly-believed-study-finds-n1276650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metabolic rate remains stable all through adult life, from age 20 to 60 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican rep heckled at fundraiser after saying Donald lost election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dan-crenshaw-heckled-fundraiser-after-saying-trump-lost-election-175835491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A confrontation Wednesday night between Rep. Dan Crenshaw, R-Texas, and an Illinois Senate candidate highlighted the divide in the Republican Party over former President Donald Trump’s baseless claims that the 2020 election was rigged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census shows USA diversifying, white population shrinking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/census-2020-house-elections-4ee80e72846c151aa41a808b06d975ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. became more diverse and more urban over the past decade, and the white population dropped for the first time on record, the Census Bureau said Thursday as it released a trove of demographic data that will be used to redraw the nation's political maps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN TO REQUIRE PROOF OF SHOT</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/san-francisco-to-require-proof-of-vaccination-for-some-indoor-activities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (KRON) — San Francisco will require residents and visitors to prove that they are fully vaccinated against COVID-19 for a number of indoor activities such as visiting restaurant…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Al Qaeda resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/potential-al-qaeda-resurgence-afghanistan-worries-u-s-officials-n1276614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gen. Frank McKenzie told NBC News that he does not believe the Taliban will stop Al Qaeda from using Afghanistan to strengthen and rebuild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House cheers empoyer efforts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/canada-business-health-australia-coronavirus-pandemic-460afab866006f92ebd1e3916b024246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci says Americans can expect to see more children infected with the coronavirus as the highly transmissible delta variant extends its hold across the country. “Quantitatively, you will see more children in the hospital,” the government’s top infectious disease expert said at Thursday’s coronavirus briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Morocco to upgrade relations, open embassies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210812171933-6qhan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-MOROCCO/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Israel, Morocco to upgrade relations, open embassies, Israeli FM says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua paper says it can no longer print, blames govt...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210812165931-lomgm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICARAGUA-POLITICS/ (PIX):Nicaragua paper says it can no longer do print editions, blames government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of Pandemic Pet Owners Experiencing Regret...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/12/post-pandemic-pet-regret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent poll of Florida pet owners who had adopted or bought an animal during the pandemic says over 1/3 is experiencing post-pandemic pet regret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mississippi-braces-for-e2-80-98failure-e2-80-99-of-hospital-system-due-to-covid-19-surge-and-lack-of-icu-beds/ar-AANfhef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is averaging nearly 2,700 new covid-19 infections a day in the past week — spiking 54 percent in the past seven days — and a hospital's parking garage is being converted to treat additional ICU patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Hunter Biden tells prostitute Russians stole his laptop...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881213/Unearthed-video-shows-naked-Hunter-Biden-claiming-Russian-drug-dealers-stole-laptop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: EXPLICIT CONTENT. Hunter Biden claims Russian drug dealers stole another one of his laptops for blackmail while he was close to overdosing in a Vegas hotel room in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: Boosters 'Inevitable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dr-fauci-inevitably-well-have-to-give-booster-shots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci suggested that coronavirus vaccine booster shots might be inevitable for everyone eventually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf eyes comeback -- as Italian Saint?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/global/shia-labeouf-abel-ferrara-film-italian-saint-padre-pio-1235040107/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shia LaBeouf could be making a comeback turn. Legendary director Abel Ferrara has exclusively told Variety that LaBeouf has come on board to play the lead role in his next feature, which centers on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Restaurants Push Back Against Mandate: We're Not Gonna Be Covid Police...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/11/nyc-restaurants-against-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting next week, proof of vaccination will be required citywide for indoor activities such as dining, gyms and concerts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic laid bare America's diabetes crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-laid-bare-americas-100338534.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly COVID-19 pandemic has exposed a deeper U.S. public-health crisis.For more than a decade, the nation has been losing the battle against diabetes.Here are the stories of diabetes patients who fell victim to the isolation and disruptions the pandemic caused, even if they weren't infected with the coronavirus.Elicia Heaston had a best friend – Kate Herrin.(ELICIA HEASTON): "Kate was my best friend, but really my sister. We met like 26 years ago in high school in our English class, and we just developed a friendship."Long before the pandemic, Herrin was among the millions of Americans struggling to control their diabetes.Then COVID-19 hit.Poor and living alone, Herrin rarely left her apartment.She stopped going in for regular lab tests, and had a harder time than ever securing medical supplies.Her health deteriorated further, until the worst happened.(ELICIA HEASTON): "They found her on the bathroom floor. I heard them radio down that there was an unconscious female on the bathroom floor and I completely lost it. The police had me unlock her phone with the passcode and I unlocked the phone and the last thing she had Googled, what was up on her phone was the signs of a heart attack.”The coroner attributed the heart attack that killed Herrin to complications of type 2 diabetes. Heaston says Herrin was afraid COVID would kill her. Instead, it isolated her, and her diabetes got worse.(ELICIA HEASTON): "It's every day I think about her, every day. There's not one day that since she's passed that I don't think about her."68-year-old John Cupo works as a building systems manager in Las Vegas.He was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes more than a decade ago.Then, in November 2019, he spotted a sore on his left foot. His podiatrist blamed diminished blood circulation due to diabetes and treated the sore.After that, Cupo agreed to visit every other week for checkups.But COVID-19 upended his routine.(JOHN CUPO): "I was too afraid to leave the house to go into a crowded doctor's office or anything like that. So I just stayed home and I was trying to treat it myself, and it just kept getting worse and worse. My foot kept getting worse, so I went to see my new podiatrist, who I had met at the hospital, and he said he needed to amputate my toes. And then my foot ended up … the bone got infected. That's what happened. And the amputation of the toes didn't work because a week later, my foot turned black and I went to the foot doctor and he said I had to have my leg amputated."Cupo had a difficult four-month recovery after the amputation.He has since grown accustomed to his prosthetic, but says he believes he would still have his leg if it weren’t for COVID scaring him to stay home.The ranks of the newly diagnosed type 2 diabetes patients are shifting younger.In part, that’s because more and more Americans are living in “obesogenic” environments where they exercise less, eat more processed foods, and gain excessive weight at an earlier age.The isolation and inactivity imposed by the pandemic compounded many of those risks.At Children’s National Hospital in Washington, D.C., diagnoses of type 2 diabetes among patients 8 to 20 years old nearly tripled in the first year of the pandemic.One of the hospital’s new patients is 15-year-old Adedotun Adebayo.(ADEDOTUN ADEBAYO): "I was a pretty active person before Covid, so when Covid hit and everything shut down and all the gyms were closed and everything, I really didn't do much exercise and I think that's probably one of the factors that contributed to me getting diabetes. Yeah, I gained a lot of weight."In March this year, Adebayo was rushed to the ICU after having passed out at church.(ADEDOTUN ADEBAYO): "I woke up and I was in the hospital like I've seen the movie movies like with the little bed that moves and everything, and I had wires and I had all this beeping stuff around me. And I remember I couldn't, I couldn't talk. I couldn't talk, my speech was very slurred. And I couldn't … I didn't even want to eat. I didn't feel hungry. I just I just kept asking for water." These days, Adebayo says he tries to wake up earlier and eat a better diet.He counts the carbohydrates in his food so he can correctly dose his meal-time insulin injections. He also takes metformin, the first-line drug for type 2 diabetes.Deaths from diabetes surged 17% to more than 100,000 in the U.S. in 2020. That’s according to a Reuters analysis of CDC data.This grim toll is the result of a public-health failure that long predates the pandemic, and it is almost certain to persist after COVID-19 abates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires Calling For Emergency Tax On Billionaires!</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90665399/millionaires-are-calling-for-an-emergency-tax-on-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups are urging a one-time tax on the $5.5 trillion in wealth billionaires gained during the pandemic to fund unemployment grants and vaccinate the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINE EFFECTIVENESS SPOOKS SYSTEM</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vaccine-efficacy-biden-pfizer-moderna-death-infetion-4403be7b-ced7-410e-9c19-67e201f031f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is intensely scrutinizing coronavirus vaccines' effectiveness over time, facing the daunting task of timing booster shots right while still convincing the unvaccinated that getting the jab is worthwhile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUNISHMENT:  Philly Mayor Orders Unvaccinated Workers Wear DOUBLE-Masks...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/08/11/philadelphia-mask-mandate-vaccine-requirements-businesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia is taking big steps to get the coronavirus pandemic under control once and for all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Warrior mindset' police training proliferated. Then, high-profile deaths put under scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Warrior-mindset-police-training-proliferated-16381887.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Murray was shot five times by a sheriff's deputy on May 4, 2019.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
