<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>JOB GROWTH SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/05/jobs-report-february-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase by 210,000 in February, while the unemployment rate held steady at 6.3%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP: Americans largely back Biden response...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-coronavirus-pandemic-only-on-ap-honeymoons-d365bff571c24f9d3575bcbd051780aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden is enjoying an early presidential honeymoon, with 60% of Americans approving of his job performance thus far and even more backing his handling of the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss mull 'burqa ban' in vote centering on security, rights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-voting-rights-coronavirus-pandemic-switzerland-europe-e79c272e5827ad543b7f890d48194a4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — At a time when seemingly everyone in Europe is wearing masks to battle COVID-19, the Swiss go to the polls Sunday to vote on a long-laid proposal to ban face-coverings, both the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: For first time, majority says COVID situation getting better...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/331832/optimism-covid-situation-reaches-new-high.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after the pandemic took hold of the U.S., a majority of Americans say the situation is improving. Half expect the disruption to persist into 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading Critic of Big Tech Expected to Join White House...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/05/a-leading-critic-of-big-tech-is-expected-to-join-the-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden is expected to name Tim Wu, a Columbia University law professor, to the National Economic Council</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Biden Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/04/reagan-democrats-biden-republicans-politics-stan-greenberg-473330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pollster who identified “Reagan Democrats” in the 1980s sees the emergence of a mirror image voting bloc. And it spells trouble for a GOP dominated by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sand shortage? World running out of crucial commodity...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/05/sand-shortage-the-world-is-running-out-of-a-crucial-commodity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world is facing a shortage of sand — and climate scientists say it constitutes one of the greatest sustainability challenges of the 21st century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangers await humans on Mars as Elon Musk sets sights on colonization...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/04/dangers-await-humans-on-mars-as-elon-musk-eyes-colonization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science journalist Shannon Stirone explains why SpaceX founder Elon Musk “is absolutely out into space” when it comes to the “unrealistic” colonization of Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 fatalities in northern Italy staggering. Did pollution play role?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19s-death-toll-northern-100009103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air quality has been terrible for decades in Bergamo, in northern Italy, which last year suffered many COVID-19 deaths. Researchers see a connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During tough times, dogs save the Queen...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/during-tough-times-dogs-save-114438587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II has acquired two new corgi puppies after the last of her succession of the dogs died several years ago, The Sun reported on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Storm Brewing Over Anti-Money Laundering Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-storm-brewing-over-trump-e2-80-99s-anti-money-laundering-push/ar-BB1egBqj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration will soon have to settle a Bitcoin fight it didn’t even start, and its decision could have far-reaching implications for the virtual currency industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin: 'BAD LUCK BANGING OR LOONY PORN' Wins Golden Bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-film-festival-2021-awards-winners-golden-bear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winners of the Gold and Silver Bears at the 2021 Berlin International Film Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unstoppable revenge of the mullet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unstoppable-revenge-mullet-045415125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Business in front, party in the back": a hairstyle considered so obnoxious that for years it verged on being an arrestable offence, the mullet has made the unlikeliest comeback of the century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not your bitch: Campaign against 'sexist' dictionaries moves to Italy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210305095546-jxvsy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women's rights campaigner Maria Beatrice Giovanardi launches petition to change Italy's Treccani dictionary after successful push to amend Oxford Dictionaries' definition of 'woman'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope lands in Baghdad, beginning  first-ever papal trip to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/islamic-state-group-ali-al-sistani-coronavirus-pandemic-baghdad-pope-francis-ca6f3bcfe979bbaf399e15d9d614b25a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — Pope Francis arrived in Iraq on Friday to urge the country’s dwindling number of Christians to stay put and help rebuild the country after years of war and persecution, brushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US new daily Covid cases at five-month low as nations try to hold off surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-new-daily-covid-cases-at-five-month-low-as-nations-try-to-hold-off-surge/ar-BB1ecXdS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States recorded fewer than 40,000 new daily cases of Covid-19 for the first time in five months on Thursday, a piece of promising news as countries across the globe struggle to hold off another infection surge before inoculations become widespread. With frustration over restrictions having long weighed on populations worldwide, leaders were seeking to balance demands for easing rules while not unleashing another explosion in cases. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercomputer shows doubling masks offers little help preventing viral spread...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210305030525-fscog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-SUPERCOMPUTER (PIX, TV):Japan supercomputer shows doubling masks offers little help preventing viral spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of CNN Owner Says Pandemic 'Really Good For Ratings'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/warnermedia-ceo-says-coronavirus-really-good-for-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WarnerMedia CEO Jason Kilar apologized Thursday after he let slip that the coronavirus pandemic will continue to dominate the news cycle on CNN because it's "really good for ratings."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief appeals for National Guard to stay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/law-enforcement-on-alert-warning-capitol-siege-plot-07a1a03fcdb14e40ac0b182fbed39d6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Worried about continuing threats, the acting chief of the U.S. Capitol Police appealed to congressional leaders Thursday to use their influence to keep National Guard troops at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever scanners can be wildly inaccurate, researchers find...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Those-fever-scanners-that-everyone-is-using-to-16002043.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Temperature-scanning devices that check for fevers in schools, workplaces...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials defend 'slave letter writing' assignment at Mississippi school...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/school-district-officials-defend-slave-letter-writing-assignment-at-mississippi-school/article_9a7151a4-440e-5217-8e08-571d5a13e3d8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at a Mississippi school district have addressed the public about a controversial assignment called the “slavery letter writing activity.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect pictured at Pelosi's desk screams 'it's not fair' in courtroom tantrum...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Capitol-riot-suspect-pictured-at-Pelosi-s-desk-16001871.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Barnett, infamously photographed during the Jan. 6 Capitol riot with his feet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  USA contributes to ongoing decline of freedom worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://thefulcrum.us/big-picture/freedom-house-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefulcrum.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More bad news for democracy defenders: A new report confirms worldwide declines in freedom for the 15th year in a row, and the United States isn't helping matters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large quakes spark Pacific-wide tsunami alerts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mass-evacuations-large-quakes-spark-232030442.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of coastal residents in New Zealand, New Caledonia and Vanuatu fled for higher ground Friday as a cluster of powerful earthquakes sparked a Pacific-wide tsunami alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece rocked by new shaker...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greece-rocked-quake-near-city-192621319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new earthquake hit central Greece near the city of Larissa on Thursday, the same region where an even stronger tremor left 11 people injured the day before, the Athens seismological observatory said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest threat against Capitol fizzles, but officials seek 2 more months of National Guard help...</title>
      <link>https://www.westhawaiitoday.com/2021/03/04/nation-world-news/threat-against-us-capitol-fizzles-but-officials-seek-2-more-months-of-national-guard-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.westhawaiitoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Capitol police and security officials are seeking a renewed emergency declaration to extend the National Guard presence at the U.S. Capitol possibly into May, according to a person familiar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANISH:  Tech savvy dad who kidnapped daughter is 'impossible to trace'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/state/washington/article249704578.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He is communicating in a way that’s almost impossible to trace, which makes it extremely difficult for investigators to generate significant leads.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great apes at San Diego Zoo first non-humans to receive shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/health/story/2021-03-04/san-diego-zoo-vaccinates-apes-against-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the first time apes have been immunized against the coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis denies involvement in wealthy Key Largo vaccination site, despite donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/politics/os-ne-desantis-florida-keys-vaccination-site-20210304-bgkgtbkulnb57hnzpzchxk2a5m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis denied that he had anything to do with providing COVID vaccines to a wealthy, gated Florida Keys community in January ahead of other state residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Pedro Pierluisi: 'Puerto Rico will be the first truly Hispanic state'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/gov-pedro-pierluisi-e2-80-98puerto-rico-will-be-the-first-truly-hispanic-state-e2-80-99/ar-BB1efupw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico — Puerto Rico Gov. Pedro Pierluisi traveled to Washington, D.C., this week to meet with White House officials and advocate for a new bill that charts a path toward statehood for the American territory. The push to make Puerto Rico the 51st state follows a referendum last year in which 52.5% of voters on the island said they are in favor of permanently joining the American ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo and Newsom, once pillars of Dem Party, now look for paths to survival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-cuomo-newsom-once-120002054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two governors were once lauded for pandemic leadership but now are fighting for political survival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near FACEBOOK headquarters, a homeless camp is dismantled, and springs back...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/near-facebook-headquarters-fire-prone-130024568.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local officials recently dismantled a Menlo Park encampment in marshlands near Facebook. But weeks later, its residents are moving back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe fears creating health passports could lead to discrimination, division...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/europe-fears-creating-covid-19-230602103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Two-tier society?' Europe conflicted over 'passports' for people vaccinated for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman smuggled firearm hidden in body cavity into jail...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/gun/hidden-gun-recovered-742928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Missouri woman arrested last month on drug and weapons charges had a small revolver hidden in a body cavity that went undetected during a strip search and two pat downs, police report. The four-inc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani's daughter: Three-Way Sex With Couples Has Made Me Better Person...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2021/03/caroline-giuliani-on-three-way-sex-with-couples</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimacy between two people is like ping-pong, but with three people, it’s like volleying a ball with no net, and no blueprint. That openness has changed my life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break Mayhem Coming for Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vaccine-hungry-florida-braces-for-spring-break-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis says Florida is open to party-hungry travelers. Residents without vaccines are freaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>75-year-old doctor who worked out of car accused of murdering five patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/long-island-doctor-faces-murder-charges-over-patient-prescription-deaths-da/2923988/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island doctor is facing murder charges after five patients allegedly died between 2016 and 2018 due to prescriptions he wrote. George Blatti, 75, was arraigned Thursday on five counts of murder in the second degree and 11 counts of reckless endangerment in the first degree. Blatti was remanded and is due back in court on March 30. If…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor on leave after 'sexist' sermon telling wives to be pretty for husbands...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article249693258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor has since “taken a leave of absence and is seeking professional counseling,” the church said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Tumbles 25% In Month As Competition Heats...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/03/tesla-stock-fall-volkswagen-competition-china-challenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla’s volatile stock price is driving away once bullish investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo 'groomed' ex-aide, 'derailed' her career...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/04/andrew-cuomo-sex-accuser-talks-harassment-in-new-cbs-interview/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former aide believes Gov. Andrew Cuomo was “trying to sleep with me” during a one-on-one meeting in his Albany office last year, according to a TV interview that aired Thursday night. During a se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAWAII TSUNAMI WARNING CANCELED...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/tsunamis-may-strike-hawaii-after-huge-pacific-quake-agency/10388981/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center has canceled a tsunami watch that had been issued for the Hawaiian islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obesity crisis to blame for USA's world worst death toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9325167/US-obesity-crisis-blame-having-one-worlds-worst-Covid-death-tolls-major-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far 518,500 Americans have died from Covid,  the highest death toll of any nation and double the number of victims in second worst-hit Brazil. Almost 70% of adults in the US are obese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat That Went Missing In NJ Found In Pittsburgh -- 4 Years Later...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/03/04/animal-friends-missing-cat-new-jersey-to-pittsburgh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cat who went missing in New Jersey in 2016 somehow found herself in Pittsburgh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New GOOGLE database could hold key to mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/google-covid-19-database-hold-key-diseases-mysteries/story?id=76211711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This "line-list" data includes age range, gender, occupation and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama mandate extended to April...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2021/03/will-gov-kay-ivey-extend-alabamas-covid-mask-order-we-will-know-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama's mask order has been in place since July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds examining communications between lawmakers and rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/04/politics/capitol-riot-investigation-lawmakers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are examining records of communications between members of Congress and the pro-Trump mob that attacked the US Capitol, as the investigation moves closer to exploring whether lawmakers wittingly or unwittingly helped the insurrectionists, according to a US official briefed on the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-silencing majority: Censorship threatening democracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.deseret.com/indepth/2021/3/2/22309605/the-silenced-majority-bari-weiss-new-york-times-cancel-culture-free-speech-democrat-republican</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deseret.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In red America and blue America, an epidemic of self-censorship is threatening democracy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers union accused of conducting racial opposition research -- on parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/mom-accuses-utla-of-conducting-racial-opposition-research-on-parents-pushing-for-in-person-classes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Middle Eastern mom who wants her child back in school is outraged after she says UTLA tried to collect racial opposition research on her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  How Covid broke U.S.-China relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/03/04/covid-trump-xi-josh-rogin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump tried to make friends with Xi. Then came covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas cop arrested for murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/dallas-police-officer-arrested-charged-in-two-murders/2570547/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dallas police officer is in custody and is facing two charges of capital murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyprus to lift veil of secrecy with register of company owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/cyprus-to-lift-veil-of-secrecy-with-register-of-company-owners/ar-BB1ec1hy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyprus to lift veil of secrecy with register of company owners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOTS GET 'PEDESTRIAN' RIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/sidewalk-robots-legal-rights-pedestrians-821614dd-c7ed-4356-ac95-ac4a9e3c7b45.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delivery fleets are creating fears of a world where people dodge heavy, fast-moving droids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guard, cops at fence; Mall deserted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-michael-mccaul-384a9dba60295a85595f311702b1d89e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on a possible threat against the Capitol (all times local): 12:10 p.m. Security is high outside the U.S. Capitol, with National Guard troops and Capitol...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RED ON YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/03/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks posted heavy losses during Wednesday regular trading as rising bond yields spooked investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Claims to Have Active Cells in DC...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iranian-terrorists-claim-to-have-active-cells-in-washington-d-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian militia groups claim to have active cells of operatives stationed in Washington, D.C., and other U.S. cities, according to chatter in online forums used by these groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Hollywood rule:  Upstages Oprah with appearance on James Corden...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1405543/Oprah-Winfrey-prince-harry-meghan-markle-news-interview-Queen-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPRAH WINFREY may feel snubbed after Prince Harry appeared on James Corden's own television show, a Hollywood insider has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN, WILLIAM, KATE COUNTERPROGRAM</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14233603/kate-william-queens-rare-tv-before-meghans-oprah-bully/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William and Kate Middleton will join a rare TV special with the Queen – before Meghan Markle and Prince Harry’s interview with Oprah Winfrey airs. Buckingham Palace has this afte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE BUILDS ON OPRAH TO DELAY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9325545/Meghan-Harry-confirm-Oprah-interview-ahead-despite-Prince-Philips-health-battle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITV released a trailer at 4pm today ahead of the two-hour show, which featured the same footage released by CBS in the early hours of this morning - but this time with ITV's branding in the corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN: Meghan's women-empowering victimhood is garbage!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9321173/PIERS-MORGAN-Spare-anymore-hypocrites-Meghan-Harrys-women-empowering-victimhood-garbage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of bombshell revelations in the UK's Times newspaper, Meghan stands accused of waging a systematic reign of bullying terror against her personal staff at Kensington Palace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QAnon shaman' regrets; Was to bring God back to  Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/qanon-shaman-60-minutes-plus-2021-03-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacob Chansley, the man seen wearing face paint and a fur helmet with horns during the January 6 insurrection, tells 60 Minutes+ he was trying "to bring God back to the Senate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eager to act, Biden and Dems leave Republicans behind...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-democrats-no-republicans-1f84cadac63439f89efc1e0ea82de735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden and Democrats in Congress are jamming their agenda forward with a sense of urgency, an unapologetically partisan approach based on the calculation that it’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  More Money Doesn't Make You Kinder; Rich DO NOT  Have More Compassion...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/rich-people-compassion-for-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who bring home the bacon are likely to experience positive emotions, including confidence, pride, and determination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GONE WITH THE WIND', 'PSYCHO' reassessed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/why-tcm-is-showing-problematic-films-like-gone-with-the-wind-e2-80-93-and-wont-rule-out-woody-allen-classics/ar-BB1ecU29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Movies like "Gone With the Wind," "Breakfast at Tiffany's" and John Wayne's "The Searchers" are all-time Hollywood classics and beloved by many. But they also have material touching on their depiction of nonwhite characters that could make audiences cringe, especially in 2021. Beginning on Thursday, Turner Classic Movies plans to re-introduce these problematic films in a four-night series called "Reframed: Classic Films in the Rearview Mirror,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLS FOR BROADCAST DELAY AS HARRY GRANDFATHER REMAINS IN HOSPITAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/meghan-markle-and-prince-harrys-interview-couldnt-come-at-a-worse-time-for-royal-family-says-royal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal expert Katie Nicholl shares why the royal family may want the tell-all to premiere at a later date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN TV MISSING DONALD...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-state-tv-really-missing-145146121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIKHAIL KLIMENTYEVRussian state TV program 60 Minutes played the clip of former U.S. President Donald Trump asking CPAC: “Do you miss me yet?” The co-host Olga Skabeeva eagerly replied: “Yes, we do!”Other experts on the Rossiya-1 network nodded and concurred. Trump’s departure has sucked the joy out of pro-Kremlin propagandists, with a host of new problems looming on the horizon for Russia. Instead of jolly boasts about “owning” America’s president, Russian state TV shows are now filled with gloomy experts, and discussions about the impending flood of U.S. sanctions are so tense they leave the pundits on the verge of coming to blows.During the Trump years, state-media mouthpieces, tightly controlled by Russian President Vladimir Putin, put on a happy face and followed his lead in exclaiming that they wanted Trump to be elected solely because he promised to improve the U.S.-Russian relations. Appearing on domestic talk shows and news programs, experts are now slipping up and admitting that they preferred Trump’s presidency mainly because he was so devastatingly bad for the United States and its allies. After President Joe Biden was elected—despite Russia’s efforts to the contrary—all pretense faded into oblivion.During his nightly program The Evening With Vladimir Soloviev this Tuesday, prominent state TV host Vladimir Soloviev exclaimed: “Why would America think that we’re interested in changing or improving our relations with them?” He added: “What makes them think we’re interested in a reset?” Soloviev predicted a “harsh and asymmetrical response” to Biden’s first round of sanctions that will include further hostilities in Ukraine, long seen in Moscow as one of the main battlegrounds in Russia’s fight against the collective West.The Biden administration announced sanctions against seven Russian officials on Tuesday in response to the attack on Navalny, which was ignored by Trump.Across Russian state-media platforms, hosts and experts concurred that Russia is in a new Cold War with the United States, with far-ranging consequences for Ukraine and other countries neighboring Russia. In February, Putin held a video conference meeting with heads of Russia’s largest media outlets, convened behind closed doors. Prior to the summit, the head of RT, Margarita Simonyan, traveled to east Ukraine and publicly argued that “Mother Russia must take Donbas home.” After the conference, Simonyan quoted Putin as saying to her: “We will never abandon Donbas. Ever.” She also admitted that America was a topic of discussion, but didn’t go into further detail.Experts and pundits across Russian state media outlets repeatedly asserted that the United States always was and will always remain Russia’s sworn enemy. Appearing on The Evening With Vladimir Soloviev, Semyon Bagdasarov, director of the Moscow-based Center for Middle Eastern and Central Asian Studies, exclaimed: “A war is being waged against us. Let’s call things for what they are. They are our enemies. They want to destroy us.” Some went even further. During the same show, Dmitry Kulikov, member of Zinoviev Club, instituted by the Kremlin-controlled media giant Russia Today, argued that Americans should be perceived as a whole other class of beings, “the others.” Anyone who aligns with the United States—from Russian dissidents to European allies—will undoubtedly be painted with the same brush.Russian propaganda operations are expanding, both internationally and domestically, with larger budgets being allotted for state-media outlets like RT and RIA Novosti. Internally, the state media will attempt to unite Russians against the collective West, headed by the United States. Internationally, Russian state media and aligned troll farms will continue their effort to inflame divisions and chip away at NATO alliances.One of the consequences of President Biden’s election was the renewed commitment to trans-Atlantic unity, an unwelcome side effect for the Kremlin. Skabeeva of Russia’s 60 Minutes bitterly described the coordination of the latest package of the U.S. and European sanctions against Russia for the attempted poisoning of opposition leader Alexei Navalny as an example of “unity that was unheard of under Trump.” Appearing on Russia-1, the deputy dean of world politics at Moscow's State University, Andrey Sidorov held out hope that the trans-Atlantic alliances were damaged to the point of no return. He pointed out: “Trump will forever remain in the minds of U.S. allies as an example of how they could be dealt with by the next administration. They will always remember that.”Without a hint of irony, Sidorov described the alleged intent of the United States to interfere in Russian elections as “the third phase” of the Cold War. By that token, Russia has been engaged in “the third phase” of the Cold War against the United States for years, having “interfered in the 2016 presidential election in sweeping and systematic fashion,” as outlined in the findings of former Special Counsel Robert Mueller.Pro-Kremlin experts anticipated the upcoming cybermeasures that would target Russia in retaliation for its malign activities against the U.S. Appearing on 60 Minutes, Alexei Naumov from the Russian International Affairs Council said: “We’ve been laughing at Americans about how easily all of their systems have been hacked, perhaps by our hackers. But Americans have very strong cyber forces, offensive cyber forces. They can represent a threat for us.” Co-host Skabeeva coldly chimed in: “At the same time, we elected their president and they weren’t able to elect ours, so it’s an open question whose cyber forces are stronger.”Russian cyberwarfare will undoubtedly continue to include influence operations targeting the United States. During his evening broadcast on Wednesday, host Soloviev chuckled: “Will there be an inauguration of Trump on March the 4th?” Other panelists laughed and acknowledged their familiarity with the bizarre conspiracy theory spawned by QAnon. During the broadcast of 60 Minutes, Deputy Speaker of the Russian State Duma Pyotr Tolstoy said: “Here in Russia, we always have an asymmetrical response. It’s a scary one... and it’s classified.” Threatening retaliation for the latest set of U.S. sanctions, Russia’s Foreign Ministry spokeswoman Maria Zakharova urged the United States “not to play with fire.” Co-host Olga Skabeeva asked Zakharova whether Russia was ready to respond to American sanctions. She smirked: “There will be a response. Don’t you even worry about that.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Reporter Nearly CRUSHED By Falling Light Fixture Live On Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-msnbc-reporter-jacob-soboroff-nearly-gets-crushed-by-falling-light-fixture-live-on-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Jacob Soboroff got hit with an unexpected surprise while on air during a windy Thursday in Otay Mesa, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How people can end up living at airports FOR MONTHS...</title>
      <link>https://theconversation.com/how-some-people-can-end-up-living-at-airports-for-months-even-years-at-a-time-154336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theconversation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some do so of their own accord, using airport amenities to meet their basic needs. Others, however, would rather be anywhere else – and find themselves at the mercy of bureaucratic wrangling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW VARIANT SPREADS IN NYC...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/one-year-since-pandemic-hit-new-york-new-strain-emerges-in-upper-manhattan-155652651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a city where more than 29,000 have died from COVID-19, any new variant of the virus is an unwelcome development, especially as New Yorkers are eager to reclaim their city in the warm-weather months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At GOLF CHANNEL, women say, sexism fuels 'boys club' culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/At-Golf-Channel-women-say-sexism-fuels-a-boys-15999821.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Cornwell was at her parents' house in Fayetteville, Ark., in January when she dialed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Travels to Iraq on Mission of Healing...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/04/pope-francis-travels-to-iraq-on-a-mission-of-healing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis begins a three-day whirlwind tour of Iraq on Friday, despite worries that he could draw large crowds at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP CEO Says Fourth Estate To Get Second Wind From Digital Deals...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/news-corp-ceo-robert-thomson-says-the-fourth-estate-digital-deals-haggling-with-facebook-1234706431/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp. CEO Robert Thomson said Thursday “the terms of trade for content are changing fundamentally,” citing a global news sharing deal the company signed last week with Google. That deal was an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racist, Sexist...Classic? Hollywood Dealing With Problematic Content...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/racist-sexist-classic-how-hollywood-is-dealing-with-its-problematic-content</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As streamers build out their lucrative libraries, they are experimenting with label warnings, context panels and even purges: "These are valuable properties that you cannot just disregard. You want to keep them, but you have to make sure they don’t damage the brand."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Seismic Rumblings in Utah Reveal Volcanic Activity Lurking Below Desert...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202103041082254734-strange-seismic-rumblings-in-utah-reveal-volcanic-activity-lurking-below-the-desert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two earthquakes near Fillmore, Utah, in September 2018 and April 2019 measured 4.0 and 4.1 on the Richter scale, their sequences recorded by seismometers within the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Apocalypse Prediction? CDC Has Preparedness Guide...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2021/03/04/zombie-apocalypse-prediction-for-2021-cdc-has-a-guide/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Journalist Robbed At Gunpoint In San Fran -- While Reporting On Crime Spike!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/03/kpix-5-reporter-robbed-gunpoint-auto-thefts-san-francisco-twin-peaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A KPIX 5 reporter investigating a series of auto break-ins around Twin Peaks in San Francisco was robbed of his camera at gunpoint Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked docs spotlight dilemma...</title>
      <link>http://axios.com/biden-child-migrant-border-hhs-leaked-99e6d9a2-20f7-415e-b75c-c23d5c417914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol referred an average of 321 children per day in the week ending March 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBT PASSES $28 TRILLION FOR FIRST TIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.wlbt.com/2021/03/01/so-just-how-concerned-should-we-be-about-americas-trillion-debt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wlbt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America has a problem. Well, almost 28,000,000,000,000 problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look inside supersonic jet that could fly London to New York in 90 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/2442184/supersonic-jet-spike-london-new-york-inside/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUPERSONIC jet which could fly from London to New York in just 90 minutes has revealed what passengers could expect from the flight. Inside the Spike S-512 Supersonic Jet cabin would be a large s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Orbs Over Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/huge-ufo-spotted-hovering-over-23607535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses from all sides of Las Vegas flooded Twitter with videos and pictures of the unusual sight, with some claiming they were a large UFO. Others dismissed them as military flares</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the taggers: New York blighted with graffiti...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9324087/NYPD-wants-publics-help-identifying-graffiti-city-launches-bid-paint-vandalism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYPD bosses announced an initiative Wednesday, asking citizens to report and help clean graffiti after the department received more than 6,000 complaints last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgotten mausoleum of Roman emperor Augustus reborn...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210304-forgotten-mausoleum-of-roman-emperor-augustus-reborn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forgotten mausoleum of Roman emperor Augustus reborn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand hit by 7.3 mag quake; People told to move to high ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-new-zealand-earthquake-73-23607486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents across the country reported feeling the tremors in the early hours of Friday morning, and the nation's Civil Defence has warned coastal residents to move to higher ground</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death rates 10 times higher in countries where most adults overweight...</title>
      <link>https://www.albanyherald.com/features/health/covid-19-death-rates-10-times-higher-in-countries-where-most-adults-are-overweight-report/article_5ee60b49-22a5-5f0d-935c-3893f786f4ec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.albanyherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The risk of death from Covid-19 is about 10 times higher in countries where most of the population is overweight, according to a report released Wednesday by the World Obesity</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
