<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS DEPLOY INTO KABUL FOR EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/08/23/world/taliban-afghanistan-biden-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deployment beyond Kabul’s airport comes as President Biden considers pushing back his Aug. 31 deadline for U.S. troop withdrawal. Violent clashes continued at Kabul’s airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tallest man in USA, 7ft 8 inches, dead at 38 from heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3526483/tallest-man-in-america-igor-vovkovinskiy-dead-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE tallest man in America who stood at 7ft 8 inches died on Friday aged 38 of heart disease, his family confirmed. Igor Oleksandrovych Vovkovinskiy, originally from Ukraine, passed away at the May…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Employers must require...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/covid-vaccine-mandate-biden-506609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s call for schools and business to require vaccination comes amid stiff resistance by some Republican governors and lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN pastor giving boot to members wearing masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/tennessee-pastor-giving-boot-to-members-of-congregation-in-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a Sunday sermon, Pastor Greg Locke at Global Vision Bible Church — located in Nashville, TN — delivered some fiery warnings to pro-PPE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person on no-fly list flown into UK...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/afghanistan-person-on-no-fly-watchlist-flown-into-uk-during-evacuation-operation-12389001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The individual, who is not being identified by the government, is understood to have reached UK soil on a British military plane, with officials being alerted "overnight".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rape gangs having sex with DEAD bodies' after going door-to-door for sex slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15944502/woman-taliban-rape-sex-dead-bodies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN who fled to India as the Taliban seized Afghanistan claims that insurgents rape dead bodies after going door-to-door to find sex slaves. The former Afghan police force member – identi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive MICROSOFT data breach leaves 38 million records exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3525714/microsoft-power-apps-exposed-data-leaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE personal records of 38million people were accidentally leaked on the open internet due to a flaw in more than a thousand Microsoft web apps, according to reports. American Airlines, Ford, J.B. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney's dad says 'star's addiction, mental health problems far worse than public realized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3525166/britney-spears-dad-addiction-mental-health-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ father has kept the true depths of his superstar daughter’s mental health and drug addiction problems secret, court documents have revealed. Jaime Spears has claimed that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal church gathering shut down by police...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com.au/national/coronavirus-nsw-update-police-break-up-blacktown-church-gathering/55e27187-190b-4a1d-8ce0-8a193875ce1a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Daily Deaths Top 1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-s-daily-deaths-top-1-000-nyc-teacher-vaccines-virus-update/ar-AANBCqT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and BioNTech SE was granted a full approval by U.S. regulators. The Pentagon is now set to require all service members to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Most Americans Paying No Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/23/the-pandemic-has-most-americans-paying-no-federal-income-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A minority of the population picking up the tab would be dangerous if the situation were to last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO chief calling for two-month halt on boosters...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/568988-who-chief-calling-for-two-month-halt-on-vaccine-boosters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Health Organization (WHO) Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus on Monday called for a two-month moratorium on COVID-19 booster shots as many low and middle-income countries still struggle to provide enough vaccine doses for their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of household wells go dry amid California drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/thousands-of-household-wells-go-dry-amid-california-drought-without-water-youre-nothing/article_61b74be2-0bab-57ba-a52b-8a1f5aa99cbf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADERA COUNTY, Calif. — Fourteen years ago, Heriberto Sevilla came across a ranch on the outskirts of Madera set among fields of stalk grass and bright wildflowers. Pepper trees dotted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A couple, their baby and their dog died on CA hiking trail -- and officials don't know why...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-couple-their-baby-and-their-dog-died-on-a-california-hiking-trail-e2-80-94-and-officials-don-e2-80-99t-know-why/ar-AANDeIX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A family of three was found dead on a California hiking trail, and investigators are short on clues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden considers his pick to run Fed, major role overseeing Wall St slips under radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-considers-his-pick-to-run-the-fed-a-major-role-overseeing-wall-street-slips-under-the-radar/ar-AANDrhQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no consensus among Democrats about who would be right to be the Fed’s top banking cop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant, Unvaccinated, Intubated: Doctors Alarmed by Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/pregnant-unvaccinated-and-intubated-doctors-alarmed-by-rise/ar-AANDmL0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More young and healthy pregnant people are ending up hospitalized on ventilators, delivering babies prematurely and sometimes dying from Covid-19 during the delta-fueled spike in cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin launches construction of new warships amid tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-fd8c3cad9c4b1c91dda13a4ca4b49555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Monday launched the construction of new nuclear submarines and other warships, part of a sweeping military modernization effort amid tensions with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Cuomo abandons dog at gov mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/state/article/Cuomo-s-dog-Captain-left-at-mansion-after-16402902.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo, who has been staying with one of his sisters in Westchester County...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Disasters Messing With Our Brains?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/08/will-pandemic-fatigue-change-how-we-process-disasters/619858/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquakes and wildfires and wars keep piling up. When does our empathy run out?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army fires first 'Iron Dome missile interceptor' in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3524780/us-army-iron-dome-missile-interceptor-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Army successfully fired its first Iron Dome missile interceptor on Monday as fears of World War Three build across the world. The troops this morning completed the first test of the missile …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Couch Potatoes 7 Times More Likely To Suffer Stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/couch-potatoes-stroke-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers add that nearly nine in 10 strokes could be attributed to "modifiable" risk factors such as sitting too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Boasts $30 Billion in Payments as Creator Wars Heat Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-23/youtube-boasts-30-billion-in-payments-as-creator-wars-heat-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media companies have thrown considerable resources and money at online creators in recent years. YouTube would like to remind everyone that it throws the most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam deploys troops to enforce rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210823131541-rgvz9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIETNAM (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Vietnam deploys troops to enforce COVID lockdown in largest city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand extending stay-at-home as outbreak grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/568971-new-zealand-extending-lockdown-as-covid-19-outbreak-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand’s government has extended its nationwide lockdown as COVID-19 cases grow around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground arm-wrestling mania slamming NYC streets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/underground-arm-wrestling-mania-takes-nyc-by-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So much of the world is being taught to shy away from people, that people are dangerous. But we are pack animals — people belong together — and the sport of arm-wrestling teaches you that together…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health worker crunch pressures states battling Delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/health-worker-crunch-delta-variant-506484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alarming spread of new cases is draining the pool of available health workers in ways not seen since the pandemic’s winter peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked footage shows grim conditions in Iran's Evin prison...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-health-religion-iran-prisons-01dfade61d7a706d630bf83d30d8cb02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The guard in a control room at Iran's notorious Evin prison springs to attention as one by one, monitors in front of him suddenly blink off and display something very different from the surveillance footage he had been watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget clash pits moderate Dems against President, Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-c2c1cfd80e7850d32d3387a9e1c05087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Outnumbered and with their party's most powerful leaders arrayed against them, nine moderate Democrats trying to upend plans for enacting President Joe Biden's multitrillion-dollar domestic program face a House showdown .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborations between Black women sparking golden age for hip-hop...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Collaborations-between-Black-women-are-sparking-a-16404913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turn on your car stereo. Or open one of Spotify's top hits playlists. Or peruse your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban warn of 'consequences' if USA extends military presence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taliban-warned-consequences-us-extends-100037785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The warning came hours after Biden said the US could extend the withdrawal deadline to help evacuation efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental health online: Police posts of crises may traumatize...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-police-mental-health-41883ccc67210e505e13bdd7aaf4713a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE — This story includes discussion of suicide. If you or someone you know needs help, please call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800-273-8255. The videos are difficult to watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210823-taiwan-team-says-it-was-told-to-remove-flag-before-le-mans-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of influx of militants disguised as refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/08/23/putin-warns-of-influx-of-afghan-militants-disguised-as-refugees-a74865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Who is among these refugees? How can we know?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces crucial moment on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/568963-this-week-biden-faces-crucial-moment-on-capitol-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is facing a critical week on Capitol Hill amid Democratic divisions on infrastructure strategy and high-profile criticism over a messy exit in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Topping $50,000 Stirs Forecast of Run Toward Record High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-nears-50-000-level-015607040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin topped $50,000 for the first time since May as crypto prices continued an ongoing recovery from a disorderly rout just three months ago.The largest virtual coin advanced 3.8% to $50,272 as of 6:53 a.m. in New York, with other tokens including Ether and Cardano’s ADA also rising. The revival in virtual currencies has excited the animal spirits of the crypto faithful, putting predictions of $100,000 or more for Bitcoin back in vogue. Others see the volatile asset carving out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Judges Order Defendants to Get Jab. Can They Do That?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/23/2-new-york-judges-ordered-defendants-to-get-vaccinated-can-they-do-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendant was charged with a number of minor crimes, including drug possession and shoplifting. He was prepared to plead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly firefight erupts at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/23/deadly-firefight-erupts-at-kabul-airport-as-evacuation-chaos-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is considering extending the deadline for the complete troop withdrawal beyond its original Aug. 31 date, Biden said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds clash in Portland as Proud Boys rally descends into violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-clash-portland-proud-boys-055220944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Colorado River Dries Up, Phoenix Will Have to Survive on Less Water...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2021/08/us/colorado-river-water-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado River irrigates farms, powers electric grids and provides drinking water to 40 million people. But as its supply dwindles, a crisis looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's peak of delta wave could be days away...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2021/08/22/floridas-peak-of-the-delta-wave-could-be-days-away-university-models-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Florida is rapidly approaching the peak of new infections of the delta wave, when the highest single-day counts could come, according to two models created by researchers at Florida…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-voting-rights-fb8ce99277e00e21189f948b98d15d55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The Rev. Jesse Jackson, and his wife, Jacqueline, remained under doctors' observation Sunday at a Chicago hospital and were “responding positively to treatments” for COVID-19, their son told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER NFL FAN BRAWL: Woman slaps man in stands, triggering huge fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3521807/brawl-nfl-game-woman-slaps-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAMATIC footage shows the moment ANOTHER huge brawl broke out at an NFL match after a woman shouted in a man’s face before slapping him. Chaos erupted in the stands at the Steelers’ pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four weeks in July: Inside Biden struggle to contain delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/four-weeks-in-july-inside-the-biden-administration-e2-80-99s-struggle-to-contain-the-delta-surge/ar-AANA8py?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After declaring ‘independence from a deadly virus’ on July Fourth, Biden and his team were caught flat-footed as the delta crisis spiraled out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump booed at Alabama rally after telling supporters to get vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/22/trump-booed-at-alabama-rally-after-telling-supporters-to-get-vaccinated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"But, I recommend take the vaccines," Trump said. "I did it. It's good. Take the vaccines."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon hints at expanded operations in Kabul; Evacuations face new hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Taliban-co-founder-in-Kabul-for-talks-as-group-16402556.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abdul Ghani Baradar, considered the Taliban's top political leader, arrived in Kabul on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue dogs shot dead in Australia due to restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/rescue-dogs-shot-dead-by-nsw-council-due-to-covid-19-restrictions-20210821-p58ksh.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several impounded dogs have been shot by a rural council under its interpretation of COVID-19 restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record hour of rainfall in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/tropical-storm-henri-leaving-impressive-rainfall-totals-in-its-wake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some parts of Central New Jersey could see as much as 10-12 inches of rain as Henri slowly churns its way out of our area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catastrophic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/catastrophic-flooding-turns-deadly-in-middle-tennessee/1004182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intense and relentless downpours resulted in catastrophic flooding across Middle Tennesse on Saturday, with one location potentially setting a 24-hour rainfall record with more than 17 inches of rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 dead, many missing after 17 inches of rain in Tennessee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-tennessee-d35389e7d661cb1a225ae55af332022e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAVERLY, Tenn. (AP) — At least 22 people were killed and rescue crews searched desperately Sunday amid shattered homes and tangled debris for dozens of people still missing after record-breaking rain sent floodwaters surging through Middle Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
