<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The sniper who picked off 250 ISIS fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/long-shot-review-triggering-a-revolution-11550519520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A memoir by an Iranian deserter turned Kurdish sniper who picked off 250 Islamic State ﬁghters during the battle of Kobani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' ROLE SLASHED?</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/19/jussie-smollett-empire-role-slashed-alleged-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett's "Empire" role slashed in wake of the alleged attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer patient who needed tongue removed has new one made from arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8455591/cancer-patient-new-tongue-made-from-arm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CANCER patient who needed her tongue removed has a new one — made from her arm. Grandmother Joanna Smith, 58, was diagnosed with cancer of the tongue and was warned unless it was removed she woul…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super gonorrhoea start of drug-resistant STD boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/8376421/this-morning-dr-sara-kayat-new-super-gonorrhoea-warning/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“SUPER” gonorrhoea may sound dramatic, but it’s a real and increasing threat. While regular “regular” gonorrhoea (AKA the clap) is the UK’s second most common ST…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I design like breathe. You don't ask to breathe -- just happens'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/karl-lagerfeld-dead-fashion-icon-chanel-designer-was-85-1178148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The creative director of Chanel, Fendi and his own eponymous brand once said, "I design like I breathe. You don’t ask to breathe — it just happens."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET CAT EARNED MILLIONS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/760613/Karl-Lagerfeld-cat-Choupette-Chanel-boss-model-cat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How people who appear happiest could be most dangerously depressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6720379/Its-possible-depressed-appearing-happy-heres-particularly-dangerous.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While smiling depression is not a technical term, it is certainly possible to be depressed and manage to successfully mask the symptoms, writes Cambridge University researcher Olivia Remes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious attack claims lives of 6 llamas near Kentucky zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/2019/02/18/kentucky-llamas-killed-strange-attack-near-louisville-zoo/2909125002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caroline Willette, one of the owners of Louisville llama farm woke up around 7:30 a.m. to see blood and tufts of wool around the property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Universe map unearths 300,000 more galaxies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/universe-map-unearths-300-000-more-galaxies-081007520.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The known Universe just got a lot bigger. A new map of the night sky published Tuesday charts hundreds of thousands of previously unknown galaxies discovered using a telescope that can detect light sources optical instruments cannot see. The international team behind the unprecedented space survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals desecrate 90 Jewish graves in east France ahead of marches...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-cemetery-antisemitism/vandals-desecrate-90-jewish-graves-in-east-france-ahead-of-marches-idUSKCN1Q81NZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vandals have daubed swastikas and anti-Semitic slogans on around 90 graves in a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVED CHANEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/obituaries/la-me-karl-lagerfeld-20190219-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fashion designer transformed Chanel from a faded fashion empire into a world power of style.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET EASTON ELLIS: The Year the Oscars Finally Got Gay Right...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/bret-easton-ellis-year-oscars-finally-got-gay-right-1187022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record of seven out of 20 nominated roles are for LGBTQ characters in 2019 — and there's not a tortured coming-out story, dreary AIDS death or noble martyrdom among them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST QUOTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190219-wit-wisdom-karl-lagerfeld-best-quotes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wit and wisdom of Karl Lagerfeld: his best quotes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary attacks Soros, Juncker in new media campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190219-hungary-attacks-soros-juncker-new-media-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary attacks Soros, Juncker in new media campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego SEAWORLD ride malfunctions in heavy winds, stranding 16 for hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/san-diego-seaworld-ride-malfunctions-in-heavy-winds-stranding-16-for-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen guests wound up trapped on a gondola ride at SeaWorld in San Diego on a Monday after an "unusual gust of significant wind" caused the ride to shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who died in Ed Buck home told friends Dem donor was 'f***ing devil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6719975/Man-dead-Ed-Bucks-home-described-Democrat-donor-f-ing-devil.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timothy Dean, 55, who was found dead in Ed Buck's California home last month, had previously told friends he was afraid of the wealthy IT mogul and warned friends not to go to his house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Allays Retail Jitters With Best Holiday Quarter in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/walmart-allays-retail-jitters-with-best-holiday-quarter-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart Allays Retail Jitters With Best Holiday Quarter in Years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100-plus inches of snow so far put Buffalo 27 inches above normal..</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/2019/02/18/buffalo-hits-100-inches-of-snow-so-far-this-winter-with-more-to-come/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday's snowfall tied the city for its ninth-earliest date on record that Buffalo has reached triple-digit snowfall out of the 37 times the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge to rule in Chicago Obama Library lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d045094f74f458dad75bd12183ee67c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A federal judge will rule on the city of Chicago's request to toss a lawsuit aimed at halting President Barack Obama's museum and library from being built in a public park. U.S. District Judge John Robert Blakey heard oral arguments last week in the case and said he would issue a ruling Tuesday. Protect Our Parks wants to stop the $500 million Obama Presidential Center from being built in the selected location. A ruling in favor of the group could signal that the Obama Presidential Center is in real trouble. The parks advocacy group accuses the city of illegally transferring park land to a private entity, The Obama Foundation. City lawyers say Protect Our Parks misread the law, has misrepresented how the approval process worked and exaggerated potential environmental disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledge, Apologize, Investigate: How Big Brands Combat Online Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/acknowledge-apologize-investigate-how-big-brands-combat-online-outrage-11550579223</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it feels like there is a steady stream of fresh outrage over consumer-brand gaffes, it may be because companies have become more adept at managing controversy than at pre-empting it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:: America's Sickness...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/02/hate-crime-hoaxes-reflect-americas-sickness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s an obvious answer to the question, ‘Why would Jussie Smollett do something like that?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gory spirit festival lights up Cambodian capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190219-gory-spirit-festival-lights-cambodian-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gory spirit festival lights up Cambodian capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh shuts 20,000 websites in anti-porn 'war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190219-bangladesh-shuts-20000-websites-anti-porn-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bangladesh shuts 20,000 websites in anti-porn 'war'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 graves vandalised at Jewish cemetery in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190219-80-graves-vandalised-jewish-cemetery-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;80 graves vandalised at Jewish cemetery in France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTORIOUS ACID TONGUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6720439/Karl-Lagerfeld-dies-aged-85-France.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld has died in France, at the age of 85, after being rushed to hospital following a short battle with pancreatic cancer, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French label under fire for casting 'unhealthy looking' model...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6720231/Chlo-comes-fire-casting-skeletally-model-campaign.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the short clip to promote the designer's spring summer 2019 range, a slim woman in a tasselled mini skirt, and carrying a Mini Chloé C handbag, struts along in the sunshine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies Roll Out Gunshot Detectors at the Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/companies-roll-out-gunshot-detectors-at-the-office-11550575801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate executives worried about workplace shootings are quietly installing gunfire-detection systems in U.S. offices and factories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERN AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.vpr.org/post/hes-2020-bernie-sanders-running-president-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vpr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders has confirmed to VPR that he is seeking the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAGERFELD DEAD IN PARIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/karl-lagerfeld-obituary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karl Lagerfeld, one of the most prolific and widely popular designers of the 20th and 21st centuries, died in Paris. He was 85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FASHION  ICON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8459388/karl-lagerfeld-dead-at-85-according-to-reports-in-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEGENDARY fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld has died in hospital in Paris aged 85. The fashion icon passed away after several weeks of ill health and was rushed to hospital last night, Closer magazin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish graves desecrated in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47289129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 80 graves are damaged at a Jewish cemetery, ahead of nationwide marches against anti-Semitism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I owe how much? Americans shocked by impact of new tax law...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/57ac6498374944f7bfb20660630c95f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait, I owe the IRS? The first tax filing season under the new federal tax law is proving to be surprising, confusing — and occasionally frightening — for some Americans, especially those accustomed to getting money back from the government. Take Andy Kraft and Amy Elias of Portland, Oregon. The couple had grown comfortable getting a small refund each year, a few hundred dollars or more. Then they found out they owe $10,160 this year. "I will never forget the moment, I thought 'We look good' and then we added in the next W-2 and my jaw hit the floor," Kraft said. "There was no way I wanted to believe that what I was looking at was accurate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  10 Dems most likely to win nomination...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/430461-the-10-dems-most-likely-to-win-the-2020-presidential-nomination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race for the Democratic presidential nomination is already heating up, even though there is almost a year to go before the Iowa caucuses.Here are The Hill’s rankings of where the contenders stand right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four-day week trial: Staff happier, more productive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2019/feb/19/four-day-week-trial-study-finds-lower-stress-but-no-cut-in-output</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study of trial at New Zealand firm finds staff were both happier and more productive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Rivals Explore Alliance to Unseat Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netanyahu-rivals-explore-alliance-in-bid-to-unseat-israels-long-serving-prime-minister-11550520674?mod=searchresults&amp;page=2&amp;pos=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s most formidable opponents are in talks to form a united front, and face a deadline this week to declare whether they will join their camps to try to unseat him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Miami, Trump Praises Political Exiles From Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-miami-trump-praises-political-exiles-from-latin-america-11550531586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday declared that the “twilight hour of socialism has arrived” in Venezuela, Nicaragua and Cuba, as he praised Latin Americans in exile who have helped lobby for change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREATENS TRANSATLANTIC TRADE WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/us-and-germany-tariff-war-plunges-relations-to-new-low-lr9p80bnf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has threatened to reignite a transatlantic trade war by imposing hefty tariffs on European car imports. “I like punitive tariffs”, he said ahead of a US Commerce Department report...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Attacks Rise in NYC... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/18/nyregion/anti-semitism-brooklyn-new-york.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent uptick in anti-Semitic incidents in New York is most noticeable in and near Crown Heights, Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Trudeau's Political Crisis Widens as Top Aide and Friend Resigns... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/canada/gerald-butts-resigns-as-prime-minister-justin-trudeaus-principal-secretary/ar-BBTLPqf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama newspaper editor calls for return of the KKK to 'clean out DC'...</title>
      <link>https://www.montgomeryadvertiser.com/story/news/2019/02/18/alabama-newspaper-ku-klux-klan-to-night-ride-again-linden-democrat-reporter-goodloe-sutton/2910436002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.montgomeryadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goodloe Sutton, the longtime editor of the Democrat-Reporter newspaper, called for lynchings in a phone call with the Montgomery Advertiser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone apologizes to judge after photo post...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6718911/Roger-Stone-posts-Instagram-photo-judge-assigned-case-looks-like-CROSSHAIRS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone apologized for sharing a photo to Instagram of Judge Amy Berman Jackson, the judge assigned to his criminal case, with what looked like a depiction of crosshairs near her head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smaller tax refunds put Republicans on defensive...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/430305-smaller-tax-refunds-put-gop-on-defensive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration and key GOP lawmakers are playing defense after early data showed Americans are getting smaller tax refunds in the first filing season under the GOP tax law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The days of socialism are numbered'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/430498-trump-on-latin-america-the-days-of-socialism-are-numbered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump repeatedly slammed socialism during a Monday speech about Venezuela, saying that the political ideology's days in North and South America are "numbered."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny S.Africa beach restaurant crowned best in world... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/tiny-africa-beach-restaurant-crowned-best-world-222011358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tiny beach restaurant in an isolated South African fishing village was named the best in the world on Monday. Chef Kobus van der Merwe, who did not begin to cook seriously until he was 30, forages every day for ingredients on the wild Atlantic shore of the Western Cape near his Wolfgat restaurant,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Wake up', Macron will tell Europe in major pre-Brexit speech...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190218212448-vpi5y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-MACRON/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-'Wake up', Macron will tell Europe in major pre-Brexit speech -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters take over Border Patrol museum, deface pictures of fallen agents...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/protesters-take-over-border-patrol-museum-deface-pictures-of-fallen-officers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of demonstrators occupied and vandalized a privately owned U.S. Border Patrol museum near El Paso, Texas, over the weekend, according to the site's top official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Vatican Secret Rules for Priests Who Father Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-vaticans-secret-rules-for-priests-who-have-children/ar-BBTMawR?li=AAgfYrC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians say Israel 'playing with fire' by closing Temple Mount gate...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Police-chase-suspect-onto-Temple-Mount-developing-report-580994 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jerusalem Police detained five east Jerusalem Arabs who tried to enter the premises of the Golden Gate, which has been closed by a court order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cartel Ambushes Soldiers Near Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/02/18/mexican-cartel-ambushes-soldiers-near-texas-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ambush by gunmen from a faction of Los Zetas killed one Mexican soldier and injured two others in Nuevo Laredo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren to Unveil Universal Child Care Plan Funded by Wealth Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-19/warren-to-unveil-universal-child-care-plan-funded-by-wealth-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INCHES OF SNOW ON VEGAS STRIP!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/weather/news/2019-02-18-snow-las-vegas-nevada-february</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cold weather pattern in the West has given Las Vegas snow twice in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does the Media Keep Falling for Obvious Hoaxes?</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/why-does-the-msm-keep-falling-for-obvious-hoaxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could it be "magical thinking," confirmation bias, malice, or just plain stupidity?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROTHERS BREAK SILENCE...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/02/18/jussie-smollet-motive-staged-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Empire” actor Jussie Smollett, upset after a racist letter sent to the show's studio didn’t get a “bigger reaction,” is suspected of paying two men to attack him a week later, according to multiple sources with direct knowledge of the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATES SUE TO STOP TRUMP EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190219004631-0tj8i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/CHALLENGE (URGENT):U.S. states sue Trump administration in showdown over border wall funds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro to throw concert rivaling Branson...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/66f55780a73a4754a41529a062f7d057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Refusing to back down amid a mounting battle over Venezuela's humanitarian crisis, the government of President Nicolas Maduro announced Monday that it will hold its own huge concert to rival one being organized by a billionaire backer of opposition leader Juan Guaido and import tons of aid from Russia. Information Minister Jorge Rodriguez said the government will throw a concert Saturday and Sunday on Venezuela's side of the border — opposite one in Colombia being spearheaded by Richard Branson, the wealthy British adventurer and founder of the Virgin Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Evidence Overwhelming Court Cases, Judges Not Prepared...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/2/18/18225231/emoji-emoticon-court-case-reference</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does a crown emoji really mean?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Vatican Secret Rules for Priests Who Father Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/18/world/europe/priests-children-vatican-rules-celibacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican confirmed, apparently for the first time, that it has general guidelines for what to do when clerics break celibacy vows and father children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops impound tractor for drag racing against motorbikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.somersetlive.co.uk/news/police-impound-tractor-after-reported-2552211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.somersetlive.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Pretty nippy' tractor weighs around 5.5 tonnes and has up to 175hp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientists Discover Mysterious 'Wireless' Brain Communication...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/neuroscientists-say-they-ve-found-an-entirely-new-form-of-neural-communication</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists think they've identified a previously unknown form of neural communication that self-propagates across brain tissue, and can leap wirelessly from neurons in one section of brain tissue to another – even if they've been surgically severed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST Writer: Story Fit Era 'Narrative'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/kyle-drennen/2019/02/18/washposts-capehart-smollett-story-fit-narrative-trump-menace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appearing on MSNBC Live With Hallie Jackson Monday morning, Washington Post opinion writer Jonathan Capehart lamented that actor Jussie Smollett’s claim of being assaulted by Trump supporters was falling apart. The liberal journalist then attempted to blame the “atmosphere of menace” supposedly created by the President to explain why so many in the media, including himself, believed the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts 'tyrannical' Maduro: Let your people go!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6717997/Trump-say-Venezuelas-democracy-irreversible.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump told america's Venezuelan expat community that their country is 'turning the page on socialism, turning the page on dictatorship. and there will be no going back.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic black snow blankets Siberian towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/black-snow-falls-from-the-sky-in-siberia-and-its-toxic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pall of eerie black snow covered several towns in the Siberian region of Kuzbass, home to 2.6 million people and one of the world's largest coal fields</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NEW DAY' FOR LATIN AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ab8a21cafa354570ad78816eb8788646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — President Donald Trump said Monday that "a new day is coming in Latin America," as he sought to rally support among the largest Venezuelan community in the U.S. for opposition leader Juan Guaido. Speaking at Florida International University in Miami before large American and Venezuelan flags, Trump said the U.S. stands behind Guaido, whom the U.S. recognizes as the country's rightful president, and condemns President Nicolas Maduro's government and its socialist policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgotten challenge to Mueller lingers at appeals court...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/18/robert-mueller-investigation-ruling-1173599</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even the lawyer who brought the challenge doubts that the three-judge D.C. Circuit panel hearing the case will upend Mueller’s authority nearly two years into his investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utterly unbelievable scale of U.S. debt...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/the-utterly-unbelievable-scale-of-u-s-debt-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debt accumulated under Donald Trump would be enough to cover the inflation-adjusted cost of U.S. involvement in the Second World War</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Kamala Freezes, Laughs Awkwardly When Asked About Tweet...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/harris-freezes-when-asked-about-calling-smollett-incident-a-modern-day-lynching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris (D., Calif.) froze and awkwardly looked around when pressed Monday on her previous tweet that the alleged attack on actor Jussie Smollett was a "modern-day lynching," before saying she needed to see all the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Heralds New Political Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ocasio-cortez-heralds-a-new-political-era-11550519444</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialism may not become America’s dominant ideology, but it’s likely to be around for a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something's killing Outer Banks humpback whales...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/latest-news/article226423755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Won't Comment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76f5620941ed4ea883fff89882983e62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on the presidential candidates (all times EST): 3:25 p.m. California Sen. Kamala Harris says she won't comment again on the investigation into a reported attack on "Empire" actor Jussie Smollett until an investigation is completed. Speaking to reporters in Concord, New Hampshire, on Monday during her first 2020 presidential campaign trip here, Harris says that "the facts are still unfolding" and that while she is "very concerned" about Smollett's initial allegation and that it should be taken seriously, "there should be an investigation." She says, "I think that once the investigation is concluded, then we should all comment, but I'm not going to comment until I know the outcome of that investigation." Harris previously tweeted that the alleged attack was "an attempted modern day lynching." She will hold a town hall later Monday in Portsmouth, her first of the 2020 cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA black market for pot stifling legal sales. Now gov wants to step up enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-gavin-newsom-crackdown-pot-black-market-20190219-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the state Cannabis Advisory Committee on the first year of legal pot sales in California says there is problem that requires urgent action: Lax enforcement has allowed the black market to flourish, threatening licensed business with unfair competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Canyon tourists exposed for years to radiation...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona/2019/02/18/grand-canyon-tourists-exposed-radiation-safety-manager-says/2876435002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elston Stephenson, safety manager at Grand Canyon National Park, says thousands were unknowingly exposed to unsafe radiation for nearly two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker seeks dialogue about race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/430289-booker-seeks-dialogue-about-race-as-he-kicks-off-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since announcing his 2020 bid earlier this month, Cory Booker has talked in personal terms about racism and the need to have “honest conversations.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Record High Name Govt as Most Important Problem...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/246800/record-high-name-government-important-problem.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-five percent of Americans name the government as the greatest problem facing the U.S., the highest percentage Gallup has recorded for this concern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Lara Logan Calls Media 'Mostly Liberal' in Scorched Earth Interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/cbss-lara-logan-calls-media-mostly-liberal-in-scorched-earth-interview-im-committing-professional-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Images Show Facility Overwhelmed by Migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/02/18/exclusive-leaked-photos-show-u-s-border-facility-overwhelmed-by-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked photos reveal the extent to which U.S. border facilities are being overwhelmed by the inflow of migrants from Central America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK security app used to 'spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-47281906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cross-party group of MPs says Facebook used its Onavo app to gather information on competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No plan for actor to do follow-up police interview...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5dc18b9dc7541f5b859ac94aceb5cdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Attorneys for "Empire" actor Jussie Smollett say there are no plans for him to meet with Chicago detectives Monday for a follow-up interview about his reported assault. Anne Kavanagh is a spokeswoman for Smollett's lawyers. She says in an emailed statement that his lawyers "will keep an active dialogue with Chicago police on his behalf." Smollett reported last month that he was physically attacked by two men who yelled homophobic and racial slurs. He said they also yelled he was in "MAGA Country," an apparent reference to President Donald Trump's campaign slogan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sailor in iconic VJ Day photo dies at 95...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/02/18/sailor-kissing-woman-vj-day-photo-times-square-dies/2904579002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man in the iconic photo of an exuberant Navy sailorÂ kissing a womanÂ in New York City's TimesÂ Square at the end of World War IIÂ has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAW DEAL? Cities, States Scale Back 'Green' Ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/18/green-new-deal-taxpayer-costs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Whether people want it or not'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Venezuela move to democracy 'irreversible'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab8a21cafa354570ad78816eb8788646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — President Donald Trump will seek on Monday to rally support in the largest Venezuelan community in the U.S. for opposition leader Juan Guaido, saying Venezuela's "current path toward democracy is irreversible." White House press secretary Sarah Sanders said that Trump will express "strong support" for Guaido, whom the U.S. recognizes as the country's rightful president, and condemn President Nicolas Maduro's government and its socialist policies. As the monthslong political crisis continues, Trump is to make a public case to Venezuela's military, which could play a decisive role in the stalemate, to support Guaido's government. The Venezuelan military has largely remained loyal to Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHN OF GOD: Judgment looms for Brazilian spiritual healer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazils-metoo-moment-spiritual-guru-161529186.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABADIANIA, Brazil (AP) — For over 40 years, spiritual healer Joao Teixeira de Faria drew people from all over the world to this small city in central Brazil, offering treatment for everything from depression to cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> HOAX FOR RATINGS BOOST?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/02/18/was-jussie-smolletts-attack-designed-to-boost-empire-ratings-once-hit-show-has-been-in-steady-decline-recently</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone is trying figure out why Jussie Smollett got himself into this mess. Why would a hot young actor in a hit series create a scandal that keeps unraveling and looking worse and worse? Maybe o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN's Stelter Under Fire For Comments on Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/cnns-brian-stelter-knocked-for-claiming-rush-to-judgment-on-smollett-story-was-from-celebrity-press-and-activists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama daughter's secret social media page: 'DONALD TRUMP IS EVIL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6717603/Malia-Obamas-secret-Facebook-account-reveals-anti-Trump-messages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook page operates under a pseudonym and does not appear to have been publicly updated since 2017. Malia graduated high school in 2016 then took a gap year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Slowdown Leaves Growth Weakest Since Financial Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-18/global-economy-stuck-with-downside-risks-in-the-near-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX STANDS BEHIND ACTOR</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/jussie-smollett-empire-fox-assault-1203140605/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;20th Century Fox Television and Fox Entertainment have voiced their support for “Empire” star Jussie Smollett after it was reported the actor and musician staged an attack on himself in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Bans Articles Exposing Hoax...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/censored-facebook-bans-conservative-articles-on-jussie-smollett-hate-hoax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You're not allowed to say that Jussie Smollett carried out a hate hoax."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARPTON:  HE SHOULD PAY PRICE IF STAGED...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/02/18/al-sharpton-hold-jussie-smollett-accountable-if-he-staged-attack/?_ga=2.201146029.267642857.1550199666-2051527208.1550003555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports have emerged that Smollett paid the budding actor-models $3,500 to stage the 2 a.m. attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's first lunar mission to launch...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-first-lunar-mission-launch-week-163307004.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel is to launch its first moon mission this week, sending an unmanned spacecraft to collect data to be shared with NASA, organisers said Monday. The 585-kilogram (1,290-pound) Beresheet (Genesis) spacecraft is to lift off atop a Falcon 9 rocket from Cape Canaveral, Florida at around 0145 GMT on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandal topples wax statue of Sean 'Diddy' Combs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5ee867ac10a4bf7a072af52441b64e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Police say someone attacked a statue of Sean "Diddy" Combs at Madame Tussauds wax museum in New York, shoving the rap impresario's likeness so forcefully it lost its head. Investigators were continuing Monday to look for a suspect in the strange episode Saturday night. Police say a man entered the museum near Times Square around 8:45 p.m., went to the statue and knocked it to the ground. The head fell off as the figure toppled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's Political Rifts Deepen as Lawmakers Quit Party Over Anti-Semitism, Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-k-s-political-rifts-deepen-as-lawmakers-quit-party-over-anti-semitism-brexit-11550492448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven lawmakers left the U.K.’s main opposition Labour Party, the biggest defection from a major British political party in nearly 40 years and the latest evidence that Brexit is accelerating a realignment of the country’s politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Executive Shake-Up Readies It for Life After iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-executive-shake-up-readies-it-for-life-after-iphone-11550503767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is shaking up leadership across its services, artificial intelligence, hardware and retail divisions as it repositions for slowing iPhone sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates spend holiday in New Hampshire, Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-02-18/democratic-candidates-spend-holiday-in-new-hampshire-iowa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 from rescue group plead guilty over cats left in trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.newarkadvocate.com/story/news/local/2019/02/15/humane-agent-pittie-paw-rescue-operators-you-failed-these-cats/2880531002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newarkadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kristin Beaupry and Joyce Meisenholder accepted a plea deal after 23 cats were found abandoned in a trailer behind their Pittie Paws Rescue in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Quietly Gives Advice, but No Endorsement...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/newspolitics/obama-quietly-gives-advice-to-2020-democrats-but-no-endorsement/ar-BBTKSpY?li=AA524b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Ramp Up Pressure on Maduro to Leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/trump-courts-2020-hispanic-vote-in-miami-with-venezuela-remarks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. recognized Guaido and is pushing Venezuelaâ€™s military to get behind him as part of international efforts to force out Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border wall a complex issue for Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ad9366c8b7c648f0a0d4b52fcac52960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas (AP) — When President Donald Trump visited Beto O'Rourke's hometown to argue that walling off the southern border would make the U.S. safer, the former Democratic congressman and possible 2020 presidential hopeful was ready. As the president filled an El Paso arena with supporters, O'Rourke helped lead thousands of his own on a protest march past the barrier of barbed-wire topped fencing and towering metal slats that separates El Paso from Ciudad Juarez, Mexico. O'Rourke clearly hopes to make his personal experience with the border a strength if he runs for president — and the battle over billions of dollars in new fortifications may well shape the 2020 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Killer' cells raise hope of universal flu vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/killer-cells-raise-hope-universal-flu-vaccine-160314396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists said Monday they had discovered immune cells that can fight all known flu viruses in what was hailed as an "extraordinary breakthrough" that could lead to a universal, one-shot vaccine against the killer disease. Researchers in Australia said that "killer T cells" -- found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED:  Chicago police to re-question actor...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/fe9c70e1cc324228838728c6806abae2/police-smollett-reps-no-updates-attack-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Chicago police said Sunday they're still seeking a follow-up interview with Jussie Smollett after receiving new information that "shifted" their investigation of a reported attack on the "Empire" actor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge refuses to block Catholic sex scandal movie...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/f890395fc45b4d10bf1c18251b58df07/french-judge-refuses-block-catholic-sex-scandal-movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A French judge refused Monday to block the release this week in French cinemas of a movie based on a Catholic sex scandal.French director Francois Ozon's film "Grace a Dieu" ("By the Grace of God") won the Berlin Film Festival's jury grand prize on Saturday. The movie, which opens Wednesday, portrays French priest Bernard Preynat, who has been accused of molesting dozens of boys during the 1980s and '90s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PRANKSTER ACTIVISTS' SWARM DC...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/184001cc014446188ea74b92d847748b/dcs-many-prankster-activists-turn-anger-street-theater</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the nation's capital, it can be hard for protesters to stand out. A group of 50 people — or even 500 — holding signs and shouting hardly merits a second glance in this city of protests.That's why Washington activists have to get creative. There's an ethos of performative prankster-style protest wired into the District of Columbia's history, dating back decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Force is strong with lightsaber dueling...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/france-force-strong-lightsaber-dueling-071315334--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's now easier than ever in France to act out ''Star Wars'' fantasies, because its fencing federation has borrowed from a galaxy far, far away and officially recognized lightsaber dueling as a competitive sport, granting the iconic weapon from George Lucas' saga the same status</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summit of European Powers Collapses Amid Holocaust Dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/israeli-summit-of-european-powers-collapses-amid-holocaust-dispute-11550501117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli summit hosting Eastern European governments fell apart after Israel’s top diplomat said Poles “suckled anti-Semitism with their mother’s milk.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Obama Quietly Coaching 2020 Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/18/us/politics/obama-2020-democratic-candidates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama has been counseling Democratic candidates on how to win the White House in 2020. But he has no plans to pick a favorite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Damage Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/kristine-marsh/2019/02/18/smollett-story-unravels-abc-defends-robin-roberts-softball</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC’s Good Morning America team went into full damage control mode Monday, after news broke over the weekend that actor Jussie Smollett had allegedly paid two men to stage his assault. Just last Thursday, anchor Robin Roberts had given the actor a softball interview, even refusing to call his story of a Trump supporter assaulting him, “alleged.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil Rights Activist Says Could Have Started Race War...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/black-civil-rights-activist-says-jussie-smollet-could-have-started-race-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for actor to be arrested for allegedly staging hate crime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box Office: Revenue Hits 8-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-winter-2019-revenue-hits-8-year-low-1187519 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Combined ticket sales were down sharply even before the worst Presidents Day weekend in at least 14 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm donor plans to father 2,500 kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/760332/sperm-donor-wants-to-father-2500-kids-joe-donor-60-minutes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sixth mass extinction; Populations of wild animals fall 50%...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/823904/sixth-mass-extinction-explained</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The populations of the world's wild animals have fallen by more than 50 percent and humanity is to blame. Here's everything you need to know.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
