<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's deadliest day; Virus STILL hasn't peaked...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-capital-goes-lockdown-quell-001139347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor of Brazil's capital city, Brasilia, decreed a 24-hour lockdown for all but essential services on Friday to curb a worsening COVID-19 outbreak that has filled its intensive care wards to the brim. The drastic step came as right-wing President Jair Bolsonaro, who has repeatedly downplayed the gravity of the pandemic that has killed 250,000 Brazilians, renewed his attacks on state governors for destroying jobs with lockdowns. "The lockdown will start today and be total, it will be 24-hours a day," said a press aide for the federal district's Governor Ibaneis Rocha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auckland starts ANOTHER lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210228004752-kwiw2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NEWZEALAND (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-New Zealand's Auckland starts second COVID-19 lockdown this month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president to propose immigrant labor program...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/28/andres-manuel-lopez-obrador-mexico-president-propo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Saturday he will propose a “Bracero” style immigrant labor program to U.S. President Joe Biden during a video call between the two leaders planned for Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the internet changed celebrity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2021/feb/27/where-are-the-next-tom-cruises-how-the-internet-changed-celebrity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In our social media-saturated society, modern fame has become fragmented resulting in a galaxy of stars vying for our attention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGRETS OF JUNK FOOD JUNKIE DURING LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/feb/28/pandemic-junk-food-doctor-cholesterol-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My doctor says my cholesterol levels are insane and I have to eat healthily. My supermarket shop has changed overnight, says Guardian columnist Emma Brockes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER PUMP:  Fed emerges as White House ally in rejecting concerns about overdoing covid bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/once-trump-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98enemy-e2-80-99-fed-emerges-as-white-house-ally-in-rejecting-concerns-about-overdoing-stimulus/ar-BB1e5CDe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, prominent economists, Republican lawmakers and some market analysts raise alarm bells about the risks of overstimulating the economy and triggering unwanted inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE tops list of 'most overpaid' CEOs with package worth $281M...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9307171/Googles-Sundar-Pichai-tops-list-100-overpaid-CEOs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEO pay increased 14 percent in 2019 from the year before, to an average of $21.3 million, according to the '100 Most Overpaid CEOs' study released on Thursday by nonprofit group As You Sow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy company to breed condors to replace birds killed by turbines...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/energy-company-breed-endangered-california-140022000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being rescued from the brink of extinction, endangered California condors now face the threat of being killed by wind turbines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury in Cyprus over 'satanic' Eurovision song choice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eurovision-song-contest-cyprus-12791c8ad6069f777beb945b5aef823e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICOSIA, Cyprus (AP) — A man has been charged with uttering threats and causing a disturbance after barging onto the grounds of Cyprus’ public broadcaster to protest what he said was the country’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Talked To People In Their Dreams. They Answered...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/27/971958260/scientists-talked-to-people-in-their-dreams-they-answered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have found that two-way communication is possible with someone who is asleep and dreaming. Specifically, lucid dreaming — dreaming while being aware you're dreaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA police probe fire, vandalism at Japanese Buddhist temple...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/los-angeles-tokyo-asia-hate-crimes-california-2bca9d89228431c9c3f537d82385f811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Authorities are investigating a vandalism and fire at a Buddhist temple in the Little Tokyo section of downtown Los Angeles. Surveillance video caught a man jumping the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lamborghini' Of Chariots Discovered At Pompeii. Archaeologists Wowed...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/27/972118983/a-lamborghini-of-chariots-is-discovered-at-pompeii-archaeologists-are-wowed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The well-preserved chariot, complete with decorative medallions depicting erotic scenes, is an "extraordinary discovery" that may have been used in wedding ceremonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man begging for food at KFC stabbed by customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/florida/fl-ne-restaurant-fight-stabbing-20210227-hzyegpvw3ngc3llq3tezcfjuzi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Branden Dion Pearson is accused of stabbing a man asking for food at a KFC restaurant in Fort Lauderdale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong police charge dozens of dissidents with security crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210228-hong-kong-police-charge-dozens-of-dissidents-with-security-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police charge dozens of dissidents with security crime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are Mexico's disappeared? Many in govt graves all along...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/where-mexicos-disappeared-many-government-110040696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 80,000 Mexicans have disappeared in the last 15 years. Many are now thought to be in government custody — among the thousands of corpses that pass through morgues each year without ever being identified and end up in common graves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper photographer attacked, seriously hurt in France...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/youth-violence-newspapers-violence-france-europe-da30513dab08ec83561e6512a38b79f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Authorities in France have opened an investigation for attempted murder after a news photographer was attacked and seriously injured while reporting on a suspected outbreak of youth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected fetus dies in womb, in 2nd such case in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/fetus-infected-with-covid-19-dies-in-womb-in-2nd-such-case-in-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;36-week-pregnant woman infected with coronavirus arrived at hospital after feeling ill; Meir Medical Center says it can't link death to virus yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia joins 15 other states in legalizing marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/27/virginia-legalizes-marijuana-471840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia is the 16th U.S. state to pass an adult-use marijuana legalization law, though sales would not start until 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor performs surgery while appearing at video court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sacramento-california-coronavirus-pandemic-324f0dd573e15fe7506846590b472db4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The Medical Board of California said it would investigate a plastic surgeon who appeared in a videoconference for his traffic violation trial while operating. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rooster kills man during cockfight...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/28/rooster-kills-man-during-cockfight-india/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was killed by a rooster with a blade tied to its leg during an illegal cockfight in southern India, police said, bringing focus on a practice that continues in some Indian states despite a decades-old ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom posts TIKTOK inside restaurant -- where indoor dining is banned...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-appears-to-post-tik-tok-inside-restaurant-in-county-where-indoor-dining-is-not-allowed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom appeared indoors at a restaurant in a county where indoor dining is not allowed, but the governor's office has said he did not dine at the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asylum seekers stream across Gateway International Bridge from Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9308485/First-migrants-walk-border-Mexico-Biden-administration-relaxed-asylum-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has restarting processing those with active cases made to wait in Mexico during the Trump administration at three border crossing between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrival of 'sticky bombs' in Kashmir sets off alarm bells...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/arrival-of-sticky-bombs-in-kashmir-sets-off-alarm-bells-101614507407763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Sticky bombs", which can be attached to vehicles and detonated remotely, have been seized during raids in recent months in the federally administered region of Jammu and Kashmir, three senior security officials told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUTHTELLERS: They revealed pandemic in China. And paid heavy price...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2021/02/asia/china-wuhan-covid-truthtellers-intl-hnk-dst/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors and journalists tried to raise the alarm in the early days of the pandemic. A year on, many have been silenced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's deadliest avalanche season in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/28/us/avalanche-death-covid-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has wreaked havoc on the US economy, health care system and schools. Some experts say it's also to blame for a recent spike in avalanche deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia says missile attack on Riyadh thwarted...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/saudi-arabia-says-it-thwarted-yemeni-rebel-missile-attack-over-capital-2380226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple blasts shook Riyadh on Saturday as Saudi state television reported that a missile attack launched by Yemen's Huthi rebels had been thwarted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of FACEBOOK moderators sue social media giant for severe mental trauma after being exposed to violent images at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9308337/Dozens-moderators-sue-Facebook-severe-mental-trauma-exposure-violent-images-work.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of Facebook moderators are suing the social media giant for severe mental trauma after being exposed to violent and sexually disturbing images at work, with some diagnosed with PTSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tells the world 'America is back.' World isn't so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-tells-the-world-America-is-back-The-15985195.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - For President Joe Biden and his circle, a low point in America's global...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hid 'fraud' on inheritance for years, niece tells judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/nation/2021/02/27/trump-niece-mary-inheritance-fraud-lawsuit/115511918/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s niece is balking at the that she waited too long to file her multimillion-dollar fraud suit against him, saying she would have sued sooner if he hadn’t covered his tracks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD cop allegedly confessed to aiding Malcolm X's assassination. His daughter says his letter is fake...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/An-NYPD-cop-allegedly-confessed-to-aiding-Malcolm-15985299.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A letter purporting to contain a New York police officer's deathbed confession about his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran behind blast on Israeli-owned ship?</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/israel-s-gantz-says-iran-could-be-behind-blast-on-israeli-owned-ship-01614457804?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Defence Minister Benny Gantz said on Saturday he believes Iran is behind an explosion earlier this week on an Israeli-owned vessel in the Gulf of Oman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As recall threat grows, Newsom shifts his governing style, pushing reopenings...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/recall-threat-grows-california-gov-130019079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom flatly rejects the suggestion that politics have played a role in his pandemic decisions and has not publicly acknowledged the recall effort even as he shifts to campaign-style events in major media markets across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Pope Francis expects to spend his final days in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-francis-expects-spend-final-210411743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis expects to die in Rome, still the Catholic pontiff, without returning to spend his final days in his native Argentina, according to a new book titled "The Health of Popes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New fears of next corona wave emerge as case declines slow, variants grow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fears-next-coronavirus-wave-case-172553841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are expressing worry that the decline in daily new coronavirus cases nationwide is starting to flatten and warned states against relaxing COVID-19 restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital authentication opens new doors for art, sports collectors...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/digital-authentication-opens-doors-art-015902230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans have been flocking by the thousands to the Top Shot online platform to buy short videos of dramatic sequences from professional basketball games, as a new virtual market enjoys astonishing success among collectors, sports fans and art lovers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba approves animal rights law after activists' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuba-approves-animal-rights-law-014752929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba has adopted long-called for animal rights regulations, a groundbreaking victory for activists in the communist nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district cancels Dr. Seuss for 'racial undertones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/26/loudoun-county-schools-cancel-dr-seuss-racial-unde/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another day, another cancellation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER to test Covid vaccine on 5 year-olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2417145/pfizer-test-covid-vaccine-children-five-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFIZER is to start testing its Covid vaccine on children as young as five. The pharmaceutical company’s boss said it has already finished enrolling volunteers aged 12 to 15 and is now looking…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global defense spending hits new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/global-defense-spending-led-by-us-and-china-hits-new-high-1.663520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and China led the growth in global defense spending, which hit a new high in 2020 despite the economic stress brought on by the coronavirus pandemic, a report said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist behind golden Trump statue at CPAC says he made it in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/artist-says-gold-trump-statue-was-assembled-in-mexico-hits-back-at-golden-calf-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artist who created the already infamous Trump "golden calf" statue says it is not an "idol" but does concede it was made in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I WAS TRYING TO BE MENTOR'</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/27/cuomo-second-aide-sexual-harassment-accusations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times reported Saturday that former aide Charlotte Bennett, 25, says Cuomo harassed her last year while she was working as an executive assistant in his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBANY ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-andrew-cuomo-7fda294d42e92a2762fc7e7b9ee0cd57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A second former aide has come forward with sexual harassment allegations against New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, who responded with a statement Saturday saying he never made advances...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER CUOMO ACCUSER</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2420837/new-york-andrew-cuomo-accused-sex-harassment-second-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOVERNOR Andrew Cuomo has been accused of sexual harassment by another former employee less than a week after he was accused by sexual harassment by a former aide. Charlotte Bennett claimed the New…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga's dogs recovered safely...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/lady-gaga-s-dogs-returned-unharmed-n1259034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two French bulldogs were taken in a violent robbery, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOYCOTT RISK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-diversity-ava-duvernay-sterling-k-brown-judd-apatow-hfpa-no-black-members-timesupglobes-1234702414/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 10:11 PM: Battered again today by some of the biggest names in Hollywood for its stupefying lack of Black members, the Hollywood Foreign Press Association tonight responded by repeating a p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, travel, peace of mind. How life changing for fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/sex-travel-peace-of-mind-how-life-is-changing-for-some-of-the-fully-vaccinated/article_51a1566d-ba27-5a02-9724-14c9155908a5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dating during the pandemic is becoming less complicated and risky for attorney Shelley O'Connor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images reveal extent of damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/27/middleeast/us-syria-iran-airstrikes-analysis-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A resident of al-Bukamal, a city near the Syrian-Iraqi border, told CNN the explosions from US airstrikes targeting a compound the Pentagon said was used by Iranian-backed militia groups were unlike anything he had heard before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Rock' v. The Don: A serious comparison...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/540290-dwayne-the-rock-johnson-v-donald-trump-a-serious-comparison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson has that 'it' factor that Trump had in 2016, and his growing platform makes Trump’s look unsophisticated and outdated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Dog Used by Police Stirs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/digidog-a-robotic-dog-used-by-the-police-stirs-privacy-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were being held hostage in a Bronx apartment. They had been threatened at gunpoint, tied up and tortured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes may show early warnings for Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.iol.co.za/news/world/the-eyes-could-show-early-warnings-for-alzheimers-researchers-say-c0271978-4424-595c-992e-a79adf9bd84a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iol.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say a picture of your eye could assess your future risk of neurodegenerative disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Russia's mass arrests: Claims of beatings, threats and 'war' against rights monitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Inside-Russia-s-mass-arrests-Claims-of-beatings-15984774.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Authorities call it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiers defy death in descent of Yosemite's Half Dome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-eb713b3d3b2de28dd9a82b5ab72798b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK, Calif. (AP) — Two skiers navigated a thin layer of snow with no margin for error down the precipitous shoulder of Half Dome in Yosemite National Park and alternately skied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon wolf makes history on lengthy journey to California...</title>
      <link>https://defenders.org/newsroom/oregon-wolf-or-93-makes-history-traveling-californias-central-sierra-nevada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;defenders.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, a gray wolf from western Oregon dubbed OR-93 became the first collared wolf to explore the central Sierra region of California. According to the California Department of Fish and Wildlife (CDFW), OR-93, a former member of the White River Pack near Mt. Hood, has traveled farther south into the state than any known wild wolf in a century, a historic journey that highlights the importance of habitat connectivity and the dispersal ability of this iconic species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will AI get along with us?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/540821-will-artificial-intel-get-along-with-us-only-if-we-design-it-that-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People would be much more guarded with social media if they realized those platforms are actively profiling them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo wife to rat out cartel?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/27/el-chapos-wife-emma-coronel-aispuro-poised-to-snitch-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emma Coronel Aispuro went back to being a brunette for her mug shot last week. The glamorous beauty-queen wife of Mexico’s most notorious drug trafficker had last appeared in public as a blonde, he…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
