<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to attend 'March for Life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-abortion/breaking-precedent-trump-to-attend-washington-anti-abortion-march-idUSKBN1ZN152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump will become the first U.S. president to attend the annual "Mar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy young man among victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Healthy-young-man-among-new-deaths-reported-of-15000796.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - A young, healthy man from Wuhan and a person living 1,500 miles from the epicenter of the coronavirus are among the latest victims of the outbreak, which has incited fear and anger across China as the important Spring Festival gets underway.  Reports of eight new deaths from the pneumonia-like virus, taking the total to 26, came as authorities enforced a lockdown across large parts of the province of Hubei, population 59 million. But they also came as the medical system clearly struggled to cope with the outbreak, with reports of crowded hospitals, stressed doctors and dwindling supplies.  Adding to the stress, Friday marked the official start of the Spring Festival, when China celebrates the arrival of the new lunar year. Authorities around the country, including in the capital, Beijing, have canceled the temple fairs and festivals that accompany the holiday to avoid having large public gatherings where the airborne virus could spread.  "The public should not gather during the Spring Festival and try stay at home as much as possible to protect themselves," Gao Fu, a member of the expert group of the National Health and Health Commission and director of the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, said Friday.  He encouraged everyone to wear masks, and photos from train stations and airports across the country showed people with their mouths and noses covered.  The Beijing Capital International Airport was unusually empty on Friday, with almost all passengers wearing masks. The Beijing city government and Shanghai local authorities have also urged residents returning to areas affected by the virus, or who have been in contact with suspected cases, to stay at home or in a centralized quarantine area for 14 days to contain the spread.  The state broadcaster, CCTV, led its midday news program with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Taylor Swift doc more wooden than Pinnochio...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/24/miss-americana-review-taylor-swifts-dull-doc-is-a-wasted-opportunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARK CITY, Utah — If you think the moon landing was staged, just wait till you see “Miss Americana,” the new documentary about pop star Taylor Swift. Most of the film, which premiered Thursday nigh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Iraq to demand ouster of US troops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iraqis-apprehensive-ahead-clerics-anti-us-rally-025518437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of supporters of populist Iraqi cleric Moqtada Sadr gathered in Baghdad on Friday for a rally to demand the ouster of US troops, putting the protest-hit capital on edge. The march rattled the separate, months-old protest movement that has gripped the capital and Shiite-majority south since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Simulation Predicts 65 Million Could Die...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/health-experts-issued-ominous-warning-170400102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus in the simulation was a fictional one called CAPS, but it bears some similarities to the Wuhan coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Police Deploy Real-Time Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/24/21079919/facial-recognition-london-cctv-camera-deployment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One nation under CCTV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In lawless stretch of Mexico, child soldiers as young as 6 drafted to fight crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/in-a-lawless-stretch-of-mexico-child-soldiers-as-young/article_34d8de6a-7d1c-5e0d-b959-50e809a5e451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — In a lawless stretch of western Mexico, children as young as 6 years old are taking up arms against organized crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOCTORS COLLAPSE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-doctors-collapse-hospitals-overwhelmed-21348105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shared online appears to show a medic sprawled on the floor after reportedly collapsing amid the outbreak in Wuhan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies after attacked by his rooster on way to cockfight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/22/india/rooster-cockfight-death-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indian man has died after a tussle with his rooster -- on their way to a cockfight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive building explosion rocks Houston; 'Warzone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2020/01/24/large-explosion-causes-buildings-home-to-rattle-in-west-houston-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many people in west Houston reported hearing a loud explosion and feeling building in the area shake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's worst cat' up for adoption at shelter. 'She's just jerk'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article239525208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-house-democrats-to-spotlight-what-they-say-is-trumps-obstruction-of-congress-2020-01-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House prosecutors will wrap up their opening arguments Friday by detailing actions they say he took that led to the second of two articles of impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468451-1/senate-impeachment-trial-day-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate impeachment trial of President Trump continues with opening arguments from House managers. Other legislative work is also possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber Breaks Down at Album Event: Don't Think I Should Be Alive...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/justin-bieber-emotional-cry-album-changes-playback-event-1203477791/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber broke down in tears describing the challenges he’s faced in the last couple of years and the people who helped him get through it. At a playback of his forthcoming album held at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton battle escalates...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/479678-gop-warns-of-drawn-out-executive-privilege-battle-over-bolton-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are using the threat of a protracted executive privilege battle as a cudgel to dissuade their colleagues from calling former national security adviser John Bolton to testify at President Trump’s impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTBREAK OVERWHELMS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7923913/Shanghai-Disney-closed-Saturday-help-prevent-spread-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Disney Resort in Shanghai said it will close from tomorrow, Saturday January 25, for 'the prevention and control of the disease outbreak' as public transport and roads are closed elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKDOWN TOO LATE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/time-im-scared-experts-fear-too-china-virus-103855664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's bid to contain a deadly new virus by placing cities of millions under quarantine is an unprecedented undertaking but it is unlikely to stop the disease spreading, experts warn. The contagious virus has already reached elsewhere in China and abroad, and even an authoritarian government has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOROS:  FACEBOOK Conspiring to Re-Elect Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/george-soros-says-facebook-conspiring-212200364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Billionaire George Soros said that nothing is keeping Facebook Inc. from spreading disinformation and the company may be in cahoots with President Donald Trump to get him re-elected.“I think there is a kind of informal mutual assistance operation or agreement developing between Trump and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Bloomberg: Fortunes collide in pricey knife fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4331d26381eb9d8bca68a2f6b69ff5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — They are circling each other like wary boxers, with taunts on Twitter, snarky asides and belittling descriptions. They rose to prominence in Manhattan on parallel tracks, amassed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems argue 'right matters' in Trump impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f41da5fc455336da11e56bc1ec6bbb09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic House prosecutors made an expansive case Thursday at Donald Trump's impeachment trial that he abused power like no other president in history, swept up by a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO BUILD HOSPITAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/09be6cd295bc66a335e6686da6bbbffb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China is swiftly building a 1,000-bed hospital dedicated to patients infected with a new virus that has killed 26 people, sickened hundreds and prompted unprecedented lockdowns of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why didn't accusers abandon Weinstein? Expert to weigh in...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/04da2daf1278be25230090a5a7cf9841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — It's the defense's go-to question at Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial: If the once-revered Hollywood mogul is a revolting sexual predator, as prosecutors and scores of women allege,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks Causing More Downtime Than Ever Before...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/ransomware-attacks-are-causing-more-downtime-than-ever-before/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average number of days it takes for organisations infected with ransomware to restore networks is now up to over 16 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case near Tokyo spurs alert for US military personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/pacific/coronavirus-case-near-tokyo-spurs-alert-for-us-military-personnel-in-japan-1.615869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force’s 374th Medical Group at Yokota posted an alert to social media that said four cases of the virus have been reported outside of China, including in South Korea and Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa caucus app sparks election security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/iowa-caucus-app-sparks-election-security-concerns-n1121581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every level of the election process has come under scrutiny since the intelligence community determined Russia tried to interfere in the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General says troop surge in Middle East may not end soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2020/01/23/us-central-command-general-says-troop-surge-in-middle-east-may-not-end-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past eight months, the United States has poured more than 20,000 additional troops into the Middle East to counter the escalating threat from Iran that peaked with the recent missile attack on American forces in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma exec sentenced to prison in opioid trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.wgbh.org/news/local-news/2020/01/23/in-opioid-trial-pharmaceutical-executive-john-kapoor-sentenced-to-55-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wgbh.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Kapoor was sentenced to 5.5 years in prison on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL concussions rise despite safety moves...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nfl-concussions-rose-10-2019-despite-safety-moves-202034996--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players suffered 224 diagnosed concussions in the 2019 regular season and pre-season combined, 10 more than in 2018 but still off alarming 2017 totals, the league announced Thursday. The data showed a rise from the 214 concussions in the 2018 season but remained well off the 281 over the same period</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ says Carter Page spy warrants 'not valid'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/23/doj-carter-page-fisa-not-valid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department recently conceded that two of the four orders to wiretap former Trump campaign adviser Carter Page were &amp;quot;not valid.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros rips, says 'fate of world' at stake in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/23/davos-2020-george-soros-says-china-leader-xi-is-trying-to-exploit-trumps-weaknesses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal billionaire George Soros slammed Trump and China on Thursday at his annual dinner on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic 'forever chemicals' found in drinking water throughout US...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/01/23/pfas-toxic-forever-chemicals-found-drinking-water-throughout-us/4540909002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report found that 20 cities and regions nationwide — including Washington, D.C., Philadelphia, Miami and Louisville — contained high PFAS levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney becomes top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/23/mick-mulvaney-trump-impeachment-102758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats say the acting White House chief of staff is the most important potential witness in Trump's trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Connection: Inside 9/11 Case That Divided the FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-saudi-connection-inside-the-9-11-case-that-divided-the-fbi/ar-BBZfp1C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN cancels Dem presidential town halls because of impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/23/politics/cnn-cancels-iowa-2020-town-halls/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has canceled the Democratic presidential town halls scheduled to take place next week ahead of the Iowa caucuses because of the ongoing impeachment trial, a CNN spokesperson said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators Play With Toys, Read Books...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/23/gop-senators-kids-toys-fidget-spinners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, Republican senators are passing the time during the impeachment trial with fidget spinners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Biden's rivals can't break his lock on black voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/23/joe-biden-black-voters-support-south-carolina-102365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His opponents have tried for a year to chip away at his African American support in South Carolina. But nothing's working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state medics monitor 16 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7919851/Washington-coronavirus-patient-contact-16-people-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington state heath officials have predicted that the number of Americans infected would likely grow as the coronavirus continues its spread at a faster rate than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue NYPD cops using sketchy facial-recognition app...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/rogue-nypd-cops-are-using-sketchy-facial-recognition-app-clearview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rogue NYPD officers are using a sketchy facial-recognition software that it’s own facial recognition unit doesn’t want to touch because of concerns about security and potential for abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'war zone' city...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/inside-wuhans-quarantine-zone-amid-viral-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soldiers wearing face masks screened people Thursday for the coronavirus in Wuhan, China — where doctors wore hazmat suits to treat patients sickened by the mystery illness, photos from insid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamic leaders make 'groundbreaking' visit to Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2aee1fb2ac13e4ed26a41e0096bac46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Muslim religious leaders joined members of a U.S. Jewish group at Auschwitz on Thursday for what organizers described as “the most senior Islamic leadership delegation" to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bernie 12-point lead in NH...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbur.org/news/2020/01/23/new-hampshire-bernie-sanders-lead-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbur.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden, Buttigieg and Warren are clumped in a close battle behind the Vermont senator, with less than three weeks until the New Hampshire primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM LEHRER DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/press-releases/from-judy-woodruff-longtime-pbs-newshour-anchor-and-co-founder-jim-lehrer-has-passed-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, DC (January 23, 2020) -- It is with great sadness that I share the news that co-founder and longtime anchor of the PBS NewsHour Jim Lehrer died today, Thursday, January 23, 2020, peacefully in his sleep at home. Lehrer, born May 19, 1934, served as anchor of the NewsHour for 36 years before retiring in 2011. Lehrer and Robert MacNeil founded the program in 1975, out of their 1973 coverage of the Senate Watergate Hearings on PBS. "I'm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING CANCELS NEW YEAR EVENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hongkongfp.com/2020/01/23/wuhan-virus-hong-kong-holiday-camps-become-quarantine-zones-lunar-new-year-festival-cancelled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hongkongfp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;by Jerome Taylor &amp; Xinqi Su Hong Kong has turned two holiday camps, including a former military barracks, into quarantine zones for people who may have come into contact with carriers of the Wuhan virus, officials announced Thursday. The international financial hub has been on high alert for the virus, which has killed 17 people since …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's reelection looks more like long shot than slam dunk?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/479078-trumps-reelection-looks-more-like-a-long-shot-than-a-slam-dunk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's approval rating is dismal, and partisans are highly engaged and unlikely to stray from their respective party nominees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani claims he has goods on Biden, threatens to go public...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/rudy-giuliani-threatens-to-go-public-with-biden-corruption-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, the personal attorney for President Trump, threatened Thursday to go public with information that would expose corruption by 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden. “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK  after 3 seconds!</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/how-will-we-know-whos-winning-streaming-war-if-every-service-counts-views-differently/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As viewers shift from traditional TV to streaming, services like Netflix have less incentive to share a common metric for sharing what counts as a "view"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Groupthink, Self-Censorship Making Journalism Lifeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/01/packer-hitchens/605365/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A writer who’s afraid to tell people what they don’t want to hear has chosen the wrong trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Egyptian mummy 'brought back to life' by scientists who recreated voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/ancient-egyptian-mummy-brought-back-21342577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Egyptian priest, known as Nesyamun, hasn't spoken in more than 3,000 years, but now his voice has been synthesised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ education now mandatory in New Jersey schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/education/nj-lgbtq-education-curriculum-lesson-plans-mandate-20200120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators in a dozen N.J. public school districts, including Haddon Heights, are testing a pilot curriculum to include instruction about the contributions of lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and disabled people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Prosecutors Paint Picture of Serial Predator... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/annabella-sciorra-testifies-harvey-weinstein-raped-her-1272310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Sopranos' actress is one of four primary witnesses testifying for the prosecution about Weinstein's conduct toward them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother caught with 200 pounds of meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/grandmother-caught-with-200-pounds-of-meth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 65-year-old grandmother is accused of trying to sneak more than 200 pounds of methamphetamine into the U.S. at a border crossing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected people seen dead in streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/infected-people-seen-dead-streets-21345585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Disturbing images on Instagram from inside Wuhan show residents dropping to the floor following a lockdown of the city by Chinese authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds:  Man stole $10 million from investor to bankroll Vegas gambling, lavish lifestyle...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/criminal-justice/ct-chicago-sports-gambler-fraud-charges-20200122-uruvy3ao4jf7xeeumtrg4jp4su-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Gorodetsky, who made a name for himself as a maverick in the Las Vegas sports betting scene with a seemingly bottomless bankroll and the guts to lay it all on the line, was charged Tuesday in federal court in Chicago with a massive fraud scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant parents deported without their children make historic return to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/migrant-parents-deported-without-their-children-make-historic-return-to-the-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the U.S. separated thousands of migrant families in 2018, it deported hundreds of parents without their children. Nine of them were allowed to return to U.S. to see their children once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 40% of Americans don't have $1,000 for an emergency!</title>
      <link>https://www.bankrate.com/banking/savings/financial-security-january-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bankrate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When in a pinch, those who lack emergency savings turn to other methods to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touches highest levels of American power...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jeff-bezos-phone-back-mbs-saudi-arabia-amazon-d9f15cf8-6f1b-4a6e-974b-3b37a0b10181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He owns one of the country's biggest companies and most influential news outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOPRANOS' Actress Stuns Courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-annabella-sciorra-rape-trial-1202838739/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annabella Sciorra recounted to a jury how Harvey Weinstein burst into her apartment sometime in the winter of 1993-94, pinned her on a bed and raped her, leaving her so traumatized that she began t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems face risks and limits in impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5dbd0f2716438d40395b36f054f7d55d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The challenge is becoming increasingly clear for House Democrats prosecuting President Donald Trump's impeachment case as the Senate convenes for a second day of arguments in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami PD suspends white officer who begins identifying as 'black'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/miami-pd-suspends-white-officer-who-begins-identifying-as-black-male/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A controversial Miami cop was suspended with pay after he argued at a Miami City Commission meeting last week that he identifies as a black male, despite his Caucasian complexion. #BREAKING: @MiamiPD Capt. @OrtizFOP tells city commission “I am a black male” after he was caught lying about his race on 2014 lieutenant’s exam and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot the Robot Dog Trots Into the Big, Bad World...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/spot-the-robot-dog-trots-into-the-big-bad-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Dynamics' creation is starting to sniff out its role in the workforce: as a helpful canine that still sometimes needs you to hold its paw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Goes Off After FOX AND FRIENDS Airs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-goes-off-on-mini-mike-bloomberg-after-fox-and-friends-airs-attack-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump fired back at Democratic candidate Michael Bloomberg in response to his new campaign ad -- airing on Fox &amp; Friends -- slamming the president's behavior as "erratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to move, Californians tour top destination: Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-01-22/californians-looking-to-leave-tour-their-destination-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of California voters have considered moving out of state. Many who do choose Texas, where lower housing costs come with trade-offs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NETFLIX New Ratings Math Sacrifices Clarity for Flashy Numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/netflixs-new-ratings-math-sacrifices-clarity-flashy-numbers-1272214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer's change to the way it measures viewers means it's harder to tell how many people actually watch a show as opposed to just sampling it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS SCARE LAX</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/lax-passenger-quarantined-after-showing-potential-coronavirus-symptoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger arriving on an American Airlines flight to Los Angeles International Airport from Mexico City was hospitalized and quarantined after showing what health officials called “disturbing" symptoms, that indicate the patient may have been exposed to the deadly coronavirus,  it was announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA student jailed in China over tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-arrests-university-minnesota-twitter-e495cf47-d895-4014-9ac8-8dc76aa6004d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student had posted images of a cartoon villain resembling Xi Jinping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg ad blasts Trump treatment of military leaders...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479529-nationwide-bloomberg-ad-blasts-trumps-treatment-of-military-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg released a new nationwide television advertisement for his presidential campaign on Thursday, blasting President Trump over his reported treatment of military leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TAUNTS TRUMP ON TWITTER: 'OBSESSED MUCH?'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/23/mike-bloomberg-trump-obsessed-much/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg taunted President Donald Trump in a tweet Thursday, accusing him of being &amp;quot;obsessed&amp;quot; with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein trial turns to accusers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/83025aa11d457221eaa7a260faeab504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A ctress Annabella Sciorra confronted Harvey Weinstein in court Thursday after keeping her rape accusation against the former Hollywood honcho largely hidden for decades....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
TARANTINO: I am in combat with blockbuster franchises...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/jan/23/quentin-tarantino-blockbusters-originals-star-wars-franchises-superhero-movie-martin-scorsese-marvel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino says ‘original movies’ are in a ‘war’ with superhero and Star Wars franchises, echoing Martin Scorsese’s attack on Marvel films</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with 'identical human appearance' unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-identical-human-appearance-21343768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RealDoll's flagship Harmony sex robot was paraded at the AVN Adult Entertainment Expo at Las Vegas' Hard Rock Hotel and Casino. It is capable of holding conversations with people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Epstein 'madam' emails hacked; Powerful friends exposed?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/23/ghislaine-maxwells-private-emails-reportedly-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell’s private emails have been hacked — and she may have been targeted in a search for damning information on her powerful network of pals, according to new court papers. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Vesuvius blast turned ancient victim's brain to glass...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8ffb49731526ee1b1741798ff0e9a7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The eruption of Mount Vesuvius turned an incinerated victim's brain material into glass, the first time scientists have verified the phenomenon from a volcanic blast, officials at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan crosses into Mexico without resistance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ccbbe21522c8771ca00afec50a9015f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Hundreds of Central American migrants crossed the river into Mexico from Guatemala Thursday after a dayslong standoff with security forces. Carrying U.S. and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Dogs found eating body of owner who hadn't been heard from for days...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/5872579/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said it's very likely the man died of natural causes and the dogs were starving after not having been fed for a while.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
