<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brazil outbreak worse than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/much-of-the-world-is-seeing-coronavirus-cases-fall-but-brazil-e2-80-99s-outbreak-is-worse-than-ever/ar-BB1e7Oj1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are at capacity, a virus variant is rampaging and vaccines are slow to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Manufacturers hobbled by shortage of tiny silicon chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-U-S-manufacturers-were-hobbled-by-a-shortage-15988468.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Semiconductor executive Tom Caulfield knew a crisis was brewing when he started getting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL CARIBBEAN 'FULLY VACCINATED' CRUISES</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2021/03/01/royal-caribbean-offer-fully-vaccinated-sailing-new-cruise-ship/6871142002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean's new ship, Odyssey of the Seas is set to debut with departures from Israel with all passengers and crew over 16 vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney left with black eye and stitches after fall knocks him unconscious!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2431704/mitt-romney-black-eye-stitches-fall-jokes-cpac/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REPUBLICAN Senator Mitt Romney with a black eye on Monday revealed he had fallen over the weekend but joked it was from attending the Conservative Political Action Conference. The senator from Utah…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden works to unify Senate Dems on $1.9 trillion bailout bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Biden-administration-Senate-Democrats-retreat-on-15989837.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden launched a lobbying effort targeting fellow Democrats on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS BEST DAY SINCE JUNE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-financial-markets-global-trade-coronavirus-pandemic-asia-9606d330cbfbfec05987a0069d9e317f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street kicked off March with a broad rally Monday that sent the Dow Jones Industrial Average more than 600 points higher and gave the S&amp;P 500 its best day in nine months. The S&amp;P 500...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems grappling with response...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-new-york-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-53449773e6510c0b8218c818535fa0d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democrats across the country celebrated New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo as the face of governing competence as President Donald Trump fumbled his administration's response to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3:  Cuomo Accused of Unwanted Advance at Wedding...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2431819/cuomo-accused-sexual-harassment-three-women-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York Gov Andrew Cuomo has been accused of unwanted touching, and asking a young woman if he could kiss her at a 2019 wedding. The story, which 33-year-old Anna Ruch shared on Monday, follows al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jab may be less effective if you're fat...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2427587/pfizers-covid-vaccine-may-less-effective-fat-study-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFIZER’S Covid vaccine may be less effective if you’re fat, a study has warned. Italian researchers said obese people make half as many antibodies – proteins that attack the virus. 🦠 Read our…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CAN I KISS YOU?'</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/01/nyregion/cuomo-harassment-anna-ruch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The young woman’s account follows two separate accusations that Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed two female state employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CASES FALL BELOW 50,000</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Evbv63nUcAMnMCb?format=png&amp;name=large</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight Truns to Possible Successor...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/01/new-york-lieutenant-governor-kathy-hochul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy swirling around Gov. Andrew Cuomo even has some Democrats calling for his resignation. That puts a spotlight on the woman who would succeed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATES EASE VIRUS RESTRICTIONS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kansas-city-michael-brown-kansas-coronavirus-pandemic-massachusetts-3599a9631d08de3945f5c95f000e5611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — With the U.S. vaccination drive picking up speed and a third formula on the way, states eager to reopen for business are easing coronavirus restrictions despite warnings from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill on high alert as QAnon claims Trump will be president on March 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2429769/capitol-qanon-march-4-donald-trump-joe-biden-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Capitol will remain on high-alert until mid-March amid a bizarre theory that Donald Trump will become president this week. Thousands of National Guard troops will remain in Washington over f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEGOOGLE lobbyists swarm AZ over bill that would reform app store...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/Policy/apple-google-lobbyists-arizona-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HB2005 would allow app developers to use third-party payment systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Investigating Donald Focus on His Finance Chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutors-investigating-trump-focus-on-his-finance-chief/ar-BB1e7Zu6?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State prosecutors in Manhattan who are investigating former President Donald J. Trump and his family business are sharpening their focus on the company’s long-serving chief financial officer, asking witnesses questions about his dealings at the company, according to people with knowledge of the matter. The increased focus on the executive, Allen H. Weisselberg, could step up pressure on him to cooperate with the investigation if the prosecutors...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic locust plague turns the sky black as swarms ravage Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-locust-plague-turns-sky-23588314</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of locusts flies through Saudi Arabia as stunned people stare and watch and record on their phones. The desert locust has been active since 2020 following a period of wet weather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY attorney general sounds alarm on cryptocurrency industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/01/new-york-attorney-general-warns-cryptocurrency-industry-play-by-the-rules-or-we-will-shut-you-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire State's attorney general warned individual investors and crypto industry players of the perils of digital assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churchill Painting Sells For Record $12 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/carlieporterfield/2021/03/01/angelina-jolies-winston-churchill-painting-sells-for-a-record-12-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the most expensive painting by the prime minister to sell at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA 'unprepared' to defend against new AI threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/541094-us-unprepared-to-defend-against-new-artificial-intelligence-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government is "unprepared" to defend the nation against new threats posed by the increased adoption of artificial intelligence technologies, according to a report released Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas top utility regulator quits in fallout over blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/storms-utilities-greg-abbott-weather-texas-38d0d0ae95ffaf44e41cf6bc17b3169a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas' top utilities regulator resigned Monday in the widening fallout from blackouts triggered by an unusually heavy and widespread winter storm that left millions in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent evangelical adoption agency to work with LGBTQ parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lgbtq-parents-bethany-christian-services-495c1b53-406c-438f-8455-3a7d28ff88b9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We’re taking an 'all hands on deck' approach where all are welcome," the agency's president and chief executive wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs send 30,000 police, soldiers to enforce travel limits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-czech-republic-andrej-babis-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-de9bba833dd336e2c1d4747842e8482e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRAGUE (AP) — Police and military forces in the Czech Republic set up 500 checkpoints across the country as one of the European Union's hardest-hit nations marked the first anniversary of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO HIRES HARVEY WEINSTEIN'S LAWYER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-hires-elkan-abramowitz-to-defend-executive-chamber-in-federal-nursing-home-probe/ar-BB1e7PRO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Elkan Abramowitz confirmed to the Daily News he and his firm are representing Gov. Cuomo and his top officials in relation to the the nursing home inquiry, but have “not been retained on the sexual harassment matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  7-hour line at HEATHROW...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-56209431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travellers complain of having to queue for up to seven hours because of new Covid measures at border control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG to launch 'harass' probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/ag-gets-cuomo-harass-probe-admin-lawyers-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Attorney General Letitia James on Monday received a formal green-light to launch an independent investigation into sexual harassment allegations lodged against Gov. Andrew Cuomo — as the admi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Secretly Got Dosed at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9313945/Donald-Melania-Trump-got-COVID-vaccine-leaving-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald and Melania Trump got the COVID vaccine in January before they left the White House, a Trump adviser told DailyMail.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most transgender murder cases remain unsolved...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/most-transgender-murder-cases-remain-unsolved-as-police-struggle-to-connect-in-lgbtq-2b-communities/ar-BB1e7wR2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — In the nearly eight months since a transgender woman was shot dead in the middle of a crowded South Florida street, Bree Black’s case has all but gone cold. No one has come forward with any leads, police say. It’s a phenomenon that experts and advocates who study violence against transgender people know all too well. They say the problem stems from the lack of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Tech 'Dine And Dash' Forces Popular LA Restaurant To Close...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/02/27/high-tech-dine-and-dash-forces-popular-korean-fusion-cafe-to-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though many restaurants remain closed during the pandemic, dining and dashing still remains a problem, and even forced one restaurant owner to close up shop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings Crash To New Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/golden-globes-ratings-fall-nbc-hfpa-tina-fey-amy-poehler-1234704025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winners notwithstanding, the obvious shortcomings of the 78th annual Golden Globes on-screen last night were reflected in the ratings for the NBC broadcast ceremony today. Though the Comcast-owned …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Sued for Alleged Racial Discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-01/amazon-is-sued-for-alleged-racial-and-gender-discrimination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. was hit with a federal lawsuit for allegedly discriminating against Black and female workers in hiring employees for its corporate offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poly throuple makes history: 3 dads on birth certificate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/poly-throuple-makes-history-3-dads-on-a-birth-certificate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family spent more than $120,000 on legal fees, contracts, implantations and tests to have daughter Piper, now 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Watt's Move to Arizona Shakes Up NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/30985209/jj-watt-announces-signing-arizona-cardinals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star defensive end J.J. Watt has agreed to a two-year contract with the Cardinals after being released by the Texans last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another victim: Sex between married couples...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-another-victim-of-covid-19-sex-between-married-couples/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The forced domesticity of lockdown may not be conducive to intimacy, but relationship experts advise partners to set aside some time to connect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Job Interview May Be With a Robot...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/03/artificial-intelligence-job-interview-problems-bias-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major companies such as Hilton and Unilever have used AI interview software, and an estimated 83 percent of US companies use some form of AI in their HR processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most transgender murder cases remain unsolved...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/most-transgender-murder-cases-remain-unsolved-as-police-struggle-to-connect-in-lgbtq-2b-communities/ar-BB1e7wR2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — In the nearly eight months since a transgender woman was shot dead in the middle of a crowded South Florida street, Bree Black’s case has all but gone cold. No one has come forward with any leads, police say. It’s a phenomenon that experts and advocates who study violence against transgender people know all too well. They say the problem stems from the lack of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer drowns trying to retrieve ball from pond...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/golfer-may-have-drowned-searching-for-ball-in-pond-deputies-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hermilo Jazmines, 74, died on Sunday after deputies found him in a pond at the East Lake Woodlands Country Club, according to the Pinellas County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RISE MOST IN MONTHS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/28/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Market breadth was strong on Monday with only about 8 stocks trading lower in the whole S&amp;P 500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities are starting to ban new gas stations...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cities-ban-gas-pollution-fb61cf2f-9893-466f-9559-9c4d27bbc3b6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movement to outlaw new gas stations is spreading in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS SET TO AIR PRIMETIME SPECIAL...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/royals/meghan-markle-prince-harry-oprah-winfrey-first-teaser-of-sit-down-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Were you silent or were you silenced?" Oprah Winfrey asks the Duchess of Sussex during Oprah with Meghan and Harry: A CBS Primetime Special, airing on March 7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU vaccine passports for summer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-eu-von-der-leyen-idUSKCN2AT2DN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Commission will propose this month an EU-wide digital certificate providing proof of a COVID-19 vaccination that could allow Europeans to travel more freely over the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/nyc-mayor-attacks-longtime-nemesis-cuomo-over-harassment-claims/ar-BB1e7rCu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio railed against Governor Andrew Cuomo over the second sexual-harassment allegation that emerged over the weekend and said the governor’s behavior can no longer be “swept under the rug.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop shot and killed trying to enforce mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/louisiana-police-officer-fatally-shot-over-alleged-mask-dispute-at-high-school-basketball-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana police officer working security at a high school basketball game was shot and killed following a mask-related dispute, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK searches for person infected with Brazil mutation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/01/uk-search-mystery-person-infected-with-brazil-covid-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. health officials are anxious to trace one of six individuals infected with a more contagious variant of the coronavirus, initially identified in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRED NYT REPORTER:  JOURNALISTS ARE JACKALS!</title>
      <link>https://donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com/nytimes-peru-n-word-part-one-introduction-57eb6a3e0d95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On February 5 this year, one week after an article about me appeared in the Daily Beast, The New York Times announced that I would be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: THE GOLDEN GLOBES DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globe-awards-show-review-2021-disastor-hfpa-inclusion-timesupglobes-tina-fey-amy-poehler-jan-fonda-dan-levy-1234703184/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 78th annual Golden Globes had a unique opportunity to right some wrongs and take Hollywood’s awards season into a new realm coming out of the coronavirus pandemic. Unless disaster was the inten…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted NYT Reporter Speaks Out: 'I've Been a Jackal Circled by Jackals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mcneil-new-york-times-medium-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first of a series of four Medium posts explaining his ouster, McNeil reflected on his decision to self-publish his defense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Mystery bright lights appear in sky 'falling' in different directions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/brit-stunned-mystery-bright-lights-23585976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aiden Macartain said he saw the lights in the early hours on Saturday and suspected they were aircraft display. His video showed the lights came hurtling down towards Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports record number of variant coronavirus cases...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/540982-us-reports-record-number-of-variant-coronavirus-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. on Sunday reported an all-time high of 306 cases of coronavirus variants, with the majority concentrated in Florida, Michigan and Texas,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How internet platform accountability is changing under Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/debate-over-holding-internet-platforms-130005261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Section 230 has been a 'brick wall' for anyone seeking to sue internet companies over user-generated content, but bills and legal strategies under consideration could represent an opportunity to change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAB Hacked; Group Promises 'Gold Mine' Of Info On 'Militias, Neo-Nazis, QANON'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/gab-hack-data-breach-ddosecrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transparency group DDoSecrets says it will make the 70 GB of passwords, private posts, and more available to researchers, journalists, and social scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hosting Turned Into Massive HYATT Public Relations Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2021/03/01/how-hosting-cpac-turned-into-a-massive-hyatt-public-relations-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not every day that a major hotel chain is compelled to disavow any association with Nazism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK meteor: Fragments of fireball hit Earth at 30,000mph?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1404082/uk-meteor-fireball-video-space-meteorite-ukfall-astronomy-evg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FIREBALL which boomed over Britain last night may have made landfall, according to researchers who believe segments of the incoming space rock may have dropped around southwest England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first space HOTEL to begin construction in 2025...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9311791/Worlds-space-HOTEL-begin-construction-low-Earth-orbit-2025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developed by the Orbital Assembly Corporation (OAC), the Voyager Station could be operational as early as 2027, with the infrastructure built in orbit around the Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley teacher union president drops daughter off at private school after calling in-person learning 'unsafe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kqed.org/news/11862469/after-leading-school-closures-berkeley-teachers-union-president-spotted-dropping-daughter-off-at-in-person-preschool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kqed.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents shoot video of Matt Meyer, president of the Berkeley Federation of Teachers, dropping his 2-year-old off for in-person instruction even as he fights against in-person instruction for Berkeley public school teachers until they are all vaccinated, which the parents' groups view as hypocrisy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gut May Determine How Long You'll Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gut-microbiome-key-to-long-healthy-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patterns in a person’s microbiome -- the organisms living in the gut -- could determine whether a person is going to age well or die early, say scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubble risk: Reckoning in markets as economy recovers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/01/bidens-market-bubbles-economic-risk-471835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I mean, Shaq has a SPAC. What could go wrong?” one economist says of the euphoria rippling through Wall Street and raising a new round of worries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Chapo: Inside look at hunt for El Mencho, Mexico's bloodiest drug lord...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/new-chapo-inside-look-hunt-el-mencho-mexico-s-bloodiest-n1113761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DEA is targeting a cartel kingpin the agency says is responsible for tons of meth flowing into the U.S. each month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-Year-Old Girl Dies After Caned During Ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/girl-dies-exorcism-sri-lanka/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two suspects - the woman performing the exorcism and the girl's mother - were arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EAT THE WHOLE SAUSAGE'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/cuomo-accused-of-pressuring-reporter-to-eat-whole-sausage-in-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video showing Gov. Andrew Cuomo challenging a female journalist to “eat the whole sausage” in front of him at the 2016 New York State Fair has resurfaced on social media — amid …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Sarkozy convicted of corruption, sentenced to jail... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-trials-nicolas-sarkozy-france-jacques-chirac-6ee89cb03ba8f3888ac64447ebf61f28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A Paris court on Monday found French former President Nicolas Sarkozy guilty of corruption and influence peddling and sentenced him to one year in prison and a two-year suspended...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forensic experts suggest Tiger Woods may have fallen asleep at wheel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/tiger-woods-may-have-fallen-asleep-at-wheel-experts-suggest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods appeared to not be paying attention in the moments before his devastating crash – and may have fallen asleep at the wheel of the luxury SUV he was driving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tortured by al Qaeda, He Saw Same Craziness in Capitol Rioters...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tortured-al-qaeda-saw-same-100825377.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Cole/APAfter they locked his body into a truck tire. After they cuffed his hands behind his back, then flipped him over so his weight rested on his knees and forehead. After they poured water over him, then beat his feet and hands with steel cables. That’s when Theo Padnos confessed to helping the CIA kill Islamic terrorist Anwar al-Awlaki, to being gay, to helping the CIA get the goods on al Qaeda in Syria, and to his desire to rape Syrian women.None of this was true.“The ideal torturer in an Islamic state is someone who takes himself out of the act entirely,” says Padnos, whose new book, Blindfold: A Memoir of Capture, Torture and Enlightenment, tells of the nearly two years he was held as a prisoner by al Qaeda in Syria. “[The torturer] does his bit without emotion. The vast majority of them thought of torture as work they had to do to purify Syria of bad elements that had crept into the nation during the time of the Assads.”Padnos, a writer who spoke Arabic, went to Syria in late 2012 with the aim of rambling along the Syrian-Turkish frontier and reporting about how the uprising against the Assad regime was affecting the average citizen. He had been to Syria in the past, had even studied at an Islamic religious school in Damascus. But the Syria he had known no longer existed, and in the book he is the first to admit that his under-estimation of the situation in 2012, and his lack of a press pass—he had no assignment—was what got him into trouble.Detainees Describe an American Presence in Their Torture Chambers“I thought I knew Syria so well that I could get along with everybody,” says Padnos. “But obviously, the whole country was in the process of a radical psychological transformation. Something had happened in the countryside that had changed the whole complexion of the society.”Padnos decided to sneak into Syria from Antakya, Turkey, with a group of men he thought were smugglers. But those companions kidnapped him, and eventually he was turned over to Jebhat al-Nusra, the Syrian al Qaeda franchise. Thrown into a cell in the basement of the Aleppo eye hospital, Padnos began an odyssey that saw him transferred to the basement of a villa, then a grocery store, a warehouse basement, a basement of Aleppo’s motor vehicles department, a janitor’s closet, a cell in a farmhouse, and towards the end of his captivity, a plush villa where he was given some small freedoms and was essentially under house arrest. Throughout all this he was tortured on a regular basis and referred to by his captors with such charming names as Pig, Donkey, Insect, and Filth.“There’s a psychological sense of terror and despair” about situations like this, says Padnos. “You don’t know how long it will go on, and where it’s going. They can drag it out for months.” But, he adds in the book, “once you know the rules, life in our society, even in its worst places, in which, I’m pretty sure, I lived, was bearable.”Padnos says his kidnappers told him they hated the West because of its arrogance, its preoccupation with sex, and its alleged submission to the Jews. Some wanted to establish an age-old Islamic dream, where Muslims would live in harmony with the land and themselves, invincible before Islam’s enemies, and at one with the Koran. Padnos admits that some of their grievances made sense, that “they feel oppressed in their own countries. A major grievance is that Islam as a religion is not the power it once was, it does not provide justice as it once did.”In this respect, the longing for a purer, more just Islamic society mirrors in some ways the anger of the mob that stormed the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6. “The major comparison is the radicalization of normal people,” says Padnos. “What happened in Syria is that huge swaths of the population became radicalized. Most of these MAGA guys, they believe they are on a spiritual quest to make America great. They have surrendered themselves to some authority they really don’t understand. Here it’s Donald Trump, over there it’s ISIS. It’s the crowd element that is frightening.”During his time in captivity, Padnos became used to what he calls “welcoming parties”—the beatings he received when entering a new prison—and began to think of his constant attempts to rid himself of lice as a “leisure activity.” He came to realize that his guards were often bored, and to relieve their boredom, they abused him. He also had an extremely contentious relationship with one fellow cellmate, Matt Schrier, a photojournalist who converted to Islam while in prison.“Matt hated me because I had refused to convert, because I felt I was more than willing to find the good in an al Qaeda suicide bomber than I was to spend a moment in conversation with him, and because I knew the secret of his bad faith. (Schrier has admitted his conversion to Islam improved relations with his kidnappers).”Padnos was finally released in August 2014, thanks to a ransom paid by the Qatari government which, he says, “probably started the problem; they sent in a lot of weapons to Syria that wound up in the hands of the radicals. They had this idea of sponsoring a revolution in Syria [but] they armed the people who tortured me.” Padnos was forced to rely on Qatari largesse because the United States has a policy of not negotiating with terrorists, something the former prisoner gets angry about when the subject is brought up.“I negotiated with terrorists every day,” he says. “I had no moral qualms about talking to anybody if it was about saving the life of an American citizen. The U.S. will talk to them, but they will not make any concessions to terrorists.”You can understand why Padnos feels that way—any hostage probably feels the same—and still disagree with him. But there are more important, and more sobering, lessons that Padnos wants readers to take away from Blindfold: “I want readers to see that a strange psychological phenomenon has taken over vast swaths of the landscape. They called it a caliphate, I call it mass craziness. It’s The Handmaid’s Tale, a nightmare society where women are sex slaves and people are tortured in the public square.”Still, Padnos made it back home to Vermont safely, and says that if nothing else, the experience made him understand “how fragile life is. I got a second chance to live, and I will not take such cavalier risks in my life again. I came through this happier than I was before, eager to live life.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risky trip to Iraq defies skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210301055735-rd1cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-IRAQ/ (PIX):Pope's risky trip to Iraq defies sceptics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, Russia warships dock in strategic Sudan port...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210301-us-russia-warships-dock-in-strategic-sudan-port</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US, Russia warships dock in strategic Sudan port</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Round-the-World Cruises Selling Out More Than Year in Advance...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/world-cruises-are-selling-out-years-in-advance-as-covid-fears-lift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Round-the-World Cruises Are Selling Out More Than a Year in Advance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Please get in touch': UK searches for mystery spreader of variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210301102740-8xcu7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN (PIX, TV):'Please get in touch': UK searches for mystery spreader of Brazil variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Sarkozy awaits verdict in corruption trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210301083803-l5sor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-POLITICS/SARKOZY-VERDICT (PIX):France's Sarkozy awaits verdict in corruption trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to speed up move to more survivable nuclear force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-politics-china-russia-united-states-f711665a7ebb3a58d6c5bb7ce899ff1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — China appears to be moving faster toward a capability to launch its newer nuclear missiles from underground silos, possibly to improve its ability to respond promptly to a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 10-second video clip sold for $6.6 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-retail-trading-nfts-insight-idUKKCN2AT1HG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In October 2020, Miami-based art collector Pablo Rodriguez-Fraile spent almost $67,000 on a 10-second video artwork that he could have watched for free online. Last week, he sold it for $6.6 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu vows payback against 'greatest enemy' Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9311537/Benjamin-Netanyahu-vows-payback-against-greatest-enemy-Iran.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli PM said the blast on the MV Helios Ray which left two holes in the vessel's side in the Gulf of Oman last week was 'indeed an Iranian act, that is clear'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Awards Ever Completely Botched Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worst-golden-globes-ever-completely-061911669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getty ImagesIt’s not news that the Golden Globes, as an awards show, are a bit of a joke. But, my, has that joke gone stale.The joke resurfaces every few years, sometimes from the ceremony’s stage itself. In 2016, host Ricky Gervais dinged them as “worthless,” likening the honor to “a bit of metal that some nice old confused journalists wanted to give you in person so they could meet you and have a selfie with you.”Tina Fey and Amy Poehler hosted Sunday night’s ceremony in unprecedented times: Because of the pandemic, each emceed from a different coast with a few dozen celebrity presenters and only masked first responders in the audience.And because of controversy surrounding the legitimacy and inclusivity of the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, which votes on the awards, they were hosting in the face of serious backlash and even a boycott. Many celebrities ahead of Sunday night shared a #TimesUpGlobes graphic with the mission statement “a cosmetic fix isn’t enough,” following the revelation that the group has not a single Black member in its ranks of 87.Ahead of Sunday’s telecast, a pre-show hosted on NBC by This Is Us’s Susan Kelechi-Watson and The Weakest Link’s Jane Lynch teased that the HFPA would be making a statement about its non-inclusive membership during the telecast. They plugged it as a reason to tune in, like the Grammys would hype a performance by Beyoncé or the Emmys would an Oprah speech. Where a sheepish tone or atonement would be expected, the telecast seemed instead to choose opportunism—and, more pathetically, it even failed at that, as became clear when the promised statement finally came.It took only about three minutes for Fey to make the first joke about the controversy in her opening monologue, with presenters Sterling K. Brown and Kelechi-Watson as well as winner Sacha Baron Cohen later ridiculing the organization from its own stage. Still, it was the HFPA that did what it has done best for decades: reveal its own punchline, apparently not understanding the laugh was at its own expense.That was this case this year when it nominated Netflix’s stale croissant of a TV series, Emily in Paris, for two major awards, snubbing Michaela Coel’s blistering triumph of what television is even capable of, I May Destroy You, and failing to nominate any of the year’s Black-led awards contenders for Best Picture: Da 5 Bloods, Judas and the Black Messiah, Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom, and One Night in Miami.It was certainly the case when three HFPA members took the stage Sunday to address its inclusivity problem. Each delivered a breezy speech so perfunctory, vague, and deflecting that they might as well have been making their own case for negligence and irrelevance. It was truly an embarrassment, such a monstrous whiff that there was no fighting the reflex to laugh.But you could also argue there’s no punchline here at all.Last week, The Los Angeles Times published a damning investigation into the organization’s long history of scandal and unscrupulousness, which escalated the backlash.This is not a revelatory characterization for an award organization whose reliably bizarre slate of nominees is universally chalked up to its notorious movie-star obsession—never forget, Golden Globe nominees Johnny Depp and Angelina for The Tourist—and whose reputation for trading votes in exchange for lavish gifts and access to celebrities stretches back to Pia Zadora’s infamous 1982 win. (Apparently voters were flown to Paris to visit the Emily in Paris set, hence those questionable nods.)But having decades of “self-dealing” and “ethical lapses,” as the Times characterized them, packaged so incriminatingly on the crest of outrage over nomination slights makes the case (for some) that the Globes should be discredited, not aired on NBC, and not given its glamorous spotlight at the prime of Oscar season—especially after reports of its lack of inclusivity.Short of reconfiguring Sunday night’s ceremony to assert its own legitimacy by giving each award of the night to Michaela Coel for I May Destroy You with a brief pause for a show-stopping rendition of “It Was Agatha All Along” by Kathryn Hahn, it’s unclear if there was anything the HFPA or NBC could have done to correct for the sins of this year’s nominations or atone for the organization’s shady practices in any satisfactory way.But even grading on the curve of an attempt to stage a live production like this during the pandemic, the Globes failed to meet even the lowest bar.The irony is that this year’s hideous mess of a telecast did actually make the case for why award shows matter.An explosive speech on the power of storytelling, diversity, and major platforms by Jane Fonda. The authenticity of stirring moments from the likes of Minari director Lee Isaac Chung and Nomadland director Chloé Zhao in their historic wins. The strength and inspiration of Chadwick Boseman’s widow Taylor Simone Ledward. Or the grace and forward thinking of a community of diverse creators who, while bruised by the myopia and narcissism of an influential organization too inept to mint its potential for good, still showed up for a complicated pandemic award show because they at least knew the power of the stories they were telling. (And, sure, also like winning trophies.)Jane Fonda Calls Out Golden Globes’ Diversity Problems in Powerful Acceptance SpeechBut the point is that, in relying on the labor of others—particularly women and people of color—to do the work it should have been doing all along, the Globes has embarrassed its reputation beyond the forgiveness its designation as “Hollywood’s boozy and kooky nonsense party” has warranted in its past. If now is not the time to sober up and detail a plan of action, then when?Three HFPA members who came on stage and said two sentences each about doing better. They ended those speeches with, “Thank you, and we look forward to a more inclusive future...” The concept of “doing the bare minimum” is writing an angry later aghast at how little effort the organization put in. The statement was such a Mad Libs of meaningless buzzwords I wonder if Emily in Paris wrote it.Here’s the thing about Sunday night’s telecast: The conversation surrounding the HFPA’s scandals was so loud there was nothing else about the ceremony that could have possibly superseded it. The fact that, as far as live Hollywood award shows shot on two different coasts in the middle of a pandemic while winners deliver acceptance speeches over weak Zoom connections go, the telecast was perfectly fine doesn’t even matter.Fey and Poehler were perfectly fine. Their monologue was perfectly fine.They were the first to directly address the inclusivity scandal, with Poehler saying, “Look, a lot of flashy garbage got nominated. But that happens—that’s like their thing. But a number of Black actors and Black-led projects were overlooked.”“And look, we all know that award shows are stupid,” added Fey. “The point is, even with stupid things, inclusivity is important, and there are no Black members of the Hollywood Foreign Press. I realize, HFPA, maybe you guys didn’t get the memo because your workplace is the back booth of a French McDonald’s, but you gotta change that.”It wasn’t a scorched-earth condemnation, but it also certainly wasn’t toothless—and it was funny. It should have been the comedy-tinged appetizer for the meal eventually served by the HFPA, who should have delivered a strong and action-oriented statement that left no question that change was on the horizon. Instead it was like they served the food and then hurriedly cleared the plates before anyone realized the meals were undercooked.In other words, they seemed to hope that a business-as-usual show, as much as that could be staged in these times, would be a distraction: “Yes, we’re probably racist...but look! It’s Salma Hayek!” No matter how funny Kristin Wiig and Annie Mumolo are as their Barb and Star Go to Vista Del Mar characters, how deliriously bizarre a bit with Maya Rudolph and Kenan Thompson is, or how unintentionally funny Tracy Morgan’s mispronunciation of Soul was, there was no distracting from it.In fact, the show’s best moments drew direct attention to it.The astounding thing about Jane Fonda is that she manages to be an even better version of Jane Fonda every time we need her to be. This year’s Cecil B. DeMille Award recipient, we knew she would deliver an important speech, but as the Globes backlash intensified, so did the stakes for her remarks. And, wow, did she deliver.It may be the first Globes speech to name-check both Buddha and Tommy Tune, but she also—and so eloquently—drew the connection between Hollywood, platforms like an award-show microphone, and elevating all voices that encapsulated why so many people are so upset about what some might dismiss as a silly, dumb awards ceremony.“There’s a story we’ve been really afraid to see and hear about ourselves and this industry: The story about which voices we respect and elevate and which we tune out,” she said. “A story about who’s offered a seat at the table and who’s kept out of the rooms where the decisions are made.”In the classiest move of the night, she then cited the films and TV series, some nominated and some pointedly not, that enlightened her to the experiences of underrepresented people: Nomadland and the wanderers; Minari and immigrants; Judas and the Black Messiah, Small Axe, The United States vs. Billie Holiday, Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom, and One Night in Miami and what it means to be Black in this country; Ramy and the experience of Muslim Americans; and the snubbed I May Destroy You and surviving sexual violence.It’s the frustrating thing about the open secret of the Globes being a frivolous awards organization with random nominees and winners. That may be true, but it is also a telecast on NBC that does wield influence.Money is spent on these awards campaigns. Rising stars are given trophies on television, and, when they’re people like America Ferrera or Gina Rodriguez or Viola Davis or Chloé Zhao, it means something to those who are watching at home and see themselves represented. Opportunity is given to winners. Boosts are given to Oscar hopefuls. People watching at home might see a TV series or movie win an award and decide to watch it—that on its own matters. Even at the Golden Globes, the image of a storyteller holding a trophy signals that their voice is important.Tina Fey and Amy Poehler Embarrass Hollywood Foreign Press in Golden Globes OpeningIt’s cool to scoff at the Golden Globes and make a personal pledge to ignore them. But what if there was a demand to make them matter? They already do, but they should earn that privilege. That’s the great ending line from Fonda’s speech: “Art has always been not just in step with history, but has led the way. So let’s be leaders.”For crying out loud, the history-making three-woman slate of directing nominees were three of the five ever nominated in the show’s 78-year history. Chloé Zhao is only the second to win, following Barbra Streisand’s Yentl victory in 1983. Zhao’s Nomadland is the first film directed by a woman to ever win Best Picture - Drama. Demand better; don’t just write it off.An award show like the Golden Globes serves dual purposes. It’s meant to entertain and it’s meant to be a catalyst for progress. That sounds pretentious, and there’s no way around it. But that’s why it’s supposed to be OK that the Globes are also a drunken party. That’s the fun part.This year created great moments of entertainment in spite of impossible circumstances. I would watch tributes to Jane Fonda and Norman Lear for hours. Baron Cohen delivered two great speeches. Andra Day, Rosamund Pike, and Anya Taylor-Joy had those kinds of unexpected (and maybe undeserved???) award-show coming out moments that are thrilling to witness. And may we all watch all future award telecasts either as seemingly high as Jason Sudeikis appeared to be, or at least wearing a pair of Jodie Foster’s pajamas.Then there was the night’s emotional highpoint, when Boseman’s widow delivered powerful words to an audience that needed to hear them. “He would say something beautiful, something inspiring, something that would amplify that little voice that tells you you can, that tells you to keep going,” Ledward said. “I don't have his words, but we have to take all the moments to celebrate the ones we love.”The issue with the Globes is how do you square those moments against the unsavory ones. Against its reputation for bad taste (though at least this year’s winners weren’t so bad, if the nominations were a bit wild)? Against its failure to course correct after decades of criticism? Against its seeming refusal to see this particular moment surrounding inclusivity as a crisis for the organization?That’s where the boycotts come in. That’s where the call for NBC to stop broadcasting the show and give it its power comes in. But that’s where, at the very least, a demand for change comes in.It’s tempting to shout, “Cancel the Globes!” But I’m not sure that’s a feasible solution. Whatever the HFPA thought it was doing to save itself with Sunday night’s telecast, however, didn’t make a case in its own favor. At what was a turning point for the show, it took a nosedive toward more shame. The work from there gets even harder. I still argue it should be done.Anyway, in the spirit of Our Lord and Savior Jane Fonda, we will end this article the way all pieces of good writing should end from now on: “And happy birthday to Tommy Tune!”Sacha Baron Cohen Brutally Mocks Rudy Giuliani in Golden Globes SpeechRead more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Charges Ahead With Digital Currency...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/01/china-charges-ahead-with-a-national-digital-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annabelle Huang recently won a government lottery to try China’s latest economics experiment: a national digital currency. After joining the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome back: Optimism abounds as MLB spring includes fans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-arizona-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-a1d831fe3bd0b495c7c4c4965589e066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Brian Delaney checked his ticket, found his seats and then sat down for a minute in the sunshine. It wasn't a typical late February day in Arizona — a little cool, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Journey far from over'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/28/cpac-donald-trump-speech-rightwing-summit-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-president repeats false claims that he won 2020 election and floats possible run in 2024 in speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York attorney general seeks to investigate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/28/andrew-cuomo-sexual-harassment-allegations-charlotte-bennett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Letitia James backs calls from congressional Democrats as governor apologises if conduct ‘misinterpreted as unwanted flirtation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends Navalny to notorious camp feared by inmates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-sends-navalny-to-notorious-penal-camp-feared-by-inmates/ar-BB1e5rjM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russian opposition leader Alexey Navalny, who survived a chemical poisoning last year that he called a Kremlin attempt to kill him, has begun serving his two-and-a-half-year sentence at a notorious penal camp. Navalny, who was removed from his Moscow jail cell Thursday, is being held at a detention facility in the prison in the Vladimir region, about 100 kilometers (60 miles) east of the Russian capital, Alexey Melnikov, secretary...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds arrested in raids across NYC for illegal parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/sheriffs-bust-hundreds-at-underground-parties-across-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 350 people across New York City were busted by the New York City Deputy Sheriffs for attending large, illegal gatherings early Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH BLUNDERS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/daniel-kaluuya-golden-globes-glitch-speech-1234917675/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You’re doing me dirty, you’re doing me dirty,” actor Daniel Kaluuya quipped at the start of his acceptance speech as the first awards presentation of the 78th Golden Globes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE MOUNTS ON CUOMO...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/28/cuomo-sorry-for-jokes-amid-sexual-harassment-claims/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Sunday tried to explain away allegations of sexual harassment as “jokes” that were misinterpreted as “unwanted flirtation” — as his office caved o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists get serious about mixing and matching vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-serious-mixing-matching-covid-140044585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mixing and matching doses of different COVID-19 vaccines was an idea that scientists dismissed out of hand. Now they're taking it seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci worried US virus cases will stick at 70,000 a day...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2021/02/28/news/nation/anthony-fauci-worried-that-us-virus-cases-will-stick-at-70000-a-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though cases have plunged from 300,000 a day to about 70,000, “that baseline’s too high,” Fauci said on NBC’s “Meet the Press.” “The thing you don’t want is to have a plateauing.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
