<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Exodus of black families from Chicago causes alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/black-families-came-chicago-thousands-131418694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILLSIDE, Ill. -- Hardis White, 78, could hardly wait to break out of suburbia.He dressed in a flannel shirt, jeans and a Bears cap, strode out of the rectangular bungalow he shares with his wife and daughter and folded his tall frame behind the wheel of his silver Nissan sedan.Forty minutes away from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporations  working with Trump administration to control online speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/corporations-are-working-with-the-trump-administration-to-control-online-speech/2020/02/14/4d3078c8-4e9d-11ea-bf44-f5043eb3918a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whenever laws are passed to put the government in control of speech, the people who get hurt are the least powerful in society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus cruise quarantine 'went awry,' US official says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2020/02/17/coronavirus-official-explains-diamond-princess-cruise-quarantine-fail/4785290002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci shed light on the decision to evacuate passengers from the Diamond Princess, 14 of whom have tested positive for the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judges' association calls emergency meeting after DOJ intervenes in cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/02/17/roger-stone-sentence-judges-worried-political-interference/4788155002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An association of federal judges has called an emergency meeting after Attorney General William Barr intervened in the case of Trump ally Roger Stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secession in Pacific Northwest? Oregon residents petition to join Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/17/oregon-idaho-border-petition-secede/4789936002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrated by liberal policies, some Oregon residents are petitioning to leave the state by moving the border with Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD ABUZZ</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mike-bloomberg-2020-hollywood-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As socially liberal as the entertainment industry is, many in this influential community are also business-minded and harbor a deep private fear of a socialist like Bernie Sanders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ad Takes on Bernie Bros: 'Really?'</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/michael-bloomberg-bernie-sanders-ad-attack-supporters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Michael Bloomberg's new campaign spot focuses on online behavior of some of Sen. Bernie Sanders' most ardent supporters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERBUGS COULD STOP CHEMOTHERAPY FROM WORKING, ONCOLOGISTS WARN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/superbugs-threaten-to-stop-chemotherapy-from-working-fjjmgtvjm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of cancer patients are at risk of contracting antibiotic resistant superbugs that could make chemotherapy unviable within the next decade, oncologists warn.Cancer patients rely on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Campaigns warn of chaos ahead of Nevada caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Campaigns-warn-of-chaos-ahead-of-Nevada-caucuses-15061369.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS - With the Nevada caucuses days away, campaign officials and Democratic activists are increasingly alarmed that they might prove a debacle as damaging as the vote in Iowa, further setting the party back in its urgent effort to coalesce around a nominee to take on President Donald Trump.  Campaigns said they still have not gotten the party to offer even a basic explanation of how key parts of the process will work. Volunteers are reporting problems with the technology that's been deployed at the last minute to make the vote count smoother. And experts are raising serious questions about an app the party has been feverishly assembling to replace the one scrapped after the meltdown in Iowa.  "It feels like the [state party is] making it up as they go along," said one Democratic presidential aide, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss the process. "That's not how we need to be running an election."  Adding to the challenge is the complexity of Nevada's caucuses. Unlike in Iowa, where caucuses are conducted in one evening, Nevadans have the option of voting early. At sites across the state, Democrats can rank their top presidential choices on a paper ballot.  On Saturday, caucus day, Democrats can gather at one of about 2,000 sites to vote for their preferred candidate. If their first choice doesn't get enough backing, voters can throw their support behind someone else, a second round of voting known as "final alignment." Early voting preferences will be treated the same way, as though the voter were attending in person.  The party had planned to use two specially designed apps for reporting results, developed by political technology firm Shadow, the same company that designed the vote-recording app blamed for the chaos in Iowa. A coding error in the Iowa app made it impossible to tally results,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>