<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Blown Away: Wild wind tosses restaurant worker onto roof!</title>
      <link>https://www.wnky.com/blown-away-wind-tosses-restaurant-worker-onto-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(WYFF/NBC News) Two people were hurt Monday night while trying to secure an event tent during a storm in Clemson, South Carolina. Managers at the Esso Club said they set up a large event tent earlier that morning for a Clemson University event. A storm hit the area later that afternoon and began to blow the plastic tables, chairs and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of 'skeleton lake' where hundreds have died leaves archaeologists baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9766122/skeleton-lake-roopkund-mystery-ancient-catastrophe-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DECADES-OLD mystery over an eerie Himalayan lake littered with human remains deepens – as scientists say hundreds of people died there spread over 1,000 years. It was previously thought that the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: AM stations wanted to keep listeners engaged -- ended up remaking Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/talk-radio-made-todays-republican-party/596380/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AM stations mainly wanted to keep listeners engaged—but ended up remaking the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Second Trailer for Brad Pitt in 'AD ASTRA' Shows Gorgeous Visuals...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/08/21/watch-surprise-second-trailer-for-brad-pitt-in-ad-astra-shows-gorgeous-visuals-delineates-father-son-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Gray’s “Ad Astra” is coming, and fast, like a meteor about to hit Earth. We have now have a surprise second trailer for the Brad Pitt- Liv Tyler- Tommy Lee Jones- Donald Sut…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'BACHELOR' Airs First Same-Sex Romance...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/bachelor-paradise-airs-first-same-sex-romance-demi-burnett-1233460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contestant Demi Burnett is exploring a relationship with a franchise outsider in a first for the summer spinoff series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Struggles to Come to Terms With Theater Chains Over 'IRISHMAN' Release...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/08/netflix-struggles-to-come-to-terms-with-theater-chains-over-the-irishman-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Martin Scorsese’s mob drama be released in theaters?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN GULAG DEATH OF EPSTEIN: ASSANGE NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/american-gulag-death-of-jeffrey-epstein-will-julian-assange-be-next_08202019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death of millionaire sex offender Jeffrey Epstein behind bars should trigger “system-wide self-reflection” on how prisoners are treated. The Metropolitan Correctional Center “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTLAND: Drug use, mental illness, homelessness rise; 'Do not feel safe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/portland-residents-tell-elected-officials-to-stop-talking-and-fix-homelessness-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland’s homeless problem has gotten so out of control that it’s hardening even the most liberal of bleeding hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not even 30, and flying own jet' -- Silicon Beach elites take seat in cockpit...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/la-me-silicon-beach-pilots-20190702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planes have long been a passion of the rich, particularly in Los Angeles. But among Silicon Beach elites, a pilot’s license is seen less as leisure than a program of self-improvement. For engineers, flying is fun with applied math. It's intellectual exercise in the guise of a sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorists harassing buses with migrant students in Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article234038627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandalized robot may solve mystery of own attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/california/article234198532.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Top 10 worst resorts for food poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-7379245/The-10-worst-resorts-food-poisoning-Hurghada-Egypt-Riviera-Maya-Mexico.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has highlighted the world's food poisoning hotspots and top of the list is Hurghada in Egypt - 380 cases have been reported since the start of 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Streaming Push Adds Intrigue to Iger Succession Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/disney-s-streaming-push-complicates-bob-iger-succession-race-1233419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the CEO goes all-in on Disney+, insiders say direct-to-consumer chief Kevin Mayer is "poised" for a boost — that is, as long as the forthcoming digital platform becomes a hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump critics eye GOP primary race even if defeating him seems 'daunting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-critics-eye-GOP-primary-race-even-if-14365954.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Joe Walsh, a pugnacious former congressman, is preparing a Republican primary challenge to President Trump that he previewed as a daily "bar fight" with the incumbent over his morality and competency.  Mark Sanford, a former South Carolina governor and congressman, said he is inching closer to a bid of his own by sounding out activists in New Hampshire and other early-voting states about an insurgency focused on the ballooning deficit.  Jeff Flake, a former Arizona senator and Trump antagonist, said he has taken a flurry of recruitment calls in recent days from GOP donors rattled by signs of an economic slowdown and hungry for an alternative to Trump.  And former Ohio Gov. John Kasich will head to New Hampshire next month to "take a look at things" after experiencing "an increase" in overtures this summer, an adviser said.  The anti-Trump movement inside the Republican Party - long a political wasteland - is feeling new urgency to mount a credible opposition to Trump before it's too late. With state deadlines for nominating contests rapidly approaching in the fall, potential candidates face pressure to decide on running within the next few weeks. So far, only former Massachusetts governor Bill Weld has declared that he is running, but he has struggled to gain traction.  Republicans considering bids, as well as those trying to draft other candidates, acknowledge that defeating Trump appears to be nearly impossible but argue that a recession or an unforeseen change in the political climate could weaken him enough to make a primary challenge more than a Never Trump fantasy.  "Anybody who says, 'I think I can beat Donald Trump,' I think is stretching it," Sanford said. "It's a daunting task and it is indeed preposterous at many different levels."  But Sanford said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX, Big Theater Chains Haggle Over Release of Scorsese 'IRISHMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/08/21/netflix-and-big-theater-chains-haggle-over-release-of-scorseses-irishman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - LOS ANGELES — When Martin Scorsese signed with Netflix to make “The Irishman,” the star-studded epic scheduled to have its premiere on the opening night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer clown craze returns as masked man chases terrified family with knife...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/it-movie-killer-clowns-craze-18975974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT TWO' First Reactions: Biggest Disappointment Of Year...</title>
      <link>https://wegotthiscovered.com/movies/reactions-chapter-call-biggest-disappointment-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wegotthiscovered.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first reactions to It: Chapter Two are in but they're not great, with some calling it a major disappointment and far too bloated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Homebuilder's Woes Show Mounting Slowdown Fears...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/luxury-homebuilders-woes-show-mounting-010127733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wealthy buyers are pulling back from some of the most expensive housing markets in the U.S., the latest sign that sky-high prices and fears of a recession are weighing on a key sector of the economy.Toll Brothers Inc., the nation’s largest publicly traded luxury-home builder, said late</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military drone shot down over Yemen...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190821105917-4tg0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEMEN-SECURITY/USA-DRONE (URGENT):U.S. military drone shot down over Yemen: officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beatings, murders, prisoners set on fire: Inside prison called 'gangland'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/21/south-mississippi-correctional-institution-prison </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates report gangs enforce the rules at South Mississippi Correctional Institution, where violence is surging and ‘horrific’ attacks leave ‘no doubt the prison is unsafe’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test predicts whether you'll die in next 10 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/scientists-develop-blood-test-predicts-18975838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from the Max Planck Institute for Biology of Ageing have developed a new blood test that can predict whether you’ll die within the next 10 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touch Football -- Now Requires Helmet...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/08/20/touch-football-sold-as-safer-now-requires-a-helmet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - COLLEGE STATION, Tex. — On a steamy afternoon in June, Jim Poynter, the coach of the 7-on-7 touch football team at Lamar High School in Arlington, Tex.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan warns NKorea now has miniaturized nukes; 'Imminent threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7378849/Japan-warns-North-Korea-miniaturized-nukes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's military last year said it was 'possible' that North Korea had achieved miniaturisation, but Tokyo now appears to have upgraded its assessment (pictured, a recent North Korean weapons test).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi's choice: Destroy Trump, or weaken America...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/xis-choice-destroy-trump-or-save-him-and-weaken-america/2019/08/20/c6e6f934-c384-11e9-9986-1fb3e4397be4_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese autocrat must finesse his statecraft if he wants to secure world-power status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl found bound and gagged on freeway; CHP says family was taking her to drug rehab...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2019-08-19/girl-17-found-bound-and-gagged-on-carlsbad-freeway-chp-says-family-was-taking-her-to-drug-rehab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHP officers found the teen tied up in the back seat of a car on south I-5 near Cannon Road in Carlsbad. The girl's father and sister said they were taking her to a drug rehab facility in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Husband of El Paso massacre victim has his SUV stolen on the day he buries her...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/social-justice-1/2019/08/19/husband-el-paso-massacre-victim-suv-stolen-day-buries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO - Antonio Basco, the grief-stricken man who lost his wife of 22 years in the Aug. 3 El Paso massacre, buried her Saturday amid an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  SET THERMOSTATS TO 82&amp;#176; WHILE YOU SLEEP!</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/federal-energy-program-suggests-keeping-thermostat-set-at-78-degrees-82-while-you-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To keep your home cool with central air conditioning while also optimizing energy efficiency (and therefore cost), keep the temperature at 78 degrees Fahrenheit or higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein preyed on women in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/jeffrey-epstein-preyed-women-during-jail-sentence-forced-victim-marry-n1044641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three lawsuits allege a complex web of companies employing "disciples" who saw to it that Epstein's sexual desires were met.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNHAM FINDS LIFE AFTER 'GIRLS' AND ANTONOFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.domino.com/content/lena-dunham-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.domino.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress, producer, and director Lena Dunham invites us insider her downtown Manhattan apartment and explains, in her own words, what it finally means to be home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW 'MATRIX' MOVIE IN THE WORKS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/matrix-4-keanu-reeves-carrie-anne-moss-lana-wachowski-1203307955/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready to re-enter the Matrix. Lana Wachowski is set to write and direct a fourth film set in the world of “The Matrix,” with Keanu Reeves and Carrie-Anne Moss reprising their roles as Neo and T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Theft Case Suddenly Dropped By L.A. D.A...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/frances-mcdormand-oscar-statuette-stolen-no-charges-1202689273/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;File this under … just plain old weird. The Los Angeles County District Attorney’s office can’t or won’t say why, but the criminal case against the man who allegedly stole Frances McDor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of large organic food scheme kills self...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41b42b957dae42ff96624f9a1a237def</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — A Missouri farmer blamed for running the largest organic food fraud scheme in U.S. history has died by suicide, weeks before he was to report to federal prison to begin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump delays Denmark meeting over Greenland proposal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f589698d5424dbda4be8d3acdf7ce6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump says an upcoming trip to Denmark is on hold because its prime minister isn't interested in selling Greenland to the U.S. Denmark owns Greenland....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Jews who vote Democrat show 'great disloyalty'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1bc3065eb2e4414289ef0ac1ac4ebaf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Showing a fresh willingness to play politics along religious and racial lines, President Donald Trump said Tuesday that American Jewish people who vote for Democrats show "either...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Jews who vote Democrat show 'great disloyalty'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/trump-jews-who-vote-democrat-show-lack-of-knowledge-or-great-disloyalty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US president slams rival party for defending Ilhan Omar and Rashida Tlaib, saying Jews who support them show 'a total lack of knowledge;' rejects call to cut aid to Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Far from recession'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-says-u-s-far-recession-white-house-economic-anxiety-n1044331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reaching a deal with China is seen as a top priority inside the White House as worrying economic signs grow ahead of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game keeper mauled to death by 3 lions inside their enclosure...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7375523/Game-keeper-killed-three-lions-owned-South-Africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, who was named as Leon van Biljon, was mauled to death at the Dinokeng Game Reserve, north of Pretoria, when the lions attacked him as he went inside their enclosure to tend to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS, Al-Qaeda Hunker Down to Rebuild...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-20/islamic-state-al-qaeda-hunker-down-to-rebuild-in-weaker-nations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for botching castration on victim he met on dark web...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/highlands-county/sebring-man-arrested-for-botching-castration-on-victim-he-met-on-dark-web-deputies-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Highlands County man is behind bars after deputies say he performed a botched castration in his home on a man he met through the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World famous porn star found living in squalor in tunnels under Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/world-famous-porn-star-found-18965788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jenni Lee still has 45,000 subscribers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Veterans Affairs pathologist charged in deaths of 3 patients...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d1ca93b6ae64bcabeff3cec533081fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — A pathologist fired from an Arkansas veterans hospital after officials said he had been impaired while on duty was charged Tuesday with involuntary manslaughter in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli, US special forces practice ship takeovers amid high tensions in Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-us-special-forces-practice-ship-takeovers-amid-high-tensions-in-gulf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IDF says last week's Noble Rose exercise not held in direct response to recent incidents around Strait of Hormuz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-MLB players arrested in connection with Caribbean drug ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/ex-mlb-players-octavio-dotel-luis-castillo-arrested-connection-caribbean-n1044546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Series champs, arrested in the Dominican Republic, were allegedly tied to "one of the most important drug trafficking structures in the Caribbean."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poachers caught butchering green sea turtles...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article234188292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware attack that crippled 23 Texas towns has cost $12M...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7373117/Twenty-three-Texas-towns-hit-coordinated-ransomware-attack-crashed-local-government-ops.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-three Texas towns were struck by a 'coordinated' ransomware attack which began on Friday morning. The exact locations have not been named but it is believed to have cost $12 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAFFIC HELL:  Most of 405 Shut Down After Big Rig Crash...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/08/20/most-of-405-freeway-shut-down-in-long-beach-after-crash-involving-big-rig-traffic-jammed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traffic was snarled along the 405 through Long Beach Tuesday after a multivehicle crash involving a big rig prompted officials to close most of the lanes on both sides of the freeway. The crash took place just after 9:30 a.m. on the southbound 405 Freeway at the connector to the southbound 710 Freeway, according to the California Highway Patrol's incident log.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camping canceled at PHISH concerts. Blame plague-infected prairie dogs...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/20/us/phish-colorado-plague-prairie-dogs-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The good news: A weekend of Phish concerts will go on as scheduled at a soccer stadium outside Denver, Colorado. The bad? No camping, because the plague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Reid rips Dems over 'Medicare-for-all,' border policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/ywadgw/exclusive-harry-reid-of-course-medicare-for-all-and-decriminalizing-border-crossings-are-bad-ideas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are so many more important things to do," the former Senate majority leader said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was paid to keep kids out of gangs. Now, he's charged in MS-13 killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/he-was-paid-to-keep-kids-out-of-gangs-now-hes-charged-in-grisly-ms-13-killings/ar-AAG44K3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California to build largest wildlife crossing in world...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d0bd2e4232dc4952a1db399afb257cd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Like many urban singles, the mountain lion P-22 lives a solitary life in a too-small habitat. And he has a hard time finding a mate in the big city. Famous for traveling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 51 events prompt emergency crowd planning...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/86167556378d4198a44e6626b02724df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Fearing they could be overwhelmed with visitors, officials in the remote Nevada county that's home to the Area 51 military base have drafted an emergency declaration and a plan to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA's  pricey fix: $700,000 condos...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/20/homeless-people-los-angeles-la-builds-pricey-koreatown-apartments/1984064001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With thousands living on the streets, Los Angeles is spending lavishly to try to solve the problem. But, $320,000 a year for a toilet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Seeks to Allay Farm-State Uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-20/trump-seeks-to-allay-farm-state-uproar-in-oval-office-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin used to fund terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-being-used-fund-terrorism-143557407.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite its lack of anonymity, Bitcoin is becoming increasingly popular among groups looking to skirt sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines expect record crowds over Labor Day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d7a30276b98b455382e9232698a98581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Airlines expect record crowds over the week-long Labor Day period, continuing a rise in travel that has boosted the airlines' profits all year. The trade group Airlines for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12,000 people, largest of tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/elizabeth-warren-st-paul-minnesota-town-hall_n_5d5b1c9fe4b0f667ed6750ca?guccounter=1rdjO4MAaVpVRf34TyuPzMTiqTfkwMhYbhxFu2X_-QRg9dNsKVnM9tbtoJGwIu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 12,000 people showed up at the Democratic presidential hopeful's town hall at Macalester College in St. Paul, according to her campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Gal pal staged IN-N-OUT photo...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7372877/Ghislaine-Maxwell-STAGED-photo-N-close-friend-attorney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first picture of Ghislaine Maxwell in more than three years was staged by her close friend and attorney, Leah Saffian, DailyMail.com has learned exclusively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Fundraising in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/dnc-chief-plans-to-raise-money-from-americans-in-mexico-city/ar-AAG4oat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  George Shreds Trump Staff: They 'Work For a Rapist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/george-conway-husband-of-trump-staffer-kellyanne-conway-shreds-wh-staff-these-people-who-work-for-a-rapist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, blasted President Donald Trump's staff for doing the bidding of "a rapist." In a Tuesday morning tweet, Conway shar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese company to launch mass sale of cloned cats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-company-launch-mass-sale-18971657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinogene plans to sell cloned cats for £29,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA CORN POLL:  BIDEN, PETE </title>
      <link>https://whotv.com/2019/08/19/final-cast-your-kernel-presidential-poll-results-showed-something-unusual/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whotv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa -- The voting is finished, and the corn kernels are packed away for the year. The 2019 Cast Your Kernel presidential poll results showed something that has never happened before in the 15 years of the poll at the Iowa State Fair: almost exactly as many fairgoers voted for a Democratic candidate for president as a Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's brain surgeon defends his brain...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/860046/joe-bidens-brain-surgeon-defending-joe-bidens-brain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enough with the worrying, former Vice President Joe Biden's brain surgeon says. As some voters murmur that the gaffe-prone Democratic presidential candidate's age is cause for extra concern this campaign cycle, Dr. Neal Kassell â€” the man who performed surgery on Biden three decades ago following two brain aneurysms â€” came out swinging for his former patient. Kassell dismissed fears about the 76-year-old Biden's mental faculties, noting that he's "as sharp as he was 31 years ago" and assuring people that the hemorrhage and subsequent operations did not result in any brain damage. "I am going to vote for the candidate who I am absolutely certain has a brain that is functioning," Kassell told Politico. "And that narrows it down to exactly one." Biden's physician, Dr. Kevin O'Connor, backed up Kassell. "Vice President Biden is in excellent physical condition," he said. "He is more than capable of handling the rigors of the campaign and the office for which he is running." In fact, several experts told Politico that voters are placing too great an emphasis on the age of several candidates, particularly the five septuagenarians who are running, including Democratic candidates Biden and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.), 70, and Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.), 77, as well as 73-year-old President Trump and his lone Republican challenger, former Massachusetts Gov. Bill Weld, who is 74. "They have prospects for survival that extend well beyond the four-year term of the office," said Dr. Jay Olshansky, who led an American Federation of Aging Research study last month that sought to determine how likely it is that a candidate would die while in office. "The bottom line is their chronological age does not matter at all." Read more at Politico. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Killed In Double Stabbing During Fight That Started Over Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/20/deadly-double-stabbing-in-brewerytown-may-have-been-over-social-media-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say two women were stabbed at Jefferson and 29th Streets, around 11:30 p.m. on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo confirms ISIS regaining strength...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/20/pompeo-confirms-isis-is-gaining-strength/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo acknowledged Tuesday that ISIS is regaining strength in Iraq and Syria — as he insisted that the caliphate is still defeated. “It’s complicated. The…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists finally know how big earthquakes start: With many smaller ones...</title>
      <link>https://heraldpublicist.com/scientists-finally-know-how-big-earthquakes-start-with-many-smaller-ones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heraldpublicist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House insists fundamentals of economy strong...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ad2fadb147145b49eb7e343ceb4aa2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The "fundamentals" of the U.S. economy are solid, the White House asserted, invoking an ill-fated political declaration of a decade ago amid mounting concern that a recession...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN CROWD SWELLS IN MN...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox9.com/news/presidential-candidate-elizabeth-warren-addresses-supporters-in-st-paul-minn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren argued for a wealth tax and major changes to the U.S. immigration system during a speech to thousands of supporters Monday evening at Macalester College in St. Paul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bret Baier Fires Back at Trump on Polls: 'FOXNEWS Has Not Changed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bret-baier-fires-back-at-trump-on-polls-fox-news-has-not-changed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fox News anchor took issue with the president’s criticism of polls that show him losing to Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. STEEL TO LAY OFF HUNDREDS IN MICHIGAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-u-s-steel-layoffs/u-s-steel-plans-to-lay-off-hundreds-of-workers-in-michigan-idUSKCN1V91XQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United States Steel Corp will temporarily lay off hundreds of workers at its Gre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists finally know how big earthquakes start: With many smaller ones...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-19/earthquakes-foreshocks-seismology-new-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New techniques to detect small earthquakes have deepened scientists’ understanding of what causes bigger quakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was paid to keep kids out of gangs. Now, he's charged in MS-13 killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-19/accused-ms-13-gang-member-worked-as-gang-interventionist-until-arrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wilfredo Vides was employed as a gang intervention counselor by a nonprofit funded with public money. He was also an active MS-13 gang member, prosecutors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stallone Drops Intense New 'RAMBO' Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/sylvester-stallone-drops-intense-new-rambo-last-blood-trailer-1233221 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Along with all the action, the preview shows glimpses of parallels from the original 1982 film and 'Rambo: First Blood Part II.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: A 'WOKE' ICON FALLS FROM GRACE...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/859819/jayzs-cardboard-corporate-activism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the rapper's NFL partnership shouldn't be a surprise to anyone</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
