<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Couple saved from landslide by their cats...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.it/20191023/storms-italian-couple-saved-from-landslide-by-their-cats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As violent storms lash northern Italy, one couple in Liguria told how their pets aided a narrow escape before their house collapsed in a landslide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate America freaks out over Warren...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/23/elizabeth-warren-corporate-america-055142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK'S SPORTING GOODS CEO quietly tests third-party bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/23/dicks-sporting-goods-ceo-presidential-run-055565 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person with measles traveled to DISNEYLAND while infectious...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-22/measles-disneyland-infectious-exposure-october-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who visited a West L.A. Starbucks the morning of Oct. 16 or Disneyland on that day should take precautions, county health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3.22 Trillion: Federal Programs That 'Transfer Income' to Hit Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/322-trillion-federal-programs-transfer-income-projected-hit-record-fy20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Mark Wilson)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Third of Jews avoid identifying religion publicly...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/467061-poll-nearly-a-third-of-jews-avoid-identifying-themselves-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a third of Jewish Americans say they have hidden their religious identity or avoided carrying items that would identify oneself as Jewish in public due to threats of anti-Semitism, according to a poll released Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Byzantine church of 'glorious martyr' uncovered in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/byzantine-church-glorious-martyr-uncovered-israel-130416095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remains of a sixth-century Byzantine church dedicated to an unnamed "glorious martyr" with elaborate mosaics, a rare crypt and a large collection of lamps were unveiled in central Israel on Wednesday. The complex, which spans over a third of an acre, was found during salvage excavations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Blackout Threat May Last Into Next Week as Winds Rise...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wildfire-risk-critical-southern-california-123051385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Californians need to brace themselves. The hot, dry windy weather that’s bringing the threat of new utility blackouts to a half-million residents is ramping up, and could potentially get worse next week.PG&amp;E Corp. has already warned about 184,000 customers in 17 northern and central California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, NY prosecutors to square off over tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-vance/trump-new-york-prosecutors-to-square-off-in-appeals-court-over-tax-returns-idUSKBN1X218U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for U.S. President Donald Trump and New York state prosecutors trying to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower who escaped 're-education camp' reveals horrors of gulag...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7599941/Whistleblower-escaped-Chinese-education-camp-reveals-horrors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sayragul Sauytbay, 43, spent five months teaching Chinese at a 're-education camp' for Uighur Muslims in Xinjiang province, where she claims to have witnessed torture and repeated rapes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico tries to kick homophobic chant out of soccer...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/mexico-tries-kick-homophobic-chant-football-014218134--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;It&amp;quot; is &amp;quot;puto,&amp;quot; a homophobic slur that Mexican fans often chant at the opposing team&amp;#39;s keeper when he takes a goal kick. The practice has landed the football-loving nation in hot water with FIFA, which has fined the Mexican federation, the FMF, 14 times over the chant since 2015</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Approval of inquiry hits new high...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approval Of Impeachment Inquiry Reaches 55 Percent, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; Voters Disapprove Of Trump's Decision On Syria 2-1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Turkey deal shatters Syria Kurd dreams of self-rule...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-turkey-deal-shatters-syria-kurd-dreams-self-111908317.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Turkish-Russian deal signed in the Black Sea resort of Sochi that carves up northeastern Syria sounds the death knell for Kurdish autonomy, analysts say. Syria's Kurds had hoped that the sacrifices made in the name of the international community to help crush the Islamic State group's "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder suspect whose case was catalyst for Hong Kong protests released...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-suspect-whose-case-catalyst-hong-kong-protests-053536641.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A murder suspect whose proposed deportation to Taiwan was a catalyst for massive anti-government protests in Hong Kong was released from prison Wednesday, but despite saying he wants to face justice will remain in the city for now. The law's proposal was prompted by the case of Hong Konger Chan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will LOUVRE show include world's priciest painting?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/louvre-show-worlds-priciest-painting-040001576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Louvre museum prepares to unveil a blockbuster exhibition of works by Leonardo da Vinci on Thursday, mystery surrounds whether the show will include the world's most expensive painting -- Salvator Mundi, attributed to the master painter. It is unlikely, but organisers have not ruled out a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese state TV keeps NBA opener off air amid row...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-row-looms-over-nba-season-openers-063007233--nba.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's state television kept the NBA's season-opening games off the air on Wednesday in the latest fallout from a row over a team executive's support for pro-democracy protests Hong Kong. The blackout added to an unusual start to the NBA season, as activists distributed t-shirts in support</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bamboozled: 'Panda dog' cafe sparks animal rights debate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bamboozled-panda-dog-cafe-sparks-china-animal-rights-105430122.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pet cafe in China where dogs are dyed black and white to look like panda cubs has triggered a heated online debate over the treatment of animals. The Cute Pet Games cafe opened last month in Chengdu, capital of southwest Sichuan province which is home to China's famous giant pandas, and features</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Futuristic Door Handles Blamed for Death in Fiery Wreck...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-futuristic-door-handles-blamed-003450557.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The futuristic door handles on Tesla Inc.’s Model S are being blamed for a fatal crash in which a police officer was unable to pull a man to safety from his burning car.Omar Awan, a 48-year-old anesthesiologist, was driving his leased Tesla in February when he lost control on a south Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flight Shame' Real, Will Make Carbon Big Business, CITI Says...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/flight-shame-real-carbon-big-065436182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- “Flight shame” -- flyers feeling guilty about their carbon footprint -- is a real phenomenon and will raise costs for airlines, consumers and companies, while catapulting emission offsetting into a big business, Citigroup Inc. predicts.The cost of offsetting planes’ carbon emissions could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media bruised by president's austerity...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191023073249-ah2y3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-MEDIA/ (PIX):Making do with less: Mexican media bruised by president's austerity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Crises Testing McConnell Firewall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-multiple-crises-testing-mcconnell-080000312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump’s serial self-inflicted crises are testing Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell and the rest of the GOP senators he’ll be counting on in an impeachment trial that lawmakers in both parties now see as all but inevitable.Trump has forced Republicans in Congress to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE touts quantum computing milestone...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-touts-quantum-computing-milestone-091505171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google said it has achieved a breakthrough in quantum computing research, saying an experimental quantum processor has completed a calculation in just a few minutes that would take a traditional supercomputer thousands of years. Quantum computing is a nascent and somewhat bewildering technology for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will House Put Investigation On TV?</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/addybaird/democrats-trump-impeachment-investigation-tv-public-hearings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Let the public see, because ultimately the public has a right to make a determination as to what they what they think happened."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp Forced To Release Booze, Drug Use Records In Lawsuit With Ex-Wife...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/johnny-depp-amber-heard-lawsuit-drug-alcohol-records-defamation-case-1202765484/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the multimillion-dollar defamation lawsuit that Johnny Depp launched against Amber Heard this spring hasn’t already gotten messy enough, a new ruling could expose a lot of dirty laundry for the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNT:  7 Republican Senators Rule Out Impeaching...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/22/republican-senator-ruled-out-impeachment-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Republican senators refused to rule out voting to remove President Trump from office in an impeachment trial over the Ukraine scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors hail first drug to 'slow down' Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/biogen-new-drug-offers-hope-for-alzheimer-s-sufferers-sh90z3q9h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors have welcomed a “turning point” in the treatment of Alzheimer’s disease after the development of a drug apparently able to slow the condition if it is caught in its earliest stages. It...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas TV station apologizes for not interrupting Cowboys coverage for tornado warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/weather-news/article236502493.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems could tie paychecks to testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/democrats-could-tie-paychecks-to-testimony-in-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are threatening to force senior Trump administration officials’ compliance with their impeachment inquiry by targeting their paychecks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise pollution hurts wildlife, but states have trouble turning down volume...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/10/22/noise-pollution-hurts-wildlife-but-states-have-trouble-turning-down-the-volume</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S aims to know what you want before you order it...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mcdonalds-3q-earnings-down-on-tech-investment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's says it's setting itself up for future growth by investing now in advances like voice recognition ordering technology. But for some investors, the short-term financial pain is hard to swallow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists urge action against GOOGLE over EU copyright dispute... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/journalists-urge-action-against-google-over-eu-copyright-234402296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of journalists called Wednesday for European officials to take action against Google over its refusal to pay media companies for displaying their content in defiance of a strict new EU copyright law. If they refuse, only a headline and a bare link to the content will appear, Google said, almost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILLER:  Permanent bureaucracy a mortal threat to America...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/stephen-miller-pushback-permanent-bureaucracy-a-mortal-threat-to-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anonymous efforts by anti-Trump federal bureaucrats to thwart the White House agenda through leaks and complaints to friendly reporters and congressional allies are a “mortal threat” to democracy and the 2016 election results, according to a top administration official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Pile of Uneaten Bacon Is Biggest in 48 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-pile-uneaten-bacon-biggest-220335498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- America is sitting on a mountain of uneaten bacon.More than 40 million pounds (18,000 metric tons) of pork bellies, the cut used for bacon making, were sitting in refrigerated warehouses as of Sept. 30, according to U.S. government data released Tuesday. That’s the most for the month since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LYNCHING'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48aa35f1bcea4bf1a34305836022bc96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Stirring up painful memories of America's racist past, President Donald Trump on Tuesday compared the Democratic-led impeachment inquiry to a lynching, a practice once widespread...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW DRAMA ROCKS WEST WING</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/anonymous-author-of-trump-resistance-op-ed-to-publish-a-tell-all-book/ar-AAJaXwc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contestants battle to win plastic surgery in new game show...</title>
      <link>https://www.c21media.net/channel-4-swears-in-surjury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c21media.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK broadcaster Channel 4 has commissioned a factual entertainment series from indie prodco Gobstopper Television in which a jury decides if someone should get plastic surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMORROW:  CA braces for more blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/where-pge-will-turn-off-power-Wednesday-California-14552778.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PG&amp;E is closely monitoring the weather to determine whether to cut off power to Northern California residents in fire-prone areas. On Monday night officials said a potential shutoff could impact up to 201,000 customers beginning Wednesday and running into Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top BOEING exec ousted as 737 MAX crisis continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/kevin-mcallister-ousted-as-boss-of-boeing-commercial-airplanes-as-737-max-crisis-continues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boeing board decided Monday to fire Kevin McAllister, CEO of Boeing Commercial Airplanes, the first executive head to roll as a result of the ongoing 737 MAX crisis. McAllister was replaced immediately by Stan Deal, chief executive of Boeing's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu down but not out after failing to form govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-politics-scenarios/israels-netanyahu-down-but-not-out-after-failing-to-form-government-idUSKBN1X11WM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in a decade, someone other than Benjamin Netanyahu will be as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Took 'meticulous' notes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/u-s-diplomat-bill-taylor-who-called-trump-s-ukraine-n1069941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats said Taylor drew a "direct line" between the president's demand that Ukraine investigate his political rivals and distribution of U.S. military aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EXPLOSIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-blasts-inquiry-lynching-key-witness-testifies-162145166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's impeachment battle hit dangerous new territory Tuesday with what a Democrat called "explosive" testimony supporting allegations that he pressured Ukraine for dirt on a political opponent. Beset by tensions at home and abroad, Trump sparked yet more controversy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers argue elephant should have same rights as humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/22/lawyers-argue-happy-the-elephant-should-have-the-same-rights-as-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers representing an elephant say she is being detained by the Bronx Zoo ‘illegally’ due to her personhood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANONYMOUS' WRITES BOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/22/politics/anonymous-trump-official-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymous senior Trump administration official whose 2018 New York Times op-ed was called treasonous by President Donald Trump has written a new book about Trump titled "A Warning" that will be published next month, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETS furious QB's 'seeing ghosts' comment aired on ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/22/jets-furious-espn-aired-sam-darnolds-seeing-ghosts-comment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jets have gone from seeing ghosts to seeing red. The team is livid with the decision to air a comment from quarterback Sam Darnold during the “Monday Night Football” broadcast on ES…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW DRAMA ROCKS WEST WING</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/anonymous-author-of-trump-resistance-op-ed-to-publish-a-tell-all-book/2019/10/22/b9ea2f42-f45a-11e9-ad8b-85e2aa00b5ce_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The authorâ€™s original 2018 column in the New York Times ricocheted around the world and stoked the presidentâ€™s rage because of its devastating portrayal of Trump in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS  PUTS BREXIT PLANS ON HOLD AFTER COMMONS WIN, AND DEFEAT... DEVELOPING... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/10191610/brexit-latest-boris-johnson-vote-commons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson has FINALLY got backing for his Brexit deal tonight from MPs – but they have wrecked his hopes for an October 31 exit. MPs opted to push his deal through to the next stage by 32…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dem Congresswoman denies improper relationship with aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/22/katie-hill-denies-improper-relationship-054313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall heat wave turns 'happiest place on Earth' into hottest place in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fall-heat-wave-turns-happiest-place-on-earth-into-hottest-place-in-america/ar-AAJaQdm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floats Mulvaney Replacements...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/politics/2019/10/22/trump-floats-mulvaney-replacements-including-mnuchin-conway/40379875/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has for weeks been privately testing the idea of replacing his chief of staff, Mick Mulvaney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A WARNING'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7601919/Anonymous-Trump-insider-rocked-White-House-resistance-op-ed-tell-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed author will release a book next month - an extended-play version of the essay that turned Washington on its head with speculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANONYMOUS' WRITES BOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1538718464/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Turkey reach 'historic' deal on Syria...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-erdogan-meet-ahead-syria-deadline-075902738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Turkey agreed on Tuesday to ensure Kurdish forces withdraw from areas close to Syria's border with Turkey and to launch joint patrols, in a deal hailed as "historic" by President Recep Tayyip Erdogan. After marathon talks in Russia's southern city of Sochi, Erdogan and Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA county's experience shows perils of ransomware...</title>
      <link>https://www.onlineathens.com/nationworld/20191022/jackson-countys-experience-shows-perils-of-ransomware</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the first Saturday in March, computer screens at the 911 dispatch center in Jefferson went dark. Staff at the county jail around the same time could no</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Floats Mulvaney Replacements Including Mnuchin and Conway...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-22/trump-floats-mulvaney-replacements-including-mnuchin-and-conway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat provides House with 'disturbing' Ukraine account...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3769e350fd334a6287474ad82042b4e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former U.S. Ambassador William Taylor, a diplomat who has sharply questioned President Donald Trump's policy on Ukraine, has provided lawmakers with a "disturbing" account of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA:  Humans could land on Mars by 2035!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10190885/nasa-mars-landing-deadline-date-manned-mission-moon/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA has doubled down on his promise to land humans on Mars in the 2030s – potentially as early as 2035. Space agency chief Jim Bridenstine made the bold claim, saying the advanced timeline is than…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke workers hospitalized; SC plant runs afoul -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/environment/article236495448.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-organic farming could increase emissions?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/organic-farming-could-increase-uk-emissions-study-153937551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An all-out shift to organic farming in England and Wales could lead to a net increase in Britain's greenhouse gas emissions as a drop in yields would lead to higher food imports, scientists estimated Tuesday. A team of researchers from Cranfield University found that direct emissions from farming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican denies risk of default over structural deficit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4203c1df6bd04b1b9fd410ee5747d9af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — A top Vatican administrator is denying the Holy See risks default over its structural deficit, saying claims in a new book about possible financial ruin are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete focus groups found gay a barrier for black voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article236518313.ece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal dog waits by roadside for years at exact spot where he lost owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/loyal-dog-waits-roadside-four-20673584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog jumped off from his owner's truck on a highway in Thailand and remained on the same spot until they were reunited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LYNCHING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7598245/Donald-Trump-calls-impeachment-push-lynching</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Democratic congressman erputed: 'You think this impeachment is a LYNCHING? What the hell is wrong with you?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  47 attorneys general are investigating FACEBOOK for antitrust violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/22/47-attorneys-general-are-investigating-facebook-for-antitrust-violations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The probe will zero in on whether Facebook broke any state or federal laws as a result of any anti-competitive conduct related to its dominance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power of online 'influencers' waning; Payments cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/social-media-influencer-marketing-1b7875c5-89f9-4fe1-938e-060ca4c8fb3c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend is driven by the obscurity around measurement and authenticity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM HALLOWEEN:  HILLARY LEAVES DOOR OPEN</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/lets-see-who-emerges-hillary-leaves-door-open-to-2020-run-sidesteps-praising-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Hillary Clinton’s latest campaign stop in Oregon, the former first lady again refused to endorse any of the current Democrats running in the 2020 presidential primary, but she did highlight her experience with impeachment and essentially described herself as the ideal candidate to take on Trump in 2020. Clinton and daughter Chelsea were at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican accuses conservative social media of fomenting hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-synod-amazon-hate/vatican-accuses-conservative-social-media-of-fomenting-hate-after-statues-dumped-idUSKBN1X11QB?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican on Tuesday accused ultra-conservative Catholic social media of fomen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tax returns fight speeds to Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/manhattan-d-trump-lawyers-strike-deal-speed-fight-over-trump-n1069751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight years of financial records are being sought in a criminal investigation into the Trump Organization about hush money payments made to two women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students arrested for ridiculing speech in viral video...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"obviously unconstitutional"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau wins 2nd term but Canada more divided...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db4ffb2f5d7d4a66b1ca371a902e7fbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Prime Minister Justin Trudeau won a second term in Canada's national elections, losing the majority but saying Tuesday he was given a clear mandate despite an increasingly divided...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Of Witches To Cast 'Binding Spell' On Trump...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/as-halloween-approaches-thousands-of-witches-will-cast-a-binding-spell-on-donald-trump-on-october-25th</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I know that the headline will sound very strange to a lot of my readers, but this is actually happening.  On October 25th at 11:59 PM, thousands of witches will simultaneously conduct a ritual which is meant to "bind" Donald Trump.  Unlike a "curse" or a "hex", a "binding spell" is not meant to caus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT: Boris warns of new election if bill nixed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/10186170/brexit-boris-johnson-battle-commons-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson has threatened to DITCH his Brexit Bill and will demand a Christmas election if he loses a crunch Commons clash with rebel MPs tonight. The future of Britain’s exit now hangs in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOACH: Superhero films 'cynical exercise' to make profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/oct/22/superhero-films-are-cynical-exercise-to-make-profits-for-corporations-ken-loach </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director joins Martin Scorsese and Frances Ford Coppola in censuring industry, calling superhero movies commodities ‘like hamburgers’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Threatening to Sue Everybody...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/with-impeachment-looming-trump-is-threatening-to-sue-everybody-who-pisses-him-off </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is reverting to his bad habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students say taxpayers should pay tuition...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/video-students-say-rich-people-and-taxpayers-should-pay-their-college-tuition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students don’t want the responsibility to pay their own tuition bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blob-like brains created in lab could have 'thoughts' and are 'suffering'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1194067/brain-medical-breakthrough-science-news-organoid-human-brain-function</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINIATURE brains which have been grown in the lab could have some form of consciousness and could be suffering as a result, scientists have worryingly claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worries grow over Fed efforts to fix funding issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/22/fed-repo-worries-continue-over-the-efforts-to-fix-funding-issues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The central bank has been working feverishly to address issues that popped up more than a month ago in the repo market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Clinton lawyer predicts at least one count of obstruction...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/466843-ex-clinton-lawyer-predicts-at-least-one-count-of-obstruction-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House counsel Greg Craig, who served as former President Clinton’s top legal advisor during his impeachment,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer monkeys found eating large rats, leaving scientists 'stunned'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10186366/monkeys-eating-rats-macaques/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREEDY killer monkeys were found to be catching and gobbling u large rats in Malaysia. Shocked scientists uncovered the rat-catching macaques on palm oil plantations – and say the hungry predators …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Pennsylvania factory layoff foreshadows Trump 2020 troubles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/economy/massive-pennsylvania-factory-layoff-foreshadows-trump-2020-troubles-n1069341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Management decisions that might have slid by in more flush times can now push a business over the edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Dem Establishment Asks, 'Is There Anybody Else?'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/anxious-democratic-establishment-asks-is-there-anybody-else/ar-AAJa37x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady setting up to move on from PATRIOTS?</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/patriots/2019/10/tom-brady-setting-up-to-move-on-from-new-england-patriots-says-adam-schefter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schefter discussed Brady's future before Monday's Patriots-Jets game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if delivery drone falls on head? Thorny legal questions loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-10-22/google-launched-drone-delivery-questions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google sibling Wing just launched commercial drone delivery in the U.S., and other companies are pursuing it. Questions about privacy, noise and liability still need to be answered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: WEALTHY, CELEBS AREN'T CHANGING FLYING HABITS TO REDUCE EMISSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/study-finds-the-wealthy-celebrities-arent-changing-their-flying-habits-to-reduce-co2-emissions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are responsible for a thousand times more CO2 emissions than the average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting killer robots in charge of life and death 'can never be undone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/campaign-stop-killer-robots-warns-20672181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Campaign to Stop Killer Robots has called for urgent action to stop killer robots before it is too late</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos BLUE ORIGIN teams with aerospace giants to build human lunar lander...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/22/bezos-blue-origin-will-work-on-lunar-lander-with-lockheed-northrop-draper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos, the founder of Amazon and space venture Blue Origin, spoke at the 70th International Astronautical Congress on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Shark tears woman's hands off during whale-watching trip...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/shark-tears-frenchwomans-hands-off-121415138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFrench tourist has lost both her hands in a rare shark attack in the Pacific islands of Polynesia, say emergency services.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
