<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NJ Proposal to Use Civil Forfeiture to Fund Diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3abyv3/civil-forfeiture-police-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey lawmakers have proposed a bill to use seized cash and other assets as funding to recruit, hire, and train minority cops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Legendary' paratroopers obliterated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17964713/russia-paratroopers-slaughtered-ukraine-putin-bungled-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s elite paratroopers have faced massacre on the battlefield amid Russia’s bungled invasion of Ukraine, experts have claimed. The tyrant unleashed his “legendaryR…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napping Too Much Linked To Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/03/17/napping-dementia-linked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Napping too much in the day as you get older could be a worrying warning sign of dementia, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan spots 4 Russian amphibious warships sailing West...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10623699/Japan-spots-four-Russian-warships-carrying-combat-vehicles-heading-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia could be sending reinforcements to Ukraine, Japan's defense ministry said after spotting four amphibious warships in the Tsugaru Strait (pictured). Russia has lost thousands of vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Africa president blames NATO...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/article-701534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shelling in Kyiv kills one as residential building hit • Nine soldiers handed over for Melitopol mayor • Theater allegedly hit in Mariupol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 4th shot offers little protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/article-701520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interim results released show that the vaccine offers little to no protection against the virus when compared to three doses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Surprised By Senate Passing Permanent Daylight Saving Time. Especially Senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/paulmcleod/daylight-saving-time-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inspiring story about how presumptuous Senate staffers can accidentally make history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion has stalled on ALL fronts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-military-intelligence-says-russias-070355358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine has largely stalled on all fronts, with Russian forces suffering heavy losses and making minimal progress on land, sea or air in recent days, British military intelligence said on Thursday. "Ukrainian resistance remains staunch and well-coordinated," The Ministry of Defence said. "The vast majority of Ukrainian territory, including all major cities, remains in Ukrainian hands."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow:  Will put USA in its place!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-put-enemies-united-states-074753510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -Russia warned the United States on Thursday that Moscow had the might to put the world's pre-eminent superpower in its place and accused the West of stoking a wild Russophobic plot to tear Russia apart. Dmitry Medvedev, who served as president from 2008 to 2012 and is now deputy secretary of Russia's Security Council, said the United States had stoked "disgusting" Russophobia in an attempt to force Russia to its knees. "It will not work - Russia has the might to put all of our brash enemies in their place," Medvedev said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK:  MAN ON MARS IN 7 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4915972/elon-musk-mars-humans-manned-mission-date/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk expects to see another giant leap for mankind not just in this lifetime, but in this decade. The SpaceX CEO tweeted that he predicts humans will touch down on the Mars in 2029.  The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: For Best Sleep, Be In Bed By 9:39 PM..</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/best-sleep-bedtime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a quarter of those who regularly have “bad” sleep find themselves wide awake at least five times a night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why would so few Americans defend their country?</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/why-are-so-few-americans-willing-to-defend-their-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many of us war voyeurs watching the news with a glass of sherry, admiration of the little-engine-that-could Ukrainian fighters is underwritten by unease. As families escape to safety, plenty of feisty Ukrainians are remaining behind to battle a far more powerful aggressor, and they’re not all me...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As abortion pills take off, some states move to curb them...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/03/16/as-abortion-pills-take-off-some-states-move-to-curb-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in more than 20 states want to restrict or ban access to medication abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violin becomes 'weapon of resistance' in shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.infobae.com/en/2022/03/17/the-violin-weapon-of-resistance-of-ukrainian-musicians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infobae.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The violin, “weapon of resistance” of Ukrainian musicians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger invokes Nazi father in emotional message...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/arnold-schwarzenegger-russia-ukraine-1235113643/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't want you to be broken like my father," the actor and former California governor said in part in a nine-minute address, attempting to punch through Russian state propaganda, in which he recalled his dad's failings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin arrests military chief for leaking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-army-general-arrested-leaking-26492398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Roman Gavrilov, the deputy chief of Russia's Federal National Guard, has reportedly been detained by the much-feared FSB security service and accused of leaking information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS OFF!! Heathrow, UK airlines drop mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-60757887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK's largest airport joins British Airways and Virgin Atlantic in easing mask-wearing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real estate sharks attempt to sell condo for $13M profit after one month!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/real-estate-sharks-try-to-flip-florida-condo-for-13m-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Florida triplex penthouse that sold at auction in February for $20.55 million is being flipped for $33.91 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's Scholz under fire after Zelensky's fierce appeal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-scholz-under-fire-zelenskys-155319097.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Thursday called on Germany to help destroy a new "Wall" Russia was erecting in Europe, as he appealed directly to Chancellor Olaf Scholz to bolster his tentative response to the invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt sites facing unprecedented cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russian-govt-sites-facing-unprecedented-072520127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian government entities and state-owned companies have been targeted over events in Ukraine, with the websites of the Kremlin, flagship carrier Aeroflot and major lender Sberbank among those to have seen outages or temporary access issues in recent weeks. The ministry was working to adjust to the new conditions, it said, as cyber attacks ratchet up. As Russia becomes increasingly isolated from global financial systems and supply chains, the government has proposed a raft of measures to support the IT sector, among others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid surge in western Europe has USA bracing for another wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-covid-surge-in-western-europe-has-us-bracing-for-another-wave/ar-AAV8kgb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyacht stuck in Norway because no one will sell it fuel...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/russian-oligarchs-superyacht-stuck-because-no-one-will-sell-it-fuel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian oligarch's superyacht is currently stuck at a dock in Norway because no one is willing to sell it any fuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers shooting themselves to get off frontline...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-soldiers-shooting-themselves-avoid-26493353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian troops are so demoralised that they're said to be looking for Ukrainian ammunition in order to shoot themselves in the legs, while others are reportedly fleeing into the woods</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside propaganda bubble: Where war isn't war...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Inside-Russia-s-propaganda-bubble-Where-a-war-17008839.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIGA, Latvia - Fake U.S. biowarfare labs. Fake killer birds. Tucker Carlson and Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA NEWS SERVICE COMES FOR DRUDGE...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/DPRK_News/status/1504359743745404928?s=20&amp;t=ijmMxdyugTxpfQRby6cgGA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond payment  in limbo as countdown to default begins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-payment-confusion-starts-countdown-074403900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia’s Finance Ministry said that it has sent payment orders for the interest on its dollar bonds to its correspondent bank, giving incremental details on a debt settlement that has come to exemplify how Moscow plans to handle its future relations with creditors. Most Read from BloombergPutin Vows to Rid Russia of ‘Traitors’ While Waging Ukraine WarRichest Russian Built NYC Power Over Decades and Lost It in WeeksUkraine Update: U.S. House Set to Revoke Russia’s Trade StatusU.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WNBA star's arrest extended to May 19 by Russian court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brittney-griner-russia-arrest-extended-d769f6dfe03a3b55f23ef24960dae787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Moscow court announced it has extended the arrest of WNBA star Brittney Griner until May 19, according to the Russian state news agency Tass. Griner was detained at a Moscow airport in February after Russian authorities said a search of her luggage revealed vape cartridges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Predictions: Will 'DOG' reign supreme?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-oscars-predictions-1d95a10f6b9385ff2c1acbb5158d5f20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of the 94th Academy Awards, Associated Press Film Writers Lindsey Bahr and Jake Coyle share their predictions for a ceremony with much still up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico Prepare for New Migrant Wave as Inflation Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberglinea.com/2022/03/17/us-mexico-prepare-for-new-migrant-wave-as-inflation-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberglinea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials from the administrations of Presidents Joe Biden and Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador in recent days discussed their concern about the impact that rising food and energy prices will have on the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS WARN 'WE'LL RISE AGAINST YOU'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10622821/Russian-soldiers-warn-Putin-RISE-against-terror-acts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three captured Russian air force pilots, warned President Vladimir Putin 'you will not hide this for long' because 'many' troops share the same feelings and 'sooner or later, we will come home'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt sites facing unprecedented cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-internet/russian-government-sites-facing-unprecedented-cyber-attacks-report-idUSKCN2LE0NB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian government websites are facing unprecedented cyber attacks and technical efforts are being made to filter foreign web traffic, the TASS news agency cited the digital ministry as saying on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans frantic to migrate as economy falters, new hurdles arise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-migrants/cubans-frantic-to-migrate-as-economy-falters-new-hurdles-arise-idUSKCN2LE15I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bray Perez, a 19-year-old Cuban university student, is fast losing friends to a growing wave of migration off the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN HAS 3 MOVES LEFT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-10622533/Russia-Ukraine-happens-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine has to sustain the ability of its forces to continue fighting effectively and counterattacking to regain lost territory if it is to hold out against the Russians, a military expert told MailOnline today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of most basic hotel amenities disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-travel-lifestyle-2bffd3573fb6bd7f33222e13605f4510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether out of necessity due to staffing shortages, out of respect for social distancing or perhaps just to save money, one of the primary amenities that sets a hotel apart from your home — daily housekeeping — is disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruined game plan visible in south...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/defence/russias-ruined-game-plan-for-ukraine-is-visible-in-the-south/articleshow/90291832.cms </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two in Israel hit with variant 'not yet known to world'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/17977307/two-people-israel-covid-variant-not-known-to-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO people in Israel have been struck with a new Covid variant described as “not yet known to the world” by experts. The novel strain caused mild symptoms of fever, headaches and muscle aches in th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With legislation languishing and midterms approaching, Dems pressure Biden to issue orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-legislation-languishing-and-midterms-approaching-democratic-lawmakers-pressure-biden-to-issue-executive-orders/ar-AAVbt2Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More humiliation as kidnapped mayor rescued...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-humiliated-mayor-kidnapped-russian-26489172</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has suffered another humiliating blow in his faltering Ukraine invasion after a city mayor who had allegedly been captured was rescued in a 'special operation'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How stronger hands lengthen life...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hand-grip-strength-falling-deaths-8dfd77a1-0561-41be-8359-12532af948ce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stronger hands prevent falls, and higher grip strength is linked to healthier hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA WARNS WILL PUT USA IN ITS PLACE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-will-put-its-enemies-such-united-states-their-place-medvedev-says-2022-03-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia warned the United States on Thursday that Moscow had the might to put the world's pre-eminent superpower in its place and accused the West of stoking a wild Russophobic plot to tear Russia apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer Documents Invasion of His Country...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6158001/ukraine-invasion-in-photos-kyiv-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Maxim Dondyuk, the story was always personal, but never more than over the past few weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Car Designers, EVs Offer Blank Canvas...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/17/for-car-designers-e-v-s-offer-a-blank-canvas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal combustion engine is exiting stage left. While it provided great transportation and performance thrills for many years, it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated and vulnerable, Hong Kong elderly taking own lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Isolated-and-vulnerable-amid-the-covid-crisis-17008347.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG - The three people who took their own lives on the same day last week in Hong...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifies 50 elites as targets for global hunt to seize assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-administration-identifies-50-russian-elites-as-targets-for-global-hunt-to-seize-assets/ar-AAV9jlu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineers hoping to perfect masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/engineers-are-hoping-to-perfect-masks-before-the-next-covid-wave-or-pandemic/ar-AAVahnG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep experts say Senate has it wrong: Standard time, not daylight saving, should be permanent!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sleep-experts-say-senate-has-it-wrong-standard-time-not-daylight-saving-should-be-permanent/ar-AAV9l4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indicator of economic hardship flashing red...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bond-traders-stunned-hawkish-fed-000428923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Defying their stock-market counterparts, Treasury traders aren’t buying Jerome Powell’s upbeat pronouncements on growth. In fact, in the aftermath of Wednesday’s policy decision, one bond-market indicator of economic hardship is flashing red for the first time since the darkest days of the pandemic.Most Read from BloombergPowerful Quake Off North Japan Kills 4, More Than 90 InjuredUkraine Update: Biden Offers Kyiv Weapons Including Armed DronesRichest Russian Built NYC Power Over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineers hoping to perfect masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/engineers-are-hoping-to-perfect-masks-before-the-next-covid-wave-or-pandemic/ar-AAVahnG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT ENOUGH TO DENT RUNAWAY INFLATION...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/16/the-fed-needs-to-get-a-lot-tougher-to-stop-soaring-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street loved the Federal Reserve’s quarter-point interest hike Wednesday, soaring 500 points on the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My life's at risk': Mexican journalists fear death every day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lifes-risk-mexican-journalists-fear-012904674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each time Maria Martinez leaves home, she fears it will be the last. Only her bodyguards prevent her from joining the eight journalists murdered already this year in Mexico, she believes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil hikes key interest rate ninth straight time, to 11.75%!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-hikes-key-interest-rate-221710071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's central bank raised its key interest rate for the ninth straight time Wednesday, as Latin America's biggest economy continues to reel from surging inflation, now exacerbated by the Ukraine war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN ISSUES NEW THREAT</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2022-03-16/a-war-of-one-putin-defends-brutal-campaign-in-ukraine-as-global-condemnation-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian leader attempted to justify his decision to begin a brutal and bloody assault on Ukraine while also expressing some recognition of the threats to his own grip on power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five people charged with acting as Chinese secret police to spy on, harass U.S. residents critical of Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/five-people-charged-with-acting-as-chinese-government-agents-to-spy-on-harass-us-residents-critical-of-beijing/ar-AAV8SVX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifies 50 elites as targets for global hunt to seize assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-administration-identifies-50-russian-elites-as-targets-for-global-hunt-to-seize-assets/ar-AAV9jlu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep experts say Senate has it wrong: Standard time, not daylight saving, should be permanent!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sleep-experts-say-senate-has-it-wrong-standard-time-not-daylight-saving-should-be-permanent/ar-AAV9l4d?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Black students sold in 'slave auction' at NC school...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/north-carolina-school-blasted-for-mock-slave-auction-of-black-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother was outraged after finding out that Black students were allegedly "sold" at a mock "slave auction" by their white classmates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First deepfake appears...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/hackers-zelensky-deepfake-surrender-ukraine-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deepfake video showing Ukrainian President Zelensky asking his soldiers to surrender has surfaced online amid Russia's ongoing invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/piers-morgan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Sales Soften as Gas Prices Bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/retail-sales-soften-high-gasoline-costs-begin-bite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growth in U.S. retail sales slowed in February after surging a month earlier, suggesting that consumers tempered their spending in some categories as inflation limited purchasing power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany record infections again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-reports-another-record-covid-074032735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany reported another record high seven-day incidence of the coronavirus on Wednesday even as the country prepares to ease restrictions. The Robert Koch Institute (RKI) registered 262,593 new infections, a 22% jump compared to a week ago, bringing the total number of infections to nearly 17.7 million. Infections have been rising again since the start of March after rules preventing unvaccinated people from accessing many indoor public spaces started to be eased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Smollett Released From Jail After Less Than Week...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/jussie-smollett-free-jail-appeal-judge-hate-crime-1234980729/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After less than a week behind bars on a 150-day sentence for faking a hate crime, Jussie Smollett will be walking out of the Cook County Jail today. A one-page order unceremoniously released by the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Schultz Back as STARBUCKS CEO as Thousands of Baristas Unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awp4b/howard-schultz-takes-over-as-starbucks-ceo-as-thousands-of-baristas-unionize</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We encourage Howard Schultz to put union-busting behind him and embrace Starbucks’ unionized future.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV comedy that launched Zelensky back on NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220316-tv-comedy-that-launched-zelensky-to-presidency-back-on-netflix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedy satire in which Volodymyr Zelensky unexpectedly becomes Ukraine's president -- his now war-time job in real life -- will be aired again on Netflix, the streaming platform announced Wednesd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Academic Grudge Turned Into #MeToo Panic...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/03/14/how-an-academic-grudge-turned-into-a-metoo-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the weaponization of sexual misconduct allegations wrecked Florian Jaeger's life and cost his university millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad's wild rant to 'scum' West...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/russia-ukraine-live-updates-vladimir-putins-wild-rant-to-scum-west/news-story/344c9ceac26156761f6c173a3a63c5dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been three weeks since Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered troops to invade Ukraine on February 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI to pay expenses for staff seeking abortion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citi-cover-travel-expenses-u-145324689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As states increasingly pass new abortion restrictions, Citigroup will now cover travel costs for U.S.-based employees seeking an abortion.Driving the news: "In response to changes in reproductive healthcare laws in certain states in the U.S., beginning in 2022 we provide travel benefits to facilitate access to adequate resources," Citi wrote in a filing for its shareholders' meetings set for next month. Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free.The policy will co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fully focused' Webb telescope beats expectations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-60771210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers align the mirrors of the $10bn observatory to produce a pin-sharp image of a star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Calls Putin 'War Criminal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/16/politics/biden-calls-putin-a-war-criminal/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden called Russian President Vladimir Putin a "war criminal" on Wednesday as Russia intensifies its attack on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Gov. Considers Running Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/former-ny-gov-andrew-cuomo-considers-running-against-kathy-hochul-despite-opposition-from-party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo is speaking with allies about possibly running against New York Gov. Kathy Hochul. Democratic Party officials scoff at the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South American burglary gang filmed EMPTYING luxury California homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10619547/Spate-home-burglaries-California-linked-criminal-tourists-target-rich.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are blaming a spate of home burglaries in California on South American 'crime tourists' who target wealthy neighborhoods for their robberies before returning home with the loot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willingness to sacrifice growth to stop inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/feds-aggressive-interest-rate-forecast-signals-willingness-to-sacrifice-growth-to-stop-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonds sold off and stocks seesawed in volatile trading after the Fed released a forecast for a slightly more aggressive series of rate hikes than expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV discusses invasion plan for seizing Baltic states...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17965158/russian-state-tv-discusses-invasion-seizing-baltic-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN state TV has aired a discussion on seizing the Baltic states as Nato bolster Eastern European allies with thousands more troops. A former senior officer laid out a chilling scenario for Put…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire engulfs Indianapolis WALMART distribution center... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/massive-fire-engulfs-walmart-distribution-center-near-indianapolis/7XIQLI6TIREHVMDNIUV46GAXNU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive fire at the Walmart distribution center northwest of Indianapolis is sending a large plume of smoke into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How cigarette tin launched zoo's 50-year love affair with pandas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-chinese-cigarette-tin-launched-dc-e2-80-99s-50-year-love-affair-with-pandas/ar-AAV8dBx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater where hundreds had taken refuge bombed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/16/europe/ukraine-mariupol-bombing-theater-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A theater where hundreds of people are said to have taken shelter in the besieged Ukrainian city of Mariupol was mostly reduced to rubble on Wednesday, according to an image shared by its city council.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
