<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Woman, baby fall in storm drain when grate gives way...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95a6855f29c84ceeb2b56a7b5cd6d3f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLARKSVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Police in Tennessee say a woman and her baby fell 20 feet (6 meters) into a storm drain and were underground for more than 30 minutes. Clarksville police tell news outlets the two were rescued Thursday night. Police spokesman Jim Knoll says the woman was walking through a parking lot carrying her baby when the storm grate she went across collapsed. Police say a passerby heard the baby crying, but couldn't see them and called 911.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foie gras off AMAZON's Calif. offerings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2cd08e9298434f56816d01b5c781576f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California prosecutors say Amazon has agreed not to sell foie gras in the state from birds that have been force-fed. State lawmakers banned that form of the fatty duck and goose liver delicacy nearly 15 years ago. Los Angeles County District Attorney Jackie Lacey said Friday a state judge approved a settlement between the online retailer, her office and district attorneys in Monterey and Santa Clara counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Sergeant In CA Bar Shooting Killed By Friendly Fire...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/12/07/sergeant-killed-in-borderline-shooting-struck-by-friendly-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities reported Friday that the Ventura County Sheriff's sergeant killed during the mass shooting at the Borderline Bar &amp; Grill last month was struck and killed by friendly fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron remains invisible...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3b7d4a322df34823b448dabd46e2e03a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — As anti-government protests rage through France and Paris locks down, fearing new riots, the man whose presidency has unleashed the anger is nowhere to be seen. French President Emmanuel Macron has stayed out of the public eye all week, leaving his unpopular government to try to calm the nation. In response, "Macron, resign!" has become the main slogan of the "yellow vest" demonstrators. The protesters' anger has been directed at the French leader, who they feel has been the "president of the rich" and is out-of-touch with ordinary people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapists go on strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/12/07/kaiser-permanente-strike-mental-health-workers-california-therapists/2225472002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 4,000 mental health workers at Kaiser Permanente are striking in California Monday to demand better access to care for their patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Post Office STOPS Accepting Packages As Holidays Hit Full Swing...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/06/park-west-post-office-no-packages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS2's Ali Bauman headed to the post office to get some answers. That's when things took a strange turn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Significant' announcement expected in CA bar shooting... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7156af6b5be84f939f672dda8dedf4c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSAND OAKS, Calif. (AP) — Authorities planned Friday to announce what they call a "significant development" in their investigation of last month's shooting that killed 12 people at a popular Southern California country music bar. The development was to be announced at a news conference at the Ventura County Sheriff's Station in Thousand Oaks, Detective Eric Buschow told The Associated Press. He declined to elaborate. Investigators have previously said they don't know why 28-year-old Ian David Long stormed into the Borderliine Bar &amp;amp; Grill in Thousand Oaks on Nov. 7 as people were dancing to country music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens Of Barred Owls Rescued After Getting Hit By Cars...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/06/barred-owls-hit-by-cars-rescued-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owls are being nursed back to health at the Tufts Wildlife Clinic in Grafton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Snow, floods to blanket South...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/storm-to-sweep-through-southern-us-with-flooding-severe-weather-into-sunday/70006811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican investigates after nuns report priest sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d7fa7a4afc040ae9b987425fc49a7c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican has launched an investigation into a small Chilean religious order of nuns after some sisters denounced sexual abuse at the hands of priests and mistreatment by their superiors, a turning point that shows the Holy See is now willing to investigate allegations of sexual violence against nuns. The scandal at the Institute of the Good Samaritan was revealed publicly in an investigative report by Chilean national television earlier this year at the height of outrage over how Chilean Catholic hierarchy covered up decades of sexual abuse of children by priests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman tapped to lead Merkel's ruling party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46474381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German politician takes over from Angela Merkel as the leader of the Christian Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7922892/paris-riots-latest-tourist-attractions-closed-france-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRENCH protesters will be faced with military “machine gun” vehicles as they try to are set to “smash and kill” their way across Paris this weekend. Major tourist attraction…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODBATH:  At least 12 dead in Brazil bank robbery shootout...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6471761/Eleven-people-killed-Brazilian-bank-raid-bloodbath.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The violence erupted in the city of Milagres, in the northeastern state of Ceara, with a fierce pre-dawn shootout between the armed robbers and the police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE WALL ST PLUNGE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/07/stock-market-dow-futures-fall-ahead-of-unemployment-figures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped sharply on Friday, concluding what has been a wild week for Wall Street. A weaker-than-expected jobs report and China-U.S. trade tensions sent the Dow Jones Industrial Average lower by 400 points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Entrepreneurs Who Flocked to China Are Heading Home, Disillusioned...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-entrepreneurs-who-flocked-to-china-are-heading-home-disillusioned-1544197068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worsening costs, taxation, tech transfer and regulation prompt foreign-owned businesses in China to throw in the towel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rappers Kendrick Lamar, Drake lead Grammy award nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/grammys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billboard Magazine's latest news, predictions, video and photos from the Grammy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOV JOBS: +155K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/07/us-created-155000-jobs-in-november-vs-198000-expected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls increased by 155,000 in November. Economists surveyed by Dow Jones had been expecting payroll growth of 198,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Goes Off On Mueller Hours Before New Bombshells...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-attacks-mueller-team-conflicts-of-interest-as-manafort-cohen-filings-loom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imminent filings in Manafort and Cohen’s cases, plus the former FBI director’s upcoming congressional testimony, apparently put the president on edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEF OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6471487/White-House-Chief-Staff-John-Kelly-expected-RESIGN-soon-Trump-stopped-speaking-him.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources told DailyMail.com that Kelly, a decorated Marine Corps general brought in last year, is 'expected' to leave the White House before the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors blame tap water in neti pot for brain-eating amoeba...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/rare-brain-eating-amoebas-kill-seattle-woman-leave-doctors-bracing-for-possible-repeats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers said the amoebas likely got into the woman's brain through the tap water she used to fill a neti pot, rather than using saline or sterile water. The organisms entered her brain after she squirted the water up into her upper nasal cavity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viggo Mortensen ready to go behind camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181207-viggo-mortensen-ready-go-behind-camera</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viggo Mortensen ready to go behind camera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepping counter report...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-has-87-pages-and-counting-in-report-to-counter-muellers-conclusions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and his lawyers are preparing a report to counter special counsel Robert Mueller's findings in his investigation into Trump's alleged collusion with Russia, and already has dozens of pages at the ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA's illegal mind-control experiments exposed in secret files...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7920010/cia-mkultra-mind-control-drugs-hypnosis-electric-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTURBING details of secret mind-control experiments carried out by the CIA have been revealed in newly released documents – that officials have been trying to hide for decades.  The new doc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tillerson unloads...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/420221-tillerson-trump-would-ask-me-to-do-things-that-i-couldnt-legally-do</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson says he often had to push back on President Trump, telling him that some of his requests would violate the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory Implantation of Microchips in Employees?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/kevin-mccandless/mandatory-implantation-microchips-employees-uk-govt-says-it-would</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds like the stuff of eschatological literature, but the idea of companies forcibly implanting their employees with microchips is making waves in Britain – although the government says it doubts the practice would be legal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece 'like war zone' with police brutality riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7924330/greece-riots-athens-police-brutality-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIOTERS torched cars and hurled flares at cops to mark the tenth anniversary of a ‘police brutality’ killing. Hundreds of demonstrators marched through Athens in tribute to 15-year-old …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE NAP:  Why I don't believe it's fishing expedition...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/judge-andrew-napolitano-why-i-dont-believe-that-mueller-is-on-a-fishing-expedition-or-is-about-to-go-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am not of the view that Mueller is on a fishing expedition or is about to go home. First, he has a few dozen defendants whom he has indicted and needs to try -- even though most are Russians indicted for hacking and interfering with the 2016 election campaign and will be tried in absentia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to reveal secrets in Cohen, Manafort filings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/mueller-to-release-new-details-on-ex-trump-aides-manafort-cohen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, federal prosecutors in New York will be filing a sentencing memo detailing Cohen's  cooperation after his guilty plea in their separate case against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High intrigue surrounds Mueller filing in Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/420107-high-intrigue-surrounds-mueller-filing-in-manafort-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday is expected to file a bombshell report that describes how former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort eviscerated his plea agreement with federal prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP set to grill Comey...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/420160-house-gop-set-to-grill-comey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are poised to grill former FBI Director James Comey on Friday in what could be the final act in a dramatic effort to probe allegations of bias at the Justice Department before Democrats take over the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift snubbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/07/grammys-2019-taylor-swifts-reputation-snubbed-for-album-of-the-year-because-of-american-music-awards-appearance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grammy nominations are out. And Taylor Swift, previously a Grammy favorite, has been snubbed. I predicted this when Swift appeared on the American Music Awards and performed from her “Reputat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar king of GRAMMYS with eight noms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/entertainment/entertainment-news/Kendrick-Lamar-Leads-Grammy-Noms-Where-Women-Make-a-Comeback-502158311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music of 'Black Panther,' with Kendrick Lamar in its starring role, officially owns the 2019 Grammy Awards, where women are heavily represented in the major four categories following a year where their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE BRACES FOR RIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-macron/france-braces-for-trouble-macron-to-address-yellow-vest-anger-idUSKBN1O60I8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France hunkered down for another wave of potentially violent protests on Saturda...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Fatigue Killing Any Movie, Show With Political Edge?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-fatigue-killing-movie-show-political-murphy-brown-front-runner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's risky, especially since the real unfolding drama on cable is more compelling," political reporter and documentarian Jonathan Alter says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Latin America, Awash in Crime, Citizens Impose Their Own Brutal Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-a-continent-awash-in-crime-citizens-impose-their-own-brutal-justice-1544110959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America has the world’s highest murder rate. With little faith in the police or courts, mobs routinely kill suspected lawbreakers in spontaneous attacks. Many lynching victims are innocent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic 'object' spotted towering over Earth from ISS; NASA live feed CUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/746841/NASA-conspiracy-alien-news-iss-international-space-station-blue-object-cut-live-feed-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI CONFUSION: America has three coasts -- 'North, South and West'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/pelosi-confusion-america-has-three-coasts-north-south-and-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy? The next Speaker of the House struggled with U.S. geography on Thursday as she once again announced her opposition to a wall along the border with Mexico. ﻿ “We, most of us, speaking for myself, consider the wall immoral, ineffective and expensive, and the President said – he promised – he also promised Mexico …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most modified youth: 40 ops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7921478/worlds-most-modified-youth-operations-split-tongue-eye-tattoos-belly-button-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A YOUNG Australian man who went through more than 40 body modification procedures claims to be “the world’s most modified youth”. Ethan Bramble from Melbourne has had a string of body modifications…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coup?</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/445836-france-radicals-weapons-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As France braces for a new wave of protests, a government spokesman warned that radicals are using the Yellow Vest movement to pursue their own goals and one of them is to topple the current leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye-Scanning Lie Detector...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-05/blade-runner-eye-scanning-lie-detector-may-be-coming-dystopian-future-near-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.9 billion people now using Internet...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/more-half-global-population-now-115946999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 3.9 billion people are now using the Internet, meaning that for the first time more than half of the global population is online, the United Nations said Friday. The UN agency for information and communication technologies, ITU, said that by the end of 2018 a full 51.2 percent of people around</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot skills will make surgeons out of nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/robot-skills-will-make-surgeons-out-of-nurses-gds3t0tw3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caesareans and other routine operations will be done by nurses as the rise of robots means common procedures do not need a hands-on surgeon, according to an expert review. Nanorobots will fix the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man posed as doctor, gave meds to unsuspecting patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.postcrescent.com/story/news/crime/2018/12/05/appleton-man-charged-posing-doctor-held-200-k-bond/2216983002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postcrescent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using the pseudonym "Doctor Kyle Ellis,"Â a man posing as a doctor treated patients and gave them medications, a criminal complaint states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rages in Anti-Mueller Tweetstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-rages-in-anti-muelller-tweetstorm-big-time-conflicts-of-interest-and-destroyed-peoples-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over mass teen roundup...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/outcry-over-mass-teen-roundup-france-braces-more-090606857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images of dozens of high-school pupils kneeling with their hands behind their heads during mass round-ups sparked an outcry Friday as France braces for more violence at "yellow vest" protests this weekend. Leftwing politicians have expressed outrage at the videos, which have gone viral on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/frances-macron-astride-the-globe-overlooked-swelling-anger-at-home-1544178601 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron has tended to respond to outrage over high fuel taxes with lectures rather than sympathy. After the weekend’s violence, he had to back down, postponing a tax increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest known wild bird to become mother 37th time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/07/worlds-oldest-bird-lays-egg-wisdom-albatross </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisdom, a 68-year-old Laysan albatross, has laid another egg with her longtime lover at the Midway Atoll national wildlife refuge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little town that pot built...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2018/12/04/the-little-town-that-pot-built</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like horror film'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Like-a-horror-film-The-efforts-to-contain-13449195.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya - The medical anthropologist was in the shower when she heard the first pops of gunfire. Initially, she thought it might be the action movie she'd left playing on high volume. Then the wall shook. The violence in eastern Congo, which has stymied the international response to a growing Ebola outbreak in the region, had arrived at the guesthouse used by many of those working to prevent the disease's spread. Terrified, Julienne Anoko dropped to the floor and crawled into the corridor outside her room. She and five others from U.N. agencies, Congo's health ministry and the World Health Organization, which she works for, hid in another bathroom for three hours until a U.N. peacekeeping force arrived and gave the all-clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola spreads to major city...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/86fd89fa73594ed0aa098c6c5a063300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — The second-largest Ebola outbreak in history has spread to a major city in eastern Congo, as health experts worry whether the stock of an experimental vaccine will stand up to the demands of an epidemic with no end in sight. Butembo, with more than 1 million residents, is now reporting cases of the deadly hemorrhagic fever. That complicates Ebola containment work already challenged by rebel attacks elsewhere that have made tracking the virus almost impossible in some isolated villages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  HOST CHRIS ROCK SHOCK: ONLY GAYS WATCH OSCARS...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A33625-2005Feb17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/07/kevin-hart-steps-down-from-oscar-host-job-after-scandal-about-homophobic-tweets-reaches-peak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart has just Tweeted: “I have made the choice to step down from hosting this year’s Oscar’s….this is because I do not want to be a distraction on a night that should …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Flies Plane Over Ukraine in Warning to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-military-plane-flies-over-ukraine-in-warning-to-russia-1544136754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon said it carried out a rare flight over Ukraine under the international Open Skies Treaty to “reaffirm U.S. commitment to Ukraine” amid heightened Russia-Ukraine tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Making President's Bed, A Housekeeper Without Papers... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/making-president-trump%E2%80%99s-bed-a-housekeeper-without-papers/ar-BBQAYz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm tired of being humiliated and treated like a stupid person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-housekeeper-new-jersey-golf-club-immigration-20181206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman working as a housekeeper at President Trump's golf club in Bedminster, New Jersey revealed that she is an unauthorized immigrant in a NYT interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation-hit Chernobyl wolves 'spreading mutant genes across Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911846/the-european-grey-wolf-population-has-boomed-at-the-site-since-the-human-population-moved-out-and-it-became-a-virtual-wildlife-preserve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS fear wolves living in Chernobyl’s radioactive forbidden zone may be spreading mutant genes across Europe. The European grey wolf population has boomed at the site since the human p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President lawyers, Special Counsel in talks following written submission...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-lawyers-special-counsel-discussions-following-written-submission-president-s-n945061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s lawyers have resumed discussions with the office of special counsel Robert Mueller in recent days, the first time that's been acknowledged since President Donald Trump submitted written responses to questions regarding the possibility of collusion between his 2016 campaign and Russia, two people familiar with the matter told NBC News on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOPES Fact-Checker Botches Fact Check...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/06/snopes-facebook-google-fact-check/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is quite literally insane fake news'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Legal 'proctological examination' hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/roger-stone-gripes-about-legal-proctological-examination-this-has-been-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR DRAMA: HOST HOMOPHOBIA HEADACHE</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-harts-past-anti-gay-tweets-creates-problem-academy-1167191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next Oscars host faces a backlash over hundreds of homophobic jokes. Said Billy Eichner: "There's real truth, anger &amp; fear behind these."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They're All Too Old': Dems Face Generational Reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/democrats-face-a-generational-reckoning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The choice in the 2020 primary ultimately comes down to one thing: who is best prepared to beat Trump at a time when Trump owns the culture? Someone who actually understands culture would be a start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers who ingested Mexican cartel cash profits busted...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-colombia-crime/smugglers-ingested-mexican-cartel-cash-say-colombia-police-after-arrests-idUSKBN1O600D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombia has arrested 27 people accused of belonging to four smuggling networks ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Heather Nauert Next UN Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-07/trump-to-pick-heather-nauert-as-next-un-ambassador-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep in mind, I'm not homophobic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/kevin-hart-deletes-old-anti-gay-tweets-after-landing-oscar-hosting-gig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart has been busy scrubbing his Twitter account of his old anti-gay tweets since he was tapped as Oscar host earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gig in jeopardy?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/should-the-oscars-fire-host-kevin-hart-over-his-homophobic-jokes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past homophobic and anti-gay jokes and tweets the comedian made, including calling someone’s picture a “gay billboard for AIDS” have resurfaced. Are they a fireable offense?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Hart Scrambles to Delete Anti-Gay Tweets After Being Named OSCARS Host...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/michaelblackmon/kevin-hart-homophobic-tweets-gay-oscars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a since-deleted tweet, Hart joked that he would break a dollhouse over his son’s head if he were caught playing with the toy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador: Enough UK guarantees for Assange to leave embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0b95cddbe0614d47b71c07c827710210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Ecuador's president has ramped up pressure on Julian Assange to leave his country's embassy in London, saying that Britain had provided sufficient guarantees that the WikiLeaks founder won't be extradited to face the death penalty abroad. Lenin Moreno's comments in a radio interview Thursday suggest that months of quiet diplomacy between the U.K. and Ecuador to resolve Assange's situation is bearing fruit at a time when questions are swirling about the former Australian hacker's legal fate in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doorstop vigilantes fight porch pirates with booby traps, dog poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/porch-pirates-are-trying-to-steal-christmas-but-doorstep-vigilantes-are-on-high-alert/2018/12/06/cbf694ea-f966-11e8-8c9a-860ce2a8148f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans fight back with booby traps, hidden cameras and even dog poop against the scourge of online commerce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Ready for 'Inevitable' Clampdown on Tech, Media?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/12/06/are-you-ready-for-the-clampdown-on-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Apple's CEO Tim Cook says "the free market is not working," bad things are coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham lied to discredit alleged rape victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ct-life-stevens-thursday-how-not-to-apologize-lena-dunham-1206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Girls" actress and director should be better at apologizing by now, but her Hollywood Reporter note to Aurora Perrineau is little more than terrible performance art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns embezzle $500,000 from school to gamble, take trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.presstelegram.com/2018/12/05/nuns-improperly-took-as-much-as-500000-from-torrance-catholic-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.presstelegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were an ATM and people know it and they won’t ask for justice,” one parent said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sits on victim naked, bashes with brass plate...</title>
      <link>https://www.komu.com/news/columbia-woman-arrested-for-domestic-assault-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.komu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested Amy Parrino after an incident in northeast Columbia on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman chases, beats man who refused to perform oral sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.columbiatribune.com/news/20181204/columbia-woman-charged-with-sex-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbiatribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Columbia woman is accused of attempting to force a man to perform oral sex on her.Boone County prosecutors on Monday charged 43-year-old Amy Nicole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC election fraud probe shines light on 'ballot harvesting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/north-carolina/north-carolina-race-shines-light-on-ballot-harvesting/884597359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) - An investigation into whether political operatives in North Carolina illegally collected and possibly stole absentee ballots in a still-undecided congressional race has drawn attention to a widespread but little-known political tool called ballot harvesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firms in China vulnerable after HUAWEI arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/us-firms-in-china-vulnerable-after-huawei-arrest-ex-us-trade-advisor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a good chance the Chinese will retaliate for the arrest of Huawei CFO Meng Wanzhou by targeting American businesses in China, says former assistant U.S. trade representative Jeff Moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE AirDrop Assaults On Rise As Criminals 'Cyber Flash' Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/airdrop-assaults-on-the-rise-as-criminals-cyber-flash-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As technology infiltrates every aspect of our lives criminals and creeps are figuring out creative ways to abuse it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ride from Hell': Carpooling in Age of UBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ride-from-hell-carpooling-in-the-age-of-uber-can-beawkward-1544112559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shared ride services become more popular, passengers clash over music, temperature and talking. Exasperated drivers try to referee; ‘They had no shame.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIATCHRYSLER to open new Detroit factory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/fiat-chrysler-reportedly-plans-to-open-new-assembly-factory-in-detroit-to-build-suv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSKINS QB facing 'devastating complications' after surgery...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/12/06/reports-alex-smith-dealing-with-post-op-infection-in-leg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington quarterback Alex Smith’s recovery from the broken tibia and fibula he suffered last month is reportedly being complicated by an infection. Eric Bickel of 106.7 The Fan reports that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDNY Chief removed over 'inappropriate behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/06/fdny-chief-james-leonard-removed-from-post-over-inappropriate-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDNY’s top uniformed member was removed from his post Thursday amid a probe into his alleged mistreatment of the department’s highest-ranking woman, the FDNY and sources said. Chief of Departme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece plans crowdfunding for new warships...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1845b762915c4de7bb71d6568fb73d51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece's defense minister is appealing to his austerity-battered countryfolk for a crowdfunding effort to raise money for new warships, promising to donate part of his own salary. Panos Kammenos says he will open a bank account on Jan. 1 where members of the public can make donations "for new frigates and a flagship." He addressed his appeal to Greece's wealthy shipowning industry, as well as ordinary Greeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>89,000 security forces deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-security/france-to-deploy-89000-security-personnel-ahead-of-saturday-protests-idUSKBN1O52BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe said 89,000 members of the security force...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Conversion Exorcisms on the Rise in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/islamic-exorcisms-aim-to-cast-out-lgbt-demons-in-worlds-largest-muslim-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's even a TV show...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
