<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside Justin Bieber's VIP, Sex Joke-Filled Celebrity Megachurch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-churchome-justin-biebers-vip-and-sex-joke-filled-celebrity-megachurch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We venture inside the Beverly Hills house of worship, where the Biebers and Kardashians take in sermons by the charismatic Pastor Judah Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Stents no better than drugs for many heart patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-heart-stent/stents-no-better-than-drugs-for-many-heart-patients-u-s-study-idUSKBN1XQ0MR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many patients with severe but stable heart disease who routinely undergo invasiv...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Saudi Arabia, TWITTER becomes more useful to repressors than the repressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/opinion/article/In-Saudi-Arabia-Twitter-becomes-more-useful-to-14840969.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This editorial appears in The Washington Post:  - - -  Omar Abdulaziz is only one person, but his story offers a way to better understand 9.9 million more. That's the number of Saudis on Twitter, a platform that has been at the center of Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's efforts to stamp out dissent and promote the misleading story that it's doing just the opposite.  Abdulaziz wrote in The Post this week that more than 30 Saudi citizens influential on the social media site told him they were blackmailed with material gained from hacking their phones - just as Abdulaziz's own phone was breached using spyware sold by the Israeli company NSO Group. These efforts were payback not only for speaking out against the regime generally but also for speaking out against the regime on Twitter in particular. Of the three most influential Saudis on Twitter, Abdulaziz wrote, one has been arrested, a second has disappeared, and he is in exile.  The ultimate aim of the blackmail Abdulaziz identifies was focused on the platform once again. The targets were ordered to tweet propaganda, or else the government would release their private communications and pictures. Complying would align them with the virtual army assembled by Saud al-Qahtani, the former royal court adviser known by activists as the "minister of flies." Abdulaziz had been amassing a counterforce called the "electronic bees" with the aid of Post contributing columnist Jamal Khashoggi. Khashoggi, when he learned regime officials had discovered their attempt, wrote to Abdulaziz: "God help us." He was murdered by the regime two months later.  Twitter is popular among Saudis as a public square because protesting in a physical public square has rarely been an option. Abdulaziz's experience first of "living democratically" online and then watching that democracy get strangled -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Say Ditching Smartphones For Week Changed Their Lives...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/students-ditch-phone-changed-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They survived! Nearly two dozen Adelphi University students made it a full week without their cell phones!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM GOV WINS</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/elections/article_2b7c0b7c-08a5-11ea-bcfe-1bd7f6b19e9d.html?1573962442332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Gov. John Bel Edwards will win a second term as Louisiana governor, defeating his Republican opponent Eddie Rispone, WWL is projecting tonight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President cast Louisiana vote as impeachment referendum...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-casts-louisiana-vote-as-impeachment-referendum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will it be enough?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUISIANA RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://voterportal.sos.la.gov/static/2019-11-16/resultsRace/Statewide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;voterportal.sos.la.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUISIANA RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2019/11/16/20963502/louisiana-election-results-live-edwards-rispone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lone Democratic governor in the Deep South is trying to hang onto his seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Denver Radio Host Fired Midshow After Criticizing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/conservative-denver-radio-host-fired-midshow-after-criticizing-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Denver radio station 710 KNUS fired host Craig Silverman during his broadcast Saturday after he criticized Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick holds his own workout, and NFL calls him a no-show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/sports/former-nfl-quarterback-colin-kaepernick-doing-workout-least-11-teams-n1084171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaepernick's former teammate, Eric Reid, expressed concern that the NFL arranged the workout primarily for publicity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 teams watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28095462/colin-kaepernick-throws-passes-40-minutes-workout-urges-nfl-stop-running</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick completed his workout for what his agent said were eight NFL teams at an Atlanta-area high school on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  MAYOR PETE POPS TO 9-POINT LEAD IN IOWA... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/16/politics/iowa-poll-cnn-pete-buttigieg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a new Democratic front-runner in Iowa, and his name is Pete Buttigieg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDSOR WILD!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/16/prince-andrew-says-he-couldnt-sweat-in-attempt-to-debunk-epstein-accusers-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive BBC interview, Prince Andrew delivered a tense, sometimes bizarre denial of ever bedding his pal Jeffrey Epstein’s sex slaves — claiming his royal disdain for hugging, and his body’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN TEAM TRUMP FLIP LA?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ecad2990a83b4d84af821ba6cbdb7d91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — In a race that has become a nail-biter, Louisiana Gov. John Bel Edwards battled Saturday to defy the partisan odds in the ruby red South and win reelection to a seat that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Shooting Leaves 5 Dead, Including 3 Children... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/Multiple-People-Injured-in-Shooting-in-Paradise-Hills-SDPD-565039022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people are injured in a shooting that occurred in Paradise Hills, said San Diego Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate in UK elections poses in S&amp;M leather and whip for TV ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10359922/uk-general-election-canterbury-liberal-democrat-candidate-claire-malcomson-sm-gear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAST minute candidate for the Lib Dems in a marginal seat has previously featured in an S&amp;M-style television ad, complete with a whip, suspenders and stockings. Claire Malcomson was parachute…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARLIE'S ANGELS' Crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/16/box-office-kristen-stewart-updated-charlies-angels-a-total-loss-with-3-1-mil-friday-including-thursday-previews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bosley must be turning in his grave. Columbia Pictures’ latest installment of “Charlie’s Angels” is a total write off at the box office. Last night the Kristen Stewart versi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a CIA analyst triggered an impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-a-cia-analyst-alarmed-by-trumps-shadow-foreign-policy-triggered-an-impeachment-inquiry/ar-BBWRhvT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of 5G weapons system on streets... after conspiracist takes apart light...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/fears-5g-weapons-system-uk-20893384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conspiracist deconstructed a light he claims a council worker whistleblower sent him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Progress in Audit Undercut by Worsening Shortfalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/pentagon-progress-in-new-audit-undercut-by-worsening-shortfalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon Progress in New Audit Undercut by Worsening Shortfalls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Protesters March to Revive Flagging Anti-Maduro Revolt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-protesters-march-revive-flagging-170505718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Supporters of Juan Guaido protested in Caracas in their first major showing in months as Venezuela’s opposition leader seeks to revive his campaign to oust President Nicolas Maduro.A week after Maduro’s ally Evo Morales was toppled in Bolivia, Guaido is seeking to boost thinning crowds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'FORD V FERRARI' Speeds to No. 1...'</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/charlies-angels-bombs-at-box-office-reasons-why-1202787938/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Terminator: Dark Fate’s failure at the B.O., and Paramount’s recent decision to make Beverly Cops 4 for Netflix, we have the further breakdown of cinema IP in Sony’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters head to polls in critical Louisiana gubernatorial race...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191009103328-6x21o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/LOUISIANA (PIX):Louisiana's Democratic governor fights for re-election in Republican-leaning state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR BASHES THE LEFT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7692719/Bill-Barr-says-Left-sabotaging-President-waging-scorched-earth-war-resistance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr, the nation's top prosecutor, made the remarks in a speech to conservative lawyers who gathered in Washington, DC, on Friday for a conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'FORD V FERRARI' Speeds to No. 1; 'CHARLIE'S ANGELS' Crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ford-v-ferrari-speeds-to-no-1-while-charlies-angels-crashes-at-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox's Le Mans biopic on pace for $30 million opening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: LIL PEEP Documentary Beautifully Stirring...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/everybodys-everything-remembering-lil-peep-the-young-anxious-emo-rapper-who-might-have-changed-music</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beautifully stirring new documentary about Lil Peep’s short life borrows its title from his last social media post: “I don’t want help but I need help,” he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers continue to struggle despite 'strong' jobs reports...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/470769-americas-workers-continue-to-struggle-despite-strong-jobs-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The priority should be to restore wealth-generating industries, like manufacturing, that can spur middle-class job growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Flooding Expected to Worsen Sunday With Rising Sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/st-marks-closed-fresh-flood-hits-venice-143012063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice was on alert for more floods and fierce winds on Saturday after an exceptionally high tide swamped the city of canals, where authorities have declared a state of emergency. Mayor Luigi Brugnaro ordered the iconic St Mark's Square closed on Friday as the latest sea surge struck with strong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAP BACK?</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/sports/will-colin-kaepernick-make-his-nfl-comeback/5701473/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three years after playing his last NFL game, Colin Kaepernick is looking to make a comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood, Texas: Kanye Takes Osteen to Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.texasmonthly.com/the-culture/hollywood-texas-kanye-west-takes-joel-osteen-to-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texasmonthly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget Staffer Could Shed Light On Inquiry Enigmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/16/779934386/omb-staffer-could-shed-light-on-impeachment-inquiry-enigmas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Closed-door testimony from the only White House staffer cooperating with the probe could provide first-hand knowledge about details that remain hazy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timing raises questions of NFL intentions...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/news/story/timing-colin-kaepernicks-workout-raises-questions-nfls-intentions-67018301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is holding a workout for Colin Kaepernick, but many believe it's nothing more than a public relations stunt. PR, sports and social justice experts weigh in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans at war with apes as villagers take revenge butchering baby-eating chimps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/humans-war-apes-villagers-take-20876196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The powerful primates are losing their fear of humans as settlements expand – with devastating and deadly results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans receiving more than 2,000 robocalls -- every second...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/16/robocalls-hit-record-numbers-as-carriers-and-lawmakers-fight-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans received a record 5.66 billion robocalls last month, prompting carriers, lawmakers and start-ups to boost efforts to block calls and catch scammers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Flooding Expected to Worsen Sunday With Rising Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/venice-flooding-is-expected-to-worsen-on-sunday-with-rising-sea-1.1348999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice is headed for its second exceptionally high tide in a week, with water levels forecast to rise 160 centimeters (63 inches) above their benchmark, the Ansa news agency reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE: Germany's Greens re-elect leadership duo after electoral wins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-greens-elect-leadership-duo-electoral-wins-144813218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's Greens on Saturday re-elected the two people leading their party after strong performances in regional and European elections. The 800 delegates gathered for their annual congress at Bielefeld, western Germany, voted overwhelming to keep Annalena Baerbock and Robert Habeck in place --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE: This is mission, not show...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/entertainment/kanye-west-visits-harris-county-jail-ahead-of-sundays-lakewood-appearance/285-a8df8545-a5bb-4bd6-8470-9f3e56e788a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rap superstar Kanye West made a surprise appearance at the Harris County Jail on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man survives croc attack by gouging its eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191116-australian-man-survives-croc-attack-by-gouging-its-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian man survives croc attack by gouging its eye</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis Flameout Rivals Dot-Com Bust as Legal Fears Curb Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-16/cannabis-flameout-rivals-dot-com-bust-as-legal-fears-curb-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Will.I.Am Accuses QANTAS Of Racial Profiling...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/will-i-am-racist-flight-attendant-qantas-twitter-090339669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline have denied that the incident had "anything to do with race" after the musician was met by police when the plane landed in Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters head to polls in critical Louisiana gubernatorial race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/470767-voters-head-to-the-polls-in-critical-louisiana-gubernatorial-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters are heading to the polls Saturday to vote in Louisiana’s crucial gubernatorial race as both Democrats and Republicans go all in to push their candidate over the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These trans bodybuilders can kick your ass...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/15/these-transgender-bodybuilders-can-kick-your-ass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They aim for the same goal as any other bodybuilder: to be strong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helmet swing is latest violent incident in sports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52ee599532fd4a8398e3467d7c4ca07b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence is part of the game in many sports but Myles Garrett crossed a line that attracts the attention of authorities sometimes from within their sport and in other cases from criminal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Crossed Antarctica Alone. Now He Plans to Row There...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/16/sports/antarctica-drake-passage-obrady.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin O’Brady ended up winning an unintended race across the frozen continent last year. He wants to go back in a boat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana gov race latest test of Trump clout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/louisiana-governor-race-2019-democrat-john-bel-edwards-race-against-republican-eddie-rispone-test-trumps-clout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, the final governor's race of the year is the next test of how much Trump's clout can lift a candidate. In Kentucky, the GOP candidate lost, but in Mississippi, the Republican won</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Wilde stolen ring found by 'art detective'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscar-wildes-stolen-ring-found-dutch-art-detective-091403182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A golden ring once given as a present by the famed Irish writer Oscar Wilde has been recovered by a Dutch "art detective" nearly 20 years after it was stolen from Britain's Oxford University. The friendship ring, a joint gift from Wilde to a fellow student in 1876, was taken during a burglary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Erupt in Iran After Gasoline-Price Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-dead-protests-erupt-iran-111419958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- At least one person was killed as protests erupted in Iran after the government unexpectedly raised gasoline prices, the semi-official Iranian Student’s News Agency reported.The fatality occurred during clashes in Sirjan in the southern province of Kerman on Friday, ISNA reported, citing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian rockets, Israeli airstrikes jolt tenuous Gaza truce...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191116062750-04ec5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/VIOLENCE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Palestinian rockets, Israeli airstrikes jolt tenuous Gaza truce</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
