<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Dutch girls who seduced Nazis -- and lured them to deaths...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/14/meet-the-dutch-girls-who-seduced-nazis-and-lured-them-to-their-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When she came across a Nazi killing an infant by repeatedly swinging its tiny body against a brick wall, Truus Oversteegen didn’t flinch. The freckle-faced teenager, who was just three months shy o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Jones Says 'Fired' From Show For 'Wrong Message For Black America'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/orlando-jones-fired-american-gods-racism-gabrielle-union-fremantle-starz-neil-gaiman-1202809444/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tumultuous run of American Gods looks to have taken another turn, with Orlando Jones declaring he has been fired from the Starz series for having “the wrong message for black America.” In a vid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid adversity and missteps, Biden resilience has been one theme of '19...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amid-adversity-and-missteps-Joe-Biden-s-14906746.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the year, former vice president Joe Biden has often been described in negative terms. It has been said he is not as sharp as he should be or once was; that he is well liked but can't excite the base of the new Democratic Party; that his agenda is little more than "return to normalcy" and that his fundraising problems belie bigger weaknesses.  All of that is well and good, but he nears the end of 2019 also as a candidate who has absorbed more criticism than just about everyone else in the Democratic field combined, and he has survived the attacks reasonably well. He remains atop the national polls, his support among African Americans has proved durable through the year, and while his numbers have slipped in Iowa and New Hampshire, he is nonetheless in the battle in those two early-voting states.  The story of Biden for most of the year has been written as a glass-half-empty narrative. What about the opposite way of viewing where he stands? I recently asked a Democrat who has been involved in several presidential races this question: What if Biden were to win the Iowa caucuses? His answer: "He could run the table."  This Democrat was not predicting it; nor was he ruling it out. But if Iowa falls into Biden's column, it would instantly change the way everyone looks at the 2020 field and the potential outcomes.  This has happened before. In December 2003, then-Sen. John Kerry, D-Mass., the perceived early front-runner, was in all kinds of trouble. He was running behind in Iowa and New Hampshire and was down in the polls nationally. His campaign had been through a staff shake-up that left supporters lacking in confidence. He seemed to be floundering.  Even some of Kerry's closest advisers were saying privately, just weeks before Iowa, that Howard Dean was the likeliest person to win that state and to become the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops refused service at California STARBUCKS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/riverside-county-deputies-allegedly-refused-service-at-starbucks/5754060/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is apologizing after two uniformed Riverside County deputies were allegedly refused service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is trap being set for president in Senate trial?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/474242-is-a-trap-being-set-for-trump-in-the-senate-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House may be seriously underestimating the resentment against the president by a number of Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble to rack up accomplishments gives conservatives heartburn...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/474550-trump-scramble-to-rack-up-accomplishments-gives-conservatives-heartburn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s race to rack up accomplishments heading into an election year is giving conservatives heartburn, with some worried he is striking deals that include giveaways to Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans Consider 'Living Off Grid' To Keep Data Safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/digital-deception-9-in-10-americans-have-been-victimized-by-an-online-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey finds that 90% of Americans have been a victim of an online scam, fraud, data breach, identity theft, or social media hacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RICHARD JEWELL' could mark one of worst openings of Clint Eastwood career...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-jumanji-next-level-nabs-47m-thursday-previews-1262508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Richard Jewell' could mark one of worst nationwide openings of Clint Eastwood's directing career and the lowest in two decades. 'Black Christmas' is also getting scrooged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover deepest point on land...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/14/us/deepest-point-on-land-scntrnd-/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study shows that the deepest point on land is under the Denman Glacier in East Antarctica. Glaciologists at the University of California, Irvine, were mapping the area only to find that the trough under the glacier went far deeper than they had imagined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G 'can spy on you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/5g-can-spy-you-critic-21083745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vocal 5G critic who makes Youtube videos describing the technology as "weapons" has claimed it can be misused to listen and watch people in their own homes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN climate talks unraveling, face failure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-climate-talks-unraveling-face-failure-110423955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UN climate summit in Madrid risked collapsing Saturday after all-night negotiations between countries left them more divided than ever over on how to fight global warming and pay for its ravages. Diplomats from rich nations, emerging giants and the world's poorest countries -- each for their own</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas mayhem feared as French transport strike continues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/christmas-mayhem-feared-french-transport-strike-continues-143133316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France reeled under a crippling public transport strike for a 10th day Saturday aimed at forcing the government to scrap a pension revamp, as fears grew of travel mayhem during Christmas. Train traffic was severely disrupted with only one out four high speed long-distance trains and three of 10 regional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reparations Mark New Front for Colleges Tied to Slavery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f390bd047c87a71d372e38ffbf477ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The promise of reparations to atone for historical ties to slavery has opened new territory in a reckoning at U.S. colleges, which until now have responded with monuments,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Was One of Mexico's Deadliest Assassins. Then He Turned on Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-was-one-of-mexicos-deadliest-assassins-then-he-turned-on-his-cartel/ar-AAK7nnX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PATRIOTS Season of Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://postofasia.com/the-patriots-season-of-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;postofasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots are 10-3. They at present maintain the No. 2 seed within the A.F.C. In all chance — a 76 p.c probability, in accordance with The New York Occasions’s playoff simulator — they are going to earn a first-round bye for the 10th consecutive postseason. And but an uneasy feeling has settled …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts another test at long-range rocket site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a65ce1c9102331e8e0036be11cb4d872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Saturday that it successfully performed another “crucial test” at its long-range rocket launch site that will further strengthen its nuclear deterrent....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST ACTOR?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791443/Harvey-Weinstein-MeToo-monster-looked-bit-broken-man.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM LEONARD: Shirt collar askew, ill-fitting suit and grey face a picture of misery and forbearance, Harvey Weinstein shuffled into a Manhattan court this week hunched over a walking frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's not fair!' </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791387/Trump-whines-impeachment-says-unjust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It's not fair that I'm being Impeached when I've done absolutely nothing wrong! The Radical Left, Do Nothing Democrats have become the Party of Hate. They are so bad for our Country!' Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church investigated over claims pastors pushed members into 'selling their blood to raise funds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7790197/Charity-Commission-investigates-Spac-Nation-Church-Bling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charity Commission has opened an inquiry into SPAC Nation after allegations emerged that pastors had told worshipppers to take out loans and even sell their blood to raise money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT WEEK*</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/hidden-by-impeachment-one-of-trumps-best-weeks-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the media and his critics focused on the bitterly divided House impeachment hearings, President Trump this week collected the most agenda wins yet, policy victories, including some backed by Democrats, that bolster arguments he’s making for reelection, according to advisers and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA high schools to open sexual and mental health clinics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/13/los-angeles-high-school-planned-parenthood-sexual-mental-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partnership between officials and Planned Parenthood will offer birth control, STI testing and care for anxiety and depression</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction of Navy ship 'Harvey Milk' begins in San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2019-12-13/construction-of-navy-ship-harvey-milk-kicks-off-with-ceremony-at-san-diego-shipbuilder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future USNS Harvey Milk, being built by General Dynamics NASSCO, has value and symbolism beyond its deckplates, advocates say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sets Off Furor... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/matt-bevin-ousted-in-kentucky-sets-off-furor-with-extreme-pardons/ar-AAK705V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept Investigates Experiments on People With Disabilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/health/2019/12/11/federal-justice-investigation-sexual-arousal-studies-glenwood-patient-disabilities/4401890002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Rea, the Glenwood Resource Center's superintendent, is on paid leave amid a DOJ investigation into potential federal rights violations at the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791533/Megyn-Kelly-breaks-silence-Bombshell-Watching-movie-incredibly-emotional-experience.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News anchor Megyn Kelly took to Instagram to post a photo of her son, Thatcher, at a movie theater, looking at a Bombshell poster, which featured Charlize Theron made up to look like Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans mayor declares state of emergency after cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/new-orleans-reports-cyberattacks-after-other-attacks-in-louisiana.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a series of widespread cyberattacks in Louisiana, which led to two statewide emergency declarations this year, New Orleans was hit on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom charged with leaving son at hospital draws sympathy...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/mom-charged-with-leaving-son-atlanta-hospital-draws-sympathy/U1dTc2HHQm2eiHGRjq0gII/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diana Elliott stands accused of abandoning her mute 14-year-old son, who police say has Down Syndrome, at Grady Memorial Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outgoing Kentucky governor pardons a man convicted of beheading  woman and stuffing her in  barrel...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/news/world/outgoing-kentucky-governor-pardons-man-convicted-of-beheading-a-woman-stuffing-her-in-a-barrel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEXINGTON, Ky. — It’s not clear if Betty Carnes was killed by asphyxiation or by the eight blows to her head that Delmar Partin delivered with a metal pipe. The coroner couldn’t tell which killed the mother of three first, but it was very clear that her head was then</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Cent and Russell Simmons bash Oprah over #MeToo documentary...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/13/50-cent-and-russell-simmons-bash-oprah-over-metoo-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media mogul’s forthcoming #MeToo documentary is already sparking controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington pulled apart by partisan divide over 'facts'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/washington-pulled-apart-partisan-divide-over-facts-015743807.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Washington these days, there are facts, alternative facts and disputed facts. The acrimonious impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump have put the spotlight on the stark partisan split in the nation's capital over where the truth lies. "There's always been a divide between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tepid reception...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-china-trade-deal-gets-tepid-reception-015910263--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials announced a truce in the trade war with China with much fanfare, but economists and trade experts call it largely a victory for Beijing. After a dispute that raged for close to two years, with several fumbled efforts at a resolution, the US agreed to cancel planned tariffs and rollback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubts Surface on $50 Billion in Farm Buys...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/doubts-surface-50-billion-china-205327779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump says China will spend $50 billion a year for U.S. farm products as part of a “phase one” trade deal between the countries. But doubts are surfacing whether that’s even possible, bolstered by China’s reluctance to confirm the figure.While the president expressed confidence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tightens info control after leaks on prison camps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1d08873154907be8a3dd93562d6785c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police chief admits anonymously trolling critic on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95e4cc24311eabad66df0cb4166b0fa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. (AP) — The police chief in Vermont's largest city used an anonymous Twitter account to troll a government critic, he admitted this week. Burlington Police Chief Brandon del...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How US-China trade deal achieved a little but left out a lot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/415cc91f3bb305ddb08620c53eea2d58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The limited trade deal that the Trump administration and Beijing announced Friday means Americans will avoid a holiday tax increase on imported toys, clothing and smartphones....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHADOW GOVT:  BLACKWATER Erik Prince held secret talks with top Venezuelan official...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191213191513-biyza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ERIKPRINCE (PIX):Blackwater founder Erik Prince held secret talks with top Venezuelan official -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES WILL HEAR TRUMP CASES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6bdd9fa291f4523ce0ef823775fba19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Friday it will hear President Donald Trump's pleas to keep his tax, bank and financial records private, a major confrontation between the president and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL SHOWDOWN  2020...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191213210422-l182n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TRUMP-RECORDS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. Supreme Court takes up Trump bid to shield financial records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt's strongman extends crackdown to new foe: Soap operas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/egypt-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By buying up TV channels, creating a tough new censor and banning edgy content, Sisi has gained an even tighter grip on Egypt than his predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Way Out, Kentucky Gov Pardons Murderers, Rapists, Hundreds More...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/12/13/787811560/on-his-way-out-kentucky-gov-matt-bevin-pardons-murderers-rapists-hundreds-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one case that has drawn particular attention, he pardoned a murderer whose family raised big money to pay off Bevin's campaign debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Cent accuses Oprah of only 'going after black men' in #MeToo cases
...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/ct-ent-50-cent-oprah-black-men-comment-20191213-6uw3iigmfzh7zea3p24jtvryya-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper 50 Cent targeted Oprah Winfrey in an Instagram post, accusing the beloved TV host and super-producer of singling out black men, such as Michael Jackson and Russell Simmons, in her #MeToo activism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL SHOWDOWN  2020</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/supreme-court-agrees-hear-trump-appeals-subpoena-fights-over-financial-n1101901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By granting review of these cases now, the justices made it possible for them to be heard during the current court term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic data on military suicide shows no clear link with combat operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2019/12/13/historic-data-on-military-suicide-shows-no-clear-link-with-combat-operations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study tracks Army suicide from the 1840s until today and finds a decrease in rates of self-harm during war time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How fake accounts went viral -- with help of YOUTUBE algorithms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/13/tech/youtube-fake-accounts-viral/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube channels posing as American news outlets racked up millions of views on false and inflammatory videos over several months this year, all with the help of YouTube's recommendation engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES WILL HEAR TRUMP CASES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/supreme-court-will-hear-three-cases-over-trumps-financial-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court said on Friday that it will hear three cases over President Donald Trump's financial records next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow War With NKorea Likely To Intensify...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-administrations-shadow-war-with-north-korea-likely-to-intensify-in-coming-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of the year, a trio of events in the North are likely to threaten President Trump's hopes for progress in U.S.-North Korea relations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Pursues Mystery Buyer of Iranian Nuke Materials...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-pursues-mystery-buyer-of-contested-iranian-nuclear-materials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is considering sanctions to prevent Tehran from exporting materials that could power an atomic weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters march on Downing Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-election-protests/not-my-prime-minister-protesters-march-in-london-against-johnson-idUSKBN1YH28F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several hundred noisy protesters marched through central London on Friday to pro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden's wife pregnant right after former girlfriend gives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7789433/Hunter-Bidens-new-South-African-wife-pregnant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Biden's new wife Melissa Cohen Biden, 32, is pregnant and in her second trimester, DailyMailTV can reveal. She was seen grabbing groceries in LA on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much entertainment 'stressing' people out...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/883299/anxious-press-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have more entertainment options than ever before. That's stressing a lot of people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshman who led charge now unsure how she'll vote...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/archives/allahpundit/2019/12/13/freshman-dem-led-impeachment-charge-let-get-back-next-week-im-going-vote-okay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians arrive in waves at Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06c09bc61c3cbd4432d1dfe751e90914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas (AP) — Growing up along the U.S.-Mexico border, hotel clerk Joe Luis Rubio never thought he'd be trying to communicate in Portuguese on a daily basis. But with hundreds of...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
