<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Govt charging $2,000 a seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/national-security-daily/2021/08/19/exclusive-bidens-iran-envoy-calls-nuclear-deals-fate-one-big-question-mark-494049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Close, Artist of Outsized Reality, Dies at 81...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/19/arts/design/chuck-close-artist-of-outsized-reality-dies-at-81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He found success with his large-scale Photorealist portraits, becoming one of the leading artists of his generation. Late in life he faced allegations of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If ICU runs out of beds, doctors can consider patient's vax status...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/watchdog/2021/08/19/if-north-texas-runs-out-of-icu-hospital-beds-doctors-can-consider-a-patients-vaccination-status/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Watchdog reveals a worst-case scenario plan devised by area doctors. In the event of no ICU beds available, vaccination status could be used as part of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bar Association To Mandate Diversity Training, Affirmative Action at Law Schools...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/campus/american-bar-association-poised-to-mandate-diversity-training-affirmative-action-at-law-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Bar Association is poised to mandate diversity training and affirmative action at all of its accredited law schools, a move top legal scholars say could jeopardize academic freedom and force schools to violate federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planes, guns, night-vision goggles: The new U.S.-made war chest...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/planes-guns-night-vision-goggles-talibans-new-us-made-war-chest-2021-08-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a month ago, Afghanistan's ministry of defense posted on social media photographs of seven brand new helicopters arriving in Kabul delivered by the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists blast push for boosters: Data NOT compelling...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/19/covid-booster-shots-scientists-blast-us-move-as-premature.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While data suggests there is a reduction in protection against mild and moderate disease, the shots still held up well against severe disease, scientists said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt charging $2,000 a seat...</title>
      <link>chttps://www.politico.com/newsletters/national-security-daily/2021/08/19/exclusive-bidens-iran-envoy-calls-nuclear-deals-fate-one-big-question-mark-494049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing set to join 'graveyard of empires'?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/18/china-set-join-graveyard-empires-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has reaped the benefits of costly American military and security efforts in Afghanistan but now faces a hostile Islamic regime near its western border, according to David Stilwell, former assistant secretary of state for East Asia and Pacific affairs, who adds that the Biden administration should not help Beijing deal with its problems there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder's ex-fiancee said he brandished gun at her...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/19/elders-ex-fiancee-said-he-brandished-a-gun-at-her-506286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandra Datig, who broke off her engagement with the California gubernatorial candidate in 2015, describes a series of troubling encounters with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect rants: 'Revolution is on. South is coming for you Joe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3503174/us-capitol-lock-down-bomb-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect who shut down the US Capitol on Thursday has surrendered to police after unleashing an anti-Biden rant on Facebook live and posing with his finger on the button of a device. Floyd …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEGOTIATIONS LIVESTREAMED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/capitol-police-investigate-bomb-threat-near-library-of-congress/ar-AANvfmn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A man who claimed to have a bomb in a pickup outside the Library of Congress surrendered to the police on Thursday, after hours of negotiations and evacuations of several government buildings in the area. The man surrendered peacefully, Chief J. Thomas Manger of the Capitol Police said at a news conference. “As far as we can tell it was just his decision to surrender,” he said. Chief Manger identified the man as Floyd Ray Roseberry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTS LEAVING HALF-EMPTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/policy/2021/08/more-seats-passengers-paperwork-taliban-slow-afghanistan-evacuation/184689/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the pace is picking up. Some 6,000 "will soon board planes," a State Department spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US CAPITOL BOMB THREAT SUSPECT IN CUSTODY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/19/us-capitol-police-respond-to-report-of-suspicious-vehicle-near-library-of-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floyd Ray Roseberry addressed President Joe Biden on a Facebook vide after telling police he had a bomb in a truck next to the Library of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran Paraplegic Skydiver Survives Accident After Parachute Gets Stuck In Wheelchair...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/19/michael-vasquez-paraplegic-skydiver-survives-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He survived a hit from a rocket propelled grenade while serving the U.S. armed forces in 2009, now veteran Michael Vasquez has beat the odds again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears Under Investigation For Striking Employee At Her Home...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/08/19/britney-spears-under-investigation-for-striking-employee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer is under investigation over an allegation that she hit an employee during a dispute at her home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS to Ban Sex Workers Who Made It Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ewk4/report-onlyfans-plans-to-ban-sexually-explicit-content</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company said it will start banning "sexually explicit content" in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-officials scramble for distance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-officials-scramble-for-distance-from-his-taliban-deal/ar-AANvywb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most Republicans focus blame on President Biden, some former Trump officials are pointing to the deal that Biden's predecessor signed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE senators positive -- despite being dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/19/sen-roger-wicker-who-is-fully-vaccinated-tests-positive-for-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens. Roger Wicker and Angus King, who are both vaccinated for the coronavirus, tested positive for Covid-19 on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS to Block Sexually Explicit Videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-19/onlyfans-to-block-sexually-explicit-videos-starting-in-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OnlyFans is getting out of the pornography business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis to vote on replacing police dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/19/minneapolis-police-public-safety-department-november-election/8149356002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minneapolis voters will soon decide if the city should replace its police with a public safety department that would include officers "if necessary."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Times Square evacuated after bicyclist tosses suspicious container...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/portion-of-times-square-evacuated-after-suspicious-container-tossed-at-red-steps/3230607/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A portion of Times Square was evacuated Thursday afternoon after something was thrown toward people sitting on the “red steps” in Father Duffy Square, but police gave the all-clear around 1 p.m. Law enforcement sources say a man riding bicycle threw what may be a cookie tin toward people sitting on the steps, prompting them to flee. Police checked out…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATE NIGHT SHAKEUP:  Gutfeld Tops Colbert in Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/gutfeld-ratings-win-colbert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' 11 p.m. ET "Gutfeld!" finally beat every other late-night show -- including Stephen Colbert's "Late Show" on CBS -- Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat-rich diet of 14th-century monks caused digestive issues, research finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2021/aug/19/meat-rich-diet-of-13th-century-monks-caused-digestive-issues-research-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Change in papal law in 1336 to allow twice-weekly consumption caused problems at Muchelney Abbey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg into the METAVERSE!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebook-launches-horizon-workrooms-virtual-reality-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg revealed the new virtual reality app in an exclusive interview with "CBS This Morning" co-host Gayle King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Begs Mob Of Teens For Mercy During Brutal Attack in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/08/18/woman-beaten-in-downtown-chicago-describes-pain-horror/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was begging for her attackers to stop, but they just kept swinging – punching her in the face. Days after the Chicago woman was thrown to the ground by a group of teen assailants downtown, she talked only to CBS 2’s Jermont Terry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg into the METAVERSE!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3502098/facebook-oculus-workroom-vr-virtual-reality-mark-zuckerberg-metaverse/&lt;B&gt;&lt;/B&gt;</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK has created a virtual reality OFFICE where you can meet up with colleagues, talk about work and even doodle on a whiteboard together. I tried out the mind-blowing beginnings of Mark Zucker…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Adult Has Only 13 Pain-Free Days -- Each Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pain-free-days-painkillers-nerve-injury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American says they only have 13 truly pain-free days every year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET FBI WARNING: CHINESE AND RUSSIAN EMPLOYEES COULD BE SPIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/fbi-delta-protocol-economic-espionage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s the insider threat the FBI has been discreetly briefing VC firms and startups about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CLAIM:  PFIZER 86% effective after THIRD shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/pfizer-covid-vaccine-86-percent-effective-after-third-shot-maccabi-677053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data was based on a follow-up study carried out by the fund’s Division of Data &amp; Digital Health of people who received their third dose at least seven days ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX satellites responsible for over HALF of close encounters in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9908743/Elon-Musks-SpaceX-Starlink-satellites-responsible-HALF-close-encounters-orbit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With hundreds of Starlink satellites in orbit, the number of dangerous approaches will continue to grow, according to a study by the University of Southampton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35 missing in North Carolina flooding...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article253570019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roads and bridges are washed out in the Canton area of Haywood County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO MUSICAL HEADED OFF-B'WAY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/legit/news/andrew-cuomo-musical-off-broadway-1235044522/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2010, Hank Morris, a big-time political consultant and powerbroker, pleaded guilty to involvement in a pension fraud pay-to-play scandal. Andrew Cuomo, who was then serving as New York’s a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION: NYT and WSJ clash on vaccine effectiveness...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/coronavirus/1003912/us-covid-19-breakthrough-infections-are-uncommon-rising-considerably-and-sort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaze burns across Sierra Nevada first time in recorded history...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/568541-wildfire-burns-across-sierra-nevada-for-first-time-in-recorded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildfire has burned across the Sierra Nevada mountain range for the first time in recorded history, according to a leading California official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAREFACE BATTLE IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/as-delta-surges-in-florida-gov-ron-de-santis-is-focused-on-battling-biden-090028999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and President Biden are feuding over how to properly respond to the new COVID surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI SCHOOLS DEFY DESANTIS</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/18/miami-dade-school-issue-mask-mandate-defy-desantis-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami-Dade County School Board has voted to implement a mask mandate for the start of the 2021-2022 school year, defying an order from Gov. Ron DeSantis that states the decision must be left up to parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Minnesota imposes restrictions as drought worsens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-droughts-467825350c91c106a34884f033e52519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The drought in Minnesota continues to get worse, exposing rocks, riverbeds and islands in the St. Croix and Minnesota river drying up entire channels in the mighty Mississippi. The Minnesota Department of Natural Resources has imposed water restrictions for much of the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nobody can get to airport'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9907573/Afghanistan-evacuation-Chaos-continues-Kabul-airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westerners and visa holders trying to flee Afghanistan cannot get into Kabul airport today because of 'huge crowds' of 'terrified locals' who are blocking the entrances, MailOnline has been told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups call on APPLE to drop plans to scan children's messages...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/568517-policy-rights-groups-call-on-apple-to-drop-plans-to-scan-childrens-messages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coalition of 90 groups around the world are calling on Apple to drop its plans to scan its products to detect images of child sexual abuse stored in iCloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handcuffed by Trump deal in Doha?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-taliban-doha-e6f48507848aef2ee849154604aa11be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After President Donald Trump signed a peace deal with the Taliban in February 2020, he optimistically proclaimed that “we think we’ll be successful in the end.” His secretary of state, Mike Pompeo, asserted that the administration was “seizing the best opportunity for peace in a generation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming Colo. town asks, 'Where will water come from?'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-census-2020-climate-change-a10d1a7ee50dd53ec6727a23ca6252e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREELEY, Colo. (AP) — "Go West, young man,'' Horace Greeley famously urged. The problem for the northern Colorado town that bears the 19th-century newspaper editor's name: Too many people have heeded his advice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bets war-weary America will reward for leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/joe-biden-bets-war-weary-america-will-reward-him-leaving-n1277104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's hard to see Republicans winning elections on a campaign promise to go back to war in Afghanistan in 2022 or 2024," says a Democratic consultant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden threatens legal action on masks in schools as feud with DeSantis intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article253591774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Wednesday said his administration is prepared to take possible legal action against governors who try to prevent local school officials from imposing universal mask mandates, throwing yet another wrench into Gov. Ron DeSantis’ plans to sanction Florida school districts that require students to wear masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcyclist Struck By Hit-And-Run Driver, Robbed While Unconscious...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/08/18/motorcyclist-hit-and-run-robbery-minneapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twin Cities motorcyclist involved in a hit-and-run needs help to find the other driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500,000 in fines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/faa-calls-for-more-than-24500000-in-fines-against-dozens-of-disruptive-airline-passengers/ar-AANuVhl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration said it was proposing more than $500,000 in fines against 34 airline passengers accused of disrupting flights. The new fines bring the total the agency has sought to impose this year to more than $1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK pushes VR for remote work but practicality, cost, nausea may stand in way...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Facebook-pushes-VR-for-remote-work-but-16397384.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook believes it has developed a tool for the future of work: a virtual reality app...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: 401(k) balances new all-time high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/19/401k-balances-hit-a-new-all-time-high-fidelity-says-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boosted by the market’s recent run-up, the number of 401(k) and IRA millionaires are at record highs, according to Fidelity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star salaries revealed; Daniel Craig tops at $100M!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/biggest-movie-star-salaries-daniel-craig-dwayne-johnson-1235043305/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago, Hollywood stars knew their place on the A-list was secure when their film topped the box office. Today, success can be measured by views on Netflix or a vague press release touting a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter, trounced in 1980, gets fresh look from history...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-middle-east-jimmy-carter-18eab7024282910f6aab29026a1e04e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Jimmy Carter is sometimes called a better former president than he was president. Nodding to Carter's decades of work as a globe-trotting humanitarian but with a glaring reminder of his landslide defeat in 1980, the backhanded compliment rankles Carter allies and, they say, the former president himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Two-thirds Americans say war not worth fighting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-asia-pacific-afghanistan-only-on-ap-503a50cd8074ced7bc36d9c12e9fd2e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A significant majority of Americans doubt that the war in Afghanistan was worthwhile, even as the United States is more divided over President Joe Biden's handling of foreign policy and national security, according to a poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vow to ban heroin, but can they survive without it?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-taliban-vow-to-ban-heroin-but-can-they-survive-without-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban vow to ban heroin, but can they survive without it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped in no-man's land...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-desperate-afghans-trapped-in-kabul-airport-no-man-s-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate Afghans trapped in Kabul airport no-man's land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit jailed in Singapore for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-briton-handed-jail-term-in-singapore-for-not-wearing-mask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Briton handed jail term in Singapore for not wearing mask</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling under intensifying scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/19/politics/joe-biden-presidency-under-scrutiny/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is struggling against an intensifying examination of his judgment, competence and even his empathy over the chaotic US exit from Afghanistan. And each attempt the administration makes to quell a furor that's tarnishing America's image only provokes more questions about its failures of planning and execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats, Chaos in Sky Prompt Record FAA Enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-19/death-threats-chaos-in-the-sky-prompt-record-faa-enforcement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-Inclusive Magic Mushroom, Ayahuasca Retreats Are New Luxury Trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-19/all-inclusive-magic-mushroom-ayahuasca-retreats-are-new-luxury-trips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resorts are starting to wake up to the appeal of mind expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Fewer Americans Drinking Alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/353858/alcohol-consumption-low-end-recent-readings.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have become slightly less likely to say they drink alcoholic beverages, and those who imbibe are drinking less, on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires Exhaust 10,000-Strong Army Fighting Them...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/another-california-town-ravaged-wildfire-125949027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- There are over 10,000 firefighters battling unprecedented blazes in California, but that isn’t enough, and the state is having a hard time finding more as flames rage across the western U.S. and Canada. Twelve major wildfires now burn in the Golden State, forcing 31,000 people to flee their homes. Dry winds raking Northern California helped the Caldor Fire east of Sacramento jump from 6,500 acres to 62,586 by Wednesday night, seriously damaging the town of Grizzly Flats and hospit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says No One Being Killed?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3495132/joe-biden-afghanistan-interview-no-one-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden has sparked fury by saying that “no one is being killed in Afghanistan” despite stowaway deaths. It comes just one day after Afghan health officials said that one person was k…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Covid Plastic Barriers Make Things Worse?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/those-anti-covid-plastic-barriers-probably-dont-help-and-may-make-things-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid precautions have turned many parts of our world into a giant salad bar, with plastic barriers separating sales clerks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Hypebeasts Hit Road With Next Level Car Customization...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/hypebeasts-hit-the-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, by its owner’s description, a “zombie killer” dream machine — a 2021 Mercedes-Benz SUV G-Wagon/Brabus, Frankenstein-built using organs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Remote TX Town Became One of Fastest-Growing Cities...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/how-a-remote-town-in-texas-became-one-of-americas-fastest-growing-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿NEW BRAUNFELS, Texas — In the not-too-distant past, motorists driving along a stretch of Interstate 35 just northeast of San</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Butt Lifts Surge, Despite Risks...</title>
      <link>/https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/brazilian-butt-lifts-surge-despite-risks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petting, Cuddling Dog 'Significantly Enhances Well-Being'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/petting-a-dog-well-being/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our research tells us that interacting through touch is key to reducing student stress," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia sees worst day of pandemic amid delta outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/australia-sees-worst-day-of-covid-19-pandemic-amid-delta-outbreak-2513812</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia has suffered its worst day since the start of the Covid-19 pandemic, with total daily cases surpassing the previous record posted more than a year ago as a delta variant outbreak spreads as far as New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Are Shadowy Taliban Leaders Now Running Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/these-are-the-shadowy-taliban-leaders-now-running-afghanistan/ar-AANu7TS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades the Taliban’s leadership structure has been in the shadows: Even before the U.S. invasion in 2001, little was known about how the group operates beyond the names of a few top leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Chinese pressure on virus origins probe shocked WHO...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-chinese-pressure-on-coronavirus-origins-probe-shocked-the-who-e2-80-94-and-led-its-director-to-push-back/ar-AANtOpM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINES 'DECLINING EFFECTIVENESS' AGAINST INFECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccines-show-declining-effectiveness-against-infection-overall-but-strong-protection-against-hospitalization-amid-delta-variant/ar-AANsKR4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results were pivotal to the Biden administration's decision to recommend booster shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milley Denies Intel Predicted Rapid Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/gen-milley-says-there-was-nothing-that-i-or-anyone-else-saw-in-intel-indicating-afghanistan-would-collapse-in-11-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Mark Milley, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, addressed questions about the intelligence assessments of Afghanistan prior to the Taliban takeover happening within several days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidman quarantine exemption sparks anger in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-kidman-quarantine-exemption-sparks-anger-in-hong-kong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kidman quarantine exemption sparks anger in Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS TO MANDATE NURSING HOME SHOTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/18/politics/nursing-homes-federal-funding/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden announced on Wednesday that he is directing all nursing homes to require their staff be vaccinated against Covid-19 in order to continue receiving Medicare and Medicaid funding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas faces tipping point...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/568484-texas-faces-tipping-point-as-covid-19-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is facing a tipping point in the state’s battle with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions in US weaponry seized...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/568493-billions-in-us-weaponry-seized-by-taliban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billions of dollars of U.S. weapons are now in the hands of the Taliban following the quick collapse of Afghan security forces that were trained to use the military equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Shifts To Stark Tone As Seeks To Stay In Office: 'Life Or Death'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/17/california-recall-newsom-shifts-to-stark-tone-as-he-seeks-to-stay-in-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom is using increasingly stark language as he campaigns in the final month of a tight recall election, calling it “a matter of life or death" that voters keep him in office and he is increasingly targeting a single Republican candidate: talk show host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  Larry David 'screamed' at Dershowitz in grocery store over Don ties...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/08/18/larry-david-screamed-at-alan-dershowitz-at-grocery-store-over-trump-ties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Larry is a knee-jerk radical,” Dershowitz told Page Six of the incident. “He takes his politics from Hollywood. He doesn’t read a lot. He doesn’t think a lot.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County prosecutors bring Ron Jeremy sex assault case to grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-county-prosecutors-bring-ron-193512983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors seek to indict porn star Ron Jeremy on multiple counts of sexual assault stemming from allegations made by 23 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans face Taliban, airport chaos in scramble to evacuate Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americans-faced-taliban-airport-chaos-012617139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden insisted late Wednesday that the U.S. was committed to getting all Americans out Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel eases restrictions on blood donations by gay men...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-israel-blood-donation-f81a405e03b93d57d8cb390f8e10cc64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel has lifted restrictions on blood donations by gay men, saying the longstanding limitation was discriminatory and denigrating, Israel’s health minister said Thursday. Earlier this year the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Grace makes landfall near Mexico's Tulum temples...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-travel-mexico-caribbean-hurricanes-ac7fbf17a36e7983b14645d909fa117e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULUM, Mexico (AP) — Hurricane Grace struck Mexico's Caribbean coast just south of the ancient Mayan temples of Tulum early Thursday, pushing a dangerous storm surge. Heavy rain and strong winds threatened to destroy flimsier homes and keep tourists off white sand beaches until it crosses the Yucatan Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants mark independence as challenges to rule rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-taliban-bd853cac9eee5e4f0cd4b76580f27b53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Afghan protesters defied the Taliban for a second day Thursday, waving their national flag in scattered demonstrations that were met with renewed violence by the militants who are facing growing challenges to their rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gulf Coast's beloved 'Redneck Riviera' now virus hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-c341a0e0ab5e9ecc3b3eedc855f33513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GULF SHORES, Ala. (AP) — Tourists and servers alike dance atop tables and in the aisles at one restaurant on the “Redneck Riviera,” a beloved stretch of towns along the northern Gulf Coast where beaches, bars and stores are packed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia was ready for win due to longtime contacts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-taliban-f25c1a8b030fb0721f9b8891f8d329e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — When the Taliban swept over Afghanistan, Russia was ready for the rapid developments after working methodically for years to lay the groundwork for relations with the group that it still officially considers a terrorist organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  No way to withdraw without 'chaos ensuing'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-withdraw-afghanistan-chaos-ensuing/story?id=79507930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden in an exclusive interview with ABC News' George Stephanopoulos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men Have Biological Clock Too, Fertility Drops After Age 50...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/men-biological-clock-fertility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say men should not wait too long to start a family - just like women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS mandates employees disclose status...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/18/media/fox-mandate-vaccine-status/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The right-wing channel Fox News, whose top personalities have for months assailed the concept of vaccine passports and argued that asking about vaccine status amounts to a major intrusion of privacy, told employees this week that they must disclose their vaccination status to the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>61% paid no income taxes in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/18/61percent-of-americans-paid-no-federal-income-taxes-in-2020-tax-policy-center-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Tax Policy Center, 107 million households owed no income taxes in 2020, up from 76 million — or 44% of all taxpayers — in 2019.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
