<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Televangelist unhinged in bizarre interview where he defends using private jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7094061/Televangelist-Kenneth-Copeland-Inside-Edition-interview-defends-using-THREE-private-jets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Televangelist Kenneth Copeland asked the Inside Edition interviewer in the May clip: 'Do you think the Jewish people believe you should be broke? They believe in wealth.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The algorithm is our boss': UBER drivers face long hours, no benefits, danger...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/01/how-much-do-uber-drivers-really-make-three-drivers-share-the-math.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Uber's initial public offering unfolded earlier this month, drivers across the country went on strike to denounce low wages and lack of benefits. CNBC spoke with the company's drivers about how their financial lives are faring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE investigating conservative commentator Steven Crowder...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/technology/446470-youtube-investigating-conservative-commentator-steven-crowder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube is investigating conservative commentator Steven Crowder after Vox host Carlos Maza accused him of harassment and making derogatory comments about his ethnicity and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller seeks quiet retreat from public life...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/446411-mueller-seeks-quiet-retreat-from-public-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller for two years avoided the spotlight while running one of the most politically charged investigations in history. Until this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Epidemic' of bugging devices used by stalkers...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/06/01/experts-warns-epidemic-bugging-devices-used-stalkers-9690533/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Anything you can possibly think of you can buy with a bug built into it.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Targets FEDEX in 'Warning' to USA...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-launches-investigation-fedex-xinhua-110317908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As details of China’s criteria trickled out, the investigation into FedEx’s “wrongful delivery of packages” was framed as a warning by Beijing after the Trump administration imposed a ban on business with telecom giant Huawei Technologies Co. To designate an untrustworthy foreign entity, China will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET or not ET? That is the question...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/the-navy-tracks-ufo-sightings-scientists-explain-what-s-really-going-on-1.584080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one doubts that the pilots are seeing something, but psychologists and specialists in aviation medicine say there are plenty of reasonable explanations for such sightings other than extraterrestrial beings. Earthly sources of light reflected by clouds or haze, for example, or optical illusions wrought by fatigue after staring through a cockpit window for hours on end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who think Amash just seeking attention couldn't be more wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/those-who-think-justin-amash-is-just-seeking-attention-couldnt-be-more-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After saying President Trump’s behavior during the Russian collusion investigation rose to the level of impeachment over a week ago, Rep. Justin Amash, R-Mich., made his first public appearance Tuesday night at a town hall in his district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas struggles to keep pace as thirst for water intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article231070813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Biden be both future and past?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Can-Joe-Biden-be-both-the-future-and-the-past-13915734.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden is off to a good start in his third bid for the White House. His opening weeks have set him apart from his Democratic rivals. For the time being, he is operating on his own timetable, at his own pace and rhythm. So far there have been no major negative effects to that strategy.  But there is a question at the heart of his candidacy, in part created by the focus of his campaign message. It involves intangibles that shape almost every presidential campaign. For Biden, it comes to this: Can he be both past and future? Can he be the custodian of a pre-President Donald Trump status quo and a candidate offering real change?  Two weeks ago, he held a rally in downtown Philadelphia. His speech was a compendium of personal reflections, political messaging and policy ambitions. His overall theme was unity and the need to bring the country together, across the partisan divide. One line, however, seemed to capture how he wants people to see the coming campaign and his place in it.  He was talking about the need for action on climate change. He had drawn some fire from climate activists for a comment attributed in a Reuters report to a Biden adviser, who indicated that he would seek a "middle ground" position on climate. To some it sounded like a lowering of ambitions, a retreat from big and bold action that many in the party favor.  Biden sought to reassure people that he views the changing climate as an existential threat to the planet, something he would take seriously and deal with aggressively. He also told his audience that the "first and most important plank" of a Biden climate policy could be summed up in two words: "Beat Trump."  His argument was hardly specious. He pointed to all the things that he - and the 22 other Democrats seeking the party's nomination - are talking about, all they would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs unlikely stars uniting Americans at box office...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/01/meet-the-unlikely-stars-uniting-americans-at-the-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year will be remembered as the year America went to the dogs. At least cinematically. We’ve just seen the release of “A Dog’s Journey.” It is not to be confused with its predecessor “A Dog’s P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How insane demand for truffles leading to sabotage, fraud and death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/01/how-an-insane-demand-for-truffles-is-leading-to-sabotage-fraud-and-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Garbriele Caporale had taken precautions. One afternoon in 2009, he put a muzzle on his cocker spaniel before they went out to search for valuable white truffles in the hills of Perano, a town in A…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After SPACEX Launch, Fear of Satellites That Outnumber All Visible Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/science/after-spacex-launch-a-fear-of-satellites-that-outnumber-all-visible-stars/ar-AACeR9y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury cinemas fighting NETFLIX with steak tartare, expensive booze, gourmet popcorn...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90356487/luxury-cinemas-are-fighting-netflix-with-steak-tartare-expensive-booze-and-gourmet-popcorn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phenomenon of a luxe night out with a brew and a view extends from the big city to big sky country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK MIGRANTS DUMPED IN SOCAL...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/06/01/border-patrol-migrants-greyhound-bus-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In San Bernardino, volunteers scrambled to provide the mostly Guatemalan arrivals with the help and logistical support that Border Patrol did not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VICTIMS</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/local/article_1b533ea8-846d-11e9-a728-df38353a0516.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday afternoon, a longtime city employee opened fire at the city municipal center and killed 12 people. Here are their names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 DEAD; SHOOTING IN VA BEACH</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/local/article_777b737e-83e3-11e9-b1d0-dff7ad725d5e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is the most devastating day in the history of Virginia Beach," Mayor Bobby Dyer said in a news conference. "The people involved are our friends, co-workers, neighbors and colleagues."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissidents 'being executed for their organs'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/01/chinese-dissidents-are-being-executed-for-their-organs-former-hospital-worker-says/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zheng Qiaozhi — we will call him George — still has nightmares. He was interning at China’s Shenyang Army General Hospital when he was drafted to be part of an organ-harvesting team. The prisoner w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Big Tech Should Be Afraid. Very Afraid...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-afraid-very-afraid-121312132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google parent company Alphabet Inc. and the other tech giants should be quaking in their fleece vests. Bloomberg News and other news organizations reported late Friday that the U.S. Department of Justice is preparing to open an investigation into Google’s compliance with antitrust laws. If it goes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump reliance on pressure tactics showing diminishing returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-s-reliance-on-pressure-tactics-is-showing-13915541.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's brinkmanship with Mexico over immigration has opened a new and risky front in his global campaign to pressure other nations to capitulate to his demands, a strategy that has paid few dividends over 21/2 years and left his major foreign policy initiatives in doubt.  From his "fire and fury" rhetoric against a nuclear-armed North Korea to an escalating trade war with China to new ultimatums aimed at Mexico, Trump has wielded threats, insults and punishments against his foreign counterparts with diminishing returns.  Though he lured Kim Jong Un to the negotiating table through a "maximum pressure" campaign of economic sanctions, Trump's historic summits with the young dictator ended in failure after talks collapsed in February.  Beijing attempted to negotiate over Trump's push for a trade deal, but President Xi Jinping has met successive rounds of U.S. tariffs on Chinese goods with commensurate retaliatory measures, deepening an increasingly zero-sum clash between the world's two largest economies.  And although Mexico took steps to comply with Trump's hard-line immigration policies - allowing Central American asylum seekers to the United States a temporary haven - Trump's vow this week to impose sweeping tariffs unless that nation curbs unauthorized immigration into the United States stirred a public backlash.  For Trump, who campaigned on achieving "peace through strength," the consistent application of a tool kit of toughness has limited his options and left him in a precarious position as he accelerates his campaign for a second term.  Despite his pressure tactics, unauthorized immigration at the U.S.-Mexican border is at a 12-year peak, the tariff wars have sent jitters through Wall Street, and Pyongyang has resumed testing of short-range...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New credit bubble ready to burst?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/A-new-credit-bubble-gets-ready-to-burst-13911193.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell gave a speech a couple of weeks back that showed that financial regulators have learned many lessons from the 2008 financial crisis, but not the most important one, namely:  If regulators wait to act until they can say with certainty that a credit bubble is about to burst, they've waited too long.  That's particularly true when it comes to the opaque and unregulated "shadow" banking system on Wall Street that has now supplanted regulated banks as the leading source of credit for businesses and consumers. This shadow system gets its money from big investors rather than depositors, and it revolves around hedge funds, investment banks and private equity funds rather than banks. These shadow banks have made borrowed money cheaper and easier to get, but they have also made the financial system and the U.S. economy more susceptible to booms and busts. And with another giant credit bubble ready to burst - this one having to do with business borrowing - we're about to learn that painful lesson again.  The rise of the shadow banking system began in the 1980s with "junk" bonds, which for the first time allowed companies with less than blue-chip credit ratings to borrow more easily and cheaply from investors in the bond market than from banks on which they had always relied.  Then, beginning in the 1990s, shadow banks moved aggressively into home mortgages and other consumer debt - auto loans, student loans, credit card debt - which they bought from banks and other lenders, packaged together and sold to investors as bond-like securities. You know how that turned out.  After the crash in 2008, shadow bankers shifted their attention to business lending, using the same "securitization" process to buy and package "leveraged" loans - bank loans to big companies that were already highly indebted - into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical threat may brew in Gulf as hurricane season begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/tropical-threat-may-brew-in-gulf-of-mexico-as-atlantic-hurricane-season-officially-begins/70008426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol station holding 7x legal limit, overcrowding could turn violent...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/border-patrol-holding-900-at-facility-fit-for-125-in-situation-that-could-turn-violent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A government watchdog is warning of a potentially “violent” situation at one Border Patrol station on the U.S.-Mexico border where migrants are held in unsafe conditions. Even so, Homeland Security officials are not planning changes anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple building a FOLDING iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9197211/apple-folding-iphone-rivals-samsung-huawei/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE could be developing a FOLDING iPhone with a flexible screen, newly unearthed patent documents show. The tech giant has submitted a patent showing a double-folding screen that can be bent back…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm chaser proposes to boyfriend as tornado looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/storm-chaser-proposes-boyfriend-kansas-tornado-looms-n1011646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I was just so emotional just because it was my happiest place, being with him next to the storms,” Joey Krastel said of the engagement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest 10% of households now represent 70% of all U.S. wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-richest-10-of-households-now-represent-70-of-all-us-wealth-2019-05-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rich are getting richer. It is a refrain that has certainly been uttered before, and likely will again, as Deutsche Bank’s chief economist says the gap...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  NKorea's Kim visits factories linked to missile launches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-koreas-kim-visits-factories-005325939.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The factories have innocuous names, but analysts say several ostensibly civilian facilities visited by North Korean leader Kim Jong Un recently are also used to build ballistic missile launchers and other weapons. On Saturday North Korea state news agency KCNA released reports of Kim providing "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practices linked to search and other businesses...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-justice-department-prepares-anti-004406436.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The probe is expected to examine Google practices linked to search and other businesses, according to the report, which also said the Federal Trade Commission had investigated Google many years ago but will defer to the DOJ this time. Google and the Justice Department did not respond to requests by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SLAPS TARIFFS ON MEX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6aca0c83523d411ca78d9c6e9ca50ab4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CULIACAN, Mexico (AP) — Tomato exporter Sergio Esquer Peiro spent much of Friday in hastily called meetings with other stunned growers, trying to evaluate the potential fallout of U.S. President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country Star Debuts Song 'Shut Up About Politics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/05/31/watch-country-star-john-rich-debuts-song-shut-up-about-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country star John Rich debuted his new song "Shut Up About Politics" during an appearance on "The Five," in an attempt to encourage people to separate political debate from their everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhoid fever...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/lapd-officers-treated-typhoid-fever-typhus-symptoms/story?id=63371616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one LAPD officer has contracted the bacteria that causes typhoid fever, Salmonella typhi, and another one is showing typhus-like symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL:  USA replacing ideal of American individual with overreaching, overbearing govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2019/opinions/george-will-is-the-individual-obsolete/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives want to dilute the concept of individualism, but that’s antithetical to America’s premise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Deflects Blame After Leaked Hacking Tools Held City Hostage...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2019/05/nsa-deflects-blame-baltimore-ransomware-attack/157376/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange showing symptoms of 'psychological torture' in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/julian-assange-showing-symptoms-psychological-torture-expert-says-n1012081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiLeaks founder "lives in constant panic ... imagine being in a nightmare and never waking up," according to the U.N. special rapporteur on torture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINGER DRAKE BECOMES STAR OF NBA FINALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/toronto-raptors-superfan-drake-spent-his-entire-night-trolling-the-golden-state-warriors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to Thursday night's NBA Finals Game 1 between the Golden State Warriors and the Toronto Raptors, league commissioner Adam Silver personally addressed talks with Drake about his conduct on the sideline. "The league office had conversations directly with Drake and his manager, and I think we ended up in a good place," Silver said, according to ESPN. He might have to reevaluate. From before the opening tip until after the final horn sounded, Drake spent his entire night trolling the Warriors like crazy. The hip-hop star and Toronto Raptors superfan showed up to Thursday night's contest -- Toronto's first-ever appearance in the NBA Finals -- wearing a jersey of former Raptors player Dell Curry. Of course, Dell Curry is the father of Golden State star Stephen Curry. Then, at one point in the contest, Curry the younger and Drake exchanged words -- with their faces just millimeters apart. Drake noticed some lint on Curry's head, and proceeded to pick it off. After the game, he posted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 IS BECOMING ISRAEL'S 'LOST YEAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Opinion/Editors-Note-2019-is-becoming-Israels-lost-year-591195</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While this turn of events is bad, there was something refreshing watching Liberman stand up for a principled cause, in this case the haredi draft bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK TELLS COURT: THERE IS NO PRIVACY!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/facebook-lawyer-no-expectation-of-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey lawyers claim accuser deleted key text messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2019/05/31/kevin-spacey-lawyers-claim-accuser-nantucket-assault-cause-deleted-key-text-messages/jRmsipRtue2avkQZtVPfhJ/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorneys say prosecutors lied for months about being in possession of the accuserâ€™s phone and also raised concerns that the sister of an official in the prosecutionâ€™s office is friends with the accuserâ€™s mother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Says 'Cured' Himself of Being Gay...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/world/2019/5/31/homophobic-philippines-president-says-he-cured-himself-being-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside DNC's plan to defeat Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/446243-inside-the-dncs-plan-to-defeat-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of young Democrats will arrive in Atlanta next month to be trained as field organizers in an effort to prepare the party’s next generation of operatives to join the eventual nominee’s presidential campaign in seven battleground states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sharing forfeits your right'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/05/31/facebook-lawyer-argues-social-media-users-no-expectation-privacy-9757049/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Facebook is in the midst of a big drive towards privacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infestation Of Rats, Roaches, Fleas At Downtown LAPD Station May Be Sickening Employees...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/29/is-vermin-infestation-making-people-sick-at-downtown-lapd-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD says an employee at that station contracted salmonella typhi, which typically comes from infected food or water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT HEAD-COUNT REACHES 51 IN HOUSE...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7091131/51-House-members-including-1-Republican-calling-Trumps-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi still isn't ready to impeach Donald Trump but 50 members of her Democratic caucus – and one lone Republican – are out for the president's political blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA X-ray of Earth captures night sky like never before...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9193745/night-sky-golden-fireworks-x-ray-image/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A STUNNING photo that shows the night sky as you’ve never seen it before has been released by Nasa. The image was snapped from space by a special telescope that tracks rogue cosmic rays in ar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First rare earth processing facility outside of China to be built in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/industrials/first-rare-earth-processing-facility-outside-of-china-to-be-built-in-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Line Corp. partners with Australian rare earth mining company Lynas to build a processing plant in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High powered guests pictured outside secretive summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7090931/Tech-billionaires-Eric-Schmidt-Peter-Thiel-seen-secretive-Bilderberg-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt and PayPal co-founder Peter Thiel are among 130 high-powered guests at the summit in the five-star Fairmont Le Montreux Palace on the shores of Lake Geneva.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historians attack Pulitzer winner's explosive MLK allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/ae/books/2019/05/30/Historians-attack-David-Garrow-s-Martin-Luther-King-allegations-1/stories/201905300167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoD spent millions on phony military gear made in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2019/05/30/dod-bought-phony-military-gear-made-in-china-including-counter-night-vision-clothing-that-didnt-actually-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The counterfeits included clothing that used a near-infrared fabric to make the wearer more difficult for enemy forces to detect with night-vision goggles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUGATTI Strategy of $13 Million, One-Off Supercars...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/bugatti-s-sky-is-the-limit-strategy-of-13-million-one-off-supercars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bugattiâ€™s â€˜Sky Is the Limitâ€™ StrategyÂ of $13 Million, One-Off Supercars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic Church reports big rise in sex-abuse allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2953774dff6e40668121a7e4589daaa9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Quantifying its vast sex-abuse crisis, the U.S. Roman Catholic Church said Friday that allegations of child sex abuse by clerics more than doubled in its latest 12-month reporting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of deepfake porn...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/05/31/deepfake-porn-ethics-able-watch-whatever-imagination-desires-9526079/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the lines between reality and lies are blurred, what do we do?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA coach fined $50,000 for comparing Kawhi to Michael Jordan...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2838903-clippers-fined-50000-for-doc-rivers-comparing-kawhi-leonard-to-michael-jordan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Clippers were fined $50,000 by the NBA after head coach Doc Rivers made public comments Tuesday comparing Toronto Raptors superstar forward Kawhi Leonard to Michael Jordan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Lemon Slams NYTIMES For Banning Reporters From Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cnns-don-lemon-new-york-times-is-extremely-short-sighted-if-it-bans-reporters-from-my-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Editor Dean Baquet said he was not sure which TV shows ‘Times’ journalists would now not appear on. ‘It’s my strong view that opinion and news need to be separated.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete campaign, brimming with cash, staffs up...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/31/pete-buttigieg-2020-election-campaign-1349301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign now numbers about 80 staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs Secretly Alarmed After Kids Died, But Heart Surgeries Continued...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2019/05/30/us/children-heart-surgery-cardiac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secret recordings captured physicians’ concerns that more children seemed to fare poorly after heart surgery. Their hospital kept doing the operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden retriever named Mueller mayor of SoCal town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/golden-retriever-named-mueller-mayor-southern-california-town/story?id=63371017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There may have been drama in Washington, D.C. yesterday but there's still Muellers in politics on the west coast -- and they happens to be a golden retrievers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Dems push Pelosi to impeach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/more-house-democrats-grow-ready-impeach-trump-making-pelosi-s-n1012451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: There are strong signs that the pro-impeachment forces in the House are both larger than she portrays — and growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area Homeless Move to Tree Houses...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/05/30/fremont-homeless-living-in-tree-houses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The homeless crisis in the Bay Area has reached new heights, literally, as transients live in tree houses in Alameda County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record floods breach Arkansas levee, overtop 2 in Missouri...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afe47b6947f044d5bbf614f449b3d40e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Relentless flooding persisted in the nation's midsection Friday, sending communities underwater and damaging or overtopping levees on three major rivers in two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foodies flock to Detroit Ramadan festivals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/25f31de0fdb24e2397d723cd6bb6fed1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEARBORN HEIGHTS, Mich. (AP) — Shortly before midnight, a buzzing crowd stood patiently in a line that bent around the corner of a community center and stretched far back into the night. After a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Cold,' Unsupportive Mother Linked To Early Aging, Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/having-cold-unsupportive-mother-linked-premature-aging-disease-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who were raised by emotionally-closed or unsupportive mothers are more prone to premature aging and disease later in life, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg security chief on leave amid racism probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Zuckerberg-security-chief-placed-on-leave-amid-13910158.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg's personal security chief has been placed on administrative leave amid allegations that he made racist and homophobic remarks about people including the Facebook founder's wife.  Liam Booth allegedly made the remarks about Zuckerberg's wife, Priscilla Chan, and some of the employees at their household, Business Insider reported earlier, citing legal letters from the former household staff. A spokesman for the Zuckerberg and Chan family office said Booth has been placed on leave while an outside law firm investigates. It didn't confirm the precise nature of the allegations published by Business Insider.  "The family office takes complaints of workplace misconduct very seriously," the spokesman told Bloomberg News in an email. "The allegations against Liam Booth were brought to the office's attention for the first time by the Bloom Firm after both former employees had left employment by the family office and engaged legal counsel."  Lisa Bloom of the Bloom Firm confirmed by email that she represents "the two individuals who have raised claims." She declined to identify the people involved or share details on the allegations.  Booth is a former Secret Service officer, according to his LinkedIn profile. He didn't immediately reply to a message outside of U.S. business hours.  Facebook's costs for Zuckerberg's personal protection amounted to $9.96 million in 2018, regulatory filings show. The chief executive officer also gets an additional annual $10 million allowance to cover security expenses for himself and his family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden realtor fees could be next housing domino to topple...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hidden-realtor-commissions-could-be-next-housing-market-domino-to-topple-as-government-probes-mls-2019-05-31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much information do Realtors keep among themselves, and what should be made transparent to housing market buyers and sellers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit man shot and paralyzed Mexico's toughest cop. Now he's seeking revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-leyzaola-mayor-20190531-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Leyzaola helped quell violence in Tijuana a decade ago. Now the homicide rate is soaring and he wants to be mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris extends smoking ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190531-france-paris-smoking-ban-52-parks-gardens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Paris will extend a ban on smoking to 52 parks and gardens in the French capital from June 8, the mayor’s office announced Friday, marking World No Tobacco Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lit firecracker thrown into NYC subway sparks chaos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/31/lit-firecracker-thrown-into-subway-train-sparks-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone tossed a lit firecracker into an F train at 14th Street during the morning commute Friday, causing chaos when it exploded, according to riders and MTA officials. Twitter user @Amelia_Vogler…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters in Iran, Iraq burn Israel, US flags...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe7f04ea375d4ff0b194c63ea22cc61e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iranians in the capital Tehran set fire to effigies of President Donald Trump, while in the Iraqi capital, Iran-backed militiamen marched over a large Israeli flag as part of...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
