<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Boris threatens to purge rebel party members as Brexit battle heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Britain-s-Johnson-threatens-to-purge-rebel-party-14406878.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - Prime Minister Boris Johnson sharply raised the stakes in the Brexit fight on Monday, threatening to kick members of Parliament out of the Conservative Party if they don't support his plans to leave the European Union next month.  The move comes as Johnson and his opponents position themselves for a fierce showdown over Brexit on Tuesday when Parliament returns from its summer recess.  A cross-party group of opposition legislators, led by Labour Party leader Jeremy Corbyn, plan to introduce legislation to block Britain leaving the E.U. without an agreement in place to regulate trade, border security and other critical issues - the so-called no-deal Brexit.  Most lawmakers in Parliament oppose leaving without an exit plan, something many analysts say could be economically damaging and lead to food and medicine shortages. Johnson has dismissed those predictions as fearmongering.  Conservative rebels reacted angrily to Johnson's threat to force them out of the party, which would mean they could not run as Conservative candidates in future elections. A general election, as soon as the next few weeks, is a possibility if Johnson and his opponents fail to reach agreement over Brexit.  Nick Boles, a former Conservative legislator who quit the party over Brexit, told the BBC that Johnson's tactics meant the party had been "taken over" by the "hard right."  "The Conservative Party has fallen prey to an almost religious obsession with the hardest form of Brexit, which is obviously a Brexit with no deal," he said in a radio interview Monday.  This week's battles in Parliament will also center on Johnson's plan to suspend Parliament for five weeks, starting sometime next week, which will sharply limit the amount of time legislators have to debate the terms of the Oct. 31...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$10,000: Travolta Hits All Time Low with 'FANATIC'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/08/31/john-travolta-hits-all-time-low-with-the-fanatic-set-to-make-less-than-10000-this-three-day-weekend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I told you last week that John Travolta, king of the B and C movies, was heading toward a big disaster with “The Fanatic.” Well, in 52 theaters last night, “The Fanatic” mad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat fire leaves 34 feared dead after bursting into flames off California... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/breaking-santa-cruz-island-boat-19168627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire is thought to have broken out just before 4am (11am GMT) this morning near Santa Cruz Island</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At this Florida camp, believers can ask for healing or chat with the dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-09-01/florida-cassadaga-spiritualist-camp-psychics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 125-year-old Cassadaga Spiritualist Camp is the country’s largest full-time assemblage of mediums, psychics and healers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13,000 houses affected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/hurricane-dorian-september-2019/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Dorian, a dangerous Category 5 storm, is battering in the Bahamas, and it's slowly crawling toward the US. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Recession signals flashing red...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/02/heres-a-list-of-recession-signals-that-are-flashing-red.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's a list of recession signals that are worrying investors that the U.S. might be going into recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hezbollah: On road to all-out war?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-49551362 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent clash between Israel and Hezbollah could be a prelude to a catastrophic conflict ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STALLED FOR HOURS!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ReaganMatt/status/1168468612455292929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The eye wall of #Dorian has been sitting over some of the same places of Grand Bahama Island for 6 HOURS.  This is just ridiculous at this point. https://t.co/uycAuyElf7”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-fascist rebellion brewing in Pacific Northwest soccer stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Anti-fascist-rebellion-brewing-in-Pacific-14406190.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seeds of dissent were visible almost immediately.  Soccer officials had notified the Timbers Army, a fan organization for the team in Portland, Oregon, on the eve of this season that the anti-fascist symbol its members had been waving on a giant banner in the north end of the stadium would no longer be permitted at games. The fan group was not happy, releasing a lengthy critique of Major League Soccer's new rules, and working with team officials for months in meetings to change the rule.  But what began as an internal dispute between the league, the Timbers front office, and the fan group has morphed into a full rebellion in recent weeks.  The symbol, a re-purposed icon from an anti-fascist group, the Iron Front from Nazi-era Germany, has popped up at stadiums around the country. The MLS ban of it has drawn coverage from left-leaning media outlets. And a recent Timbers game became the venue for a nearly stadiumwide protest that saw two rival fan groups join in silence for more than a half-hour before openly flouting the symbol's ban.  How did a simple game - the beautiful game - become the setting for such a heated political struggle?  - - -  The Portland Timbers were incorporated into the MLS in 2010, part of a long wave of expansion for the league that continues today as the sport's popularity grows.  They have attracted a particularly active fan base, embodied most feverishly by the Timbers Army, a supporters group of some 5,200 paying members that makes the stadium's North End its raucous home every game.  The league has made relatively lenient rules in its stadiums a point of pride as it seeks to embrace a more participatory style of fandom that marks soccer in Europe and South America, where the game's foothold is strongest. Compared to many football or baseball...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump aides claim victory, but others see incompetence and intolerance...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-aides-claim-victory-but-others-see-14406249.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When President Donald Trump presided over the battle tanks and fighter jets, the fireworks and adoring fans on July 4, he couldn't have known that the militaristic "Salute to America" - as well to himself - would end up as the apparent pinnacle of the season.  What followed was what some Trump advisers and allies characterize as a lost summer defined by self-inflicted controversies and squandered opportunities. Trump leveled racist attacks against four congresswomen of color dubbed "the Squad." He derided the majority-black city of Baltimore as "rat and rodent infested." His anti-immigrant rhetoric was echoed in a missive that authorities believe a mass shooting suspect posted. His visits to Dayton, Ohio, and El Paso, Texas, after shooting massacres in those cities served to divide rather than heal.  Trump's economy also began to falter, with the markets ping-ponging based on the president's erratic behavior. His trade war with China grew more acrimonious. His whipsaw diplomacy at the Group of Seven summit left allies uncertain about American leadership. The president returned from his visit to France in a sour mood, frustrated by what he felt was unfairly negative news coverage of his trip.  The two months between Independence Day and Labor Day offered a fresh and vivid portrait of the president as seen by Trump's critics - incompetent, indecisive, intolerant and ineffective.  White House officials promote the summer of 2019 as one of historic achievement for Trump, offering up a list of more than two dozen accomplishments. But privately, many of the president's advisers and outside allies bemoan what they consider to be a period of missed opportunity and self-sabotage.  In the final lull before the 2020 campaign starts to intensify this fall, Trump could have worked strategically to solidify his position...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Biden Want to Be Doing This?</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/02/does-joe-biden-want-to-be-doing-this/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - “How badly do you want to be president?” Joseph R. Biden Jr. was asked after a recent speech in Prole, Iowa. The answer to such an inquiry would appear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of sex health threat?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7412829/Scientists-claim-lack-sex-life-pose-health-risk.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not uncommon for married couples of a certain age to lose some of their spark in the bedroom. But for over-50s who let their love life enter the doldrums might be affecting their health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colossal damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7418967/Hurricane-Dorian-Second-strongest-storm-HISTORY-batters-Bahamas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Category 5 hurricane was lingering over the island of Grand Bahama this morning, moving westward at just 1mph, bringing up to 30 inches of rain and leaving an airport under five feet of water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot pole dancers debut at nightclub...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7418523/Gyrating-ROBOTS-debut-French-pole-dancing-club.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gyrating robots at SC-Club in Nantes have CCTV cameras for heads and are intended to explore the notion of voyeurism, according to their creator, British artist Giles Walker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media takes hits in bitter partisan era...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/459457-media-takes-hits-in-bitter-partisan-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news media is taking hits from all sides, underscoring the bitter partisan divide and fierce war over the “official story” coming out of President Trump’s Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 2020 danger if Dem scores upset in NCarolina special election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-faces-more-2020-danger-if-democrat-scores-upset-n-n1047226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: The closely watched Sept. 10 vote will fill a House seat that is vacant after last year's results were invalidated due to election fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Deepfake App Goes Viral; Privacy Of Millions 'At Risk'...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2019/09/02/chinese-best-ever-deepfake-app-zao-sparks-huge-faceapp-like-privacy-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's FaceApp all over again—only this time it's a Chinese app instead of a Russian one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Number Govts Shutting Down Internet To Quash Dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/02/governments-shut-down-the-internet-to-stifle-critics-citizens-pay-the-price/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - HARARE, Zimbabwe — When Zimbabwe turned off the internet during a recent crackdown, Obert Masaraure, a prominent government critic, had no way of knowing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Hezbollah exchange border fire first time in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/01/middleeast/israel-hezbollah-army-base-attack/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iran-backed Lebanese militant group Hezbollah has attacked an Israeli army base and a nearby military vehicle as tensions remain high along the border between Israel and Lebanon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of dollar as we know it?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/459546-the-end-of-the-dollar-as-we-know-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That the dominance of the dollar is being questioned is not surprising at the present juncture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorian strikes with record fury...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02c093eb6ce24d24a959e6d87088590a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McLEAN'S TOWN CAY, Bahamas (AP) — In a slow, relentless advance, a catastrophic Hurricane Dorian kept pounding at the northern Bahamas early Monday, as one of the strongest Atlantic storms ever...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAWLING...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190902033026-8hwtp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-DORIAN/ (UPDATE 16, PIX, TV):UPDATE 16-'Monster' Hurricane Dorian pummels Bahamas, forecast to threaten Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/E4BAXqEcGYk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;youtu.be&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDa3T_uU4AIPq7B?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE LOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.pscp.tv/Jeff_Piotrowski/1mnxezMblpNKX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pscp.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Dorian Update:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ MPH GUSTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/live-category-5-dorian-nearing-landfall-in-bahamas-with-220-mph-wind-gusts/70009223</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Kevin Hart Suffers Major Injuries In Calabasas Car Accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/09/01/kevin-hart-car-accident-malibu-off-road-passengers-trapped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart suffers major back injury when his car veered off the road in nasty accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE LOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.pscp.tv/w/1mnxezMblpNKX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pscp.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Dorian Update:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Small deviation of track could bring intense core onto Florida coast'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/012056.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer killed as she's hit by pyrotechnic device in front of horrified fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/singer-killed-shes-hit-pyrotechnic-19120826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING VIDEO: Joana Sainz, 30, was performing with the Super Hollywood Orchestra when the stunt went horribly wrong at a fiesta in Spain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDZyP9jVUAIl6Hb?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory evacuation ordered in Palm Beach, including Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article234614387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right party posts best-ever results...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/germany-state-elections-far-right-afd-5cd2e231-0fa7-4563-ac0b-f487b177d49d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the party still came up short of victory in Saxony and Brandenburg, as some had feared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDZWVHfUwAE66pD?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH AND WAIT; NOW CATASTROPHIC CAT 5...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/storms/hurricane/news/2019-09-01-hurricane-dorian-category-5-near-bahamas-florida-georgia-carolinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Counties Order Evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/news/news/2019-09-01-hurricane-dorian-impacts-florida-evacuations-ordered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Depth Look At Track Forecast...</title>
      <link>https://blog.weather.us/an-in-depth-look-at-dorians-track-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blog.weather.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUNMAN FIRES AFTER TRAFFIC STOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e765453e0fc34cbbb75311763d4b3709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDLAND, Texas (AP) — The death toll in a West Texas shooting rampage increased to seven Sunday as authorities investigated why a man stopped by state troopers for failing to signal a left turn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 DEAD IN TEXAS RAMPAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/death-toll-odessa-shooting-rises-7-17-month-old-child-n1048711?cid=eml_nbn_20190901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll from the Texas rampage rose to seven on Sunday morning. The gunman is also dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby monkey shakes in terror after being snatched from mum for lab testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/baby-monkey-shakes-terror-after-19118939</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists slam heartbreaking video of baby monkey being ripped from parents’ arms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THISCLOSE; NEXT TURN CRITICAL FOR USA...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2019-09-01-hurricane-dorian-category-5-near-bahamas-florida-georgia-carolinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impacts along the coast are already beginning. Here's our latest forecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDY1N1gVAAE3tFn?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ MPH GUSTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT5+shtml/011330.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMB SHELTERS OPENED...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/IDF-fires-artillery-shells-into-Lebanon-report-600309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the report, several shells were fired causing fires on the Lebanese side but no injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF responds with artillery fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.israelhayom.com/2019/09/01/report-mortars-fired-into-lebanon-from-northern-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.israelhayom.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hezbollah took responsibility for anti-tank missiles that were fired from inside Lebanon toward IDF forces on the northern border on Sunday afternoon, and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks, tornadoes and taxes: Cape Cod's tough summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/673bf180c907467ba8773072fd261de3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between great white sharks, freak tornadoes and new taxes on vacation rentals, Cape Cod businesses have had a challenging summer. Lodging and beach visit numbers are down on the famous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUNMAN FIRES AFTER TRAFFIC STOP</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/gunman-large-hijacked-mail-truck-shooting-random-people/story?id=65316967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were killed when a gunman opened fire in a series of shootings near Odessa in western Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech or big labor? Dems line up with unions...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/big-tech-big-labor-2020-democrats-line-unions-65324482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most major Democratic White House hopeful have waded into a California clash between labor unions and tech giants such as Uber and Lyft over the definition of work in a changing economy, in a rare case of presidential politics in a state policy debate</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
