<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SUBWAY $5 Footlong going away...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/09/10/subway-5-footlong-going-away-but-paninis-may-their-way-exclusive/1206727002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other changes include bolder flavors, new decor and more locally-inspired foods and discount deals, according to Trevor Haynes, the current CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Police Tell Citizens to Report 'Offensive' Comments Even if Not 'Hate Crimes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.prisonplanet.com/uk-police-tell-citizens-to-report-offensive-comments-even-if-theyre-not-hate-crimes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prisonplanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Paul Joseph Watson &lt;/b&gt;| While country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article218114880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Hurricane Florence’s biggest threats in North Carolina could be flooding due to days of rain. Find out what NOAA is expecting to protect your home from damage before the storm hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbugs jumping frequently between humans and animals...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-09-superbugs-frequently-humans-animals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MRSA staphylococcus is an example of a superbug. These bacterial strains are resistant to most antibiotics and can cause serious infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Shelves Emptied...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/09/10/intensifying-hurricane-florence-could-strike-us-southeast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapidly intensifying Hurricane Florence could strike a direct and dangerous blow anywhere from the Carolinas to the Mid-Atlantic region later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shhhh! Dem leaders don't want to say 'impeach'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/shhhh-dem-leaders-don-t-want-say-impeach-bill-clinton-n907906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top three Democratic leaders in the House — Reps. Nancy Pelosi, Steny Hoyer and Jim Clyburn — were all there in '98.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore takes mic away after David Hogg urges foreign meddling in American elections...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/at-toronto-film-fest-david-hogg-urges-foreign-meddling-in-american-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took Michael Moore to correct anti-gun protester David Hogg’s proposal for Canadians to meddle in American elections. After screening Moore’s anti-Trump “Fahrenheit 11/9” at the Toronto Film Festival, Hogg and other Parkland, Florida high school students joined the millionaire filmmaker on stage during a Q&amp;A. ﻿ “I have a question for you guys,” Hogg …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exotic pets trade activity rises on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/10/the-associated-press-wildlife-group-exotic-pets-trade-activity-rises-on-facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK— A wildlife monitoring group says research it has conducted since 2016 has found that people are increasingly buying and selling endangered animals on Facebook groups in Thailand. TRAFFIC says in a report to be launched online Wednesday that its researchers found increased activity among 12 Facebook groups it has monitored. Facebook said in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Atmospheric brick wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.perspectaweather.com/blog/2018/9/9/1030-pm-sunday-potential-tremendous-rainfall-amounts-from-hurricane-florence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.perspectaweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes are focused on Hurricane Florence as we begin the new week and chances for a major&amp;nbsp;impact on the US east coast continue to grow. Florence is now churning slowly towards the US east coast as a category 2 hurricane and may make a landfall late&amp;nbsp;Thursday somewhere along the Ca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seventeen years after Sept. 11, Al Qaeda may be stronger than ever...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/middleeast/la-fg-al-qaeda-survive-20180910-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the almost 17 years since the twin towers crumbled, and despite hundreds of thousands killed and billions of dollars spent, Al Qaeda remains a threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentines seek soup kitchens, barter markets amid crisis...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/09/10/argentines-seek-soup-kitchens-barter-markets-amid-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men wait outside the metal-grill door of a soup kitchen in a slum, hoping to get a small serving of beef and mashed potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Village Says 'Yes' to 2,500-Franc a Month Free Money Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/09/10/swiss-village-says-yes-to-2-500-franc-a-month-free-money-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swiss Village Says ‘Yes’ to 2,500-Franc a Month Free Money Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High stakes as 2-month sprint to Election Day begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/de2a478fc3b74e9f97d80ac2e2fb7f06/High-stakes-as-2-month-sprint-to-Election-Day-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Control of Congress and the future of Donald Trump's presidency are on the line as the primary season closes this week, jump-starting a two-month sprint to Elect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials destroying crosses, burning bibles in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c09b2ee4b71540c8a7fd6178820c5970/Group:-Officials-destroying-crosses,-burning-bibles-in-China</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's government is ratcheting up a crackdown on Christian congregations in Beijing and several provinces, destroying crosses, burning bibles, shutting churches a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli music scene jolted by international boycott movement...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/israeli-music-scene-jolted-international-boycott-movement-57719210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Meteor Festival was meant to bring together indie groups from around the world in what organizers billed as a Woodstock-like "cutting edge musical journey that surpasses borders and distorts time and space." Instead, some 20 acts, including headliner Lana Del Rey, withdrew at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH: Meet America's Preeminent Right-Wing Guerrilla Street Artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/matt-labash/meet-sabo-americas-preeminent-right-wing-guerrilla-street-artist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Street artist Sabo may just be ‘some guy who lives in some dump,’ but he is taking on and taking down the likes of Jimmy Kimmel and Meryl Streep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro- and anti- whaling nations set for clash in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180910-pro-anti-whaling-nations-set-clash-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Vote Could Swing Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pennsylvania-vote-could-swing-congress-1536571800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats could capture the House if the state flips enough seats, as this year’s battlefield moves to the suburbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New-Ager Set to be Youngest-Ever Starting QB...</title>
      <link>https://www.wralsportsfan.com/new-age-sam-darnold-tries-to-solve-an-age-old-jets-problem/17831911/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wralsportsfan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORHAM PARK, N.J. — Shortly after the New York Jets chose a quarterback out of the University of Southern California with the third overall pick in April’s NFL draft, the team’s incumbent at the position, Josh McCown, received a text from his oldest daughter, Bridget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Bear-Market Risk Indicator Highest Since 1969...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-10/goldman-bear-market-risk-indicator-at-highest-since-1969-chart </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Trump to Close PLO Office in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-administration-to-close-palestine-liberation-organization-office-in-washington-1536546125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is expected to announce Monday it will close the Palestine Liberation Organization’s office in Washington, widening a campaign of pressure amid stalled Middle East peace efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Battles USA For Control World's Fastest Wireless Web...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-5g-race-china-and-u-s-battle-to-control-worlds-fastest-wireless-internet-1536516373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new wireless era promises to transform how people use the internet, and two countries are fighting over who dominate. At stake are billions of dollars in royalties, a head start in developing new technologies and national security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large church in Beijing outlawed...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-religion/china-outlaws-large-underground-protestant-church-in-beijing-idUSKCN1LQ07W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing city authorities have banned one of the largest unofficial Protestant churches in the city and confiscated "illegal promotional materials", amid a deepening crackdown on China's "underground" churches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowy extremist sect accused of plot to kill intellectuals in India..</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/A-shadowy-extremist-sect-is-accused-of-plotting-13214996.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGALORE, India - The killers trailed her for months, watching her every move. When the day came, they were ready for her. Journalist Gauri Lankesh had locked up the office of her scrappy weekly newspaper and had just returned home here when the killers arrived on a motorcycle. One of them - his face obscured by a helmet - drew close and began shooting. One, two, three shots. Lankesh tried to flee, but the last bullet ended her life. The journalist's death a year ago reverberated across India. She was given a state funeral in Bangalore, and thousands marched in protest around the country, chanting, "I am Gauri. We are all Gauri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol agent shot at while sitting in patrol car...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-border-patrol-agent-shot-at-20180909-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Border Patrol agent was shot at early Sunday morning while sitting in his marked patrol car near the San Ysidro Port of entry, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic, Pacific churn with storms at same time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/rare-event-atlantic-pacific-churn-storms-same-time-n907826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storms in the northeast Pacific have generated the most 'accumulated cyclone energy' on record for the season thus far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall Sparks Fear and Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/inside-cbs-leslie-moonves-fall-sparks-fear-outrage-1141492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moonves’ fall means control shifts to Shari Redstone, who has been locked in a bitter legal battle with Moonves and the majority of the CBS board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE: Complicated Legacy...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/09/les-moonves-leaves-complicated-legacy-at-cbs-1202460800/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fall of Les Moonves is stunning for the sheer velocity with which one of the most powerful moguls in the media business got dethroned. Once regarded as creative executive with few equals, Moonv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE INTERNET KIOSKS TRACKING MOVEMENTS?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/09/08/linknyc-free-wifi-kiosks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Code accidentally made public on the internet suggests that LinkNYC may be actively planning to track users’ locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic skin lets prosthetic limbs 'feel'...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1355626/researchers-have-developed-an-electronic-skin-that-lets-prosthetic-limbs-feel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, "e-dermis" can react to both pain and pressure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela calls march against US after reported coup bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-calls-march-against-us-reported-coup-bid-003451695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's government announced it would hold a massive march Tuesday against US meddling after reports that US officials met secretly with Venezuelan military officers to discuss plans to oust President Nicolas Maduro. The United States "acknowledges having met at least three times with military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRACKDOWN: Muslims In China Face 'Political Indoctrination'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang-rights/muslim-minority-in-chinas-xinjiang-face-political-indoctrination-human-rights-watch-idUSKCN1LQ01F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Turkic mostly Muslim Uighur minority in China’s Xinjiang region face arbitrary detentions, daily restrictions on religious practice and "forced political indoctrination" in a mass security crackdown, Human Rights Watch said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper exec worries as APPLE urges to join subscription service...</title>
      <link>https://www.recode.net/2018/9/7/17832750/apple-new-york-times-washington-post-wall-street-journal-texture-news-eddy-cue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recode.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last March, Apple bought Texture, a digital magazine service. Now it wants the New York Times, the Washington Post and the Wall Street Journal to join up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging knifeman slashing spree in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/7216406/paris-attack-at-least-seven-injured-by-rampaging-knifeman-suspect-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT least two British visitors to Paris were among seven victims of a savage knife attack in the French capital, police said last night. A suspect ‘of Pakistani or Afghan origin’ began ‘slashing pas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Republican rescue mission for Ted Cruz...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/09/09/ted-cruz-reelection-trump-813354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national party wasn't expecting to have to defend a well-known senator in a conservative bastion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOONVES OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/leslie-moonves-departs-cbs-ceo-chairman-financial-package-withheld-pending-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS and Moonves will donate $20 million to one or more organizations that support the #MeToo movement and equality for women in the workplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SEASON:  Miami Dolphins players kneel during national anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2018/09/09/nfl-player-protests-kneel-anthem-kenny-stills-albert-wilson/1248376002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kenny Stills and Albert Wilson became the first players of the 2018 regular season to kneel in protest during the national anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOONVES OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/09/les-moonves-cbs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS is near completion of a settlement that would both end its litigation with National Amusements — and sever ties with CEO Leslie Moonves, according to people familiar with the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD SPEAKS:  'People better wake up to what's going on'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bob-woodward-fear-trump-in-the-white-house-people-better-wake-up-to-whats-going-on-in-the-oval-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For his 19th book, "Fear: Trump in the White House," the veteran reporter interviewed more than 100 officials and staffers, who describe chaos and discord in the administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINED $17,000...</title>
      <link>https://olympics.nbcsports.com/2018/09/09/serena-williams-fined-us-open/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;olympics.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fines were for her three code violations in the final.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD:  Trump spooked Pentagon with almost-sent tweet on NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-spooked-pentagon-almost-sent-tweet-n-korea-161039669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump spooked the Pentagon leadership with a tweet that -- had it been sent -- North Korea would have read as a sign of an imminent US attack, journalist Bob Woodward said in an interview that aired Sunday. Woodward, whose new book "Fear: Trump in the White House" hits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER SUSPENDS BENGHAZI HERO After Criticism of Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/09/twitter-suspends-benghazi-hero-after-criticism-of-president-obama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Italian government plans to curb Sunday shopping...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/italian-government-plans-curb-sunday-shopping-di-maio-161412774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Italian government will introduce a ban on Sunday shopping in large commercial centres before the end of the year as it seeks to defend family traditions, Deputy Prime Minister Luigi Di Maio said on Sunday. In a bid to spur economic growth, the then Italian Prime Minister Mario Monti liberalised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWEDEN SWINGS RIGHT</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/anti-immigration-party-set-election-gains-sweden-swings-095749774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right parties have made spectacular gains throughout Europe in recent years after a refugee crisis sparked by civil war in Syria and conflicts in Afghanistan and parts of Africa. In Sweden, the influx of 163,000 asylum seekers in 2015 has polarized voters, fracturing the political consensus and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild West of Internet Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/local-internet-laws-threaten-to-go-global-1536490801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google this week will argue in EU’s top court against expanding “right to be forgotten,” the highest-profile case yet to test where jurisdiction begins and ends with data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics rave over 'HALLOWEEN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2018/09/09/halloween-hits-toronto-film-festival-and-critics-cheering/1247483002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday night "Halloween" screened its epic, bloody finale at the Toronto International Film Festival, an event that welcomed Jamie Lee Curtis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE pulls ads by Putin critic Navalny...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/09/google-pulls-youtube-ad-by-putin-critic-alexei-navalny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unrest breaks out as Google pulls YouTube ads by Putin critic Alexei Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents harvest dead son's sperm to create 'designer grandson'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/heartbroken-parents-harvest-dead-sons-13215814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealthy pair took the extraordinary step after their 26-year-old son was killed in a motorcycle crash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided America challenges ad industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180909-divided-america-trump-era-challenges-ad-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brains can be 'radicalized' for mass murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726912/robots-artificial-intelligence-ai-mass-murder-terrorism-isis </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP SCIENTIST: A.I. Greater Threat Than Terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/09/06/head-of-british-science-association-ai-greater-concern-than-terrorism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A.I. is a bigger concern than terrorism or climate change, according to the new head of the British Science Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Confronts Defining Moment as Global Order Realigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/09/09/merkel-confronts-a-defining-moment-as-the-global-order-realigns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Confronts a Defining Moment as the Global Order Realigns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Toxic red tide algae moves north near Tampa Bay, killing hundreds of thousands of fish... </title>
      <link>https://www.beaumontenterprise.com/news/article/Toxic-red-tide-algae-moves-north-near-Tampa-Bay-13216055.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.beaumontenterprise.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The toxic algae bloom that has carved a trail of dead animals and triggered a putrid stench along western Florida's coastline has drifted further north, killing hundreds of thousands of fish in the Tampa Bay region. The legions of dead fish were reported in a 20-mile stretch of coastline from Clearwater to St. Petersburg, environmental officials with Pinellas County told the Tampa Bay Times on Saturday. County workers roamed beaches and trawled offshore to collect the fish carcasses to head off decomposition as some beachgoers turned back. Rotting fish and the strong odor of the algae has previously repelled locals and imperiled Florida's vital tourism sector for much of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK ACTORS WIN ALL EMMY GUEST CATEGORIES FOR FIRST TIME...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/awards/emmys-black-actors-sweep-guest-categories-1202933820/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in Emmy history, the trophies for all four guest actor categories went to African-American performers. Tiffany Haddish won best guest actress in a comedy for hosting “Satur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Moonves Accused of Sex Crimes, Assault in New Ronan Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/as-leslie-moonves-negotiates-his-exit-from-cbs-women-raise-new-assault-and-harassment-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six additional women have accused the television executive of sexual misconduct, as the board of the CBS Corporation weighs the terms of his departure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
