<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Group that brought down Keystone XL faces own agonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/20/350org-mckibben-boeve-keystone-00009866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the upstart that changed the face of America’s environmental movement. But 350.org, founded by the legendary Bill McKibben, has been laid low by a budget crunch, equity fights and union strife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing ceremony: Games marked by restrictions, boycotts, and doping scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/beijing-winter-olympics-draw-close-rcna16610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Games had the strictest Covid restrictions yet, and were overshadowed by a U.S.-led diplomatic boycott over China's human rights record and blindsided by a high-profile doping saga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserves easiest route to Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-cancels-plan-to-withdraw-troops-from-belarus-preserving-its-easiest-route-to-strike-ukraine-s-capital-kyiv/ar-AAU5PS8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard deploys for new emergency: Teacher shortages...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/20/new-twist-in-pandemics-impact-on-schools-substitutes-in-camouflage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESTANCIA, N.M. — The chorus of small voices ringing from a third-grade classroom on a recent morning signaled how far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next affordable city already too expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/The-Next-Affordable-City-Is-Already-Too-Expensive-16931227.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it was the date night when he and his wife spent two hours driving 19 miles to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowy money built steel empire -- with bank's help...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2022/02/20/Ihor-Kolomoisky-US-banks-warren-ohio-steel-plant-ukraine/stories/202202200063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months after Ukraine oligarch Ihor Kolomoisky and his partners abandoned an Ohio steel plant and left scores of workers without jobs, financial crime experts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madoff sister, husband dead in possible murder-suicide...</title>
      <link>https://bocanewsnow.com/2022/02/19/murder-suicide-bernie-madoffs-sister-dead-in-boynton-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bocanewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bodies Of Madoff Sister, Brother-In-Law, Found In Valencia Lakes. BY: ANDREW COLTON | Editor and Publisher BOYNTON BEACH, FL (BocaNewsNow.com) (Copyright © 2022 MetroDesk Media, LLC) [EXCLUSIVE] — The sister of disgraced financier Bernie Madoff was killed in a murder-suicide in Valencia Lakes, West of Boynton Beach. Her husband, Marvin Weiner, is also dead. The […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to arm resistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/19/west-plans-to-arm-resistance-if-russian-forces-occupy-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invasion ‘must be seen to fail’, says Boris Johnson, as western allies hold secret talks about how to give military backing to Kyiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abused' Prince Andrew 'sex slave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4724511/jean-luc-brunel-dead-jeffrey-epstein-prince-andrew-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s pal Jean-Luc Brunel who is alleged to have also abused Prince Andrew “sex slave” Virginia Giuffre has been found dead in prison. The disgraced fashion agent was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fortress Australia' re-opens after 2-year closure...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/fortress-australia-re-opens-after-two-year-covid-closure-01645362307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia opens its international borders to all vaccinated tourists Monday, nearly two years after the island nation first imposed some of the world's strictest Covid-19 travel restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine family 'fears for her safety'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/19/ghislaine-maxwells-family-fears-for-safety-after-jean-luc-brunel-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of Ghislaine Maxwell say they fear for her safety after model agent Jean-Luc Brunel was found hanged in his Paris prison cell on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky rips West for inaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/zelensky-rips-the-west-for-inaction-as-shelling-makes-russia-ukraine-war-seem-increasingly-imminent/ar-AAU4UGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia plans biggest war in Europe since 1945...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-60448162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson tells BBC that intelligence suggests Russia intends to launch an invasion encircling Kyiv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crises keep travel-hungry Biden close to White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/594971-crises-keep-travel-hungry-biden-close-to-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden wants to leave Washington more and promote his policies directly to the American people, but outside circumstances — such as the resurgence of the pandemic or the threat of war between Russia and Ukraine — keep pulling him back to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris: 'Real possibility of war in Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/video/ukraine-crisis-we-are-talking-about-the-real-possibility-of-war-in-europe-says-kamala-harris-12547076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Vice President Kamala Harris told reporters in Munich that "we are talking about the real possibility of war in Europe".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeii: Rebirth of Italy dead city that nearly died again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-technology-business-italy-europe-fd7499b179f254ad442c468fdc94394b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POMPEII, Italy (AP) — In a few horrible hours, Pompeii was turned from a vibrant city into an ash-embalmed wasteland, smothered by a furious volcanic eruption in A.D. 79. Then in this century, the excavated Roman city appeared alarmingly close to a second death, assailed by decades of neglect, mismanagement and scant systematic maintenance of the heavily visited ruins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron says final NBA season will be played with son...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/20/sport/lebron-james-cavaliers-lakers-bronny-nba-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebron James said there are no certainties over his future in the NBA, though he is certain about one thing -- he'd like to play his final season alongside his son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Infected in England won't need to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boris-johnson-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-pandemics-2a717a276b483431f30622f7fa7602cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — People with COVID-19 won't be legally required to self-isolate in England starting in the coming week, the U.K. government has announced, as part of a plan for “living with COVID” that is also likely to see testing for the coronavirus scaled back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE NUKE DRILLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-oversee-nuclear-drills-ukraine-crisis-mounts-2022-02-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's strategic nuclear forces held exercises overseen by President Vladimir Putin on Saturday, and Washington accused Russian troops massed near Ukraine's border of advancing and being "poised to strike".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minister dives for cover as frontline heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220219-ukraine-minister-dives-for-cover-as-frontline-heats-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bent in a semi-crouch Ukraine's interior minister ran back from an exposed frontline position, as mortar shells crashed in the fields around him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New study finds Ivermectin ineffective...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-697027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients administered Ivermectin had a "notably higher" incidence of adverse events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once-taboo ketamine booms for at-home mental care...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220220-once-taboo-ketamine-booms-for-us-at-home-mental-care</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are paying to get a star of the psychedelic medicine movement –- ketamine -– shipped to them for at-home mental health treatments that are being called both a breakthrough and a gamble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truckers Arrested at Gunpoint as Police Advance Against Ottawa Protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-canada-ontario-arrests-9125c793e27a3fce81d3baaa953d6f2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA, Ontario (AP) — Hundreds of police in riot gear swept through Canada’s capital Saturday, retaking control of the streets around the Parliament buildings and appearing to end the siege of Ottawa after three weeks of protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison pumps $15M into super PAC aligned with Tim Scott...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/19/larry-ellison-pumps-15m-into-super-pac-aligned-with-tim-scott-00010377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The donation brings the Oracle chair's giving to the group, Opportunity Matters Fund, to $25 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th Shot In Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/19/health/fourth-covid-19-vaccine-dose-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world approaches the second anniversary of the declaration of the Covid-19 pandemic by the World Health Organization, on March 11, more nations are rolling out -- or are discussing the possibility of -- fourth doses of coronavirus vaccine for their most vulnerable. In the United States, leading public health officials say they are "very carefully" monitoring if or when fourth doses might be needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once savvy, NBC Olympics deal shakier after Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-figure-skating-eileen-gu-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-7f07dd3e1a4b299d9171e5ee2b53410a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — There were many reasons to think NBC made a savvy business deal in 2014 when it locked up the American media rights to the Olympics through 2032 for $7.75 billion. As the Beijing winter games come to a close, it's harder to see them now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
