<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Poop-testing startup, compared to THERANOS, charged in $60M fraud scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/ubiome-richman-apte-sec-filing-charges-fraud-16042042.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A married pair of San Francisco entrepreneurs were indicted Thursday on multiple federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos highlight secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-border-patrols-immigration-4462413114790eebc81ba82857c475b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden's administration has tried for weeks to keep the public from seeing images like those that emerged Monday showing immigrant children in U.S. custody at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious new system keeps migrants guessing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/honduras-mexico-coronavirus-pandemic-immigration-central-america-1cbd87dabb52664295e50683888eb578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROWNSVILLE, Texas (AP) — After hearing rumors that Central American families with younger children were being allowed into the U.S., Irma Paz left Honduras with her husband and two kids on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics accuse 'white shark Mafia' of blocking research...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/shark-fight-pits-state-against-private-research-group/35813385#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would seem to be the collegial world of local shark research has in fact become a simmering feud between competing factions, with some saying the public is the loser because the research is not keeping up with great white's growing incursions on our local waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straphanger urinates on Asian woman in NYC subway car...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/22/straphanger-urinates-on-asian-woman-in-nyc-subway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man urinated on an Asian woman aboard a Queens-bound subway train over the weekend, cops said Monday. The disgusting act unfolded around 1:30 p.m. Saturday when the creep pulled out his penis on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver allegedly tries to kidnap passenger...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/uber-driver-allegedly-tries-to-kidnap-passenger/10440958/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamal Essalak is accused of trying to kidnap an Uber passenger in Boston last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Iger On Life After DISNEY: 'I'm Not Retiring. I Can't Possibly Do That'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/bob-iger-on-life-after-disney-im-not-retiring-i-cant-possibly-do-that</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top FOX producer dies from corona...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/22/media/fox-business-network-producer-eric-spinato-death/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Spinato, the head booker and senior story editor for the Fox Business Network, died over the weekend, the network said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia: Another tax-free haven?</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/opinion/commentary/ct-opinion-west-virginia-tax-cut-cal-thomas-20210322-ukxmrtq5ojgijmkne3wykxd7vm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice wants to eliminate the state's income tax. Syndicated columnist Cal Thomas explains why he thinks it's a great idea — and why other states should take note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO says he'll try to give 100-hour-a-week workers Saturdays off...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/22/goldman-ceo-tells-exhausted-workers-hell-try-to-give-them-saturdays-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs boss David Solomon has heard the complaints from junior bankers about their 100-hour work weeks — and he promises he’ll try to give them Saturdays off. In a voice memo lat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overstimulated? Stocks soar 75% in historic 12-month run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-stock-markets-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-028b5d5d24b425788df8ee59123e0ad8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — It was one year ago that the terrifying free fall for the stock market suddenly ended, ushering in one of its greatest runs. On March 23, 2020, the S&amp;P 500 fell 2.9%. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen Loses 1 Million Viewers After Apologies for Toxic Workplace...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/22/ellen-degeneres-loses-1-million-viewers-after-apologies-for-toxic-workplace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Ellen DeGeneres returned from a summer hiatus to open the 18th season of her daytime talk show in September,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's top diplomat dons anti-lockdown mask: 'FCKNG QRNTN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-china-lavrov-mask/russias-top-diplomat-dons-anti-lockdown-mask-bearing-profane-slogan-idUSKBN2BE2LS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov donned an anti-lockdown mask during a visit to China on Monday which bore a profanity-laden slogan that his ministry said suited him "just right".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ leads nation in new positive tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2021/03/nj-reports-28-covid-deaths-2608-cases-as-state-leads-nation-in-new-positive-tests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 18% of New Jersey's adults have been fully vaccinated in the three months since the first COVID shots were administered, but cases have continued to increase in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK unveils plan for smaller, more high-tech armed forces...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-unveils-plan-smaller-more-173704346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain plans to cut the size of its army and boost spending on drones, robots and a new “cyber force” under defense plans announced by the government on Monday. Defense Secretary Ben Wallace said the British Army would shrink from 76,500 soldiers to 72,500 by 2025. Wallace said the military would no longer be “overstretched and underequipped” and that new investment in equipment, infrastructure and technology “marks a shift from mass mobilization to information age speed, readiness and relevance for confronting the threats of the future.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Millenial put on 41 pounds!</title>
      <link>https://www.apa.org/news/press/releases/2021/03/march-weight-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apa.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>42% report undesired weight gain...</title>
      <link>https://us4.campaign-archive.com/?u=a2680485cafe47a9affc149a3&amp;id=16febb9b4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us4.campaign-archive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARK ATTACKS BOY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9389123/Boy-nine-attacked-shark-minutes-walked-water-vacation-Miami-Beach.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Weiskopf, from Minnesota, was vacationing in Florida with his parents Kristine and Ren when he was attacked in the waters off Miami Beach on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cases rise across more than half of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/22/covid-cases-rise-across-more-than-half-of-the-us-as-country-races-to-vaccinate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Chief Medical Advisor Dr. Anthony Fauci urged states last week not to declare victory prematurely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ ARRESTS</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/21/miami-beach-city-commission-extends-curfew-causeway-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami Beach City Commission has voted to extend the entertainment district curfew and causeway closures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rep who called for Cuomo to resign apologizes for groping woman, steps down...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2556540/rep-tom-reed-apologizes-sexual-misconduct-cuomo-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW York Republican who called for Governor Andrew Cuomo to resign over sexual harassment allegations has himself apologized for groping a female lobbyist. U.S. Rep. Tom Reed was last week accuse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satirist says grateful to politicians but needs a break!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-tv-satirist-says-grateful-to-politicians-but-needs-a-break/ar-BB1eQkxk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Israel heads into its fourth election in two years, the presenter of the country's favourite satirical TV show has a request, and he's only half joking. "I would like us to finally have a stable government and make a boring programme," says Eyal Kitsis, frontman of the Channel 12 show "Eretz Nehederet" ("A Wonderful Country"). As much as Israel's political turmoil may be straining the patience of the electorate, it has been television gold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three fully-vaccinated Hawaii residents --  infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.kitv.com/story/43490943/3-fully-vaccinated-hawaii-residents-contract-covid19-doh-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kitv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vaccine that is 95% effective will protect 95 out of 100 people, meaning 5% may still contract the virus if exposed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus killing nasal spray?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210322142323-9i5gq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPRAY:Israel, New Zealand OK sale of virus killing nasal spray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rebuffs FACEBOOK appeal in user tracking lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210322123811-xqncf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/FACEBOOK (URGENT):U.S. Supreme Court rebuffs Facebook appeal in user tracking lawsuit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air travelers top 1.5 million for first time since covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210322112906-vmla4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-AIRLINES (URGENT):U.S. air travelers top 1.5 million for first time since March 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's third wave of covid could head for Britain, warns Boris...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/covid-19-boris-johnson-warns-europes-third-wave-will-hit-uk-but-is-reassured-eu-doesnt-want-jabs-blockade-12253582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM plays down the prospect of an EU ban on COVID jabs after speaking to Emmanuel Macron and Angela Merkel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravers feel the music at socially distanced silent disco in Barcelona...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321160311-0pq6v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-SILENT DISCO (PIX, TV):Ravers feel the music at socially distanced silent disco in Barcelona</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens US Army base and top general...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/national-security-iran-only-on-ap-army-1285df40348182e1b74dc403607c5928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has made threats against Fort McNair, an Army post in the U.S. capital, and against the Army’s vice chief of staff, two senior U.S. intelligence officials said. They said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI BEACH MOVES TO SHUT DOWN SPRING BREAK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/miami-beach-curfew-shut-down-spring-break-partying-fd842ba507cc96beb0a3795ad6578364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A party-ending curfew imposed after fights, gunfire, property destruction and dangerous stampedes broke out among huge crowds of people in Miami Beach could extend...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden aims to prevent border crossings from swamping agenda...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-mexico-immigration-alejandro-mayorkas-f6bd1d1e3741d985ae658eba0fd94df0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is scrambling to manage a growing humanitarian and political challenge at the U.S.-Mexico border that threatens to overshadow its ambitious legislative...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli election seen as referendum on divisive Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-referendums-benjamin-netanyahu-elections-coronavirus-vaccine-d1f466f8329f70cc231a318419852558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israelis vote Tuesday in their fourth parliamentary election in just two years. Once again, the race boils down to a referendum on Prime Minister Benjamin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill to aid publishers vs. FACEBOOKGOOGLE rises again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bill-aid-us-publishers-vs-google-facebook-307c451756af1d9a517bf72e37a58945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A congressional effort to bolster U.S. news organizations in negotiations with Big Tech has supporters hoping that third time's the charm. The bill, the Journalism Competition and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle-aged couple busted for lewd spring break encounter in Florida park...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/veteran-spring-breakers-321965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 21--Along with the drunken collegians rampaging across Florida this weekend, a couple in their forties allegedly engaged in an illicit spring break encounter that ended with their arrest for l</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: VIAGRA Also Lengthens Lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/viagra-erectile-dysfunction-longer-life-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOLNA, Sweden — Taking Viagra may do more than just benefit a man’s love life. A new study finds the erectile dysfunction drug can also help lengthen a patient’s lifespan, too. Researchers at the Karolinska Institutet in Sweden report that men who have survived a heart attack could prolong their life by taking the drug.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin, Once Holdout, Says He'll Get Jab!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-once-a-holdout-says-he-ll-take-covid-vaccine-tuesday/ar-BB1eQ9XF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said he plans to get vaccinated on Tuesday against Covid-19, more than three months after Russia started mass inoculations to protect the population from the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump predicted news ratings would 'tank if I'm not there.' He wasn't wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-predicted-news-ratings-would-e2-80-98tank-if-i-e2-80-99m-not-there-e2-80-99-he-wasn-e2-80-99t-wrong/ar-BB1eQdd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most national networks and news sites have seen their audience numbers drop since Inauguration Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows water hundreds of feet below surface of Lake Michigan is warming...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/study-shows-water-hundreds-of-feet-below-the-surface-of-lake-michigan-is-warming/article_99ab4cef-5c5b-5bbc-ac27-57d72371355d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Climate change is reaching all the way down to the depths of one of Earth’s largest lakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the (generation) gap: Young Britons ponder point of having monarchy...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/mind-the-generation-gap-young-britons-ponder-point-of-having-a-monarchy/article_73747b1f-f188-54b1-b627-1a3748d306ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Pandemic lockdowns and lack of opportunity drove 24-year-old drama school graduate Sarah Evans back to her family home in small-town Wales. In the general store where she works,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Pauses Further Reopenings as Case Counts Rise...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/news/coronavirus/nj-reopenings-on-pause-amid-rise-in-covid-variants-gov-murphy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey residents will not see any new reopening announcements in the coming weeks as the state battles a surge in COVID-19 variants, Gov. Phil Murphy said Monday. The governor, speaking on CNN,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic surfing hopeful killed by lightning while training...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/03/22/sport/katherine-diaz-killed-surfing-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 22-year-old Olympic surfing hopeful from El Salvador has died while training for an upcoming qualifying competition, the country's National Institute for Sport (INDES) has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first ship tunnel to be built under Norwegian mountains...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/norway-ship-tunnel/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway has got the go-ahead to construct a $300 million underground route to allow vessels navigate the country's treacherous Stadhavet Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FRANCIS AND THE GODFATHER': Is Hollywood creatively bankrupt?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/entertainment/movies/francis-and-the-godfather-is-hollywood-becoming-creatively-bankrupt/ar-BB1ePzWz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In case you haven’t heard, they are making a movie about the making of the greatest movie ever made. No, not Citizen Kane – David Fincher covered that in Mank. Francis and The Godfather is about … (spoiler alert) … The Godfather. It looks to be a prestige affair. Directed by Barry Levinson and starring Jake Gyllenhaal (as producer Robert Evans), Elle Fanning (as his wife Ali MacGraw), Elisabeth Moss (Eleanor Coppola) and, as the 31-year-old...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jihadis could soon launch attacks in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1413160/Jihadi-terrorists-launch-space-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JIHADIS could soon launch attacks in space because satellites impact our everyday lives, according to the head of the RAF. Air Chief Marshal Sir Mike Wigston, Chief of the Air Staff, said future wars will be won or lost in orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican MAGA Fan Flames...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/mexican-maga-conspiracy-theorists-fan-085202551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyTIJUANA, Mexico—As President Joe Biden comes under fire from all sides over an emerging migrant crisis at the southern border, two Mexican social media influencers are regularly visiting a camp here to rile up their U.S.-based viewers. Among other things, the Trump devotees are spreading false conspiracy theories about an orchestrated “invasion”—and “child trafficking” funded by Democrats.But one of the influencers, who occasionally contributes to a U.S. right-wing media network, is a deportee with a federal drug-trafficking conviction who has since repeatedly re-entered the U.S. to broadcast with Marjorie Taylor Greene allies, including a longtime friend of hers, The Daily Beast has learned. The other influencer is a U.S. and Mexican citizen who was filmed shoving a migrant child.Hundreds of asylum seekers from Central America, Mexico, Haiti, and other countries are living in tents in a plaza just south of San Diego. They include new arrivals and families who have been waiting months or years for a chance to apply for asylum since former President Donald Trump threw up unprecedented barriers to legal entry, some of which Biden has yet to undo. Many fear for their lives because of gang violence in Tijuana and death threats at home.Now, stuck in limbo, they must also contend with the xenophobia, racism, and hostility the conspiracy theorist livestreamers are stirring up as a sort of twisted, homegrown continuation of MAGA-style hate in Mexico.Border Officer Smuggled Drugs Into Prison for Convicted Killer Boyfriend: FedsAt the camp on Wednesday, masked children played in the sunlight, maneuvering donated toys between their tents. A 21-year-old Guatemalan woman, who spoke under the condition of anonymity because she does not feel safe in Mexico, said she had been in Tijuana for two years. She showed The Daily Beast a file of documents she was hoping to present to U.S. officials to make her case for asylum, including the death certificates of two cousins she said were killed by a gang. One of the livestreamers, Oscar Ramirez, had visited the camp earlier in the day.“They make us feel bad,” she said of the propagandists. “They reduce our prospects of being able to enter the U.S.”Ramirez is a Mexican Trump fan known as “Oscar El Blue.” He has more than 86,000 followers between Facebook and YouTube, and was featured on Steve Bannon’s “War Room” three times this month as a self-styled “independent” reporter. With slicked-back hair and a large “45” tattoo on his arm, he appeared on Bannon’s show with Ben Bergquam, a correspondent for Real America’s Voice, a conservative news network founded in 2018 that streams Bannon’s show.Bergquam, who calls himself a Christian conservative, promotes hysteria about immigration and defends the integrity of the Proud Boys, the far-right gang that has been designated a hate group by the Southern Poverty Law Center, a terrorist entity by the Canadian government, and featured prominently in the January attack on the U.S. Capitol. He refers to congresswoman Greene, known for promoting QAnon conspiracy theories, as a “friend” in a photograph with her. (A spokesperson for Greene did not respond to a request for comment.)At the camp alongside Bergquam, Ramirez called Tijuana the most “violent and delinquent [city] in the world,” saying his hometown can’t handle the asylum seekers. In his Mexican accent, he told Bannon, “Tijuana citizens are paying a high price for this globalization.” Ramirez also claimed without evidence that U.S. nonprofits were promoting “fake families.”In another appearance on Bannon’s show alongside Bergquam, this time in Yuma, Ramirez warned of “a lot of cartel activity” and said he had just met suspicious men who looked Middle Eastern. “I tried talking to them in Spanish, and they didn’t understand a word,” he said. “This is just an open gate!”Ramirez claims he is only against illegal immigration and that he is trying to help asylum seekers and combat child trafficking. “I’m not promoting no negative feelings toward immigrants,” he told The Daily Beast. “I’m an immigrant myself.”But Ramirez has publicly stated that Central Americans who want to immigrate to the U.S. are “lazy,” in search of “easy money, easy welfare.” He frequently conflates asylum seekers and their advocates with traffickers.People who peddle white supremacist and race-baiting ideas have long used brown and Black allies as shields against criticism. Having Mexicans on the border performing right-wing political stances on immigration blunts allegations of racism, despite the established problem of colorism and internalized racism among Latinos.As Ramirez’s star rises by virtue of his fearmongering about the border, Real America’s Voice viewers are likely unaware he has a federal drug trafficking conviction. According to court records reviewed by The Daily Beast, he was sentenced to four years in prison for importing methamphetamine in 2008. A service dog flagged his vehicle at the port of entry resulting in “the discovery of 23 packages of a white crystalline substance concealed inside the rocker panels,” including a package weighing nearly 25 kilograms that tested positive for meth. He said it was his “third smuggling venture,” per the records. He spent four years in prison before he was deported.Ramirez initially denied to comment on the case, accusing this reporter of trying to “cover up the enormous trafficking of children and humans.” But he later confirmed to The Daily Beast that he is the individual named in the court records and said, “It is something I did in my past, and I regret it very much.”Bannon and Real America’s Voice did not respond to requests for comment about their decision to feature a convicted drug trafficker as a talking head on border security.In a buried 2019 video, Ramirez alluded to a troubled past, telling viewers he had been struggling after the 2008 recession and made a mistake. “I got busted in the border and they took away everything,” he said, adding that it was his dream to return to the U.S.In April 2020, Ramirez’s dream came true: Less than two years after partnering with Bergquam at Real America’s Voice, he was apparently able to re-enter the U.S. in spite of his conviction, which made him inadmissible. A video shows him driving up to the El Paso port of entry with Anthony Agüero, another right-wing influencer whom Ramirez calls a “brother,” the other half of Ramirez’s Border Network News and a Bergquam associate. Agüero allegedly took part in the Jan. 6 insurrection and chanted with the Proud Boys, laughing hysterically as they tore up a Black Lives Matter sign. He is a close friend of Marjorie Taylor Greene, according to a CNN investigation, which also found he has a history of criminal violence.In videos published about a month after Trump shut down the border to asylum seekers and all non-essential traffic due to the pandemic, Ramirez and Agüero sat in a car without masks, grinning widely and cracking up as they drove up to the border. Ramirez thanked Agüero and said, “Second chances in life, they really happen,” he said. Later, apparently in El Paso, he celebrated, “I’m back in the United States of America as an essential worker!” He promised to continue fighting “the invasion of the caravans,” then headed to a rally to reopen Texas where protesters defied stay-at-home orders. Ramirez agreed with the protesters, saying not reopening was “crazy.” He has appeared on video visiting San Diego and Yuma, where he interviewed Sheriff Leon Wilmot about cartel activity at the border.According to the Immigration and Nationality Act, individuals convicted of drug trafficking are inadmissible to the United States without a very hard-to-get waiver from the Department of Homeland Security for a visa. That would be issued with a recommendation from the State Department or the attorney general. Immigration attorneys told The Daily Beast it would be virtually impossible to obtain the waiver without political connections or working as an informant. Under Trump, DHS limited its exercise of discretionary power, even for families with no criminal record.Ramirez told The Daily Beast he obtained a visa under the Trump administration but declined to give details, becoming agitated when pressed, telling this reporter to “be careful” because he knows “all the journalists” in Mexico. Neither DHS nor the Department of Justice responded to requests for information about Ramirez’s alleged visa. The State Department declined to comment, citing “privacy protections.” Agüero replied, “I don’t talk to fake news!” Berquam declined to comment on Ramirez’s case.Ramirez has also repeatedly dressed up in eye goggles, a face mask, a plastic face shield, and a full-body white suit, laughing at people who fear the coronavirus.“This is the way you look!” he said in one video, giggling.Ramirez’s fans often use the language of QAnon when railing against immigrants. “Those Kids need to be sent back,” one user commented on his page. “The DAMN DEMOCRATIC CABAL only wants children trafficking human trafficking caravan,” wrote another. “satan has control of the demoncrates!” a different person said. “Biden opened the flood gates, this is ALL his fault send them to him and Jill,” added another.Ramirez is not the only influencer in Tijuana triggering anti-immigrant feelings.This month, Paloma Zuniga, a dual U.S. and Mexican citizen known as “Paloma for Trump,” posted a video in which she argued with migrants who asked her to stop filming the camp. Many fear for their lives and do not want their images broadcast. She refused to stop, saying she was on a public street. “I’m not afraid of you!” she cried. Several people formed a blockade, chanting “Get out!” in Spanish. Some came close, and she told them that touching a person was a crime.She remarked wryly to her audience, “These are the people who want to come into America, guys.”Republicans Pray for a Border Crisis to Bring Biden DownZuniga claimed Ramirez, who is effectively her rival, turned the camp against her. They used to be collaborators, but now Zuniga is very upset with him and makes a number of accusations about him. Ramirez declined to comment about Zuniga, whose antagonistic style does its own damage. Wearing a “Make Tijuana Great Again” red baseball cap over her long dark hair, Zuniga garnered more than 70,000 followers under Trump, when asylum seekers arrived in caravans. In 2018, she was part of a confrontation in which some protesters hurled rocks and insults at the Central Americans. Zuniga later expressed regret for her involvement in the incident. Then, in 2019, she was filmed chasing and physically shoving a child who was trying to enter the U.S. with his father. “Go back!” she cried in Spanish. “You can’t enter, this is not your country!”Zuniga told The Daily Beast that she felt bad about that incident, too. “I was wrong for doing that,” she said. “What kind of demon got into me?”Facebook shut down her account in 2019. She started a new one, but was surpassed in followers by Ramirez. She insists she has nothing against asylum seekers, only their alleged organizers and alleged criminals hiding among them. Still, she has scared some families. A woman who came from Honduras fleeing death threats two years ago and is still waiting for a chance to request asylum told The Daily Beast that Zuniga tried to record her three-year-old daughter without permission. “She scares me,” she said on condition of anonymity because of her precarious situation. “She scares most of us.” Zuniga denies filming or photographing children without permission.In July 2019, Zuniga participated in a border wall symposium near El Paso organized by Bannon as part of the “We Build The Wall” campaign that got the former Trump aide arrested on charges of defrauding donors—at least until he was pardoned. At the event, speakers railed against an alleged invasion. Days later, prosecutors say a white racist executed 23 people at an El Paso Wal-Mart, citing a “Hispanic invasion.” Zuniga told The Daily Beast she condemns acts of violence, and doesn’t see a connection with her rhetoric. “I don’t believe killing people is the answer,” she said.Still, like Ramirez, Zuniga promotes unfounded conspiracy theories about “well-funded” organizations paying for migrants to flood the U.S.“The migrants are people who are very, very easy to manipulate, OK?” she said in one video.Zuniga previously partnered with Bergquam, who now broadcasts with Ramirez. As the border has again become a source of international concern, she has continued visiting the asylum seekers and making videos.Immigrant rights defenders are concerned the hysteria that the livestreamers are promoting could attract violent actors to the camp, or stall immigration reform efforts in Congress and keep doors closed to asylum seekers. That, in turn, could compel vulnerable people to risk their lives by entering illegally, such as a mother who recently drowned in the Pacific Ocean trying to swim to San Diego from Tijuana. This even as the number of migrant children in U.S. custody surges and officials reportedly consider flying people across the country and housing families in hotels to ease overcrowding.Meanwhile, the asylum seekers at the Tijuana camp continue to fantasize about one day finding safety in the country that is footsteps from where they sleep. If the past is any indication, few who manage to enter, even without drug-trafficking convictions or any criminal history, will be permitted to hold onto those dreams for very long.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An outsider's eye, an instant camera and America seen anew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mississippi-coronavirus-pandemic-only-on-ap-1d5d40b3d2c5c25578e498f36fe211ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through the lens of an instant camera, through the eyes of an outsider, oft-neglected corners of America take on a very different cast. There is beauty in the swing ride at the Mississippi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders tells Musk to 'focus on Earth' and pay more tax rather than spend wealth on space travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/bernie-sanders-elon-musk-focus-on-earth-pay-more-tax-2021-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Space travel is an exciting idea, but right now we need to focus on Earth and create a progressive tax system,' said Senator Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside crowded border patrol tent in Donna, Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/photos-overcrowded-border-patrol-migrant-tents-0525a96b-0dc8-473f-b59c-38b0b3e52760.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because the Biden administration has restricted media coverage at housing facilities, images like these offer a rare window into conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ahead but win uncertain in new Israel vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210322-netanyahu-ahead-but-win-uncertain-in-new-israel-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu ahead but win uncertain in new Israel vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops' posts to private FACEBOOK group show hostility, hate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-race-and-ethnicity-shootings-police-22355db9b0b7561ce91fa2ddfbcd2fc1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — In a private Facebook group called the Pittsburgh Area Police Breakroom, many current and retired officers spent the year criticizing chiefs that took a knee or officers who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where would major tsunami strike? Malibu, Venice, Long Beach get ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/projects/la-tsunami-maps-tracking-risk-california-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. tsunami maps: Tracking risk along the California coast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flock to Iceland's erupting volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210322-thousands-flock-to-iceland-s-erupting-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands flock to Iceland's erupting volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base jumper plunges to death from at Florida hotel after parachute failed to open in time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9388307/BASE-jumper-plunges-death-14th-floor-balcony-Florida-hotel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man, believed to have been in his 20s, has died after his parachute failed to open in time during a BASE jump from a 14th floor balcony at the Sunrise Beach Resort in Panama City Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Das Auto' goes electric as VW takes on TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/das-auto-goes-electric-vw-103617199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Volkswagen chief executive Herbert Diess joined Twitter in January, he used his first tweet to warn pioneering electric car maker Elon Musk that he was coming after him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determined to Tax Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-determined-to-tax-rich-after-windfalls-from-covid-crisis/ar-BB1ePhGQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s economic team at the White House is determined to make good on his campaign pledge to raise taxes on the rich, emboldened by mounting data showing how well America’s wealthy did financially during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Navy Starts Drills to Protect Oil Sites as Attacks Mount...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-navy-starts-drills-protect-064903110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia started naval exercises in the Persian Gulf to improve its ability to foil “terrorist attacks” on oil facilities, underscoring the kingdom’s concern about a rise in drone and missile strikes claimed by Yemen’s Houthi rebels.The exercises will enhance the security of vital installations and oil fields, and secure freedom of navigation in the region’s waters, the official Saudi Press Agency said. They will be conducted by the Royal Saudi Navy with participation from Saudi Aramco, the state oil company.This month alone, the Houthis, who are backed by Iran, have claimed assaults on a fuel depot in Jeddah, the Ras Tanura export terminal and a refinery in Riyadh, the Saudi capital.The Saudi government said the missiles used for the March 19 refinery attack were made in Iran.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's Digital Dollar Momentum Worries Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/federal-digital-dollar-momentum-worries-060000433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The financial services industry, braced for what could be its biggest disruption in decades, is about to get an early glimpse at the Federal Reserve’s work on a new digital currency.Wall Street is not thrilled.Banks, credit card companies and digital payments processors are nervously watching the push to create an electronic alternative to the paper bills Americans carry in their wallets, or what some call a digital dollar and others call a Fedcoin.As soon as July, officials at the Federal Reserve Bank of Boston and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, which have been developing prototypes for a digital dollar platform, plan to unveil their research, said James Cunha, who leads the project for the Boston Fed.A digital currency could fundamentally change the way Americans use money, leading some financial firms to lobby the Fed and Congress to slow its creation -- or at least ensure they’re not cut out.Seeing the threat to their profits, the banks’ main trade group has told Congress a digital dollar isn’t needed, while payment companies like Visa Inc. and Mastercard Inc. are trying to work with central banks to make sure the new currencies can be used on their networks.“Everyone is afraid that you could disrupt all the incumbent players with a whole new form of payment,” said Michael Del Grosso, an analyst for Compass Point Research &amp; Trading LLC.Lawmakers, U.S. Treasury Department officials and the Fed haven’t yet approved the rollout of a U.S. virtual currency, which could still be years away. Nor have they decided how a digital dollar would interact with the existing global payments network. Still, the U.S. and other countries seem committed enough to digitizing their currencies that it’s making financial industry executives nervous.“The fire has been lit,” said Josh Lipsky, who has helped convene government officials from the U.S. and other countries working on digital currencies as director of the GeoEconomics Center at the Atlantic Council. “The world is moving very quickly on these projects.”At issue are forms of digital cash being considered by the U.S. and other governments. The growing popularity of Bitcoin, Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies, whose market value has grown to more than $1 trillion, inspired the projects. Unlike those privately created tokens, the new currencies would be issued by central banks as an alternative to paper bills. Cash wouldn’t go away, but its use would likely decline.Using the currencies could be as simple as holding up the screen of a mobile phone to be scanned. Behind the scenes, the digital cash would move from one account to another. This is similar to how most money already works -- the majority of U.S. dollars are just digital entries in bank accounts -- but the new currency could potentially avoid the go-between of a commercial bank or credit-card network. For vendors, settlement would happen almost immediately, without having to wait for the money or worry about fraud.The U.S. effort got an extra push last month, when Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said such a project could help Americans who don’t have access to the banking system.In video remarks last week to a payments conference in Basel, Switzerland, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell may have eased some of the banks’ concerns when he said “digital currencies would need to be integrated into existing payment systems alongside cash and other forms of money.”Cunha said the Boston Fed and MIT hope to unveil some of their work in the third quarter, including at least two prototype software platforms that could move, store and settle transactions made with digital dollars. He wouldn’t say if either platform uses the blockchain technology that underlies Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Once the prototypes are released, Cunha said, others will be able to see and build on the code.The Fed’s work is meant to show what’s possible without taking a stand on major issues that the central bank, Treasury and Congress must address, Cunha said. These include whether the Fed itself should host customer accounts, whether to allow anonymity, and what protections consumers would have in case of a cyber-breach or mistaken transaction.“We think it’s important that we not wait for the policy debate because then we’ll be a year or so behind,” Cunha said. “This will take significant outreach to the industry and serious debate.”The potential that the central bank could cut banks out of their middleman role in the lucrative U.S. payments system is causing angst among banks.So is the push coming from Ohio Democratic Senator Sherrod Brown, the new chairman of the Senate Banking Committee. Brown is urging the Fed to move quickly to create digital-currency accounts for Americans who can’t easily access the financial system and have been forced to deal with payday lenders who charge higher fees and interest rates. Brown’s plan could threaten the deposits that commercial banks rely on to make mortgages and other loans.“Rushing anything of this potential magnitude could introduce unintended consequences that threaten the stability of the banking system without contributing meaningfully to economic inclusion,” said Steve Kenneally, senior vice president of payments at the American Bankers Association.The ABA, which says it’s lobbying Congress on the issue, last year in written testimony called the digital dollar a costly solution in search of a nonexistent problem.Two lobbyists for a large bank said they’re in contact with lawmakers to keep track of the issue. They expect lobbying to pick up once banks can actually see the Fed’s work and how it might affect them, said the lobbyists, who requested anonymity to discuss internal conversations.Interest in a digital currency has gathered momentum in part because many banks take days to give consumers access to checks deposited in their accounts and some charge stiff overdraft fees. Those without bank accounts sometimes must pay high fees to cash paychecks or transmit money to relatives.Some of the profits of credit-card companies, such as Visa and Mastercard, could be at risk if the new currencies let Americans more easily make transactions without their involvement and fees.Spokespeople from both companies say their firms are working with central banks to ensure the new currencies can run over their networks. Mastercard in February began to issue pre-paid debit cards loaded with the “Sand Dollar,” a digital currency issued by the Bahamas.“We’re increasingly having conversations with central banks as they think about designing potential central bank digital currency, CBDC, and we’re talking to them about how they think about design,” said Visa’s North America president Oliver Jenkyn, at a Morgan Stanley conference earlier this month. “So there’s a lot of talking, but there’s actually a lot of action alongside it as well.”Other countries are further along. China is currently piloting a digital yuan in several cities. Lipsky said there’s a chance its currency could be ready for a broader debut at the 2022 Winter Olympics in Beijing, which he said could cause tensions if American athletes are asked to use a currency that the Chinese government can completely track.Brown earlier this month sent a letter to Powell urging him to speed up the research. “We cannot be left behind,” Brown wrote.Among other threats, Brown pointed to the development by Facebook Inc. and other companies of their own cryptocurrency, once called Libra. That currency, since renamed Diem, was slated to launch in 2020 but has struggled to win regulatory approval.Advocates of existing cryptocurrencies, like Bitcoin, have mixed feelings about the Federal Reserve muscling into the industry.A Fedcoin could acclimate Americans to purchasing Bitcoin, said Jerry Brito, who heads Coin Center, a cryptocurrency advocacy group. But depending on the government’s direction, such a currency could be used to track Americans’ spending, destroying the partial anonymity that was once the promise of crypto, he said.A U.S. digital dollar could also put the final nail in the coffin for Bitcoin as a means of exchange, Brito said. Crypto enthusiasts have already started to acknowledge that’s happening anyway, and instead tout the currency as a store of value or “digital gold.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Next phase' of criminal probe into Trump finances: Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-investigation-witnesses-ins/next-phase-of-criminal-probe-into-trump-finances-finding-witnesses-idUSKBN2BE15X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators in a criminal probe of former U.S. President Donald Trump’s real-estate business are combing through millions of pages of newly acquired records with an eye toward identifying witnesses who can bring the documents to life for a jury, say two people familiar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police detective divorces wife after she was photographed with another man at MAGA riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386187/Police-detective-divorces-wife-photographed-man-Capitol.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Heinl (left), 55, of Ross Township, Pennsylvania, was photographed inside the US Capitol building alongside Kenneth Grayson on January 6, the FBI alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after drone found with a bag of heroin on board...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-arrested-drone-found-bag-191047706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation is continuing to determine whether the suspect was using the drone to sell drugs, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321235557-he6bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAKISTAN-LGBT/MADRASA (TV, PIX):A transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI BEACH DECLARES EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-19-pandemic-miami-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-4c4ac71405e13f063e38dde30ef260d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Pointing to over 1,000 arrests in one of the nation’s top party spots, Miami Beach officials warned Sunday that the unruly spring break crowd gathering by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys indictment says group leaders used radios and encrypted chats to coordinate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/proud-boys-capitol-riot-coordination-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the men used paramilitary gear, handheld radios and encrypted messaging applications to coordinate with other Proud Boys before and during the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremists in police ranks spark growing concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/elections/2021/03/21/police-charged-capitol-riot-reignite-concerns-racism-extremism/4738348001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Racially biased policing was already a concern. Now, charges against officers in the Capitol riot inflame fears of extremists infiltrating law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global shortage in computer chips 'reaches crisis point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/mar/21/global-shortage-in-computer-chips-reaches-crisis-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer price rises loom while dearth of semiconductors slow production from Samsung to Ford</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH BEACH OVERRUN BY MASKLESS HORDES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/miami-beach-freaks-out-over-massive-spring-break-crowds-declares-state-of-emergency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time and time again during this pandemic, tourists are ruining everything,” a Miami Beach resident said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb's plan to pay Black residents reparations could be national model...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-race-reparations/chicago-suburbs-plan-to-pay-black-residents-reparations-could-be-a-national-model-idUSKBN2BD0B8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, in the Chicago suburb of Evanston, Cordelia Clark ran a restaurant out of her kitchen and parked cabs for her taxi company in her backyard because Black residents were effectively barred from owning or renting storefronts in town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  How 'Owning the Libs' Became GOP's Core Belief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/21/owning-the-libs-history-trump-politics-pop-culture-477203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weird journey of a tongue-in-cheek catchphrase from conservative-mocking putdown to the defining tenet of the Republican Party’s way of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican AGs take blowtorch to President's agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/21/gop-attorneys-general-biden-477365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On everything from climate change to immigration and abortion rights, GOP attorneys general are leading the charge to dismantle White House policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Vaccine Obsession Hasn't Swung Election to Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-vaccine-obsession-hasn-t-swung-election-to-him/ar-BB1eNCYc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine “world champions.” Israel’s “the first” to return to normal life. Other leaders in awe of Benjamin Netanyahu’s achievements in taming the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRAZENECA, once touted as a pandemic slayer, faces challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/astrazeneca-once-touted-as-a-pandemic-slayer-faces-challenges/ar-BB1eODgv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the stakes hadn’t been so high, the saga might have felt like a soap opera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biden's failure to contain the border surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/no-end-in-sight-inside-the-biden-administration-s-failure-to-contain-the-border-surge/ar-BB1eNeEh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration has emerged as one of the administration’s most urgent challenges — seized on by Republicans as a political cudgel, posing risks to Democrats in the 2022 midterms and potentially undermining Biden’s governing agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black leaders react to crackdown: 'Unnecessary force'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/black-leaders-react-to-south-beach-spring-break-curfew-crackdown-unnecessary-force/ar-BB1eOwEy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 21—After weeks of uninhibited partying on South Beach by spring breakers, police turned away throngs of people — many of them Black — from world-famous Ocean Drive with a SWAT truck, pepper balls and sound cannons. The tactics were intended to enforce an 8 p.m. curfew announced only hours earlier on Saturday to rid the city of what police and politicians have described as unruly and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company says ORAL covid vaccine on its way...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-company-says-oral-covid-19-vaccine-on-its-way-662712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oral vaccine could potentially allow for people to self vaccinate at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considering releasing illegals into USA without court date...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-rio-grande-valley-considering-releasing-migrants-into-u-s-without-court-date</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Fox News has learned from a senior source with Customs and Border Protection (CBP) that a plan is under consideration for Border Patrol agents in the Rio Grande Valley Sector (RGV) to begin releasing illegal border crossers who claim asylum without issuing a Notice to Appear (NTA) - meaning they will depart custody without a court date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN VOGUE staffer who supported editor's ousting used 'N-word' in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/senior-teen-vogue-staffer-mccammonds-ousting-used-n-word-in-decade-old-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Teen Vogue staffer who posted a letter expressing concern about Alexi McCammond for past tweets racist against Asian Americans used the N-word in tweets from over 10 years ago herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Germany police clash with protesters against new virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386215/Angela-Merkel-extends-Germanys-Covid-restrictions-month-despite-anti-lockdown-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters angry at Covid-19 restrictions rallied in cities across Europe over the weekend, even as several nations reimposed partial lockdowns to fight new surges in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT TEAMS MOVE IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9384843/Miami-Beach-unveils-curfew-uncontrollable-crowds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring breakers invading Miami Beach have become so uncontrollable that authorities imposed a curfew on Saturday as SWAT teams were seen moving in to clear people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad arrested after taking toddler into elephant enclosure at San Diego Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/21/us/san-diego-zoo-arrest-elephant-toddler/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A visitor at the San Diego Zoo was arrested on Friday shortly after taking his two-year-old daughter into an elephant enclosure, according to a press release from the San Diego Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 unaccompanied children in CBP custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/20/politics/unaccompanied-migrant-children-cbp/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more than 5,000 unaccompanied children in US Customs and Border Protection custody, according to documents obtained by CNN, up from 4,500 children days earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS: Govts 'to insist' on vaccines for flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-56460329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Governments are going to insist" on vaccines for international travellers, Qantas' boss tells the BBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Pilots Bumpy All-terrain Rig On Siberian Holiday...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/putin-pilots-bumpy-all-terrain-rig-on-siberian-holiday-01616327706?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, during a holiday in Siberia with Defence Minister Sergei Shoigu, piloted an all-terrain vehicle through thick woodland and traversed a swaying rope bridge, Kremlin footage showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSH FOR NEW NATIONAL HOLIDAY, 'EMANCIPATION DAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/national-holiday-emancipation-e9e8dc33-04e7-4390-a3bb-c1d867b3e036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a movement to create an official holiday, but not all supporters agree on the best date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/JanineStanwood/status/1373062537332293635?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid long-haulers still suffer extreme symptoms -- year later...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/20/these-covid-long-haulers-suffer-side-effects-a-year-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after getting COVID, these New Yorkers are still suffering shocking complications — forcing them to give up their jobs and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli court upholds school's barring of refusenik teacher...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321125834-n0iq2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-VACCINE (PIX):Israeli court upholds school's barring of COVID refusenik teacher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321113002-71rem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-MAFIA/ (PIX, TV):Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Springs military community works to address 'ideologies'...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/military/colorado-springs-military-community-to-address-extremism/article_effc1e48-839b-11eb-a6ee-03012c27f35d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spurred by the Jan. 6 storming of the U.S. Capitol, the military is taking a hard look at extremism in its ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infections continue to climb in Turkey amid relaxed measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-turkey-istanbul-coronavirus-pandemic-financial-markets-d501dffbb5a9cacedd28d81a3d60aa6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey’s weekly regional COVID-19 figures keep increasing and deaths rising as the country maintains more relaxed restrictions for now. The country's official death toll in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of 1 murder says he really killed 16...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-woodbury-new-jersey-new-mexico-missouri-tigers-mens-basketball-d2ac672be586e5332a7bc36e3b9e47c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODBURY, N.J. (AP) — A man charged with beating to death a New Jersey resident he says sexually abused him as a child now claims he has killed a total of 16 people, including his ex-wife and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON 'OUT INDEFINITELY'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nba-los-angeles-los-angeles-lakers-lebron-james-trae-young-d546428403947a7dbaf21a2b9ff983a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — LeBron James left in the second quarter with a high right ankle sprain that the Lakers said will sideline him indefinitely, and Los Angeles went on to fall 99-94 to the Atlanta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Married 66 years, husband, wife pass minutes apart of virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-florida-fort-lauderdale-lebanon-coronavirus-pandemic-ed9ea972b0ff037952a02aa864399043</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Bill and Esther Ilnisky spent nearly seven decades together as Christian ministers and missionaries, including stints in the Caribbean and Middle East before preaching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ties with Russia, China sink as Biden toes tough lines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-russia-vladimir-putin-china-national-security-550deda11d43e6bb7c1a8230ee8917ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. relations with its two biggest geo-political rivals are facing severe tests as President Joe Biden tries to assert America's place in the world and distinguish himself from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WAR WITHOUT END:   Defense chief arrives in Kabul on 1st trip to Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-afghanistan-lloyd-austin-ashraf-ghani-6d57e76434b146c6dfb93aeb208f3464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, on his first visit to Afghanistan as Pentagon chief, said Sunday that the Biden administration wants to see “a responsible end” to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama-era officials return to White House worth millions...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/obama-era-officials-return-white-house-worth-millions/story?id=76582015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As several Obama-era officials return to the White House under President Joe Biden, they're reuniting with fuller pockets according to new financial disclosure reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
