<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to tax tourists as influx grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/zealand-tax-tourists-fund-infrastructure-052910321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists to New Zealand are to be charged a special tax, under new government plans announced Friday to deal with the growing influx of holidaymakers coming from overseas. Visitor numbers have surged by nearly a third in the past three years to 3.8 million in the 12 months to April -- almost as big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President preps China tariff target list, Beijing ready to retaliate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-prepares-china-tariff-target-list-confrontation-escalates-014628928--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Friday was due to unveil a final list of Chinese imports that would face punishing tariffs, fanning fears of a trade war as Beijing warned that it could swiftly strike back. The threat of massive duties on billions of dollars of goods sent Shanghai stocks to their lowest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawking's voice to be beamed into space during memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hawkings-voice-beamed-space-during-memorial-044308410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A message from late British astrophysics giant Stephen Hawking will be beamed towards the nearest black hole as his remains are laid to rest in London's Westminster Abbey on Friday. As the ashes of the British theoretical physicist are interred, a specially-written composition featuring his famous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban chief who ordered Malala assassination 'killed in airstrike'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/taliban-chief-ordered-malala-assassination-104729550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the Pakistan Taliban has been targeted in a United States drone strike in eastern Afghanistan. Afghan officials said Mullah Fazlullah, who is one of the world's most wanted militant leaders, had been killed in Kunar province, but Pakistan security sources said his death had not yet been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Flee and Thieves Loot Venezuela's Reeling Oil Giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/workers-flee-and-thieves-loot-venezuela-s-reeling-oil-giant/17628941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL TIGRE, Venezuela — Thousands of workers are fleeing Venezuela’s state-owned oil company, abandoning once-coveted jobs made worthless by the worst inflation in the world. And now the hemorrhaging is threatening the nation’s chances of overcoming its long economic collapse, union leaders, oil executives and workers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's World Cup star accused of helping drug lord...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-rafael-marquez-20180615-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican soccer legend Rafael Marquez, who is preparing to compete in his fifth World Cup, was sanctioned last year by the U.S. Treasury Department for allegedly aiding a notorious drug trafficker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man On Horse Charged With DUI...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/horse-dui-boy-trampled-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armando Martinez Ruiz is now facing DUI charges. The spooked horse trampled an 8-year-old boy in the crowd, breaking his leg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITZ-CARLTON Crackdown Still Haunts the New Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/15/ritz-carlton-crackdown-still-haunts-the-new-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A climate of fear permeates the kingdom months after the government’s corruption purge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Immigration Drama Could Spell End For Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/angela-merkels-battle-with-bavaria-refugees-migration-masterplan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Looking to Dodge Property Tax Caps Turn to Alaskan Trusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/06/15/rich-looking-to-dodge-property-tax-caps-turn-to-alaskan-trusts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Looking to Dodge Property Tax Caps Turn to Alaskan Trusts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For House Flippers, Reality Meets Reality TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/15/realestate/for-house-flippers-reality-meets-reality-tv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new generation of real estate investors inspired by HGTV is discovering that renovation isn’t nearly as easy as it looks on television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We'll stop becoming president'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/fbi-agents-text-reportedly-disclosed-by-justice-watchdog-well-stop-trump-from-becoming-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent who worked on the special counsel's Russia probe texted another investigator that 'We'll stop' Donald Trump from getting elected president, The Washington Post reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed: GDP estimate rises to 4.8%...</title>
      <link>https://www.fxstreet.com/news/atlanta-fed-q2-gdp-estimate-rises-to-48-from-46-201806141617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fxstreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key conservative presses for shield law after seizure of NYT reporter's records...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/392322-key-conservative-presses-for-shield-law-after-seizure-of-nyt-reporters-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department’s seizure of a New York Times reporter’s private email and phone records has sparked one of President Trump’s top GOP allies in Congress to say he’ll aggressively pursue legislation to protect journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump campaign chief Manafort to ask judge not to jail him...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/former-trump-campaign-chief-manafort-to-ask-judge-not-to-jail-him-idUSKBN1JB12X </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort is set to ask a federal judge on Friday not to revoke his bail and send him to jail pending trial after Special Counsel Robert Mueller filed new charges of witness tampering last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Viva Le Resistance': Attorney removed over  texts...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5846147/FBI-lawyer-working-Muellers-Russia-probe-texted-colleague-Viva-le-Resistance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI lawyer exchanged messages after the election with another colleague and proclaimed: 'Vive la resistance.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray vision will soon give soldiers superhero ability to see through walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6536698/x-ray-vision-soldiers-able-see-through-walls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIONIC soldiers with X-ray vision could soon be a reality thanks to a new wireless system that uses radio-waves to map people’s movements behind walls. Researchers at MIT trained artificial i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies see report on FBI as path to undercut Mueller probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-allies-seize-on-DOJ-report-as-they-seek-to-12995738.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Thursday's report from the Justice Department's inspector general gave new and potent ammunition to President Donald Trump and his allies in their ongoing efforts to undermine special counsel Robert Mueller III's investigation of Russian interference during the 2016 presidential campaign. Even as Trump faces his own legal complications, Republicans quickly seized on the report as a meaningful development that they believe will further bruise Mueller's credibility with the public and bolster the president, whose administration has long been gripped by the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENTS RECEIVED FREE HANDOUTS FROM JOURNALISTS... </title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/agent-journalist-gifts-could-be-federal-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IG promises further reports on potential leaks for gifts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rollercoaster terror at Daytona Beach: Riders flung 34 FEET, others left hanging...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5846887/Daytona-Beach-Boardwalk-rollercoaster-derailed-two-people-fall-34-feet-ground.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screams filled the air at the Daytona Beach Boardwalk on Thursday night after a rollercoaster car derailed, dropping two people 34 feet to the ground and leaving eight others trapped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Employees Referred for Investigation...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/14/inspector-general-refers-five-fbi-employees-for-investigation-over-hostile-political-messages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department inspector general has referred five FBI employees for investigation in connection with politically charged texts, revealing in its report on the Hillary Clinton email case that more bureau officials than previously thought were exchanging anti-Trump messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York files suit against Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180614145037-m3zna</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/TRUMP FOUNDATION:New York sues to dissolve Donald J. Trump Foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Viva Le Resistance': Mueller attorney removed over anti-Trump texts...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/mueller-lawyer-resisted-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENTS REGULARLY RECEIVED FREE HANDOUTS FROM JOURNALISTS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/ig-report-fbi-agents-bribed-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FULL REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.justice.gov/file/1071991/download</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justice.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used GMAIL for FBI business...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/james-comey-used-gmail-for-official-fbi-business-numerous-times.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comey's use of a private email account was inconsistent with Justice Department policy, according to a report by the Office of the Inspector General.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHDOG SLAPS 'INSUBORDINATE' COMEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/99ed3059a42e4ed99e71d2486a18856c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on a report by the Justice Department's internal watchdog on the FBI's handling of the Hillary Clinton email investigation (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival chemists forensically examine drugs for attendees...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/14/drug-tests-festivals-wont-stop-getting-arrested-save-life-7631688/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you ever safely say you know what's inside your drugs?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of daylight saving time inches closer...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article213187609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Assembly Bill 807, the first step to ending daylight saving time, passed the state Senate on Thursday, April 14, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT APPROVES $50B IN TARIFFS ON CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/donald-trump-approves-tariffs-on-about-50-billion-of-chinese-goods-1529016073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump approved assessing tariffs on about $50 billion of Chinese goods, said individuals familiar with the decision, as the U.S. ratcheted up its trade fight with Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians Prep 5,000 Kite Bombs In Gaza To Mark End of Ramadan...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Palestinians-prep-5000-kite-bombs-to-mark-end-of-Ramadan-in-Gaza-559981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli media report Palestinians plan to launch 5,000 such devices into southern Israel to mark Eid al-Fitr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild animals become nocturnal to avoid humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/14/party-animals-quite-the-contrary-humans-cause-wild-critters-to-adopt-the-night-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans are influencing the behavior of wild animals, causing them to flee daylight and seek the cover of darkness for protection, according to a new study from UC Berkeley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Probe Cohen for Possible Illegal Lobbying...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/prosecutors-investigating-michael-cohen-for-possible-illegal-lobbying-1529012696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors in Manhattan are investigating whether Michael Cohen, the longtime personal lawyer for Donald Trump, illegally engaged in secret lobbying, people familiar with the investigation said, as part of a broader investigation into Mr. Cohen’s business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>99-Million-Year-Old Frogs Found In Amber...</title>
      <link>https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/06/oldest-frogs-fossils-amber-cretaceous-dinosaurs-science/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was exhilarating to hold these small fossils up to the light to reveal the frogs within.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indigenous Chileans fight loggers by burning forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/14/chile-mapuche-indigenous-arson-radical-environmental-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chile’s Mapuche people are resorting to increasingly radical tactics to reclaim their ancestral land from exploitive industries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermassive black hole imaged eating star for first time...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-06-astronomers-distant-eruption-black-hole.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, astronomers have directly imaged the formation and expansion of a fast-moving jet of material ejected when the powerful gravity of a supermassive black hole ripped apart a star that wandered too close to the cosmic monster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BEST BIRTHDAY!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5845629/Ivanka-Eric-lead-tributes-Donald-Trump-72nd-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka and Eric Trump have lead the tributes to President Donald Trump on his 72nd birthday by posting throwback photos from their childhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hawaii it's 'raining' green crystals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/14/hawaii-volcano-green-crystals-olivine/701389002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the never-ending parade of weird phenomena erupting from Hawaii's Kilauea volcano comes a "rain" of green crystals, which have been spotted on the ground after falling from the sky. "It is literally raining gems," tweeted meteorologist Erin Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Close To Deal For Future Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-14/apple-is-said-to-near-deal-for-animated-movie-in-hollywood-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. has decided on its next Hollywood act: making feature films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man running for mayor killed in Mexico, 16th candidate dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-running-mayor-killed-mexico-16th-candidate-dead-202407926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — The mayor of a small town in western Mexico who was running for re-election has been killed, the 16th candidate murdered ahead of the July 1 elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top FACEBOOK Strategist Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/top-facebook-strategist-to-step-down-1529006487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s top policy and communications executive, Elliot Schrage, is stepping down after a decade at the social-media giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN: Economy Growing At 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/trumps-forecast-of-4-percent-gdp-growth-close-to-coming-true-as-americans-spend-tax-bill-proceeds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging consumer spending is driving GDP well above prior estimates, and it is now tracking near 4 percent for the second quarter, almost doubling the pace of the first quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: IQ Scores On Decline For Decades...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/iq-scores-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the decline in IQs is related to the environment, not genetics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leslie Jones wants 'SNL' to do fewer political jokes...
</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/14/leslie-jones-wants-snl-to-do-fewer-political-jokes-next-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I do hope that next year will be a lot more funny-funny based stuff, more comedy-based stuff instead of a lot of political stuff.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macrons' new $580,000 dinner plates spark cash row...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-44480957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's presidential couple are the centre of claims that a fortune is being spent on porcelain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi beauty queen draws criticism for Israel visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6296e17b78814c148eeeee5d606d0d22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Sarah Idan, Iraq's 2017 Miss Universe beauty pageant contestant, is visiting Israel this week, a trip that has enraged people back home.        Idan was cr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFPOST EDITOR MAKES HOLOCAUST JOKES...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/huffpost-anti-semitic-homophobic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Where da jews, where da jews, where da jews at'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI orders bias training for employees...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/14/fbi-orders-bias-training-employees-after-latest-em/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI will make its employees undergo bias training, Director Christopher Wray promised Thursday, in one of a number of steps he said they’ll take to try to prevent a repeat of problems that plagued the bureau during the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer teens smoking, doing drugs -- and drinking milk...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fewer-us-teens-smoking-doing-drugs-drinking-milk-175623893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fewer U.S. teens are smoking, having sex and doing drugs these days. Oh, and they're drinking less milk, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Woman who hid loaded gun in vagina sentenced 2 years...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/anika-witt-sentenced-902843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 14--A woman who had a loaded handgun hidden in her vagina at the time of her arrest last year has been sentenced to two years in state prison on weapons and heroin possession charges, Illinois</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police thwarted attack on sex club...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-police-thwarted-attack-sex-club-171400475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police thwarted an attack on a swingers' club in the Loiret region north of Paris last month, arresting a "radicalised convert" to Islam, a source close to the inquiry said Thursday. "An improvised explosive device was found at his home and the man admitted that he wanted to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires Now Control Half of World's Personal Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-14/millionaires-now-control-half-of-the-world-s-personal-wealth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rich are getting a lot richer and doing so a lot faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Foreign actors' accessed Hillary emails...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/14/foreign-actors-accessed-hillary-clinton-emails-documents-show.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Foreign actors” obtained access to some of former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton’s emails -- including at least one email classified as “secret” -- according to a new memo from two GOP-led House committees and an internal FBI email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas home prices MOST overvalued...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/business/housing/las-vegas-home-prices-most-overvalued-in-us-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas home prices are rising at one of the fastest clips in the country, with builders fetching record dollar amounts and resale values approaching prior highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14% of Americans have sex at work...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/14/shocking-number-of-americans-have-sex-at-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one in ten Americans have “done the business” at their business, according to a new survey. A new study of 2,000 people found that 14 percent of those polled have actually had sex at thei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym-Goers Turn To 'Shock Therapy' Workout...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/14/shock-therapy-workout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“That's why we only suggest twice a week, so it will be equal to six days working out and take a day off to enjoy your family."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agent texted 'We'll stop' Trump from becoming president...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-receiving-briefing-ahead-of-public-release-of-report-expected-to-criticize-fbi/2018/06/14/c08c6a5a-6fdf-11e8-bf86-a2351b5ece99_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is expected to hear from senior Justice Department officials about the handling of Hillary Clinton’s email probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after bringing meth to police station for testing...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/dumbass/man-seeks-meth-test-563914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man concerned that he had been rooked by a methamphetamine dealer contacted Florida police and asked them to test his drugs and “press charges” against the dealer if he had “been given the wrong na</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky sues WALGREENS, says it has role in opioid epidemic...</title>
      <link>http://www.lex18.com/story/38424163/beshear-sues-walgreens-for-dual-role-in-states-opioid-epidemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lex18.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFORT, Ky. – Attorney General Andy Beshear filed suit against Walgreens on Thursday for its dual role as distributor and pharmacy in allegedly failing to legally monitor its own operations that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel under pressure in escalating row over immigration...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-under-pressure-escalating-row-over-immigration-112453794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel faced a tense showdown Thursday within her divided conservative camp over the flashpoint issue of immigration that could threaten her political future. Merkel was confronted with an open rebellion by her hardline Interior Minister Horst Seehofer, long a fierce critic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk firm tapped to build Chicago high-speed transit...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-firm-tapped-build-chicago-high-speed-151737621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's The Boring Company has been tapped to build a high-speed underground transportation system for Chicago -- the first US city to bank on the entrepreneur's futuristic concept for mass transit. The project, to be officially announced Thursday, would employ tunnels and autonomous electric</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BEST BIRTHDAY!</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/life/974251/Ivanka-Trump-Twitter-Donald-Trump-birthday-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IVANKA TRUMP is known to have a close relationship with her father, Donald Trump, notoriously referred to as “daddy’s girl” by the US president. As he celebrates his 72nd birthday today, his doting daughter shared an never-seen-before snap to Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadians boycott US products, cancel vacations to America...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/14/canadians-boycott-us-products-cancel-vacations-to-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blame America. Canadians have taken to practicing pocketbook diplomacy in defense of Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, who is caught in a trade war of words with President Trump, by boycotting America…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg Movie Lighting Up Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/ruth-bader-ginsburg-box-office-star-documentaries-are-hot-summer-1119867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sundance and Cannes titles focused on the legal icon, Fred Rogers and Pope Francis have had staying power in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC, Maryland, sue Trump...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2018/02/emoluments-suit-vs-trump-now-personal-as-well-as-official/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Spend 7% Of Income On Gasoline...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/aaa-report-americans-spend-7-of-income-on-gasoline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triple A says according to a new report, Americans are spending $69 more each month to fill up their tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York files suit against Trump, alleging his charity engaged in 'illegal conduct'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180614144134-1x0kj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRUMP-BRIEF/ (URGENT):BRIEF-New York sues Donald Trump, others over Trump Foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD CUP</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/2018/06/13/2026-world-cup-donald-trump-usa/697199002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States, along with Canada and Mexico, won Wednesday's vote to host the 2026 World Cup, and it was President Trump who helped, not hinder, the bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA,</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/12/historic-summit-is-a-cause-for-celebration-not-nitpicking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a glorious day for cynics, especially lazy ones. It doesn’t take much effort to find loopholes, inconsistencies and other deficiencies in the agreement signed by President Trump and Kim Jon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BEST BIRTHDAY!</title>
      <link>http://observer.com/2018/06/donald-trump-extravagant-birthday-parties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past festivities have included cakes in the form of Trump as Superman, a paid visit from Pamela Anderson and even a break-in by a blacklisted reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHDOG SLAPS COMEY</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-14/comey-broke-from-fbi-procedures-in-clinton-probe-watchdog-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI Director James Comey “deviated” from FBI and Justice Department procedures in handling the probe into Hillary Clinton, damaging the law enforcement agencies’ image of impartiality even though he wasn’t motivated by political bias, the department’s watchdog found in a highly anticipated report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traces of radioactive contamination found in homes of nuke-site workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/study-traces-of-radioactive-contamination-found-in-homes-of-six-hanford-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The levels are low, but if some microparticles are inhaled or ingested by nuclear-site workers or their families, the radioactive dust is a “potential source of internal radiation exposure,” the study’s author writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Announces Suspension of Drills With South...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201806141065406760-pentagon-us-drills-south-korea/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a press conference after with North Korean leader Kim Jong-un during their summit in Singapore earlier on June 12, Trump said it was inappropriate to hold "war games" in the region in order to negotiate a deal with Pyongyang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashian pushes president for more commutations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/kim-kardashian-west-pushes-white-house-dozens-more-drug-sentence-n882991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"OK, we did this," Kardashian West tells "Today" after Alice Johnson was freed. "Let's open up this conversation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Present for President? Report Expected To Condemn FBI In Clinton Case...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5842335/Inspector-generals-bombshell-report-Clinton-email-case-released-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Department Inspector General Michael Horowitz released the report on Thursday, just in time for the President Trump's 72nd birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., Canadian, Mexican cities lobby to be 2026 hosts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/let-jockeying-begin-u-s-canadian-mexican-cities-lobby-be-n882966 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But seven of the 23 proposed match sites won't make the cut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Retail sales surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-14/retail-sales-surge-may-biggest-jump-8-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/us-weekly-jobless-claims-june-9-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New applications for U.S. unemployment benefits unexpectedly fell last week and the number of Americans on jobless rolls declined to a near 44-1/2-year low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Eating Amoeba Found In Louisiana Water System...</title>
      <link>http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/brain-eating-amoeba-louisiana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potentially deadly brain-eating amoeba has been found again in Terrebonne Parish, Louisiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems say Obama return from sidelines overdue; 'There's f*cking no one else'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/392181-dems-say-obama-return-from-sidelines-is-overdue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When former President Obama left the White House, he pledged to take a back seat to make room for other Democrats in the party to shine.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
