<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The Don's DNA sought in lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/feb/22/donald-trumps-dna-sought-in-e-jean-carroll-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for a woman who accused former President Donald Trump of raping her in the mid-1990s and then filed a defamation lawsuit against him said Tuesday she will not seek to depose Trump prior to trial because it would cause unnecessary delay, but she added that a DNA sample was still being sought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters already accusing 'TRUTH SOCIAL' of censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/truth-social-censorship-stew-peters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right figures are already claiming to have experienced 'censorship' on Truth Social, Trump's new social media app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mickelson Sorry for Endorsing Golf With 'Scary Motherf***er' Saudis...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/phil-mickelson-sorry-for-endorsing-golf-with-scary-motherfer-saudis-i-need-to-be-held-accountable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phil Mickelson apologized for comments in which he rationalized working with human rights violator Saudi Arabia to leverage the PGA for more money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debunking War Propaganda in Real Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kb75e/the-internet-is-debunking-russian-war-propaganda-in-real-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s become increasingly difficult for Russia to publish believable propaganda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elton John plane suffers failure at 10,000ft; Makes emergency landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/17737318/elton-john-emergency-landing-private-jet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIR Elton John was caught in a terrifying mid-air drama when his private jet suffered hydraulic failure at 10,000ft. The plane twice aborted landing on a day winds hit 80mph. Fire crews raced to Fa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam APPLE staff held hostage by suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-amsterdam-hostage-incident-apple-26302421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media users have shared videos of a suspected gunman in an Apple store in Amsterdam's bustling Leidseplein district, with a large police presence seen in the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ultimate influencer -- born 100 years too soon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ultimate-influencer-born-100-years-140035676.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vito Paulekas and his dancing Freaks were a magnet for '60s housewives, celebrities and musicians on the Sunset Strip. Why has his legacy been forgotten?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls up some reservists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-boris-johnson-business-england-russia-a0889e3621c0e1c2d0f343a0eae81bdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on the Russia-Ukraine crisis : OTTAWA, Ontario — Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says Canada is sending hundreds more troops to eastern Europe and imposing new sanctions on Russia in response to the deployment of forces into Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA:  Moscow has 'legitimate' security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/feb/22/china-moscow-has-legitimate-security-concerns-nato/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Tuesday appeared to back Russian grievances over Ukraine and NATO following Russian President Vladimir Putin’s recognition Monday of two separatist enclaves in the eastern part of the country, noting what it called Moscow’s “legitimate security concerns.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlet accidentally leaks own censorship instructions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-chinese-news-outlet-accidentally-leaked-its-own-censorship-instructions-on-russia-ukraine-coverage-report/ar-AAUaWmm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside California's cannabis crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/Inside-California-s-Cannabis-Crisis-16935780.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click here to read the full article.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary sending troops close to border...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/595363-hungary-sending-troops-close-to-ukraine-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hungarian defense ministry on Tuesday announced in a Facebook post that it would be sending troops close to the Hungarian-Ukrainian border, which is situated in the northeastern region of Hungary, Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside High-Stakes Fight to Control Narrative...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/annals-of-espionage/inside-the-high-stakes-fight-to-control-the-narrative-on-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Putin searches for a false pretense to invade Ukraine, the Biden Administration has moved to release, in real time, what it knows of Russia’s war plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis Crash Book Reading With Giant Swastika Flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/so-ugly-neo-nazis-crash-book-reading-with-giant-swastika-flag/ar-AAUaLXf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer attacked, dragged at MCDONALD'S drive-thru...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Woman-Attacked-By-Suspect-Who-Accused-Her-Of-16936084.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND (BCN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beekeepers turn to anti-theft technology...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/beekeepers-turn-anti-theft-technology-hive-thefts-rise-83035377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As almond trees start to bloom in California, so do beehive thefts that have become so prevalent that beekeepers are now turning to GPS tracking devices, surveillance cameras and other anti-theft technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House candidate apologizes to girls after sleepover, vomiting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-oklahoma-oklahoma-city-wine-congress-a2fde9506dbccf44fb2f3066645ad8a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A U.S. House candidate in Oklahoma has apologized after reports that she became intoxicated at a Valentine's Day weekend sleepover for middle-school-aged girls, berated several of the children and vomited in a hamper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First ever recording of moment someone DIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4745912/brain-recording-moment-death-thoughts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE first ever recording of a dying brain has revealed we might relive some of our best memories in our last moments. Scientists accidentally captured our most complex organ as it shut down, showin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the Love Bomber...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-rise-of-the-love-bomber/ar-AAUas4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students Strip Searched for Vaping Devices...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/18/students-strip-searched-for-vaping-devices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutor says no criminal charges will be filed, because the girls could leave their undergarments on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whatever became of the anti-Trump prophets?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whatever-became-of-the-anti-trump-prophets/ar-AAUa3ei?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPAC SET FOR WILD AGENDA: Two 'Lock Her Up' Panels!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/from-the-moron-in-chief-to-two-lock-her-up-panels-here-are-the-5-wildest-items-on-the-agenda-at-cpac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agenda for the Conservative Political Action Committee’s (CPAC) annual confab is out and it's as wild as you would expect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky hints at pursuing nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2022/02/22/ukraine-zelensky-seeks-end-russia-diplomatic-ties-after-hinting-pursuing-nuclear-weapons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky announced on Tuesday that he was reviewing a request from his diplomats to cut all ties to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX FAIL COVERUP?  CDC Isn't Publishing Large Portions of Virus Data...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/22/cdc-withholding-covid-data-over-fears-of-misinterpretation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC has admitted it is withholding large portions of COVID-19 data from the public because it fears the information could be misinterpreted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't Say Gay' bill in Florida requires schools to out students?</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/politics/florida-dont-say-gay-bill-amendment-would-force-schools-to-out-students-in-6-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An amendment to the ‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill filed by Rep. Joe Harding would force schools to disclose student LGBTQ status within 6 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavily Hedged Traders Have Been Awaiting a Stock-Market Storm...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/heavily-hedged-traders-awaiting-stock-163022101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Whatever happens in Ukraine or how it affects Federal Reserve policy, the outcome will land in markets where investors have had time to prepare for the worst. It may be one reason the worst has so far been avoided. Most Read from BloombergU.S. Condemns Russian Move at UN, Reassures Kyiv: Ukraine UpdatePorsches, Lamborghinis Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 MillionBiden to Speak as EU and U.K. Unveil Sanctions: Ukraine UpdateU.S. Stocks Decline on Ukraine Shock; Oil Gains: Markets Wrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY HALTS PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/germany-blocks-nord-stream-2-112330674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany on Tuesday halted the Nord Stream 2 Baltic Sea gas pipeline project, designed to double the flow of Russian gas direct to Germany, after Russia formally recognised two breakaway regions in eastern Ukraine. Europe's most divisive energy project, worth $11 billion, was finished in September, but has stood idle pending certification by Germany and the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory  tests ordered for ALL Hong Kong residents...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-hong-kong-4bb8dd1225887f06f5a0d981a4b52505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Hong Kong will test its entire population of 7.5 million people for COVID-19 in March, the city’s leader said Tuesday, as it grapples with its worst outbreak driven by the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You CAN Catch Omicron Twice...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/20/what-the-hell-the-unlucky-australians-who-have-caught-covid-twice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many assume they will be immune after catching Covid, experts say the emergence of Omicron has seen a significant increase in reinfection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami becoming crypto industry HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/blockchain-com-is-leasing-a-miami-office-for-its-crypto-workers/ar-AAU9XPL?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We need a miracle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/22/we-need-a-miracle-anxious-ukrainians-await-putins-next-move.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now the critical question is whether Putin will stop at the eastern territories of Luhansk and Donetsk, or push on to take more of Ukraine and its capital Kyiv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT PUTIN RATTLES WEST</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-weighs-recognition-two-ukrainian-162545162.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EU's top diplomat says that 'Russian troops are on Ukrainian soil' — but that it was not yet 'a fully fledged invasion.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to address nation at 2pm... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-deliver-remarks-russia-ukraine-163230341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden will deliver remarks at 1 p.m. ET (1800 GMT) on Tuesday to provide an update on the situation concerning Russia and Ukraine, the White House said. The United States will announce potentially severe new sanctions and export controls against Russia on Tuesday in response to Moscow's decision to recognize two breakaway regions of Ukraine as independent and send troops there. A White House spokesperson on Monday said the announcement of sanctions would be coordinated with allies and partners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Bitcoin Crash?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-extends-dip-below-40-012809489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin traded near a more than two-week low as fears of a possible Russian invasion of Ukraine prompted some analysts to predict the largest cryptocurrency could slide toward the key $30,000 level. Most Read from BloombergU.S. Condemns Russian Move at UN, Reassures Kyiv: Ukraine UpdatePorsches, Lamborghinis Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 MillionEU and U.K. Propose Sanctions to Confront Putin: Ukraine UpdateU.S. Stocks Slip on Ukraine Shock; Oil Gains: Markets WrapStocks Retreat, Ru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Russian False Flag Attack Succeed in Information Age?</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/02/what-are-false-flag-attacksand-could-russia-make-one-work-information-age/362246/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Russia fool the modern world?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANGER:  CYBERATTACKS ON SATELLITES</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ukraine-russia-crisis-cyberattacks-could-affect-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Russia mounts cyberattacks against the United States, the targets could include banks, power plants, water treatment facilities, and communications. Those attacks could also impact GPS for navigation, farming, automation, and oil exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Dems tune out news...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democrats-national-news-biden-era-engagement-38881407-3e4f-4002-b3fa-e03de1be4e14.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the 1st time since the study began in 2018 that Democrats report having less interest in national news than Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most beautiful building on Earth' opens in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/uae/live-museum-of-the-future-the-most-beautiful-building-on-earth-opens-in-dubai-1.1645540479214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohammed bin Rashid opens Dubai's Museum of the Future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter fired at officers. Police say it was 4-year-old, acting on dad's instructions...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-shooter-fired-at-officers-Police-say-it-was-a-16937668.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As police struggled to arrest a man who allegedly pulled a gun on McDonald's workers for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beekeepers turn to anti-theft technology as hive thefts rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-health-business-united-states-theft-449f7234e63f8ae757bf75b1866e51b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODLAND, Calif. (AP) — For a few frenzied weeks, beekeepers from around the United States truck billions of honeybees to California to rent them to almond growers who need the insects to pollinate the state's most valuable crop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House calls 'invasion'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-russia-vladimir-putin-46cef648807d0e3c2bac9793ad9022a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The White House on Tuesday began referring to Russian troop deployments in eastern Ukraine as an “invasion”  after initially hesitating to use the term — a red line that President Joe Biden has said would result in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE NOCTURNALS: Ultra-introverts reveling in quiet and solitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2022/02/ultra-introverts-nocturnal-lives/622856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most people are fast asleep, some ultra-introverts are going about their lives, reveling in the quiet and solitude. They challenge a core assumption of psychology: that all humans need social connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court formally ends Trump's fight over Capitol attack records...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-formally-ends-trumps-fight-over-capitol-attack-records-2022-02-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Tuesday brought a formal end to former President Donald Trump's request to block the release of White House records sought by the Democratic-led congressional panel investigating last year's deadly attack on the Capitol by a mob of his supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convoy organizer eyes Beltway shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/595277-truck-convoy-organizer-eyes-dc-beltway-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A truck convoy organizer says that his group has plans to shut down the Capital Beltway in the D.C. region this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Beckel dies at 73...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/595276-bob-beckel-dies-at-73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime cable news pundit and political analyst Bob Beckel died on Monday. He was 73.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices skyrocket 19%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/22/homes/us-home-prices-case-shiller-december-2021/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland's new Forest Lagoon spa immerses visitors among trees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/forest-lagoon-spa-iceland/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucked away in the northern woodlands of Iceland lies a cozy new spa set to soothe visitors who are looking to enjoy natural hot springs and greenery in equal measure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: The Long Crusade of Clarence and Ginni Thomas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/22/magazine/clarence-thomas-ginni-thomas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court justice and his wife battled for years for a more conservative America. New reporting shows how far she was willing to go after Donald Trump’s 2020 election loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. 'MATRIX' legal slugfest exposes Hollywood's shifting priorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/warner-bros-matrix-legal-slugfest-exposes-hollywoods-shifting-priorities/ar-AAU80uC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA Emerges As 'Life-Changing, Life-Saving' Drug For Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/viagra-dogs-eating-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megaesophagus is a condition which affects the esophagus of many dog breeds. The organ enlarges and loses its ability to move food to the stomach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. spy plane takes spotlight in empty airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-drone/u-s-air-force-spy-plane-takes-spotlight-in-empty-ukraine-airspace-idUSKBN2KR19F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Ukraine's airspace has been largely empty amid the crisis with Russia, a remotely piloted U.S. military vehicle called the RQ-4 Global Hawk has flown over the country in circles for hours at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Kitchen Sponge Crawling With More Bacteria Than Lab Petri Dish!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/kitchen-sponges-more-bacteria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact, no matter how much you replace your sponge, you’ll always run into the same issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORSCHEs, LAMBORGHINIs Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/porsches-lamborghinis-lost-at-sea-may-cost-vw-155-million/ar-AAU7UdI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Successfully Map Out Entire Human Gut For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/first-map-human-gut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have successfully mapped out the entire human GI tract, including how different cells living in the gut are important to daily life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Crackdown Risk Roars Back With Probe of Jack Ma Empire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-crackdown-risk-roars-back-103142902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- From Alibaba to Tencent, China’s largest companies are once again at the center of a market storm, spurred by speculation that Beijing is readying another assault on the world’s biggest internet arena.Most Read from BloombergU.S. Condemns Russian Move at UN, Reassures Kyiv: Ukraine UpdatePorsches, Lamborghinis Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 MillionStocks Retreat, Ruble Weakens on Ukraine Tension: Markets WrapKremlin Cautious on Prospect of Biden-Putin Summit Amid TensionsTrump Holds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China walking tightrope between Russia and West...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-keeps-walking-its-tightrope-between-russia-and-the-west-as-tensions-flare-in-ukraine/ar-AAU9oTf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four in 10 people 'not confident using numbers in everyday lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishnews.com/business/2022/02/22/news/four-in-10-people-not-confident-using-numbers-in-their-everyday-lives--2594773/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR in 10 (40 per cent) people do not feel confident about using numbers in their everyday lives, a survey has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen cancels virtual engagements over Covid symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/22/uk/queen-elizabeth-ii-covid-update-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Queen Elizabeth II canceled her planned virtual engagements on Tuesday as she continues to suffer from mild Covid-19 symptoms, Buckingham Palace has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Peacekeeping' forces in tanks roll into Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4742020/russian-tanks-ukraine-putin-doctors-bloodshed/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s tanks have rolled into Ukraine creating the most “dangerous situation since the Cuban Missile Crisis”. Around 10,000 troops moved into two Russian speaking breaka…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany halts pipeline project...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/germanys-scholz-halts-nord-stream-2-certification-2022-02-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Olaf Scholz put on ice the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring Russian gas to Germany on Tuesday after Russia formally recognised two breakaway regions in eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icahn launches proxy fight with MCDONALD'S over treatment of pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/20/carl-icahn-launches-proxy-fight-with-mcdonalds-over-treatment-of-pigs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carl Icahn, the famed billionaire corporate raider, has pushed McDonald's for better treatment of pigs in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrologers explain 'power shift' significance of 2/22/22 for USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/21/astrologers-explain-power-shift-significance-of-2-22-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little more than two hours after midnight, the deuces will be too wild to ignore: 2:22:22 on 2/22/22, a Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Wendy Williams Show Ends...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/wendy-williams-producers-to-announce-sherri-shepherd-as-permanent-replacement-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary talk show host is officially out after 13 seasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Immense fraud' found after $6 TRILLION in virus spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/immense-fraud-creates-immense-task-for-washington-as-it-tries-to-tighten-scrutiny-of-6-trillion-in-emergency-coronavirus-spending/ar-AATZ0cF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/defying-west-putin-orders-troops-to-ukraine-rebel-regions/ar-AAU8rKm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin ordered Russian troops into two Moscow-backed rebel regions of Ukraine on Monday, defying Western threats of sanctions in a move that could set off a potentially catastrophic war with Kyiv. Earlier, the Kremlin leader recognised the independence of two rebel-held areas of the Donetsk and Lugansk regions of Ukraine, paving the way for an operation to deploy part of the potential invasion force he has massed around the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia court decriminalizes abortion, adding to Latin America momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Colombia-court-decriminalizes-abortion-adding-to-16936452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia - Colombia's constitutional court voted Monday to decriminalize...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN EMERGENCY MEETING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-agrees-biden-putin-summit-071704190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russian President Vladimir Putin officially recognized two self-proclaimed separatist republics in eastern Ukraine, a move that torpedoes European-mediated peace talks and further escalates tensions with the West. Most Read from BloombergUNSC to Hold Emergency Meeting On Russia’s Move: Ukraine UpdateStocks Retreat, Ruble Weakens on Ukraine Tension: Markets WrapKremlin Cautious on Prospect of Biden-Putin Summit Amid TensionsTrump Holds Onto Piles of Cash, Gives None to GOP Candidat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS MILITARY BASES</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-russia-now-build-military-004809042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has acquired the right to build military bases in Ukraine's two breakaway regions under treaties signed by President Vladimir Putin with their separatist leaders. Putin on Monday officially recognised the two breakaway regions - the self-proclaimed Donetsk People's Republic and the Lugansk People's Republic - as independent statelets, defying Western warnings that such a step would be illegal and kill peace negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL NEARS $100</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/oil-price-charts/#Brent-Crude</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oilprices from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-boris-johnson-europe-emmanuel-macron-2b7c2949ae3168effce9d0cb2584bb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A long-feared Russian invasion of Ukraine appeared to be imminent Monday, if not already underway, with Russian President Vladimir Putin ordering forces into separatist regions of eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
