<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Yang's quixotic campaign gets serious...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-yang-idUSKBN1WS096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entrepreneur Andrew Yang knows most people initially viewed his candidacy for U....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattis warns of resurgence: 'Enemy gets the vote'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/mattis-warns-isis-could-resurge-enemy-gets-vote-after-trump-n1065431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'enemy gets the vote', we say in the military," Mattis said. "And in this case, if we don't keep the pressure on, then ISIS will resurge."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is World Economy Sliding Into First Recession Since 2009?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/is-the-world-economy-sliding-into-first-recession-since-2009/ar-AAIGvvG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary: USA 'preparing to evacuate' remaining troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/turkey-syria-mark-esper-secretary-of-defense-us-preparing-to-evacuate-all-troops-from-northern-syria-face-the-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have American forces likely caught between two opposing advancing armies," Secretary Mark Esper told "Face the Nation"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists endorse mass civil disobedience to force climate action...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-scientists-idUSKBN1WS01K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 300 scientists have endorsed a civil disobedience campaign aimed at fo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey deliberately 'bracketing' US troops with artillery fire in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-forces-say-turkey-was-deliberately-bracketing-american-troops-with-artillery-fire-in-syria/ar-AAIGNOo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside PG&amp;E's Blackout Control Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-did-not-go-well-inside-pgandes-blackout-control-room/ar-AAIGpCa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans wrestle with strategy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/465492-republicans-wrestle-with-impeachment-strategy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans realize they need to push back more aggressively on the fast-moving impeachment inquiry in the House, but they have yet to display a unified strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Escapes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e90fd08a89e49d9bcae6a85a131a64a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AKCAKALE, Turkey (AP) — Turkish forces approached a key Kurdish-held town in northern Syria on Sunday, setting off clashes that allowed hundreds of Islamic State supporters to escape from a camp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Relationship With Jeffrey Epstein That Bill Gates Now 'Regrets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-relationship-with-jeffrey-epstein-that-bill-gates-now-regrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein, the convicted sex offender who committed suicide in jail, managed to lure an astonishing array of rich, powerful and famous men into his orbit. There were billionaires (Leslie Wexner and Leon Black), politicians (Bill Clinton and Bill Richardson),...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuation orders lifted in Saddleridge fire zone as firefighters make progress...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-12/saddleridge-fire-favorable-weather-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters hope to get the upper hand on the Saddleridge fire in the San Fernando Valley on Saturday, aided by favorable weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters erect 'Lady Liberty' statue on Hong Kong mountain top...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191013-protesters-erect-lady-liberty-statue-on-hong-kong-mountain-top</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters erect 'Lady Liberty' statue on Hong Kong mountain top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who says you can't eat red meat? Food advice questioned anew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/968e18606fba4a3c8084d2c83e0ffe56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — So is red meat good or bad for you? If the answer were only that simple. A team of international researchers recently rattled the nutrition world by saying there isn't enough...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un May Be Hiding Hog Apocalypse From World...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1190054/North-Korea-news-pigs-swine-flu-apocalypse-Asia-illness-death-health-Kim-Jong-Un</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH KOREA might be concealing a massive African swine fever outbreak, according to recent reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President orders army onto streets of Ecuadorian capital...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3163699112084840882bcb603cb7aa2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Ecuador's army took to the streets after President Lenín Moreno ordered the first 24-hour curfew in decades in response to a day of attacks on government buildings and media...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA to require abortion medication at colleges...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/health/california-to-require-abortion-medication-at-public-colleges/5613445/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is the first state to require public colleges and universities to offer abortion medication at campus health centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will testify denial came from Trump personally...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gordon-sondland-key-ukraine-witness-to-testify-his-quid-pro-quo-denial-came-from-trump-personally-wapo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gordon Sondland reportedly plans to tell lawmakers he cannot vouch for whether or not Trump was being honest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Envoy who denied quid pro quo now says he isn't certain...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Exculpatory-text-relayed-by-Trump-Sondland-to-say-14517612.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The U.S. ambassador to the European Union, Gordon Sondland, intends to tell Congress this week that the content of a text message he wrote denying a quid pro quo with Ukraine was relayed to him directly by President Donald Trump in a phone call, according to a person familiar with his testimony.  Sondland plans to tell lawmakers he has no knowledge of whether the president was telling him the truth at that moment. "It's only true that the president said it, not that it was the truth," said the person familiar with Sondland's planned testimony, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss sensitive diplomatic matters.  The Sept. 9 exchange between Sondland and the top U.S. diplomat to Ukraine has become central to the House Democrats' impeachment inquiry into whether the president abused his office in pressuring Ukraine to open an investigation into his political rival Joe Biden and his son, who sat on the board of a Ukrainian energy company. The White House and its defenders have held up Sondland's text, which included "no quid pro quo's of any kind," as proof that none was ever considered.  Sondland will hold out the possibility that Trump wasn't truthful in his denial of a quid pro quo as well as an alternative scenario in which the president's interest in the scheme soured at a time when his administration faced mounting scrutiny over why it was withholding about $400 million in security assistance to Ukraine and delaying a leader-level visit with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky.  "Whether he's deciding it's getting too hot to handle and he backs off whatever his position really was a month earlier, I don't know," the person said of Sondland's understanding.  Hours before Sondland called the president, he received a text message from the acting ambassador to Ukraine, William Taylor, raising...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Bees better at math when punished for wrong answer..</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/us/bees-count-study-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bees are more likely to discern between numbers when the wrong answer earns them punishment, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS DEBATE ON TUESDAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/democratic-debate-on-tuesday-features-a-surging-elizabeth-warren-and-a-recuperating-bernie-sanders-2019-10-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday’s Democratic presidential debate will have a significantly different backdrop than prior ones. Warren is now challenging Biden for the front-runner...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump again touts partial trade deal with China...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-again-touts-partial-trade-deal-china-151339956--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Saturday touted his partial, unsigned trade deal with China as a major achievement and the best deal US farmers have ever secured. "WOW, the Farmers really hit pay dirt," Trump tweeted. Friday's initial agreement, which marks a halt in the 18-month trade war,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors save baby born with three legs and two penises...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10119935/doctors-save-baby-born-with-three-legs-and-two-penises-after-mum-refused-to-have-an-abortion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN doctors have revealed how they saved a baby born with three legs after the mum refused to have an abortion. Remarkable images show the Russian boy before and after surgery to remove the ext…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rightwing media making plans for post-Trump future?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/oct/11/are-fox-news-and-rightwing-news-making-plans-for-a-post-trump-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Fox anchors have become more stridently critical of Trump following the revelations of the impeachment inquiry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw, angry, uncensored: Welcome to impeachment-era campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/11/trump-impeachment-campaign-044829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot hard to tell apart from humans after AI upgrade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-giant-says-dolls-20546804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: 1AM Dolls told Daily Star Online of 'major strides in realism' in sex robot manufacturing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sessions Senate Buzz Swirls in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/12/jeff-sessions-2020-u-s-senate-run-buzz-swirls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTSVILLE, Alabama -- Republicans voters in Alabama will not go to the polls for another four and a half months to cast a ballot for who they would prefer to face incumbent Sen. Doug Jones (D-AL) in the Nov. 3, 2020 general election. | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador president orders curfew, military control in Quito...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indigenous-protesters-ecuador-agree-talks-182233310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador President Lenin Moreno on Saturday ordered the capital Quito and surrounding areas to be placed under curfew and military control, on the 11th day of deadly protests against government austerity measures. The order "will take effect" Saturday from 3 pm (2000 GMT) and "facilitate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ailes Would Have Never Let This Happen'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/shepard-smith-donald-trump-reaction-fox-news-exit-1202758469/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump may be rubbing salt into the wound of Shepard Smith suddenly exiting Fox News Channel today, but the anchor could be back soon-ish to shine a spotlight of truth on the ex-Celebrity App…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Relationship With Jeffrey Epstein That Bill Gates Now 'Regrets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/12/business/jeffrey-epstein-bill-gates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Gates, the Microsoft co-founder, met several times with Mr. Epstein, a sex criminal, a Times investigation found. Mr. Gates now concedes an error in judgment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN CALLS OUT FAKEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/money/elizabeth-warren-runs-fake-facebook-ad-accusing-zuckerberg-of-supporting-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ad was intended to troll Facebook for allowing the Trump campaign to run a blatantly false ad about Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kurds leader tells USA 'you are leaving us to be slaughtered'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/12/politics/syrian-kurds-us-turkey-military-operation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commander of the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces told a senior US diplomat, "You are leaving us to be slaughtered," demanding to know whether the US is going to do anything to protect Syrian Kurds as Turkey continues its military operation targeting America's Kurdish allies in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Columbus: More states jettison day paying homage to the explorer...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-columbusday-debate-20191012-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON Growing up on the Sandia Pueblo Reservation, New Mexico state Rep. Derrick J. Lente learned the same Christopher Columbus stories in school that his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Stands by 'Great Guy' Giuliani as Probe Deepens...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/465528-trump-defends-crime-buster-giuliani-amid-reported-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday defended his personal attorney Rudy Giuliani as the former New York City mayor faces scrutiny from Congress and a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESTRUCTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/12/california-wildfires-los-angeles-suburbs </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people feared dead and numerous buildings destroyed as 100,000 evacuated but utility restores power to many consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLASHES WITH COLLEAGUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/shepard-smith-stepping-down-from-fox-news </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news anchor was a frequent target of the president’s ire because of his penchant for calling B.S. on his own network’s pro-Trump spin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are these L.A. people sleeping in pods stacked on top of each other?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-12/when-finding-affordable-housing-in-l-a-means-living-in-a-pod-or-a-bunk-bed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No private bedrooms for these L.A. residents. They choose to live in pods or rooms filled with bunk beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS REVIVAL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7566157/Turkish-military-incursion-Syria-giving-jihadists-chance-regroup.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a televised statement, senior SDF official Redur Xelil said the Syrian Democratic Forces were continuing to cooperate with the US-led coalition against Islamic State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETWORK EXODUS?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/media/shepard-smith-leaving-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shepard Smith said on his Friday show that after more than two decades at Fox News, he was stepping down as chief news anchor, and leaving the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA WILDFIRES RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/southern-california-wildfires-burning-unchecked-142637647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gusting winds fueling a fast-moving wildfire in southern California showed no signs of abating Saturday as a blaze that forced the evacuation of some 100,000 people kept burning out of control. A red flag warning of critical fire danger -- strong winds and very low humidity -- has been extended into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW ORLEANS: 1 killed, 18 sent to hospital after crane collapses at HARD ROCK construction site...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/person-killed-18-hospital-crane-collapses-hard-rock/story?id=66232002 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crane collapsed at the Hard Rock Hotel construction site.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
