<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Decades of service...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bob-dole-dead-98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Senate Majority Leader Bob Dole died Sunday morning at age 98 after he was treated for lung cancer earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN FIRES CUOMO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/04/media/cnn-fires-chris-cuomo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN said Saturday that anchor Chris Cuomo has been "terminated" by the network, "effective immediately." The announcement came after an outside law firm was retained to review exactly how Cuomo aided his brother, former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX ALLEGATION...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/05/chris-cuomo-hit-with-sexual-misconduct-allegation-from-former-co-worker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former co-worker of Chris Cuomo made a sexual misconduct allegation against the former CNN anchor, who was fired Saturday for his involvement with trying to mitigate sexual harassment accusations…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Plunges in Another Sign of Global Market Nerves...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-plunges-over-20-another-063422558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin plunged along with other cryptocurrencies on Saturday, in another indication of the risk aversion sweeping across financial markets.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female FoundersAutomating the War on Noise Pollution‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsThe largest digital token fell as low as $42,296 before paring some of the tumble. It was trading at about $48,300 as of 10:31 a.m. in New York on Saturday, a drop of about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4210410/bob-dole-cancer-republican-cause-of-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Senate majority leader and Republican presidential candidate Bob Dole has died at the age of 98. The Elizabeth Dole Foundation confirmed that Dole, who had been diagnosed with stage 4 lung c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier and Stalwart of Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/05/us/politics/bob-dole-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Dole, a son of the Kansas prairie who was left for dead on a World War II battlefield, became one of the longest-serving Republican leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia planning military offensive against Ukraine with 175,000 troops, U.S. intel warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-planning-massive-military-offensive-against-ukraine-involving-175000-troops-us-intelligence-warns/ar-AARrLIF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWII veteran and three-time presidential candidate passes away at 98...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/05/bob-dole-wwii-vet-and-3-time-presidential-candidate-dead-at-98/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, a decorated veteran who overcame near fatal wounds in World War II to become a respected Senator and three-time Republican presidential candidate, died on Sunday. He was 98. “It is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer robbed at gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/san-francisco-chronicle-photographer-robbed-at-gunpoint-in-west-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Francisco Chronicle photographer was robbed at gunpoint on Friday afternoon in West Oakland, California, during an assignment, the newspaper reported. The robbery came on the heels of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$7B startup gets flack as CEO lays off hundreds over ZOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/tech/article/Better-mortgage-firm-has-mass-layoff-Zoom-16673576.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The last time I did this, I cried,' the CEO said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Iran's Natanz nuke facility just attacked for third time in two years?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/sabotage-at-irans-natanz-nuclear-facility-30-analysis-687849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most mutated virus ever seen'...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/scientists-call-omicron-most-mutated-virus-wed-ever-seen-why-does-that-matter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Young, a virologist at the University of Warwick, described omicron as “the most heavily mutated version of the virus we have seen,” including potentially worrying changes never before see…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF brunch spot asks 3 cops to leave; 'Multiple weapons'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/restaurants/article/SF-brunch-spot-asks-3-armed-San-Francisco-police-16675627.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hilda and Jesse says the request was not a 'political statement.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edward Shames, last 'Band of Brothers' member, dead at 99...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/04/politics/edward-shames-easy-company-world-war-ii-band-of-brothers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Col. Edward Shames, the last surviving officer of the historic World War II parachute infantry regiment of the US Army known as Easy Company, died Friday at the age of 99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie theaters go out of style...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/movie-theaters-go-out-of-style-covid-7e351545-43f5-48fe-8d81-4149bbf78f48.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former moviegoers can watch new movies at home, maskless and with free snacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett Taking Stand Seen as Risky Potential Defense Tactic...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/movie-theaters-go-out-of-style-covid-7e351545-43f5-48fe-8d81-4149bbf78f48.html&gt;Movie theaters go out of style...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former moviegoers can watch new movies at home, maskless and with free snacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave a result of liberal justice reforms, critics say...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/04/violent-la-crime-wave-jacqueline-avant-slay-result-of-liberal-reforms-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Los Angeles, where left-wing lawmakers and activists have pushed a litany of progressive reforms that help violent criminals spend less-time behind bars, justice is not only fleeting — it&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers, facing labor shortage, accommodate unvaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211205135735-78oy9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CANADA-JOBS (PIX):Canadian employers, facing labor shortage, accommodate the unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs sniffing dogs could be introduced to Parliament to combat use...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10276885/Drugs-sniffer-dogs-introduced-Parliament-combat-use-heart-Westminster.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior MPs are considering the move after an investigation found traces of cocaine at 11 out of 12 sites tested for the class A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds march in Belgium...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-belgium-brussels-a198e91209c3900b2c064bdc6fd19c82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Hundreds of people marched through central Brussels on Sunday to protest tightened COVID-19 restrictions imposed by the Belgian government to counter the latest spike in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's choice: Hot war or deeply frozen conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/ukraine-russia-donbas-region-nato-vladimir-putin-war-frozen-conflict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rather than igniting new hostilities in Ukraine, the Russian president may see advantage in a never-ending standoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandates lose steam in USA; Europe doubles down...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-europe-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccines-a41663cf-decf-4256-a739-898eb318edff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe cracks down on the unvaccinated while courts pause U.S. vaccine mandates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son 'could receive lighter sentence if he turns'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4208355/ethan-crumbley-parents-blame-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALLEGED school shooter Ethan Crumbley could get a lighter sentence if he blames his parents for giving him the gun used in the shooting, said an expert. Attorney Matthew Barhoma, founder of Ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech braces for breakups as UK opens new era of enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/big-tech-breakup-uk-enforcement-era-facebook-giphy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In ordering Facebook to sell Giphy, the CMA has gone further than any other competition regulator in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlusconi 'quietly campaigning' to be Italy's next president...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10276825/Silvio-Berlusconi-quietly-campaigning-Italys-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 85-year-old media tycoon, infamous for his 'bunga bunga' sex parties, remains Italy's longest serving post war leader, having been in office three times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sounds alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-ukraine-russia-invasion-f54a180a-3b52-45f7-9774-067e28da8450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and Putin are expected to have speak by phone on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Nationalists Stage Rally in DC, Find Themselves Stranded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/white-nationalists-stage-bizarro-rally-in-downtown-d-c-find-themselves-stranded/ar-AARts8x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Shady Billion-Dollar Phone Sex Industry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-shady-billion-dollar-phone-095800604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyIn 2019, when I was asked by three award-winning filmmakers to host and co-write a podcast called Operator, which would explore phone sex in the 1990s, of course I responded, “Yes! Yes! YES!” As soon as I learned the basics about American Telnet, a company that made billions off of adult pay-per-call lines, I was chomping at the bit to fly down to Florida to interview everyone involved. What I found is that the more sex work changes,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany advises against Christmas travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-travel-d5cb2d658afec5aeb84c3a028cba0c44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's incoming transport minister is advising people against traveling over Christmas as the country tries to stem a wave of coronavirus infections. Federal and state leaders on Thursday announced tough new restrictions that largely target unvaccinated people , preventing them from entering nonessential stores, restaurants, sports and cultural venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anime Convention Goer Says 15 Friends Sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/man-who-had-omicron-says-friends-also-got-sick-after-nyc-anime-convention/ar-AARto86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak on cruise ship approaching New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-louisiana-new-orleans-1f8edb74567df1abdbc29161d800056f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Ten people aboard a Norwegian Cruise Line ship approaching New Orleans have tested positive for COVID-19, officials said Saturday night. The Norwegian Breakaway had departed New Orleans on Nov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief says China ops near Taiwan resemble 'rehearsals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-taiwan-pentagon/chinese-military-flights-near-taiwan-look-like-rehearsals-pentagon-chief-idUSKBN2IJ0NQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin on Saturday said Chinese military flights near Taiwan look like "rehearsals" though he did not indicate that he expected Beijing actually to carry out such operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The woman who could bring down Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-woman-who-could-bring-down-Roe-v-Wade-16674783.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon after the U.S. Supreme Court agreed to consider Mississippi's 15-week abortion ban,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm grows over smash-and-grab robberies amid holiday season...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/584057-smash-and-grab-crimes-raise-alarms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in smash-and-grab robberies across the U.S. has jolted businesses, prompting owners and leaders to take precautions to protect brick-and-mortar shops amid a busy holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes break out in Jerusalem after Palestinian who stabbed Israeli killed by police...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/clashes-break-out-in-jerusalem-after-palestinian-who-allegedly-stabbed-israeli-is-killed-by-police/ar-AARsFd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli flight forced to reduce altitude due to spy plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/israeli-flight-to-russia-forced-to-reduce-altitude-due-to-spy-plane-687816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin set video call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-83e399de3cd43eee751553aafb543052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Presidents Joe Biden and Vladimir Putin will speak in a video call Tuesday, the Kremlin said, as tensions between the United States and Russia escalate over a Russian troop buildup on the Ukrainian border  that's seen as a sign of a potential invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More omicron detected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-new-york-city-kathy-hochul-5129e53128a7a249d36790402220aecc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York announced three more cases of the omicron variant of the coronavirus Saturday, bringing the number of state cases linked to the new variant to eight. “The omicron variant is here, and as anticipated we are seeing the beginning of community spread," state Health Commissioner Mary Bassett said in a news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Erupts as Top Diplomats Face Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-russia-tension-on-ukraine-erupts-as-top-diplomats-face-off-1.1691101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken and Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov had a testy exchange over Ukraine at a dinner with dozens of their colleagues this week, according to people familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
