<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Group Urges Residents To Help Protect Feral Cats During Deep Freeze...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/29/feral-cats-shelters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dangerously-cold temperatures plaguing Chicago this week could be deadly for many outdoor creatures, including the estimated 200,000  feral cats that live in the Chicago area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Muslims demand NIKE recall shoes with 'Allah written on sole'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8285782/muslims-nike-recall-air-max-trainer-allah/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIKE has been urged to recall “offensive” Air Max trainers because they have “Allah’s name in Arabic” on the sole. Saiqa Noreen was appalled when she spotted text on the bottom of the shoe and accu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates face political risks when pressed on healthcare specifics...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democratic-candidates-face-political-risks-when-13571912.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Sen. Kamala D. Harris spoke about health care at a CNN forum Monday evening, she threw her support behind a "Medicare-for-all" plan, sounding similar to other candidates seeking the Democratic presidential nomination. But when pressed for details, the senator from California explained the idea in a way most Democrats assiduously avoid: She agreed that Medicare-for-all also means private insurance for none. "Let's eliminate all of that," Harris said, referring to private health insurance. "Let's move on." In a single flourish, Harris, D-Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro pummels Venezuelan slums as his power comes under attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/south-america/maduro-pummels-venezuelan-slums-as-his-power-comes-under-attack-20190130-p50ujg.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former STARBUCKS CEO has spent months researching presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Former-Stabucks-CEO-has-spent-months-researching-13571868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before announcing his presidential ambitions this week, former Starbucks chief executive Howard Schultz secretly undertook a months-long effort to prepare an independent presidential campaign against the nation's two-party political system, deploying more than six national polls and laying the groundwork for paid advertising that could debut in the next two months. The full reach of the project suggests that his stated goal of disrupting the U.S. political process is not likely to fade away anytime soon, despite enormous historical barriers to success and Democratic predictions that his entry in the race will help President Donald Trump get reelected. An early advertising effort, made possible by Schultz's net worth of about $3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT SOAP OPERA DRAGS ON...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/brexit-vote-summary-7-key-13925303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May is now stronger and ready to fight the EU - but the battle's impossible and it could all still turn against her. We've learned a lot tonight - here's the Commons drama decoded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD investigates Turkish flags hung at Armenian schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-turkish-flags-armenian-schools-20190129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Armenians, the flags call to mind the million-plus that died at Turkish Ottoman hands beginning in 1915.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  APPLE to fix FaceTime bug that allows eavesdropping...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/947951d023a844d09129895877d3c7a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has disabled a group-chat function in FaceTime after users said a software bug could let callers activate another person's microphone remotely. With the bug, a FaceTime user calling another iPhone, iPad or Mac computer could hear audio — even if the receiver did not accept the call. The bug is triggered when callers add themselves to the same call to launch a group chat. That makes FaceTime think the receiver had accepted the chat. The bug, demonstrated through videos online , comes as an embarrassment for a company that is trying to distinguish itself by stressing its commitment to users' privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bars opposition leader from leaving nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/314d3842c81f426cb03b2702cd0b3e23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's Supreme Court barred opposition leader Juan Guaido from leaving the country Tuesday, a move certain to heighten tensions as the man challenging President Nicolas Maduro's claim to the presidency presses forward with establishing a transitional government and the U.S. warns of "serious consequences" if he is harmed. The government-stacked high court announced the order just hours after chief prosecutor Tarek William Saab announced that he was opening a criminal investigation into Guaido's anti-government activities and requested that restrictions be placed on his movements abroad. The court also approved Saab's request that all of Guaido's financial assets be frozen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>English's dominance as global language under threat from new tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8292860/tech-speak-without-learning-foreign-language/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENGLISH holds a special status among the world’s dialects, but its global dominance could be under threat, says a language expert. Gaston Dorren, a best-selling author, has warned that new technolo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENGINEERS TRANSLATE BRAIN SIGNALS INTO SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/01/190129081919.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Footage Surfaces of Shirtless Bernie Singing With Soviets...</title>
      <link>https://forward.com/schmooze/418282/footage-of-shirtless-bernie-sanders-singing-drunkenly-with-soviets-in-88/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;forward.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grainy footage of a shirtless, hammered Bernie Sanders singing ‘This Land Is Your Land’ is making the rounds on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jailed for 41 days after cop says laundry detergent was heroin...</title>
      <link>https://cbs12.com/news/local/i-was-falsely-charged-for-trafficking-heroin-local-man-released-from-jail-deputy-fired</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbs12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;ldquo;I had 92 grams of laundry detergent in my door and that&amp;rsquo;s what I was falsely charged for trafficking of heroin,&amp;rdquo; said Matthew Crull of Jensen Beach. Crull is one of eleven people released from county jail after Martin County Sheriff William Snyder fired Steven O&amp;rsquo;Leary. Former deputy O&amp;rsquo;Leary was terminated for falsifying narcotics arrests. The 28-year-old said he spent 41 days behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Cancel 1,000+ Flights as Arctic Chill Bears Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/airlines-cancel-flights-as-arctic-chill-bears-down-on-midwest-11548804596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand flights are being grounded as a blast of arctic air barrels over the Midwest, bringing with it temperatures too low for airfield workers to load bags or get planes ready for takeoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSER TO DECODING THOUGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/the-download/612843/brain-implants-ai-and-a-speech-synthesizer-have-turned-brain-activity-into-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neural networks have been used to turn words that a human has heard into intelligible, recognizable speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE Slammed for 'Insulting Islam' With Logo Resembling 'Allah'...</title>
      <link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/focus/athletic-outdoor/nike-air-max-logo-allah-petition-change-org-1202735890/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;footwearnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The petition was started five days ago on Change.org.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO: GARCETTI NOT RUNNING... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/29/eric-garcetti-will-not-run-for-president-1136400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Garcetti is scheduled to hold a press conference today at 8 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual 'empty trash bag' orbiting Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/empty-trash-bag-spotted-orbiting-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actually, it's probably a leftover piece of a rocket, but astronomers have never before seen an object like it orbiting so far out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro Fights Back With Targeted Killings, Media Blackout...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-29/maduro-blacks-out-social-media-in-bid-to-bury-guaido-s-message</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopefuls hesitate to define 'Green New Deal' meaning...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2019/01/29/hopefuls-hesitate-define-meaning-green-new-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They love to talk about a landmark climate deal but are short on specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gwyneth Paltrow sued for 'hit and run' ski accident; 'Brain injury, broken ribs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/01/29/utah-man-is-suing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Utah man is suing actress Gwyneth Paltrow for a “hit-and-run ski crash” on the slopes at Deer Valley — alleging she hit him and then skied away as he lay in the snow with serious injuries. And he’s asking for damages in excess of $3.1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much sex on famous nudist beach causing massive damage, say furious environmentalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/world-travel/europe/sex-on-ibizas-famous-sand-dunes-is-ruining-the-environment/news-story/e0d5cb26a4aa386b2829742e39f84723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Randy tourists having sex on Ibiza’s most famous nudist beach are causing massive damage to the island’s protected sand dunes, say furious environmentalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD: Beto counter-narrative driving political class nuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/29/opinions/beto-orourke-is-driving-the-political-class-nuts-axelrod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether or not the Texan -- blogging from a road trip at the moment -- runs in 2020, others could learn something from him about shattering old political shibboleths; about genuinely listening, empathy and the need for an authentic, connecting narrative that can help lift our divided country, writes David Axelrod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musician finds migrants hiding in tour bus to cross UK border...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-01-29/amy-shark-finds-stowaways-on-tour-bus/10757260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shark's crew discovers the pair in the luggage compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Wants to Be Big in Entertainment. First, A $49 Billion Problem to Fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-t-wants-to-be-big-in-entertainment-first-it-has-a-49-billion-problem-to-fix-11548777413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The telecom giant is attempting to expand its footprint in a media industry currently in a state of flux. But since acquiring DirecTV in 2015, the satellite pay-TV service has become a drag on AT&amp;T’s business and public image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First quarterly decline in revenue and profit in over decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-posts-drop-in-quarterly-revenue-and-profit-11548797780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. posted a quarterly decline in both revenue and profit, the first time in more than a decade for the December quarter, underlining its need to reignite slowing iPhone sales and get more growth from services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare fruit selling for $1,343 each!</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/rare-durian-on-sale-in-indonesia-for-1343-each</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAKARTA (DPA) - A rare variety of durian is being sold for 14 million rupiah (S$1,343) each at a shopping mall in an Indonesian town. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services Business Jumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/apple-services-business-grows-19-percent-weak-iphone-sales-1180902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEO Tim Cook had warned investors that the quarter would be a disappointing one due to soft iPhone sales an a weakening economy in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASH PILE GROWS TO $245,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/29/apple-now-has-tk-cash-on-hand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple disclosed its cash pile in its first-quarter 2019 earnings report on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE opens new chapter as iPhone sales fall, stock sinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c281923e5ab14348a7dd673cee7e661e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Apple hoped to offset slowing demand for iPhones by raising the prices of its most important product, but that strategy seems to have backfired after sales sagged during the holiday shopping season. Now, CEO Tim Cook is grappling with his toughest challenge since replacing co-founder Steve Jobs 7 ½ years ago. Even as he tries to boost iPhone sales, Cook also must prove that Apple can still thrive even if demand doesn't rebound. It figures to be an uphill battle, given Apple's stock has lost one-third of its value in less than four months, erasing about $370 billion in shareholder wealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Dog Stuck In Drainage Ditch For 5 MONTHS Rescued...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/01/28/coco-dog-stuck-drain-ditch-five-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dog is safe tonight after spending the last five months trapped in a drainage ditch in South Sacramento.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo defense rests after just 30 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6645135/El-Chapos-defense-case-rests-just-30-minutes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzman called just one witness and put one document into the record on Tuesday before resting the case at his U.S. drug-trafficking trial in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Mocks 'Billionaire'...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/dc/elizabeth-warren-mocks-howard-schultz-electability</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) took a shot Tuesday at former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz&amp;#8217;s chances of mounting a serious presidential campaign,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE earnings raise Wall St. nerves... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/apple-stock-price-earnings-pros-weigh-in-2019-1-1027905964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound bombs explode in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-security-blast/sound-bombs-explode-in-southeast-iran-police-officers-wounded-idUSKCN1PN2HR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sound bombs exploded in front of a police station in the city of Zahedan in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-deal Brexit voted down...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/british-lawmakers-vote-down-bid-to-prevent-no-deal-brexit-idUSKCN1PN007</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British lawmakers voted on Tuesday against a bid to prevent a potentially disord...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abrams to deliver Dems' State of Union response...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/abrams-deliver-dems-state-the-union-response/2Oo3TTBaQB8OMaRNhBoc9L/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacey Abrams will deliver the Democratic response to President Donald Trump’s State of the Un...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel chiefs contradict president on NKorea, ISIS threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bb33704147f4951a040dcb53d709586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Directly contradicting President Donald Trump, U.S. intelligence agencies told Congress on Tuesday that North Korea is unlikely to dismantle its nuclear arsenal, that the Islamic State group remains a threat and that the Iran nuclear deal is working. The chiefs made no mention of a crisis at the U.S.-Mexican border for which Trump has considered declaring a national emergency. Their analysis stands in sharp contrast to Trump's almost singular focus on security gaps at the border as the biggest threat facing the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White gold: Unstoppable rise of alternative milks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2019/jan/29/white-gold-the-unstoppable-rise-of-alternative-milks-oat-soy-rice-coconut-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: How wellness upstarts spoiled milk’s healthy reputation – and built a billion-dollar industry from juicing oats and nuts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI final report finds no motive for Vegas shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/shootings/fbi-final-report-finds-no-motive-for-las-vegas-shooting-1584677/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly 16 months, the agency said it cannot determine why gunman Stephen Paddock killed 58 people and injured nearly 900 others in October 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 kids kidnapped, killed for body parts...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/ten-children-in-tanzania-kidnapped-and-killed-for-their-body-parts-authorities-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanzanian authorities say that 10 children who were kidnapped in December were found dead were killed for their body parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS:  Tax Cuts 'Accelerated' Wage Increases...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/starbucks-gop-tax-cuts-accelerated-wage-and-benefit-increases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa leader arrested for 'terroristic threats'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/29/antifa-leader-marines-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheDCNF's reporting led to Joseph Alcoff's arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tracking 3 migrant caravans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/29/us-tracking-three-migrant-caravans-one-12000-peopl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government is tracking three separate migrant caravans, one of them estimated to be more than 12,000 people in size, heading north toward the U.S., a top Pentagon official said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital let woman pull plug on wrong man...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Hospital-let-woman-pull-the-plug-on-wrong-man-13570102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was told her brother was dying, so Shirell Powell hurried to St. Barnabas Hospital in the Bronx last July. The prognosis was bad, Powell was told, she claims in a recently filed lawsuit. Her brother, Frederick Williams, was unconscious from an apparent drug overdose and had suffered severe brain damage. Doctors didn't believe he was going to make it, she said she was told. She sat at his bedside, looking at the 40-year-old man on life support, tubes obscuring his face, and cried. Soon, she called his family in Virginia, including two teen daughters, she told the New York Post, and told them they needed to drive up to say their goodbyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon sending thousands more troops to Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0e34832e77f945c0bd8aefdb1facb1af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting Defense Secretary Pat Shanahan says the U.S. will be sending "several thousand" more American troops to the southern border to provide additional support to Homeland Security. He says the troops will mainly be used to install additional wire barriers and provide increased surveillance of the area. Plans call for about 150 more miles of concertina wire. The Pentagon has approved an extended U.S. deployment to the border through the end of September. Officials have been working out how many forces are needed and which ones should be tapped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI doesn't find motive for Vegas mass shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00b90ac3e97a41c3b3c078855b32d75f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A high-stakes gambler who rained down a hail of gunfire, killing 58 people from his high-rise casino suite in Las Vegas wanted infamy and mass destruction, the FBI told the Associated Press Tuesday, but took whatever motive might stretch beyond that to his grave. "It wasn't about MGM, Mandalay Bay or a specific casino or venue," said Aaron Rouse, the special agent in charge of the FBI's Las Vegas office. "It was all about doing the maximum amount of damage and him obtaining some form of infamy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodell-Critical Outlet Banned, Threatened Arrest Over Fake Passes...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/29/barstool-sports-pft-commenter-arrested-at-super-bowl-media-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Portnoy was not arrested, but instead banned from the Super Bowl after he was caught with a fake pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Begs Users to Stop Calling Serial Killer Ted Bundy 'Hot'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/netflix-begs-people-to-stop-calling-serial-killer-ted-bundy-hot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are literally THOUSANDS of hot men on the service -- almost all of whom are not convicted serial murderers," streaming service tweets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot owners swap used parts on forum...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8305623/sex-robots-used-second-hand-buy-doll-forum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX ROBOT owners are swapping “used” parts and selling “bruised, battered” dolls on a creepy online forum. Randy bot-bonkers flog their second-hand dolls to each other – som…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Belichick beat league built for parity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jan/29/bill-belichick-new-england-patriots-strategy-nfl-super-bowl-liii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots head coach is an economics major, and his exploitation of market inefficiency has helped him dominate the NFL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Kellyanne Leaked While Aide Drafted Statement Denying She Leaked...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6640749/Kellyanne-Conways-White-House-leaking-worst-kept-secret-town-says-former-aide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House aide Cliff Sims on Monday claimed Kellyanne Conway's leaking about President Donald Trump to reporters was 'the worst-kept secret in town.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Confidence Falls Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/01/29/consumer-confidence-falls-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidence fell for the third consecutive month but remains quite high by historical standards. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway slams Trump: 'Your stupidity knows no bounds'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/427445-george-conway-slams-trump-your-stupidity-knows-no-bounds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway and a frequent critic of President Trump, blasted him on Tuesday, saying his “stupidity knows no bounds” after Trump ripped into former aide Cliff Sims for h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Star Recovering from Homophobic Attack, Chemical Substance Used...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/empire-star-jussie-smollett-homophobic-attack-chicago-chemical-substance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some journalists wonder if profession is tweet-crazy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd0b37f7e04d48fdae04451459f72703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — If Twitter is the town square for journalists, some are ready to step away. That's happening this week at the online news site Insider — by order of the boss. Reporters have been told to take a week off from tweeting at work and to keep TweetDeck off their computer screens. The idea of disengaging is to kick away a crutch for the journalists and escape from the echo chamber, said Julie Zeveloff West, Insider's editor-in-chief for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign threatens to sue ex-staffer for tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6644447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has lashed out at authors in the past – most notably journalist Michael Wolff, who he called 'a total loser who made up stories.' The book quickly became an Amazon best-seller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slams Kamala Plan to Abolish Private Insurance...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/howard-schultz-blasts-kamala-harris-plan-to-abolish-private-insurance-thats-not-american/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What industry are we going to abolish next? The coffee industry?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Brady Conquered His Greatest Opponent: Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-tom-brady-conquered-his-greatest-opponent-age-11548767181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady throws short passes. He gets rid of the ball quickly. He never gets hit. And it’s how he’s in his ninth Super Bowl at 41 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby Targeted by Drone Camera in Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/29/bill-cosby-prison-drone-camera-photo-lockdown-sci-phoenix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's an eye in the sky over Bill Cosby, and Pennsylvania Prison officials are pissed about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Vatican priest resigns over advances to nun...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20190129/senior-vatican-priest-resigns-over-advances-to-nun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Vatican priest accused of making advances towards a nun during confession has resigned, the Vatican said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DON'T GO OUTSIDE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/weather/ct-met-chicago-weather-dangerous-cold-outlook-20190128-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the coldest air masses in years will drop temperatures to around 23 below zero by Tuesday night, according to the National Weather Service, with a daytime high of about minus 14 on Wednesday and another plunge to minus 25 overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals face fight for survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/weather/ct-met-chicago-cold-weather-wild-animals-20190128-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wild and feral animals that live outdoors in Chicago could be fighting for their lives Wednesday and Thursday when the polar vortex brings temperatures expected to dip more than 20 degrees below zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign preparing to sue ex-staffer...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/427417-top-official-says-trump-campaign-preparing-to-sue-ex-staffer-who-wrote-tell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top official for President Trump's 2020 campaign said Tuesday that the campaign was preparing to file a lawsuit against former White House communications aide Cliff Sims for violating a non-disclosure agreement (NDA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexander the Great 'buried alive after disease paralyzed him for six days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8303195/alexander-the-great-was-alive-while-body-was-prepared-for-burial-after-rare-disease-left-him-paralysed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mystery over the death of Alexander the Great may have finally been solved – and his passing was grislier than historians had ever imagined. The fearsome military genius succumbed to a rare dis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked men, drugs, karmic baths: What it's like at greatest spiritual gathering on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/india/articles/kumbh-mela-india/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane passenger meltdown after seated between 'two fat pigs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/plane-passenger-meltdown-because-shes-13920671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed passenger was later ejected from the flight because of her abusive comments on the United Airlines flight from Las Vegas to New Jersey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEED A MIRACLE: Marianne Williamson launches campaign...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/427394-author-marianne-williamson-running-for-2020-dem-nomination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author and activist Marianne Williamson has announced a bid for the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination, joining a crowded field of candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Revolution: Part Deux...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-01-28/french-revolution-part-deux</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte's Crime War, Which Has Killed Thousands, Turns Toward Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dutertes-crime-war-which-has-killed-thousands-turns-toward-children-11548763638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine strongman Rodrigo Duterte is widening his crackdown on drugs and crime by lowering the country’s legal age of responsibility, a move opponents say risks sweeping children up as criminals in violence that has killed thousands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans in Texas sounding alarm about 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/texas-republicans-fear-trump-could-lose-the-state-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Republicans in Texas are sounding the alarm about 2020, warning President Trump could lose the usually reliably red state unless he devotes resources and attention to it typically reserved for electoral battlegrounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrants cross Arizona border after 'busloads' dropped off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/28/politics/migrants-arizona-arrests/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the early morning hours Thursday, several busloads of migrants were dropped off on Highway 2 in Mexico, just south of the Arizona border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashless experience coming? VISA says yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/01/29/cashless-super-bowl-coming-visa-says-yes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — So you’re headed to the Super Bowl some year in the future, and you’re wondering how much cash you’ll need for the big game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could be new Clinton if Dems impeach: Sympathetic and stronger than ever...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/427329-trump-could-be-the-new-clinton-if-democrats-impeach-sympathetic-and-stronger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rehabilitated Trump could then be even more formidable than incumbent presidents seeking re-election already are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists test shark bite-resistant wetsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.surfertoday.com/surfing/14838-scientists-test-a-shark-bite-resistant-wetsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.surfertoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By using a special material similar to Kevlar, researchers from Flinders University, in Australia, hope to reduce the blood loss in shark attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second fuel pipeline explodes in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://punchng.com/second-fuel-pipeline-explodes-in-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;punchng.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pipeline in Mexico exploded while people were stealing fuel from it, near where a similar blast this month left 115 dead, an official said. The new blast struck Monday in the central state of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Egypt, stray dogs pose growing urban challenge...</title>
      <link>https://aawsat.com/english/home/article/1566966/egypt-stray-dogs-pose-growing-urban-challenge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;aawsat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alaa Hilal was out shopping in Cairo when she was attacked by a stray dog in broad daylight -- an increasing problem of daily life in Egypt which is stirring debate. "I got out of my car and saw an exceptionally large street dog," the 38-year-old hou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu's toughest ballot rival, ex-general Gantz, to break silence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190129085435-w1gtu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/GANTZ (PIX, TV):Netanyahu's toughest ballot rival, ex-general Gantz, to break silence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Govt Seen as Most Corrupt in Seven Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-leads-plunge-lower-by-populists-in-annual-corruption-index#gs.lneflmVF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trumpâ€™s U.S.A dropped six places to 22nd globally in the 2018 corruption-perception index published by Transparency International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems float idea of primary challenge for Ocasio-Cortez...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/427364-some-dems-float-idea-of-primary-challenge-for-ocasio-cortez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) has infuriated colleagues by aligning with a progressive outside group that’s threatening to primary entrenched Democrats.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
