<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA sees highest 24-hour death toll increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/us-sees-highest-24-hour-coronavirus-death-toll-increase-since-outbreak-started</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States experienced the largest 24-hour jump in the coronavirus death toll since the outbreak was discovered in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY THANKS TEAM, COACHES, FANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/03/17/tom-brady-leaving-new-england-patriots-nfl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is making it official ... he's leaving the New England Patriots after 20 seasons and continuing his NFL career in another city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague of locusts set to descend upon Middle East in time for Passover...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/plague-of-locusts-set-to-descend-upon-middle-east-in-time-for-passover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Extremely alarming' desert locust swarms forming in Horn of Africa -- but will skip Holy Land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio considering shelter-in-place edict...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/17/coronavirus-in-nyc-bill-de-blasio-says-a-shelter-in-place-edict-is-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio may soon order New Yorkers to only leave their homes for food, medicine and exercise — a major escalation of the Big Apple’s coronavirus containment plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SAYS GOODBYE TO PATRIOTS</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/03/17/tom-brady-leaving-patriots-thanking-belichick-and-kraft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is leaving the New England Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Nationalize Big Firms in Radical Response...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-france-nationalist/france-could-nationalize-big-companies-if-necessary-finance-minister-idUSKBN2141AO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is prepared to use all means to support big companies suff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears ignite civil war as families, friends, neighbors clash over what's safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/coronavirus/coronavirus-covid-pandemic-philadelphia-montgomery-county-pennsylvania-families-20200316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One side is armed with a bottomless supply of statistics, frightening news stories, and personal pleas from those most at risk; the other with skepticism and an understandable desire to maintain normalcy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Dead of Night, Israel Approves Harsher Tracking Methods Than Gov't Stated...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-cellphone-tracking-authorized-by-israel-to-be-used-for-enforcing-quarantine-orders-1.8681979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$850 BILLION RESCUE PLAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8121047/Trumps-850-BILLION-rescue-plan-Steven-Mnuchin-ask-massive-spending-save-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is now asking for $850 billion or more from Congress in phase three of an economic stimulus package to combat the unstable economy during the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS VOLATILE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/16/us-stock-futures-rise-slightly-following-dows-third-worst-day-ever.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average and S&amp;P 500 had their worst day since the "Black Monday" crash of 1987, falling 12.9% and 12%, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Could be Next Hotspot With 'Avalanche' of Cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-could-next-virus-hotspot-064016084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- India could become the next global hotspot for virus cases, with experts warning containment measures that proved successful elsewhere in Asia may not work in the world’s second-most populous country.The South Asian nation, which has so far reported 125 infections and three deaths, is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under lockdown, Armageddon is like end of the world...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200317095420-8jz5h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-RELIGION (PIX):Under coronavirus lockdown, Armageddon is like the end of the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upside-Down World of Negative Rates Coming for U.S. Savers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/upside-down-world-negative-rates-100000573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mattresses full of money, getting paid to take out a mortgage, surging demand for safe-deposit boxes -- these are some of the ideas people have about what happens when interest rates turn negative.Just a few months ago, such scenes -- at least in the U.S. -- seemed unthinkable. But with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'D' word rears head as markets brace for recession...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/d-word-rears-head-coronavirus-050658349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus shockwaves rippling through U.S. stocks are forcing investors to contemplate outcomes more dire than a recession, including several quarters of declining economic activity, a credit crisis or even a depression. "This market looks like it has already priced in most of a garden variety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are at war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/17/coronavirus-france-president-macron-warns-we-are-at-war.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France will spend 45 billion euros ($50 billion) to help small businesses and employees struggling with the coronavirus outbreak, after President Emmanuel Macron declared "we are at war" against the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Rich Stranded as Private Jet Operators Say No to Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/super-rich-stranded-as-private-jet-operators-say-no-to-travel-1.1407304</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private jet operators are turning away wealthy clients as coronavirus-related travel bans restrict their ability to operate, despite a surge in requests from people willing to shell out as much as $150,000 to secure a spot on their planes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All Around Us Is Chaos.' Inside Rural Town Upended...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/17/all-around-us-is-chaos-inside-a-rural-town-upended-by-the-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CYNTHIANA, Ky. — Closing in on a week after the coronavirus had descended on his small, rural community, James D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawling Monkeys. Wandering Deer. Blame Coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/16/brawling-monkeys-wandering-deer-blame-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a video posted last week, a mob of monkeys runs around a city plaza in Thailand. Something gets thrown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty surrounds Dem primary as Ohio scraps vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/87b33645ee45b69a953e5a45a95698d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Democratic presidential primary is consumed with uncertainty after leaders in Ohio called off Tuesday's election just hours before polls were set to open, citing the need to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-line Shiites storm Iran shrines closed over coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e92d93551ee6c6ae51d0acaaad9eb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Hard-line Shiite faithful in Iran pushed their way into the courtyards of two major shrines just closed over fears of the new coronavirus, Iranian state media...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex workers face ruin amid virus fears, brothel closures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/62a2ea1dc6b3bf7d10b1d7305dc1a391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — It's 7 p.m. on a Friday night, a time when Aurel Johannes Marx's three-room brothel on the edge of Berlin would normally be preparing for its first customers. Sex for sale has long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military faces limitations in responding to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24c349f9c8fa71b9dda2cafb9e86229f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon is already helping combat the coronavirus outbreak in the United States and is considering ways to do more. But the military faces limits. Its health care...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in San Francisco screeches to halt amid shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07672ee6aded6e8ac5954c07676eb926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — First, people were advised to avoid large gatherings. Californians adjusted. Life went on. Kids went to school, some people worked from home, but mostly it was business...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Derby pushed back; First delay since 1945...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdrb.com/news/kentucky-derby-to-be-postponed-until-september-as-concerns-heighten/article_5e88ecce-6557-11ea-8c64-1bf69c1bc962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdrb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's no word yet on the status of Derby Eve galas, any other pre-Derby events or the other two races in the Triple Crown of horse racing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of coronavirus cases passed on by 'stealth transmission'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/coronavirus-stealth-transmission-causing-vast-21704520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new report, infectious disease expert Jeffrey Shaman believes there were at least half a dozen stealth coronavirus cases to every one diagnosis at the start of the epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychologist's science-based tips for emotional resilience... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/lifestyle/article/A-psychologist-s-science-based-tips-for-emotional-15135619.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the news about the coronavirus pandemic becomes grimmer, and governments and businesses issue closing or work-from-home directives, many of us are experiencing a variety of negative emotions. We feel anxiety in response to the uncertainty of the situation; sadness related to losing our daily sources of meaning and joy; and anger at whatever forces are to blame for bringing this upon us. As a psychologist, I believe following evidence-based recommendations for bolstering mental resilience can help us weather this crisis.  It's normal to be unsettled and concerned about the upending of life as we know it. "Humans find comfort and safety in the predictability of the routines of daily living," said John Forsyth, a professor of psychology at the University at Albany in New York and co-author of "Acceptance and Commitment Therapy for Anxiety Disorders." As our lives have dramatically changed overnight, many are struggling with finding ways to deal with the new reality. "We have two children home from college, along with a girlfriend of one, and another high schooler who is distance-learning," said Jane Legg, an elementary school teacher from Bethesda, Maryland. "It's like a lot of people cramped in a small ship, all trying to get their work done."  Many parents of younger children are facing the stress of taking care of them at home, often while teleworking themselves. And families with elderly or sick members are dealing with even stricter isolation in an attempt to prevent covid-19 in this vulnerable population. "I feel especially sad and worried for my elderly mom and aunt who are sequestered in their assisted living facilities," said Larry Eastman, a retired engineer in Ellicott City, Maryland. "And I'm concerned about my dad being isolated, because he's not leaving home."  Nobody knows how long the pandemic will last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASINOS WANT BAILOUT!</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Casinos-ask-Congress-for-emergency-aid-as-15135870.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Casinos have joined the airline industry in asking Congress for emergency financial help as Las Vegas and other tourist destinations take a severe financial hit from the coronavirus outbreak.  The requested aid for the casino companies, raised by lobbyists in recent days, could come in the form of a comprehensive bailout package, similar to what lawmakers may provide to airlines, cruise companies and the hospitality industry. Other possibilities include direct cash payments, deferred taxes, or special bankruptcy protections, said two people with knowledge of the conversations, who were not authorized to speak publicly.  One person said that on a strategy call Monday with members of the American Gaming Association, which represents the industry, a representative of Wynn Resorts raised the possibility of the industry seeking cash payments. Wynn Resorts was previously run by one of President Donald Trump's biggest political donors, Steve Wynn, though he resigned from his post in 2018. A Wynn Resorts representative did not respond to requests for comment.  The American Gaming Association issued a statement to The Washington Post on Monday, saying that with the $260 billion industry at a "near standstill," additional funds are needed to support casino companies and their employees.  "As state governments close casinos as a part of the urgent public health response to COVID-19, elected leaders should move just as urgently to support the workers and businesses who will bear the brunt of those effects," said the AGA, referring to the disease caused by the novel coronavirus. "Our immediate priorities are actions that provide liquidity to allow us to support employees."  The casino industry has been battered by shutdowns related to the coronavirus, with an increasing number of states demanding that all casinos, restaurants and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's the end game?</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/health/story/2020-03-15/whats-the-covid-19-end-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The answer to this question changed dramatically this week with unprecedented action on social distancing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite dire warning, some refuse to give up their routines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/lifestyle-buzz/despite-dire-coronavirus-warning-some-refuse-to-give-up-their-routines/ar-BB11gwUG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKDOWN FOR 15 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8118415/Donald-Trump-tells-America-lockdown-15-days-stop-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Monday released a series of coronavirus guidelines to slow the spread that calls for a lockdown of America, including the closing of restaurants and schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcgis.com/apps/opsdashboard/index.html#/bda7594740fd40299423467b48e9ecf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcgis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France calls for all citizens to remain confined in homes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/487870-frances-macron-calls-for-all-citizens-to-remain-confined-in-homes-were</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron on Monday called for citizens to restrict themselves from taking unnecessary trips outside of their homes for at least two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico under 24-hour isolation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/puerto-rico-first-us-territory-under-24-hour-224602015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Puerto Rico was under 24-hour isolation Monday, governor Wanda Vazquez told local media, leaving the island the first major US jurisdiction to take such drastic measures against the coronavirus pandemic. "All citizens should stay in their homes 24/7 until March 30," Vazquez told WKAQ 580 AM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With megaphones, Brazil orders Rio beach-goers home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/megaphones-brazil-orders-rio-beach-goers-home-170412860.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone hoping to escape wall-to-wall coronavirus coverage with a day at the beach can forget about it in Rio de Janeiro, where authorities armed with megaphones blared out messages Monday ordering everyone home. Rio state Governor Wilson Witzel had warned residents to stay away from the waterfront in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 pledge to 'do whatever it takes' to safeguard economy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/g7-pledge-whatever-takes-safeguard-economy-173736911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaders of the G7 industrial powerhouses pledged Monday to join forces to halt economic freefall in the wake of the coronavirus pandemic, which they called "a human tragedy." As the outbreak caused more countries to shut down and brought the global economy to a screeching halt, the leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  World should learn lessons from China... </title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200317000930-0b0vn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHINA-EDITORIAL:World should learn lessons from China in coronavirus fight - China Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia considers tougher movement restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316233425-9st08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (PIX):Australia considers tougher movement restrictions to combat coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American tempers fray...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316220412-nzjlg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MOOD (PIX):Fear and loathing bloom as American tempers fray in coronavirus crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -3000</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd3276744b861e2669fd761733e9d2b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The U.S. stock market plunged to its worst day in more than three decades as voices from Wall Street to the White House said the coronavirus may be dragging the economy into a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is our generation's great test'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a342998638cdccb56172a1663e8d6edf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Officials in six San Francisco Bay Area counties issued a sweeping shelter-in-place mandate Monday affecting nearly 7 million people, ordering residents to stay at home and go...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun sales surging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9402d0680bbd3f27836a283c1956d671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — The world's largest gun store, in metro Atlanta, has had lines that are six and eight people deep. A gun store in Los Angeles had lines that stretched down the block. And at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds dropping case for 2 Russian companies in troll probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7527e051bd8c4be1beef9d7c37c8290e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department is moving to drop charges against two Russian companies that were accused of funding a social media campaign to sway American public opinion during the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somali who confirmed Rep. Omar married her brother says he's living in fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8097281/Community-leader-confirmed-Ilhan-Omar-married-brother-living-fear.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wheelchair-bound Abdihakim Osman, who once campaigned for Ilhan Omar and considered her a friend, came forward last month to confirm that Ilhan Omar married her own brother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France deploys 100,000 police to enforce lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316205604-r3s2w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-MINISTER (URGENT):France to deploy 100,000 police to enforce coronavirus lockdown - minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba welcomes cruise ship with COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dc592c74308c0997037b2d3231f14962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — A British cruise ship that was turned away from several Caribbean ports after passengers fell ill with novel coronavirus is scheduled to dock in Cuba Tuesday after the island agreed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinemas close...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/46d247ad42a1975d18ab2434c3b7976d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. movie theaters nationwide are preparing to shut down after President Donald Trump announced new guidelines urging against gatherings of more than 10 people because of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates vote as Chicago sets up polling places in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/16/chicago-inmates-vote-polling-places-set-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirjerathan Wilson never thought it was worth the trouble to vote and never had. But inside Cook County Jail, Wilson sees it differently: voting is a chance to remind himself that his opinion matters and to show his family that he’s doing more than just letting one day bleed into the next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi Judge Shot, Critically Wounded Outside Courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2020-03-16/mississippi-judge-shot-critically-wounded-near-courthouse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida beaches busy...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/health/2020/03/16/coronavirus-florida-beaches-in-pinellas-county-remain-open-for-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to Governors: Get Respirators...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-to-governors-on-ventilators-try-getting-it-yourselves/ar-BB11h0TU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More state delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1cf882a5a45b584e30e0663fb7667421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Ohio's governor wants the state to delay in-person voting for the state's Tuesday presidential primary for three months to let the coronavirus outbreak subside, but Florida,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco orders residents to stay inside...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/local-politics/article/Bay-Area-must-shelter-in-place-Only-15135014.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The orders fall just short of a full lockdown, and it wasn’t immediately clear how, or to what degree, they would be enforced. People will still be able to go shopping for essential items such as food and household supplies, and seek medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo to turn college dorms into medical facilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.lohud.com/story/news/health/2020/03/16/ny-plans-turn-college-dorms-into-medical-sites-fight-covid-19/5061163002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lohud.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If COVID-19 cases keep surging in New York it will overwhelm hospitals, Cuomo said. Here's what state government is doing if feds fail to act</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China is planning to use crisis to its advantage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2020/03/16/how-china-is-planning-use-coronavirus-crisis-its-advantage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing is trying to game the situation to take even more control of the industries of the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R.E.M.'s 'It's The End Of The World' Back On Charts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/coronavirus-has-r-e-m-s-its-the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it-climbing-charts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lenny Bruce is not afraid, but the rest of us aren't doing so hot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA pulling out of key Iraq bases
...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-51914600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision to leave three sites shows the US is looking to dramatically reduce its footprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSAL Breaks Theatrical Window...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/universal-trolls-world-tour-the-hunt-invisible-man-coronavirus-1203535541/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With movie theaters closing or reducing seating capacity due to coronavirus, Universal Pictures will make its movies available on home entertainment on the same day as the films’ global theat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No spying from home in CIA's coronavirus plan...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-health-coronavirus-cia/no-spying-from-home-in-cias-coronavirus-plan-idUKKBN2133A5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the age of the coronavirus, working from home is no option for many employees...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to Governors: Get Respirators...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/902682/trump-governors-try-getting-respirators-coronavirus-patients-yourselves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governors across the United States are scrambling to make sure their health care systems have enough respirators to help people diagnosed with the coronavirus, but President Trump surprised them Monday by telling them not wait for the federal government, The New York Times reports. 'Respirators, ventilators, all of the equipment â€” try getting it yourselves,' Trump reportedly told the governors during a conference call. He did say the federal government 'will be backing' the states, but, for now, they should try to resolve the issue on their own. 'Point of sales, much better, much more direct if you can get it yourself,' he said. Beyond that, Trump reportedly stayed on course by sounding optimistic amid the pandemic, promising the governors 'we're going to get it remedied and hopefully very quickly.' Trump has invoked some strict travel measures since the outbreak began, but his critics have argued he's been slow to grasp the severity of the situation, leaving the most intense measures to the states. Read more at The New York Times. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general warns: 'We could be Italy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/live-updates-us-life-shuts-down-due-to-coronavirus-as-surgeon-general-warns-we-could-be-italy/ar-BB11eTQt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Want $50 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/16/us-airlines-seek-more-than-50-billion-in-aid-as-coronavirus-roils-business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. airlines are seeking government assistance of more than $50 billion, including a mix of direct aid and loan guarantees,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA CLOSES BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/cbsa-border-airports-screening-trudeau-covid19-coronavirus-1.5498866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada is barring entry to all travellers who are not Canadian citizens or permanent residents, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau announced today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Asks Govt to Help...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/business-asks-government-act-avert-devastating-hit-69622212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's largest business organization is asking government leaders to act rapidly to help companies have access to cash and avert a “potentially devastating” hit to the economy as the coronavirus pandemic forces closures and quarantines worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked document:  UK crisis to last 12 months with 8 million in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/15/uk-coronavirus-crisis-to-last-until-spring-2021-and-could-see-79m-hospitalised</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Public Health England document seen by Guardian says four in five ‘expected’ to contract virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing index record decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/empire-state-manufacturing-index-sees-record-decline-to--215-in-march-2020-03-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers:The New York Fed’s Empire State business conditions index plunged a record 34.4 points to -21.5 in March, the regional Fed bank said Monday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Prince's superyacht capsizes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/544248/saudi-prince-superyacht-capsize-sink-greece/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $79MILLION superyacht owned by a Saudi prince capsized and partially sunk while it was docked in Greece. The 230ft Nourah of Riyad, owned by Prince Turki bin Mohammed bin Fahd Al Saud, was being …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich People Raising Quick Cash From  Art Collections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/rich-people-are-raising-cash-from-their-art-collections/ar-BB11g3kF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed throwing money in wrong place, says former top banking regulator...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/exclusive-fed-is-throwing-money-in-the-wrong-place-says-sheila-bair-former-top-banking-regulator-2020-03-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheila Bair, a top U.S. banking regulator during the 2007-’08 global financial crisis, said the Federal Reserve needs to quickly shift its focus to getting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and isolation for many Asian American seniors...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/coronavirus-means-fear-and-isolation-for-many-asian-american-seniors/article_fcfc2fde-f7f1-567e-9deb-1eef0ca3f253.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — On church days, Willy Chang, 72, is skipping service, including steering clear of his usual after-service lunch spot, and is definitely not stopping at his neighborhood market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police ask public to stop calling 911 over lack of toilet paper...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/do-not-call-911-just-because-you-ran-out-of-toilet-paper-oregon-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One police department in Oregon posted a reminder on their Facebook page, asking the public to not call 9-1-1 if they run out of toilet paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED PUMPS, PUMPS, PUMPS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/16/fed-says-it-will-offer-an-additional-500-billion-in-overnight-repo-funding-markets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed increased the amount of liquidity it's offering in short-term lending to the financial industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 earthquakes in 15 hours rattle Carolinas, Tennessee...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article241227321.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Battle 'Overwhelming Anxiety' With Longterm School Closures...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-parents-students-across-us-contend-with-school-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's public school system joins others across the country in shutting down, forcing families to find child care and meals at a moment's notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 BONUS FOR EVERY CITIZEN?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-recession-direct-payments-americans-ubi-c3393d14-33ad-47c2-a739-f2fec150b212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing chorus of liberal and conservative economists are lining up behind such a proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kid Rock's Nashville Bar Refuses To Close, Calls  Mandate 'Unconstitutional'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/country-music/2020/03/16/kid-rock-nashville-bar-refuses-close-amid-coronavirus-concerns-mayor-mandate-unconstitutional/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of Kid Rock's Big Ass Honky Tonk Rock N' Roll Steakhouse in Nashville said he is [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slash almost all flights...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/global-airlines-slash-almost-flights-virus-spreads-wings-145441420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major world airlines on Monday axed almost all flights on a temporary basis as the worsening coronavirus crisis sparks travel bans, ravages demand and sends shares into freefall, triggering pleas to help carriers survive. IAG, owner of British Airways and Spanish carrier Iberia, announced it would slash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU BAN ON VISITORS?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316150745-3kno6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/EU (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-EU executive proposes shutting bloc's external borders for 30 days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia bans public events, closes schools...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316145442-8xfje</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MOSCOW-EVENTS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Russia ramps up coronavirus controls, bans public events, closes schools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte puts Philippines under quarantine, says 'we are in fight of our lives'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200316135824-ivaic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PHILIPPINES (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Duterte puts Philippines under quarantine, says "we are in the fight of our lives"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVING THROUGH HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b64cf00f37d8da2fad3533aa7686c53d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Millions of Americans began their work week holed up at home Monday against the coronavirus outside their doors, as the escalating outbreak shifted the nation’s daily routines in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 In 5 Americans Expect They'll Be Diagnosed With Coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/national-nightmare-1-in-5-americans-expect-theyll-be-diagnosed-with-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey conducted by StudyFinds reveals that about one in five Americans believe they'll catch the coronavirus eventually, and a third admit having some fear about leaving their own home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court will delay oral arguments...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/supreme-court-announces-it-will-delay-oral-arguments-n1160386</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justices will not be in the courtroom when they were to resume hearing cases next week and no date has been set for their return..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoot Stray Dogs, Win Cash Prizes: How Chinese Officials Slaughtered Canines...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/03/16/shoot-stray-dogs-win-cash-prizes-how-chinese-officials-slaughtered-canines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A southern China community neighbourhood management office offered cash rewards to citizens for slaughtering “stray” dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient: 'Like nothing I had ever quite experienced'...</title>
      <link>https://www.beaconjournal.com/news/20200315/hudson-coronavirus-patient-lsquolike-nothing-i-had-ever-quite-experiencedrsquo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.beaconjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hudson resident Amy Driscoll followed all the recommended protocols. Wash your hands. Use hand sanitizer. Don’t touch your face. She still</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of Americans Losing Sleep...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/202003161078578597-nearly-one-third-of-us-losing-sleep-over-coronavirus-worries-wyoming-hawaii-top-list---survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are feeling the strain of 'coronavirus fatigue' as new cases are being reported by the Trump administration and numerous bureaus amid a state of emergency...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY, NJ, CT announce statewide business closures...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/16/ny-nj-conn-announce-state-wide-coronavirus-business-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businesses across New York, New Jersey and Connecticut will be shuttered to stem the coronavirus contagion in an unheard-of accord among the three states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside $110 million private jet: Flying penthouse apartment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/see-inside-worlds-newest-private-115100351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aircraft seats 19 and features a master bedroom and en suite bathroom with a shower, catering to the highest echelon of the elite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger and his tiny horses urge people to stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/mar/16/arnold-schwarzenegger-and-his-tiny-horses-urges-people-to-stay-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-California governor says ‘Listen to the experts, ignore the morons’ in Twitter video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Roker Pulled Off Air as Outbreak Hits 'TODAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/coronavirus-hits-30-rock-after-today-employee-tests-positive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer for the third hour of the morning show has tested positive for the coronavirus leaving NBC to try and trace their contacts with other members of the team at 30 Rock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ventilator shortage?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/hospitals-us-government-potential-ventilator-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the number of cases from the coronavirus continue to climb, U.S. hospitals and government officials are preparing for the possibility of a potential shortage of ventilators, a machine that has proven effective in helping the most severely ill patients breathe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rout threatens to wipe out all gains since inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/trump-has-lost-the-majority-of-his-stock-market-gains-amid-equity-rout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What was once a 61% Dow gain since Trump's election has evaporated to far thinner 18.2% rally as the index sank from an all-time high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teetering economy sparks talk of second stimulus package...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/487531-teetering-economy-sparks-talk-of-second-stimulus-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate returns to work Monday to take up the House-passed coronavirus relief package, but senators are already starting discussions about a second round of economic stimulus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
