<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg slams Trump's handling of Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1151874/mark-zuckerberg-fauci-coronavirus-cases-us-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARK Zuckerberg has blamed the Trump administration for the US coronavirus outbreak becoming “worse than many other countries” due to “less effective” leadership. The Facebo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which sparks set off Miami's wildfire?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/which-sparks-set-off-miamis-covid-wildfire-the-clues-are-in-the-cases-experts-say/ar-BB16Q9qM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci Wants to See Him 'Humiliated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/scaramucci-says-he-wants-to-see-trump-humiliated/ar-BB16PEEk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims 'Racist' Donald Has Used N-Word, Anti-Semitic Slurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-mary-trump-accuses-president-trump-of-using-n-word-anti-semitic-slurs-in-msnbc-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump accuses President Trump of using N-word, anti-Semitic slurs in MSNBC interview with Rachel Maddow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book sells Record 950,000+ Copies on First Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/16/media/mary-trump-book-sales/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump's tell-all book had sold a staggering 950,000 copies by the end of its first day on sale, publisher Simon &amp; Schuster said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-'ELLEN' Employees Allege Toxic Work Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/krystieyandoli/ellen-employees-allege-toxic-workplace-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If [Ellen] wants to have her own show and have her name on the show title, she needs to be more involved to see what's going on,” one former employee said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://nflpa.com/covid-19-updates-information</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nflpa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest updates for players on returning to work, testing and COVID-related protocols for players, teams and facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with fraudulently claiming $9 million in covid relief --  and gambling with it in Vegas!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-man-accused-gambling-away-covid-relief-funds-013747667.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California man was arrested and ordered held without bond on Thursday for fraudulently obtaining some $9 million in coronavirus relief funds and using some of the money to gamble in Las Vegas. Prosecutors say he used some of the money to make risky stock market bets, and squandered hundreds of thousands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/07/16/mask-mandate-colorado-issued-jared-polis-face-masks-required/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Jared Polis issued a statewide mask mandate on Thursday as the number of COVID-19 cases are showing what he called a "significant uptick."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS PROMPTS DRASTIC MEASURES AS DEATH TOLLS SET RECORDS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06d8396db10d3ead960da4fc11cd02ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The coronavirus kept surging in hot spots around the U.S. on Thursday, with one city in South Carolina urging people to pray it into submission, a hospital in Texas bringing in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Campaign's Unappreciated Shrewdness...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/15/the-unappreciated-shrewdness-of-the-joe-biden-campaign-364844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump can’t be counted out. But the Biden campaign is canny enough that it isn’t going to make it easy for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Move Oregon's Border' petitioner files suit to move 17 counties to 'Greater Idaho'...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/pacific-northwest-news/2020/07/move-oregons-border-petitioner-files-federal-lawsuit-in-quest-to-move-17-counties-to-greater-idaho.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike McCarter wants to know if citizens in 17 counties would like to divorce Oregon and get hitched to Idaho instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breach exposes one of tech's biggest threats: Its own employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/twitter-breach-exposes-one-tech-s-biggest-threats-its-own-n1234076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cybersecurity professionals broadly agree on a central problem: Computers and code are fixable, but humans are not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALS Exploring New Home To Avoid DC Protocols...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/nationals-exploring-alternative-sites-for-2020-home-games-to-avoid-dc-coronavirus-protocols-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nationals may be forced to play their home games in Virginia to start the season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72 NFL players test positive...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/507718-72-nfl-players-have-tested-positive-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 72 NFL players have tested positive for COVID-19 as of July 10, according to the NFL Players Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Pours Money Into Biden's Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/7/16/21326740/silicon-valley-biden-trump-fundraising-reports-steve-ballmer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is sweeping up cash from billionaires, CEOs, and political kingmakers in a show of force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA's anonymous 'snitch hotline' lights up...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/sport/american-sports/nba/nbas-anonymous-snitch-hotline-has-received-multiple-submissions/news-story/d76eae645b1e50febdfe341c5d0fb0f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA’s move to install a “snitch hotline” sent social media into a spin when it was first announced, but now it’s reportedly getting a working over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House vows not to 'let science stand in way' of reopening schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8531199/White-House-vows-not-let-science-stand-way-Donald-Trumps-push-reopen-schools.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kayleigh McEnany asserted Thursday that President Donald Trump will not let 'science stand in the way' of his push to reopen schools in the fall in the midst of the coroanvirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia governor suspends all local mask mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/16/politics/georgia-kemp-mask-mandate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia Gov. Brian Kemp on Wednesday suspended all local government mask mandates despite the rise in coronavirus cases and hospitalizations in his state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX names Ted Sarandos co-CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/16/netflix-names-ted-sarandos-co-ceo.html?__source=newsletter%7Cbreakingnews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20-year Netflix veteran will join current chief executive Reed Hastings in the role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faculty demands free tuition for black students...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/california-faculty-union-demands-free-tuition-for-black-students-removal-of-armed-campus-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time to transform higher education,’ union states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to Use Tracking Wearable Tech to Prevent Covid Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/07/social-distancing-effective-navy-considers-employee-tracking-wearables-find-out/166925/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are looking to launch a proximity tracking program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci Wants to See Him 'Humiliated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-16/scaramucci-seeks-end-of-trumpism-in-his-push-to-elect-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharm CEO says raising hopes 'grave disservice'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-health-coronavirus-vaccine-merck-co/merck-ceo-says-raising-covid-19-vaccine-hopes-a-grave-disservice-report-idUKKCN24F2S4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 vaccines under development are not guaranteed to work and people who say to expect a vaccine before year-end are doing a "grave disservice to the public," Merck &amp; Co Inc's chief said, according to an interview published on a Harvard Business School website on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beachgoers Turn Hostile After Being Offered Free Masks...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/15/solving-the-mask-shortage-in-huntington-beach-youtube-video-chad-jt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two YouTubers, Chad Kroeger and JT Parr, went to Huntington Beach to hand out masks to beachgoers during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitoes flying free as health depts focus on virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc7a3de603413b95676f4fe451cb840b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bug spray, swollen welts, citronella. It’s mosquito season. And in a normal year, the health department serving Ohio’s Delaware County would be setting out more than 90 mosquito traps a week...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Coronavirus Death Surge Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2020/07/second-coronavirus-death-surge/614122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was always a logical explanation for why cases rose through the end of June while deaths did not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time, Latinos largest group of Californians admitted to UC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/for-the-first-time-latinos-are-the-largest-group-of-californians-admitted-to-uc/ar-BB16PEri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala made her mark confronting Biden. Could they be running mates?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-07-16/kamala-harris-joe-biden-vice-president-debate-clash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden and Kamala Harris' debate confrontation over race still echoes a year later as Biden weighs his vice presidential pick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People with Type A blood may have higher risk of severe symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/16/health/blood-types-coronavirus-wellness-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most humans fall into one of four blood groups — A, B, AB or O. Ordinarily, your blood type makes little difference in your life except if you need to have a blood transfusion — and now, if you have Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Epicenter of the epicenter': Young keep at it in Miami Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/07/16/vacationers-party-florida-even-covid-19-cases-surge/5449754002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's COVID-19 surge hasn't stopped visitors from partying in Miami Beach, which Mayor Dan Gelber calls "the epicenter of the epicenter."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus data has already disappeared after administration shifted control from CDC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/16/us-coronavirus-data-has-already-disappeared-after-trump-administration-shifted-control-from-cdc-to-hhs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We were surprised because the modules that we normally go to were empty. The data wasn't available and not there," coronavirus researcher Ryan Panchadsaram said. "There was no warning."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Lincoln Tunnel flooding amid traffic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/16/video-shows-lincoln-tunnel-flooding-amid-traffic-standstill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water flooded the Lincoln Tunnel roadway Tuesday as drivers lined up bumper-to-bumper during the evening rush, video shows. “Well, that’s concerning. I’m inside the Lincoln Tunnel, which is underwa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN host secretly recorded in hotel room in sabotage attempt...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/16/espns-rachel-nichols-secretly-recorded-in-florida-hotel-room-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN host Rachel Nichols was secretly recorded having a private conversation about the network’s personnel matters while in her Florida hotel room, according to a report. Nichols, the 46-year-old h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Utah, debate stirs over Estonian radioactive waste...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200716160912-rxagt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MINING/URANIUM (PIX):In Utah, a debate stirs over Estonian radioactive waste</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breach another warning shot for election security...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Cybersecurity-202-Twitter-breach-is-another-15413196.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This time, the massive Twitter hack Wednesday was seemingly just a petty scam to raise bitcoin - at least based on what's known so far. But next time, it could be far more serious.  The unknown hackers held the Twittersphere in thrall as they seized control of high-profile accounts and sent phony tweets from Joe Biden, Barack Obama and a who's who of top companies and business and entertainment leaders. It took Twitter hours of work and an unprecedented shutdown of all verified accounts to halt the operation.  U.S. adversaries that gained that sort of power could sow mass chaos on Election Day by tweeting out phony information about voter fraud or polling locations shut down by the coronavirus or terrorist attacks. And because the breach targeted Twitter controls, over which campaigns are powerless, they might have no power to stop the stream of phony tweets from flowing.  If Twitter once again shut down verified accounts' ability to tweet while it investigated a breach, that would also cut off a key avenue for campaigns, government officials and law enforcement to correct misinformation.  Such an attack could be particularly disastrous during a close election if people don't vote because of the confusion.  "Russia's most dangerous play is how do you inflict the maximum amount of chaos on Election Day," Clint Watts, a distinguished research fellow at the Foreign Policy Research Institute who tracks Russian influence operations, told me. "They want to further erode confidence in democracy, and this is emblematic of a way they can do that."  Rachel Tobac, chief executive of SocialProof Security, called the breach very concerning. "We are extremely lucky that these attackers are monetarily motivated and not sowing mass chaos all over the world," she said.  Other prominent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced Labor at world's top surgical glove maker?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-sanctions-worlds-top-surgical-glove-maker-over-002421917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US has banned the import of surgical gloves from two subsidiaries of Malaysia's Top Glove -- the world's biggest manufacturer of the product -- over forced labour concerns, despite soaring demand during the coronavirus pandemic. It noted the "critical need" for disposable gloves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI MOVES IN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200716153610-4he0z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWITTER-CYBER/FBI (EXCLUSIVE, URGENT):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. FBI is leading an inquiry into the Twitter hack - sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo announces 'three strikes' rules on bars and restaurants... </title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200716153339-1x1z3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/NEW YORK (URGENT):New York's Cuomo announces new restrictions on bars and restaurants after compliance issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portuguese officers raid clinics claiming 'ozone therapy' cures...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200716134202-sx0o5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PORTUGAL-RAID (PIX):Portuguese officers raid clinics claiming 'ozone therapy' cures COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  MORGAN STANLEY joins Wall St's gold rush with record profit... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-joins-wall-street-113519531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Morgan Stanley wrapped up a week of wins for Wall Street trading desks, capitalizing on the Federal Reserve’s extraordinary rescue measures with record profit.Fixed-income trading revenue almost tripled, driving a 73% jump in total trading that surged past expectations, according to a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Races to Unravel How Cyber-Attack Came From Inside...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/twitter-racing-unravel-mystery-cyber-104500795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As Twitter Inc. grapples with the worst security breach in its 14-year history, it must now uncover whether its employees were victims of sophisticated phishing schemes or if they deliberately allowed hackers to access high-profile accounts.On Wednesday, some of the world’s most prominent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We expected something more than constant heckling from man who was supposed to be our leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/I-m-a-GOP-governor-Why-didn-t-Trump-help-my-15412313.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My wife, Yumi, and I stood on the tarmac, waiting in cloth masks, on the morning of April...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Won in '16 by a Divine Hand, What Would a '20 Loss Mean?</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearreligion.org/articles/2020/07/16/if_trump_won_in_16_by_a_divine_hand_what_would_a_20_loss_mean_499192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearreligion.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to practically every polling and data metric (except fundraising and enthusiasm among President Donald Trump’s base), the president’s reelection prospects look bleak. Nonetheless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to Use Tracking Wearable Tech to Prevent Covid Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/07/social-distancing-effective-navy-considers-employee-tracking-wearables-find-out/166925/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Greenwich Mansions With Pools All the Rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/greenwich-mansions-with-pools-are-all-the-rage-in-pandemic-era/ar-BB16NJmL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book sells Record 950,000+ Copies on First Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/mary-trumps-book-on-president-sold-record-950000-copies-on-first-day-of-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary L. Trump's tell-all book on her uncle President Donald Trump reportedly sold over 950,000 copies on its first day of release, Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOPELESS': Republican Gov. rips Trump's virus response in scathing letter...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/925865/marylands-gop-governor-publishes-scathing-indictment-trumps-coronavirus-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can apparently count Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan (R) among the solid majority of Americans who are unimpressed with President Trump's COVID-19 response. In a brutal Quinnipiac University poll released Wednesday, for example, 62 percent of registered voters said Trump is hurting the effort to fight COVID-19, while 67 percent said they don't trust the information he shares about the disease. Unlike most Americans, though, Hogan has a front-row seat to Trump's response, both as a governor and chairman of the National Governors Association. Hogan published a detailed, withering critique of Trump's response in an op-ed Thursday in Trump's least-favorite newspaper, The Washington Post. He started with the extraordinary effort he and his Korean-born wife, Yumi Hogan, made to fly 500,000 COVID-19 tests in from South Korea in April, sending them into safe hiding under armed guard because 'the federal government had recently seized 3 million N95 masks purchased by Massachusetts Gov. Charlie Baker.' This airlift from Seoul 'shouldn't have been necessary,' Hogan writes, but 'I'd watched as the president downplayed the outbreak's severity and as the White House failed to issue public warnings, draw up a 50-state strategy, or dispatch medical gear or lifesaving ventilators from the national stockpile to American hospitals. Eventually, it was clear that waiting around for the president to run the nation's response was hopeless.' Dr. Anthony Fauci and other federal health experts gave a dire, 'unfiltered,' and prescient briefing to Americans governors in early February, Hogan writes, and 'it was jarring, the huge contrast between the experts' warnings and the president's public dismissals' He detailed things Trump did and said, and more importantly, the things he did not do. 'Governors always do the hard work, make the tough decisions and take the political heat,' Hogan writes. 'But an undertaking as large as a national testing program required Washington's help. We expected something more than constant heckling from the man who was supposed to be our leader. Trump soon disabused us of that expectation.' Read the essay at The Washington Post. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES RECORD HIGH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-cases-fatalities-continue-rise-across-us-001801216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new coronavirus cases and fatalities continued to mount across the United States on Wednesday, with Texas and Oklahoma recording new highs. Johns Hopkins University, which tracks the spread of the disease, said late Wednesday that 67,632 new cases of the disease had been reported across</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida biggest one-day increase in deaths since pandemic started...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200716143306-y6l4u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida reports biggest one-day increase in COVID-19 deaths since pandemic started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Sets Record Highs In Deaths, New Cases...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/16/covid-19-deaths-new-high-texas-governor-abbott-face-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks after Republican Governor Greg Abbott ordered most of the state's 30 million residents to wear masks, Texas is still scrambling to contain one of the biggest coronavirus surges in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese executives get 'pre-test' injections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/93a7be6c6ac427e6211074ab9cfc9dbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — In the global race to make a coronavirus vaccine, a state-owned Chinese company is boasting that its employees, including top executives, received experimental shots even before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russian hackers' trying to steal research...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47797e89ddb470b3244fae3a799481c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain, the United States and Canada accused Russian hackers on Thursday of trying to steal information from researchers seeking a coronavirus vaccine, warning scientists and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN MANAGER REPLACED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44daa7d151f436b520d5f7c824142aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump shook up his campaign staff amid sinking poll numbers less than four months before the election, replacing campaign manager Brad Parscale with veteran GOP...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'PAINTED BIRD' Caused Walkouts With Pedophilia, Bestiality, Nazis. It's Extraordinary Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-painted-bird-caused-walkouts-with-its-pedophilia-bestiality-and-nazis-its-an-extraordinary-film</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Czech filmmaker Václav Marhoul discusses his controversial Holocaust-set drama, why it’s less violent than “Joker,” and how his upcoming Joseph McCarthy movie is a rebuke of Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're just overwhelmed': The view from inside hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/were-just-overwhelmed-the-view-from-inside-hospitals-as-coronavirus-surge-hits/article_a6f76d93-ad48-53c5-8501-0c23c8f89b47.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — For months, California hospitals avoided the dreaded surge in coronavirus patients that threatened to overwhelm wards and stretch thin staff and supplies. But now, with coronavirus hospitalizations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama to debut podcast on SPOTIFY...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/507623-michelle-obama-to-debut-podcast-on-spotify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Michelle Obama is debuting a podcast on Spotify later this month as part of a partnership between the firm and the Obamas' production company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Shopper Pulls Gun on Man in Dispute Over Face Covering...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4fb809ccb50fee2034bbad98c7499257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROYAL PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — An unmasked man pulled a gun on a masked shopper and threatened to kill him during an apparent confrontation over masks at a Florida Walmart store, sheriff's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russian hackers' trying to steal research...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/16/us-and-allies-say-russian-hackers-targeting-corona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian hackers are targeting organizations involved in developing a vaccine for the novel coronavirus, according to a joint advisory issued Thursday by the U.S., U.K. and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief of White House's 'Operation Warp Speed' can keep investing in pharma firms...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/Chief-of-White-House-s-Operation-Warp-Speed-15407822.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The co-director of President Donald Trump's Operation Warp Speed can maintain extensive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launches sweeping loyalty test across administration...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/15/trump-appointees-loyalty-interviews-364616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political appointees across the Trump administration are being subjected to unusual interviews to gauge their support for the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY: USA has devolved into version of her 'incredibly dysfunctional family'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Mary-Trump-says-the-U-S-has-devolved-into-a-15412603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, President Donald Trump's niece, said that watching the country's leadership devolve into "a macro version of my incredibly dysfunctional family" was one of the factors that compelled her to write her book, "Too Much and Never Enough: How My Family Created the World's Most Dangerous Man."  In an interview Wednesday with The Washington Post, Mary Trump said she blames "almost 100%" her grandfather, Fred Trump -- the family patriarch whom she describes as a "sociopath" in her 214-page memoir of sorts -- for creating the conditions that led to Trump's rise and, ultimately, what she views as his dangerous presidency.  Much like in her extended family, Mary Trump said, a similar dynamic is now playing out on the national stage, with Trump simultaneously possessing "an unerring instinct for finding people who are weaker than he is," while also being "eminently usable by people who are stronger and savvier than he is" and eager to exploit him.  Her book -- which was published Tuesday and became an instant bestseller based on advance orders alone -- so worried her family that the president's brother unsuccessfully tried to block its publication in court. Unlike the bevy of other books critical of Trump, this is the only one written by a family member with firsthand knowledge of the Trump clan, and Mary Trump, who earned a doctoral degree in psychology, uses that background to analyze her uncle and his pathologies.  Assessing the current moment, in which Trump has amplified racism and stoked the flames of white grievance and resentment, Mary Trump said that the president is "clearly racist," but that his behavior stems from a combination of upbringing and political cynicism.  "It comes easily to him and he thinks it's going to score him points with the only people who are continuing to support him," she said.  Mary...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data map shows 45% of counties seeing uncontrollable spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8529781/Data-map-shows-45-counties-seeing-epidemic-spread-COVID-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data map, compiled by spatial analytics company Esri , shows that an 'epidemic trend', or uncontrollable spread, of coronavirus cases is occurring across the Sun Belt states and Midwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: 'Big money' wants to sell stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/16/cramer-big-money-wants-to-sell-regardless-of-earnings-economic-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Let the sellers get their job done. There's some agenda here. They're obviously not caring about news," CNBC's Jim Cramer said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The true story of the heartthrob prince of Qatar and his time at USC...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/true-story-heartthrob-prince-qatar-120033827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a Qatari sheikh came to live in L.A., an entire economy sprouted to meet his wishes. "His highness doesn't like to hear no," one associate told a professor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians turn anger on each other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californians-turn-anger-other-over-130019954.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Californians have expressed anger at politicians and the governor over the pandemic. After a second shutdown, many turned their anger on other Californians for not being careful enough</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Women Attack Airline Employees With Shoes, Phones, Bottles Over Delay...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/15/spirit-airlines-attack-fort-lauderdale-internaitonal-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three women are facing battery charges after authorities say they attacked Spirit Airlines employees at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport on Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO FUN: 8 In 10 College Students Won't Attend Parties...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/07/15/poll-college-students-say-they-wont-party-fall-2020-semester-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll from College Reaction/Axios found that students are eager to return to campus and willing to not party in doing so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four more years? Trump struggles to outline second term plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d1a9a629ade8ba444da6d31b997baef5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump is adamant that he wants another four years in office. It's less clear what he would do with them. The Republican president repeatedly assailed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confederate flag again flown over NASCAR race...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nascar/2020/07/15/nascar-all-star-race-confederate-flag-banner-flies-over-bristol-track/5447733002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The banner included “SCV.org” beside the Confederate flag. The Sons of Confederate Veterans organization operates that website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims rise more than expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/16/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans who filed for unemployment benefits rose more than expected last week as the country continues to grapple with the economic impacts of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC to restrict attendance at convention amid virus surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rnc-convention-limit-attendance-coronavirus-florida-41180245-99fb-44b3-ba81-8724e541db73.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only delegates will be able to attend the convention over the first three nights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA gov bans cities, counties from mandating masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/georgia-governor-extends-coronavirus-restrictions/75SLQWLJ6FBULIGVEDMNSY5M64/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Brian Kemp on Wednesday extended Georgiaâ€™s coronavirus restrictions, largely keeping existing rules in place amid growing calls from local governments for more drastic action as illnesses spike across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closest pictures of Sun ever taken reveal mysterious 'campfires'...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/closest-images-sun-space-science-121548219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spacecraft was designed and assembled in Britain before it blasted off from Florida in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Women Attack Airline Employees With Shoes, Phones, Bottles Over Delay...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/07/15/police-3-philadelphia-women-attack-spirit-airlines-employees-with-shoes-water-bottles-at-florida-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident was caught on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU court cancels US data-sharing pact over snooping concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74960a2c6af8b96a35df5afe35f9f84b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union’s top court ruled Thursday that an agreement that allows thousands of companies — from tech giants to small financial firms — to transfer data to the United States is invalid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists call for volunteers to be infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/16/scientists-call-for-volunteers-to-be-infected-with-the-coronavirus-to-test-vaccines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 100 prominent scientists, including 15 Nobel laureates, are calling for healthy volunteers to be exposed to the coronavirus to see whether vaccines against Covid-19 actually work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Greenwich Mansions With Pools All the Rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/greenwich-mansions-with-pools-are-all-the-rage-in-pandemic-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenwich Mansions With Pools Are All the Rage in Pandemic Era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Cookie Fight Will Shape Future of Digital Advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/google-s-cookie-overhaul-could-reshape-the-digital-ad-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Googleâ€™s Cookie Fight Will Shape Future of Digital Advertising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany readies tougher lockdowns to ward off second wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-readies-tougher-lockdowns-ward-off-second-wave-111403213.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany plans to allow for tougher lockdown measures to contain local outbreaks and ward off the threat of a second coronavirus wave, according to a draft agreement between the federal and regional governments. The new rules would include a ban on travel "in and out of the affected areas"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court police vehicle set ablaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/police-cruiser-set-ablaze-outside-of-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Supreme Court car was set ablaze on Wednesday afternoon outside the high court and police have a suspect in custody, Fox News is told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Fumble Exposes Netanyahu When He Needs to Look Strong...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/virus-fumble-exposes-netanyahu-when-he-most-needs-to-look-strong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virus Fumble Exposes Netanyahu When He Most Needs to Look Strong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade of Dollar at Imminent Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/decade-dollar-imminent-risk-slide-014722088.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The slump in the dollar is threatening to bring to an imminent end its near-decade-long uptrend against major peers.Deutsche Bank’s Trade-Weighted Dollar Index -- a gauge of the currency against the U.S.’s most-important trading partners -- has fallen to test the trendline in place since</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
