<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Second defector reveals details of bioweapons program...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/16/second-china-defector-gives-biological-weapons-inf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. intelligence agencies recently increased their knowledge of China’s covert biological weapons program with the help of a defector from the People’s Liberation Army, according to people familiar with the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour market recovery stalling;  Nearly 30 million on unemployment benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN2681Y1?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits fell less than expected last week and applications for the prior period were revised up, suggesting the labour market recovery had shifted into low gear amid fading fiscal stimulus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: WE MAY NEVER KNOW ELECTION RESULTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-baselessly-states-election-result-may-never-be-accurately-determined-minutes-after-fox-friends-segment-airs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump baselessly questioned the validity of the November 3rd general election in a Thursday morning tweet that criticized what he called "unsolicited ballots," and cited the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> WHO warns Europe cases higher than March...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/rich-nations-snap-vaccine-stocks-041922669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization on Thursday warned of "alarming rates of transmission" of Covid-19 across Europe and cautioned against shortening quarantine periods as countries in the region scrambled to find ways to reduce infections without resorting to new lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODBYE, LA:  SHAPIRO MOVING MEDIA COMPANY TO NASHVILLE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/the-daily-wire-ben-shapiro-jeremy-boeing-1234577589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Wire, the conservative media company started by Ben Shapiro, Jeremy Boreing and Caleb Robinson, plans to move its headquarters from Los Angeles to Nashville. Boreing said that the move wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAIWAN TICK TOCK:  CHINA WARNS STONES BECOME TORPEDOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2020-09-17/china-threatens-us-over-taiwan-visit-stones-may-become-torpedoes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-model claims Trump forced tongue down throat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/sep/17/donald-trump-accused-of-sexual-assault-by-former-model-amy-dorris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Amy Dorris alleges Trump forced his tongue down her throat and groped her at 1997 US Open</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to tell when your iPhone is listening or watching you...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1487788/iphone-listening-ios-14-update-microphone-active/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you’ve ever panicked that an app might be listening through your iPhone’s microphone, Apple has got you covered. The latest iPhone update adds a new “warning dot” that al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly revealed USPS documents show an agency struggling to manage Trump, AMAZON and the pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/New-documents-detail-USPS-s-spring-in-crisis-15574142.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It would be months before Louis DeJoy took the reins of the nation's mail system, and the U.S. Postal Service already was mired in crisis.  Mail carriers were revolting, fearful they had few protections against the newly emerging coronavirus. The Trump administration was bearing down on its finances, sending USPS officials scrambling over what they saw as a potential illegal takeover of agency operations. And then there was a looming standoff with Amazon, which privately signaled it could take some of its lucrative delivery business elsewhere.  The tensions surfaced at an April 9 meeting, when Amazon executives "stated their concerns" about the Postal Service's economic plight amid the pandemic and questioned its "viability to them as a continued shipping partner," according to a once-secret memo circulated within the agency, which described the situation as an "inflection point." (Amazon founder Jeff Bezos owns The Washington Post.)  The wide-ranging headaches that so troubled the USPS in April ultimately foreshadowed a summer of upheaval, thrusting the once-venerated mail service into a political maelstrom months before a presidential election. Newly disclosed details of these struggles are laid bare in nearly 10,000 pages of emails, legal memos, presentations and other documents obtained by The Washington Post from American Oversight, a watchdog group that requested them under the Freedom of Information Act.  The documents, which mostly span March and April, depict an agency in distress, as its deteriorating finances collided with a public-health emergency and a looming election that would be heavily reliant on absentee ballots. During that period, the USPS occasionally relied on the legal counsel of well-connected Republicans, including Stefan C. Passantino, who once served as a top White House lawyer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family films monster alligator swimming in floodwaters outside home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_641f9412-f83c-11ea-a35f-d743591502f8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mobile, Alabama meteorologist Thomas Geboy points out, debris and possibly downed power lines aren't the only reasons residents should stay out of Hurricane Sally floodwaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election: Battleground Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/10/05/election-battleground-arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could be the tipping-point state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> WHO warns Europe cases higher than March...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-who-warns-serious-situation-22698326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia 'has enough uranium' for nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-has-enough-uranium-22698903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential reserves have been identified at three deposits in the kingdom, according to a Chinese report. One expert said it would be “well in excess” of what a few power plants would need</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE KILLERS NEW SPACE WEAPON...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-russia-have-weaponised-space-22697271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Secretary of Defense Mark Esper claimed Moscow and Beijing have "turned a once peaceful arena into a war-fighting domain" which threatens the country's air superiority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-map-new-cases-infections-united-states-6aee486c-d136-47c7-a865-052f90426316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationwide, cases were up slightly while testing was down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREZ DEBATE IN A WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/516810-the-memo-warning-signs-flash-for-trump-on-debates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upcoming debates offer President Trump his best chance to shift momentum in an election campaign he appears to be losing — but some signs don’t augur well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF ISIS 2020;  New Leadership Chain Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://cgpolicy.org/articles/exclusive-look-into-the-islamic-states-new-leadership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cgpolicy.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homicides up 52% in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/09/17/chicago-covid-shootings-homicides-surge-affecting-people-color/5804396002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's second-largest county has recorded more homicides this year than in all of 2019, the Cook County Medical Examiner’s Office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Declares Venus -- a Russian Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencetimes.com/articles/27334/20200917/venus-russian-planet.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's space chief has claimed that Venus is a 'Russian planet' after news of biosignatures were detected which could indicate that there is life on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr under fire over comparison of virus lock-in to slavery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/843dcf4c766a1684164e428752939e07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr drew sharp condemnation Thursday for comparing lockdown orders during the coronavirus pandemic to slavery. In remarks Wednesday night at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daytime TV's Dark Side: 'TMZ on TV,' 'ELLEN,' 'ROSIE' Employees Detail Abusive Work Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/daytime-tvs-dark-side-former-tmz-on-tv-ellen-and-rosie-employees-detail-abusive-work-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines selling tickets for scenic 'flights to nowhere'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/938039/airlines-are-now-selling-tickets-scenic-flights-nowhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They take off and land at the same airport, but for some jetsetters, these 'flights to nowhere' are enough. The Association of Asia Pacific Airlines says because of the coronavirus pandemic, there has been a 97.5 percent drop in international travel in the region. Taiwan's EVA Air and Japan's ANA wanted to find a way to make money and ensure their pilots could keep their licenses, so they started offering special scenic flights. Last month, an ANA plane that is typically bound for Honolulu instead flew around for 90 minutes with 'a Hawaiian experience on board,' Reuters reports. Qantas is now following in their footsteps, offering a flight that takes off from Sydney and, after flying low over the Australian Outback and the Great Barrier Reef, lands back in Sydney seven hours later. Tickets ranged in price from $575 to $2,765, and with 134 seats available, the flight sold out in 10 minutes. A spokeswoman told Reuters on Thursday it was 'probably the fastest selling flight in Qantas history. People clearly miss travel and the experience of flying. If the demand is there, we'll definitely look at doing more of these scenic flights while we all wait for borders to open.' Chen Shu Tze, an engineer from Taipei, took advantage of Tigerair Taiwan's flight to nowhere that travels over South Korea's Jeju island. For $236, she got a seat on the plane and a one-year voucher for round-trip tickets from Taiwan to South Korea, as soon as travel bans are lifted. 'The pandemic has a devastating impact on the tourism and airline industry, so I want to help boost the economy, and I miss flying,' she told Reuters. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK MOVES ARIZONA BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/516842-cook-political-report-moves-arizona-to-lean-dem-in-biden-trump-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cook Political Report shifted the presidential race in Arizona toward D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys could have 'fundamental rights' as Switzerland holds historic vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/monkeys-could-fundamental-rights-switzerland-22698723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country's top court gave the go-ahead for citizens to decide on amending their region's constitution to include "fundamental rights to life for nonhuman primates"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Topples Virgin Mary Statue Outside NYC Church In Broad Daylight...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/caught-on-video-man-topples-statue-of-virgin-mary-outside-brooklyn-church-in-broad-daylight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows a man in a hat climbing a fence outside Our Lady of Solace and clambering up a religious shrine. He grabs the statue of the Blessed Mother, knocks it over and hurls it onto the sidewalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudes wear masks in Tunik installation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nudes-wear-masks-spencer-tunick-093717454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers strip (nearly) naked, for a socially distanced art installation at Alexandra Palace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone lands in outfield at WRIGLEY FIELD, causing delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1126c1238ac4ebb536ec8b593d567f3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Umpires hastily cleared the field during a game between the Cleveland Indians and Chicago Cubs on Wednesday night when a small drone flew into Wrigley Field over the bleachers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrapped plan to ship masks. Standoff with AMAZON. Docs detail USPS in crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2020/09/17/usps-trump-coronavirus-amazon-foia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wide array of political, legal and financial headaches troubled the U.S. Postal Service in March and April, foreshadowing a summer of upheaval, nearly 10,000 pages of emails, memos and other private agency documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON launches 'invitation only' site for luxury items...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1484098/amazon-invite-only-luxury-stores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has revealed an invitation-only section of its website called Luxury Stores. The ‘luxury’ experience is currently only avaliable for select Prime members in the US. Those who fit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Mask Pastor in ICU...</title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2020/sep/16/after-balking-at-masks-pastor-and-church-staff-in-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Coeur d’Alene pastor who opened his large church in early May for in-person services that allowed and even encouraged unmasked congregants to gather has been recovering from COVID-19 at the Kootenai Health intensive care unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Zuckerberg 'Alliance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/facebook-and-mark-zuckerberg-need-trump-even-more-than-trump-needs-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Needs Trump Even More Than Trump Needs Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruised Branson Seeking $400 Million to Fund Next Business Foray...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richard-branson-joins-blank-check-230048592.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Richard Branson is on the hunt for his next big business opportunity after staving off a crisis in his empire of travel and leisure-focused companies hit hard by the coronavirus pandemic.Branson is inviting investors to buy shares of a listed shell firm, known as a special purpose acquisition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future is cyborg: Study finds support for human augmentation...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN2680KP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two thirds of people in leading Western European countries would consider augmenting the human body with technology to improve their lives, mostly to improve health, according to research commissioned by Kaspersky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evangelicals Taking on QAnon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/17/the-evangelicals-who-are-taking-on-qanon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Seth Brown, the executive editor of the Biblical Recorder, a Southern Baptist newspaper in Cary, N.C., delivered a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing mounting economic woes, Hawaii to launch pre-travel testing program...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/09/16/live-governor-discuss-states-covid-response-new-infections-slowly-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But months after first announcing the plan, key details of the testing program still have to be worked out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After early virus warning, 10 days of distraction...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/After-early-virus-warning-10-days-of-distraction-15573335.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In explaining why he repeatedly misled the American public about the early dangers posed by the novel coronavirus, President Donald Trump has argued that he did not want to engender panic - and suggested that his actions showed he took the looming pandemic seriously.  But a detailed review of the 10-day period from late January, when Trump was first warned about the scale of the threat, and early February - when he acknowledged to author Bob Woodward the extent of the danger the virus posed - reveals a president who took relatively few serious measures to ready the nation for its arrival.  Instead, enabled by top administration officials, Trump largely attempted to pretend the virus did not exist - spending much of his time distracted by impeachment and exacting vengeance on his political enemies. He also carried on as usual with showy political gatherings and crowded White House events.  The period would presage Trump's disjointed and often dismissive approach to the virus in the months to come, as the president and his aides repeatedly sought to diminish the danger of a pandemic that has now claimed nearly 200,000 American lives while leaving millions more infected or out of work. Trump and White House officials disagree, arguing that the president took definitive steps in the early days of the virus that showed his resolve and helped limit the death toll.  Joe Grogan, former head of the Domestic Policy Council, said that the analyses now, more than half a year later, are "all ex post facto about where this was going to go." Grogan said Trump was "focused on the issue but getting frustrated with others internally who were panicking about it because they were raising their voices and being hyperbolic."  "The president didn't want to panic people," Grogan said. "Taking a step back, messaging was a challenge....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As smoke continues to shroud LA County, residents worry about long-term exposure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/smoke-continues-shroud-l-county-202301478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hardware stores have seen a run on portable air purifiers as smoke from the Bobcat and El Dorado fires continues to blanket Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC Poll highlights key barriers for Trump and Biden in final weeks before election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poll-highlights-key-barriers-trump-110041315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With seven weeks to go, Biden finds resistance from swing voters who think he&amp;#39;s too liberal. Trump needs to motivate supporters uncertain about voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human footprints dating back 120,000 years found in Saudi Arabia! </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ancient-footprints-saudi-arabia-show-180200239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 120,000 years ago in what is now northern Saudi Arabia, a small band of homo sapiens stopped to drink and forage at a shallow lake that was also frequented by camels, buffalo, and elephants bigger than any species seen today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House offered tests to Big Ten to resume football...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/white-house-offered-tests-big-ten-resume-football/story?id=73062256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House offered to provide the the Big Ten with enough COVID-19 tests for play to begin, but it sourced the tests from a private company instead, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Chief Downplays Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2020-09-16/defense-secretary-esper-downplays-russias-threat-not-a-challenge-in-the-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never-before-seen pics show Epstein cavorting on private island...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1486037/pics-jeffrey-epstein-young-women-private-island/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEVER-before-seen photographs capture Jeffrey Epstein’s life on his private Caribbean island with scantily dressed young women he allegedly demanded sex from several times daily. Epstein is picture…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr issues blistering critique of his own Justice Dept... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Barr-issues-blistering-critique-of-his-own-15573598.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr delivered a scathing critique of his own Justice Department on Wednesday night, insisting on his absolute authority to overrule career staff, whom he said too often injected themselves into politics and went "headhunting" for high profile targets.  Speaking at an event hosted by Hillsdale College, a school with deep ties to conservative politics, Barr directly addressed the criticism that has been building for months inside the department toward his heavy hand in politically sensitive cases, particularly those involving associates of President Donald Trump.  "What exactly am I interfering with?" he asked. "Under the law, all prosecutorial power is invested in the attorney general."  Barr's comments were remarkable, in that the head of the Justice Department catalogued all of the ways in which he thought his agency had gone astray over the years, and in its current formulation harms the body politic. Barr has drawn considerable criticism for intervening in criminal cases in ways that help benefit the president's friends.  Barr said it was he, not career officials, who have the ultimate authority to decide how cases should be handled, and derided less-experienced, less-senior bureaucrats who current and former prosecutors have long insisted should be left to handle their cases free from interference from political appointees.  Barr said that argument, in essence, means "the will of the most junior member of the organization" would make decisions, but he insisted he would not "blindly" defer to "whatever those subordinates want to do."  "Letting the most junior members set the agenda might be a good philosophy for a Montessori preschool, but it is no way to run a federal agency," Barr said.  The attorney general, the nation's top law enforcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Police Considered Using Controversial Heat Ray Against DC Protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/09/16/913748800/military-police-leaders-weighed-deploying-heat-ray-against-d-c-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours before federal police cleared peaceful protesters near the White House on June 1, a whistleblower got an email asking to find a device that would make protesters' skin feel like it was burning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing dummies help BOEING track viruses on planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/coughing-dummies-help-boeing-and-united-track-viruses-on-planes/ar-BB196JIA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Anti-Maskers Parade Through TARGET, Shouting 'We're Not Gonna Take It'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/maga-clad-anti-maskers-parade-through-target-demanding-take-your-masks-off-and-shouting-were-not-gonna-take-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of anti-maskers, many in MAGA apparel, recently invaded a Target in Florida this week-- encouraging shoppers to remove their masks while yelling "we're not gonna take it anymore.&amp;quo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Trump expressed anti-vaccine views since 2007!</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/how-donald-trump-became-an-anti-vaccinationist-2019-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has repeatedly claimed that childhood vaccines cause autism. He likely got the idea from the former chairman and CEO of NBCUniversal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP data shows 60% of business closures due to pandemic are permanent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/16/yelp-data-shows-60percent-of-business-closures-due-to-the-coronavirus-pandemic-are-now-permanent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yelp on Wednesday released its latest Economic Impact Report, revealing business closures across the U.S. are increasing as a result of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS ON COAST...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2020-09-16-hurricane-sally-latest-news-alabama-florida-gulf-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one person died as Sally lashed the coasts of Alabama and the Florida Panhandle with wind, rain and storm surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN:  TRUMP FEARS TAX FRAUD CHARGES</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/michael-cohen-says-trump-is-afraid-hell-end-up-facing-tax-fraud-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  Trump contradicts CDC chief on when vaccine will be widely available...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-cdc-redfield-vaccine-d266121c-88f0-4b82-bd97-4a4125089f93.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I believe he was confused."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Blowtorch Attack Inside CA Tea Shop...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/09/15/man-armed-with-blowtorch-wd-40-axe-knife-sets-customers-hair-on-fire-at-berkeley-boba-tea-shop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bizarre blowtorch attack in Berkeley ended when the victims subdued the attacker, but not before he pulled out a knife and an axe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis City Council that pushed to dismantle police now irate at rising crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/16/minneapolis-city-council-that-pushed-to-dismantle-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minneapolis City Council that passed a unanimous resolution in June for a “transformative new model” of law enforcement is confused and livid over rising crime and slow response times by cops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Johnson Says U.K. Labs Can't Cope Testing Demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/johnson-says-u-k-labs-can-t-cope-with-virus-testing-demand/ar-BB196BLx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIDGE WASHES AWAY</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/georgia-news/category-2-hurricane-sally-slows-gathering-a-deluge-for-the-gulf-coast/LCIKG6LJPBHTLORUWAHQX7JPEA/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Sally: Live updating storm damage and flood reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly nearly loses home -- over 6 cents in back taxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/elderly-homeowner-nearly-loses-home-over-6-cents-in-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny debt, which homeowner Glen Kristi Goldenthal neglected to pay on her 2019 taxes, then accrued to more than $300 in interest by last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing left in bucket': Resources run thin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e7b23107d0b2369d1c6230ef4f0a6e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Silvera came off the fire lines in Northern California after a grueling 36 straight days battling wildfires and evacuating residents ahead of the flames. Before that, he and his crew had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Living' Coffin Uses Mushrooms to Compost Dead Bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/v7ga4j/this-living-coffin-uses-mushrooms-to-compost-dead-bodies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘Living Cocoon’ has already been used in one burial, at the Hague</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids at Republican Rally In Philly Pelted With Eggs In Drive-By Attack...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/09/15/police-searching-for-suspects-who-threw-raw-eggs-at-children-adults-attending-republican-rally-in-wilmington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the victims were standing by a wall when the three suspects threw eggs from a passing vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI HERALD slammed for running 'racist, anti-Semitic' insert in paper...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/miami-herald-under-fire-for-running-racist-insert-in-paper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Spanish-language version of the Miami Herald is under fire for publishing an “inflammatory, racist and anti-Semitic” insert in its paper — with editors admitting they had no i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs in hard-hit Madrid: 'Like March in slow motion'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/94f0ded19728c9f7e33748b88cdf7019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — It feels like a flashback. Pneumonia, a common acute manifestation of the COVID-19 disease, is keeping Spanish intensive care wards busy again. And it's also leaving medical workers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed expects to keep rates near zero -- through 2023...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/16/federal-reserve-zero-interest-rate-416202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The central bank shed more light on its pledge not to raise interest rates until prices begin to rise more rapidly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American military employee facing German jail after 'going on bar crawl with COVID'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8739599/American-military-employee-26-facing-jail-Germany-going-bar-crawl-COVID.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Munich public prosecutor has opened an investigation after the woman, named only as Yasmin A., left, went out partying in bars, right, in Garmisch-Partenkirchen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake used as face mask on bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-manchester-54163293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger said she thought the man was wearing a "funky mask" until she spotted it slithering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP closing printing plant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/news-corp-in-multiyear-deal-to-print-the-post-wsj-at-new-nyc-plant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp. on Wednesday announced plans to shift printing of the New York Post, the Wall Street Journal and Barron’s to a new press in New York City. Under a multiyear agreement unveiled Wedn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotels facing painful wave of permanent closures...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Hotels-permanently-closing-15569121.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large number of U.S. hotels temporarily closed their doors as bookings dried up last spring due to the coronavirus epidemic. And as fall approaches, it looks like a significant number of them might not be able to reopen as expected even if business starts to pick up to a healthy level again.  Although big banks and other lenders often allowed some flexibility for strapped hotels to make their mortgage payments during the pandemic, their patience is running low and foreclosure is looming for some major urban properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE WHITE HOUSE STAFFERS INFECTED...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/white-house-staff-members-reportedly-test-positive-for-covid-19-less-than-24-hours-after-president-donald-trump-visited-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House staff members have reportedly tested positive for COVID-19 less than 24 hours after President Donald Trump visited Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCMASTER: Terror Threat In U.S. 'Far Greater' Today Than 9/11...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/scott-pelley-hr-mcmaster-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Pelley previews the 53rd season of 60 Minutes, his interview this Sunday with former National Security Advisor H.R. McMaster and his conversation with legendary journalist Bob Woodward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: What happens if results are contested?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa1f88c9ff0681bd78b147137c09b3d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Is it possible the election will be up in the air and we won't have a president on Inauguration Day: Jan. 20, 2021? Even if the election is messy and contested in court,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney says probe 'not legitimate role of government'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1de4ee7909548a132796767779ee56d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Utah Sen. Mitt Romney is sharply criticizing a Republican investigation into Democrat Joe Biden’s son, saying it's “not the legitimate role of government” to try and damage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posts Video of Himself Urinating on a Grammy Award Placed in Toilet... </title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/09/16/showstopper-kanye-posts-video-of-himself-urinating-on-a-grammy-award-placed-in-toilet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has posted a video to Twitter in which he’s urinating on a Grammy Award placed in a toilet. It’s him, he’s wearing his ugly sneakers. Kanye has 21 Grammy Awards from 69…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS SPOKESMAN TAKES LEAVE AFTER MENTAL BREAKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/top-hhs-official-takes-leave-absence-after-facebook-rant-cdc-n1240051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came days after top HHS spokesman Michael Caputo warned of a CDC plot against the president and urged Trump supporters to "buy ammunition."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTFACEBOOK launch augmented reality reporting project...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/new-york-times-facebook-augmented-reality-0973fa9e-ffcc-4a68-91ec-ffb77d757745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the first time that The Times has experimented with AR technology at scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director says masks might be better than vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/nation-world/us-outlines-sweeping-plan-to-provide-free-covid-19-vaccines/FFIOZFPD6BFM5P47GRLDG56HQI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC Director Robert Redfield has told a Senate committee that face masks may offer more individual protection against COVID-19 than a potential coronavirus vaccine, according to reporter Max Burns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of NYC's top earners consider fleeing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/nearly-half-of-nycs-top-earners-considered-relocating-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of New York City residents earning six figures or more have considered fleeing the Big Apple during the coronavirus crisis over cost-of-living concerns, according to a new poll. Researc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC's Trump Town Hall Loses to 'AMERICA'S GOT TALENT' in Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/abc-trump-town-hall-draws-152953550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Stephanopoulos welcomed Donald Trump Tuesday to an ABC News town hall, when ABC welcomed in 3.8 million viewers. NBC’s “America’s Got Talent” roughed up the town hall’s audience in their shared 9 p.m. hour. NBC and CBS tied for first in ratings, both with a 0.6 rating/4 share in the advertiser-coveted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals Decapitate historic statue of Jesus in El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1482244/vandals-decapitated-statue-jesus-church-altar-elpaso/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING pictures show how vandals DECAPITATED a historic statue of Jesus on a church altar in Texas. The Diocese of El Paso shared pictures of the Sacred Heart of Jesus – a 90-year-old statue – th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD SECRETS:  Chateau Marmont Staff Allege Racial Discrimination, Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/rot-at-hollywoods-playground-chateau-marmont-staff-allege-racial-discrimination-sexual-misconduct-and-neglectful-management</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Public Schools Spend $30K Per Student; 23% of 8th Graders Proficient in Reading...  </title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/dc-public-schools-spend-30k-student-only-23-8th-graders-proficient  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cartel Gunmen Burn Rival's Face Off as He Begs for Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/09/16/graphic-exclusive-cartel-gunmen-burn-rivals-face-off-in-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunmen from a narco-terrorist cartel burned off the face of a rival and recorded the man’s agony as he begged for death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye asks campaign staff to avoid 'fornicating'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/516658-kanye-west-reportedly-asked-campaign-staff-to-avoid-fornicating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West reportedly requested that staffers working on his long-shot presidential bid abstain from sex outside marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Tunnel Under Vegas for Self-Driving Cars Almost Complete...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/09/elon-musk-boring-company-tunnel-las-vegas-near-completion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Tunnels under cities with self-driving electric cars will feel like warp drive,” Musk tweeted on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  President Stuck at 42% Job Approval...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/320303/trump-stuck-42-job-approval.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating is proving rock steady this summer, but at a level that's not promising for reelection.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
