<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GRAMMYS Open with Emotional Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/grammy-awards-honor-kobe-bryant-1202842292/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just hours after Kobe Bryant was killed in a helicopter crash in Southern California, the Grammy Awards quickly put together a tribute honoring the late NBA legend. Moments after Lizzo opened this …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC uses clip of LeBron James...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/313638/bungling-bbc-shows-clip-of-lebron-james-instead-of-kobe-bryant-on-ten-oclock-news-report-of-his-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUNGLING BBC news bosses reported on basketball superstar Kobe Bryant’s tragic death – by using footage of LeBron James by mistake. The News At 10’s top story was about Bryant’s fatal h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Takeaways from his manuscript... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/5-takeaways-on-trump-and-ukraine-from-john-bolton-s-book/ar-BBZlMQD?li=BBnba9I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAMMYS Open with Emotional Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-2020-grammys-mourned-kobe-bryant-1273006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The basketball great's shocking death was felt at the music awards show on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Unfortunately Stuttered'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/kobe-bryant-dead-msnbc-n-word-alison-morris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a report on the death of Kobe Bryant, an MSNBC uttered something that sounded like the N-word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Trump's spiritual adviser calls for 'all satanic pregnancies to miscarry,' she says it was metaphor...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/After-Trump-s-spiritual-adviser-calls-for-all-15005707.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida pastor and longtime spiritual adviser to President Donald Trump says she was speaking in metaphor when she recently prayed in a sermon for all "satanic pregnancies" to end in miscarriage.  In video of the Jan. 5 sermon, posted by the liberal advocacy group Right Wing Watch, televangelist pastor Paula White breathlessly calls on Jesus Christ to "command all satanic pregnancies to miscarry right now."  "We declare that anything that's been conceived in satanic wombs, that it will miscarry, it will not be able to carry forth any plan of destruction, any plan of harm," White said before an auditorium of congregants.  As of Sunday morning, the clip, which was just under two minutes long, had been viewed more than 2.5 million times.  White's words are largely being interpreted literally - that she wishes for evil women to have miscarriages - but she shared a rare response to the criticism in which she explained that she was speaking in metaphor, praying for evil plans to be foiled in her congregants' lives.  "I don't normally respond but clearly this has been taken out of context," White tweeted Sunday. "I was praying (Ephesians) 6:12 that we wrestle not against flesh and blood. Anything that has been conceived by demonic plans, for it to be cancelled and not prevail in your life ..."  Ephesians 6:12, according to the King James Bible translation, reads: "For we wrestle not against flesh and blood, but against principalities, against powers, against the rulers of the darkness of this world, against spiritual wickedness in high places."  After watching the clip, André Gagné, a theological studies professor at Concordia University and expert on the Christian right, said White was probably speaking in metaphor when she called for the miscarriages. He pointed to a book by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Takes On German Ecology Critics of TESLA Plant Near Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/musk-takes-on-german-ecology-critics-of-tesla-plant-near-berlin/ar-BBZlC08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITNESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/sixers/kobe-bryant-helicopter-crash-eyewitness-20200126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive boom was heard in Calabasas, Calif., followed by a few seconds of silence. Then a fireball erupted on a hillside off Las Virgenes Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer Rocks Pro-Trump Gown at GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/joy-villa-shocks-pro-trump-impeached-elected-gown-at-2020-grammys-1272938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the singer’s third pro-Trump fashion statement at the music awards show; she notified the White House that she would wear “something to be supportive.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans Flock To STAPLES Center For Memorial Despite GRAMMYS Barricade...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/kobe-bryants-fans-gather-around-staples-center-to-honor-late-nba-star-140291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles arena has been closed off due to Sunday evening's GRAMMY Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 KILLED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98f3978b392cbd3d9143529267b1f1ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALABASAS, Calif. (AP) — NBA legend Kobe Bryant, his 13-year-old daughter and seven others were killed in a helicopter crash on a remote, steep hillside in Southern California on Sunday, his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Makes Worst Broadcasting Blooper... </title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-while-reporting-kobe-bryant-death-msnbc-anchor-somehow-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some markets, a 15 second delay prevented the word from being broadcast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/2020/01/23/kobe-bryant-life-after-nba-oscars/4521103002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobe Bryant talked to USA TODAY Sports about life after the NBA, projects with his award-winning multimedia company and coaching his daughter's team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOBE DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/01/26/kobe-bryant-killed-dead-helicopter-crash-in-calabasas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobe Bryant has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASKETBALL LEGEND IN HELICOPTER CRASH ...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-26/aircraft-slams-into-hillside-explodes-in-flames-near-calabasas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobe Bryant, Lakers legend, died when the helicopter he was traveling in crashed into a hillside in Calabasas shortly before 10 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, Sports, Weather, Traffic and the Best of LA/OC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clive Davis Showcase Sparkles...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/26/clive-daviss-annual-star-studded-pre-grammy-dinner-tops-itself-with-jay-z-beyonce-nancy-pelosi-in-audience-beck-cyndi-lauper-chance-the-rapper-on-stage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Grammys are in disarray, the Recording Academy is dealing with scandal, but Clive Davis’s famous annual all star pre-Grammy gala went on last night as if there were  no problems in the wo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE IN ORANGE COUNTY</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/25/case-of-coronavirus-confirmed-in-orange-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patient was hospitalized in isolation and was in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY:   'It's very likely I'll be in favor of witnesses'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/479933-romney-its-very-likely-ill-be-in-favor-of-witnesses-in-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Sen. Mitt Romney (R) said Saturday that it is “very likely” he will be in favor of calling witnesses in the Senate impeachment trial against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOBODY CAN LEAVE'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nobody-leave-trapped-wuhan-residents-stock-094555250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police at a roadblock on the outskirts of Wuhan turned away cars trying to leave the virus-stricken city on Saturday, as other anxious residents trapped inside spent the Lunar New Year stocking up on masks and medical supplies or in long hospital queues. Authorities have prevented anyone from leaving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks Head Into Darkest Phase of the Nordic Negative-Rates...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/banks-head-darkest-phase-nordic-050000832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Apple Podcast, Spotify or Pocket Cast.If you want to know what long-term negative interest rates are doing to banks, watch Denmark in the coming months.Danes have lived with subzero rates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY FLU YEAR!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e3165077bc60bd14f2c2d031c2e6272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A new viral illness being watched with a wary eye around the globe accelerated its spread in China on Sunday with 56 deaths so far, while the U.S. Consulate in the city at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNION LEADER goes Klobuchar...</title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/opinion/editorials/union-leader-primary-endorsement-amy-klobuchar-can-win/article_8df3186b-b37f-582a-a676-1307e63dc98c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are a New Hampshire voter who thinks Donald Trump is doing a good job, you can probably sleep in on primary day, Feb. 11. Try as they might,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victim writhes around and shakes uncontrollably...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-victim-writes-around-shakes-21362578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The disturbing clip shows a woman holding the head of the patient while they appear to be having a fit under a blanket in China as the death toll creeps up to 56</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Down Big to 2020 Rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-friends-covers-fox-news-poll-completely-ignores-part-showing-trump-down-big-to-2020-rivals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A just-released Fox News poll offered some dire numbers for President Donald Trump. But if the commander-in-chief was watching Fox &amp; Friends on Sunday morning (and he was, for at least part of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diddy Slams Recording Academy: Black Music Has Never Been Respected...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/diddy-combs-slams-grammys-recording-academy-black-music-1203480681/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean “Diddy” Combs slammed the Recording Academy before a star-studded crowd at the annual Clive Davis Pre-Grammy Gala on Saturday night, saying that hip-hop and black music have “never been respec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNT:   Troubles won't end with Senate acquittal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/479942-trumps-troubles-wont-end-with-a-senate-acquittal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be more House inquiries into new revelations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders bolsters frontrunner status...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479833-sanders-bolsters-frontrunner-status-a-week-before-iowa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One week before the Iowa caucuses, Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is growing in strength and increasingly looks like the favorite to win the Democratic nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  50% WANT CONVICTION AND REMOVAL...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/479973-fox-news-poll-half-of-americans-say-trump-should-be-convicted-and</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of Americans say the Senate should vote to convict and remove President Trump from office, according to a new Fox News poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un's Aunt Appears in Public for First Time in 6 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-uns-aunt-appears-in-public-for-first-time-in-six-years/ar-BBZkyWf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry and Meghan's Big Funding Source Is Private. Sort of...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/harry-and-meghans-big-funding-source-is-private-sort-of/ar-BBZkYRQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos throws lavish party at new DC mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7931191/Jeff-Bezos-throws-lavish-party-new-Washington-DC-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos threw a lavish party at his finally completed Washington DC mansion attended by Ivanka Trump and Jared Kushner, Microsoft founder Bill Gates and actor Ben Stiller Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HILLARY' lands in Sundance, and 2020 election, like hand grenade...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/26/hillary-the-docu-series-lands-on-sundance-and-2020-primary-like-a-hand-grenade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARK CITY, Utah — Hillary Clinton threw a hand-grenade at the 2020 Democratic presidential primary election Saturday with her new documentary, “Hillary.” The one-sided, four-part Hulu series about …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu hopes to 'make history' at talks on Trump peace plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-hopes-history-talks-trump-peace-plan-100817882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu voiced hope Sunday that he can "make history" in Washington this week during talks on US President Donald Trump's peace plan for the Middle East. Netanyahu has been invited to meet Trump at the White House on Monday and Tuesday to discuss the project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diddy rips in fiery speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/26/sean-diddy-combs-rips-grammys-clive-davis-gala-spe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean “Diddy” Combs called out the Grammy Awards for dissing rap and R&amp;B stars in its major categories in a blazing speech that earned him a standing ovation from Beyonce, Jay-Z and several other music industry players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders tops field in New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/poll-sanders-buttigieg-top-democratic-field-new-hampshire-n1122366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four top Democrats all lead President Trump for the general election in the Granite State according to a new NBC News/Marist survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How California's homelessness surged...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/no-one-catch-us-how-california-s-homelessness-crisis-exploded-n1123156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is decades and decades of failures,” experts say of the persistent homelessness crisis that continues to plague California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities Prepare for Food Stamp Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cities-prepare-for-the-worst-as-trumps-food-stamp-cuts-near/ar-BBZkkDh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can spread before symptoms show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-hnk-intl-01-26-20/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg to focus on converting Trump voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/26/politics/buttigieg-iowa-last-week-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg will close out his campaign in Iowa focusing on his ability to win over disaffected Republicans who backed President Donald Trump in 2016, his campaign tells CNN, hoping that Democrats who are hellbent on defeating Trump in November will be wooed by a candidate who can eat into the President's support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermont weighs emoji license plates...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/26/vermont-weighs-emoji-license-plates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill in Vermont would take vanity license plates into new territory with the introduction of emojis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy associate has more recordings of president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/25/politics/recording-trump-lev-parnas-igor-fruman-ukraine-ambassador/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nearly 90-minute recording released Saturday of President Donald Trump at a 2018 donor dinner that included indicted businessmen he has claimed he doesn't know features Trump speaking animatedly about removing the US ambassador to Ukraine -- at one point stating, "Get rid of her!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Super Sniffer Dogs Help Detect Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2020/01/25/799404129/how-super-sniffer-dogs-are-helping-detect-disease-around-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our canine buddies can do more than play fetch. Turns out dogs' incredible sense of smell is a secret weapon in medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transmission ability getting stronger...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200126105121-12mxo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 5, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 5-China scrambles to contain 'strengthening' virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris cancels Lunar New Year parade...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200126094846-oyltd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/FRANCE-PARADE:Paris cancels Lunar New Year parade over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren wins prized DES MOINES REGISTER endorsement...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/25/warren-wins-prized-des-moines-register-endorsement-104643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the most coveted media endorsement in the first-in-the-nation state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuses Dems of plot to subvert election...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-team-opening-defense-accuses-democrats-of-plot-to-subvert-election/ar-BBZkgbt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General: USA committed to Syria fight; Missions up against ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/326607078ac93c00b86b8e924a23da95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREEN VILLAGE MILITARY OUTPOST (AP) — U.S. troops at military outposts ín eastern Syria asked variations of the same question to their top commander Saturday: What is our future here? What are the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
