<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2020/09/05/fox-news-journalists-defend-colleague-targeted-by-president-trump/#263dcfdf2a84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My sources are not anonymous to me and I doubt they are anonymous to the president.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNAL CONFUSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/05/media/the-atlantic-trump-military-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Fox News has worked to undermine and discredit the work of other news organizations that have reported damning details about President Trump and his administration. But on Friday, something unusual happened: The network turned a skeptical eye toward reporting from its own correspondent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirby, LaBeouf Grieve Over Loss of Newborn in 'PIECES OF A WOMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/pieces-of-a-woman-film-review-venice-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: He has yet to find magic potion to get ahead in race...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-has-yet-to-find-magic-potion-to-get-ahead-15545477.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential election is now eight weeks away, and the structure of the contest is little changed from where it has been for some time. President Donald Trump is struggling and at times floundering. The question is whether he has the skills to turn around his candidacy in hopes of replicating his 2016 surprise victory.  At the traditional Labor Day kickoff to the fall campaign, the race remains former vice president Joe Biden's to lose - which of course could still happen. Trump has tried many things over the past months in an effort to avoid becoming a one-term president. So far, nothing has proved to be the magic potion the president seems to believe is out there.  Trump has claimed Biden is mentally challenged. He has gone after Biden's son Hunter as corrupt. The president has accused Biden of being a radical leftist, a socialist. He says the former vice president is weak. He says his challenger is soft on China. He has said Biden supports violent protesters and doesn't support the police. Oh, he's also said Biden's 1994 crime bill was too tough on crime (and by implication, therefore, on the side of the police).  He is now preaching law and order, seizing on months of nightly protests in Portland, Ore., which often have turned violent, along with the protests and violence that followed the police shooting of Jacob Blake in Kenosha, Wis. He claims the nation's cities are ablaze and that a Biden presidency would destroy the suburbs. The rhetoric aimed at suburban voters is grounded in racism.  It is premature to say the law and order message isn't working, though there's been minimal movement in the polls since the conventions ended. What is left in the Trump tool kit if this message fails to do what Trump hopes it will do?  Trump's mistakes, record and history plague his candidacy. He paints his record in glorious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer culture skewered in film at Venice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d7ab5511afd1787133056db3ff6a36b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE (AP) — Coronavirus lockdowns have kept most U.S. filmmakers and actors away from the Venice Film Festival, but Gia Coppola and Maya Hawke have brought a bit of today’s America to the Lido...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions threaten work stoppages amid calls for racial justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02da00cb921ec61a69d8a30c9ff56244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ahead of Labor Day, unions representing millions across several working-class sectors are threatening to authorize work stoppages in support of the Black Lives Matter movement amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-news-reporters-leap-to-defend-jennifer-griffin-from-trumps-demand-she-be-fired-for-reporting-he-trashed-vets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News reporters leapt to the defense of their colleague Jennifer Griffin after President Donald Trump demanded her firing after she confirmed the key elements of a raft of stories in which Trump denigrated military veterans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERBY DAY SHOWDOWN: Militia gather at Churchill Downs ahead of protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8701095/Armed-Trump-supporters-gather-near-Churchill-Downs-ahead-Kentucky-Derby-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavily armed pro-Trump activists and far-right militia members have gathered near Churchill Downs in Louisville vowing to protect the city ahead of a day of Black Lives Matter protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting in person Nov. 3? Expect drive-thrus, sports arenas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f347fec097280234fdef8589def9a44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Voting will look a little different this November. States are turning to stadiums, drive-thrus and possibly even movie theaters as safe options for in-person polling places...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Already Itching to Sue Frats Over Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/college-students-are-already-itching-to-sue-frats-over-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fraternities and sororities are undoubtedly engaging in risky behavior during the pandemic. But can they be sued for it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Braces For EMP Attack?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/dhs-braces-potential-emp-attack-presidential-election-nears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Orthodox Jews clash with secular Israeli officials over measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Ultra-Orthodox-Jews-clash-with-secular-Israeli-15545201.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - Israel's rapidly escalating coronavirus crisis is aggravating a religious divide in the Jewish state, with ultra-Orthodox leaders accusing mostly secular health officials of discrimination and fostering anti-Semitism by focusing on outbreaks in highly observant communities.  As the government struggles to contain the outbreak, ultra-Orthodox Jewish rabbis, cabinet ministers and parliament members have resisted attempts to curtail activities in ultra-Orthodox areas, including many that have emerged as covid-19 hot spots.  Facing particular ire has been Ronni Gamzu, the pugnacious former hospital administrator appointed last month as the government's "corona czar." Gamzu has clashed with religious leaders over his efforts to impose targeted lockdowns on neighborhoods with high infection rates, block a yearly pilgrimage to the grave of a revered Hasidic rabbi in Ukraine and compel virus testing for thousands of foreign students who have recently arrived to attend religious schools, or yeshivas.  Gamzu said last week that 80% of the most recent coronavirus cases occurred in ultra-Orthodox neighborhoods. The government expects to enact targeted restrictions Monday in 10 hot spot communities, many of them ultra-Orthodox.  The tensions have riven Israel's coronavirus cabinet, the government body that sets policy. On Friday, one day after Israel recorded 3,141 new cases - the largest single day per capita increase in any country since the pandemic began - cabinet discussions grew heated over proposed lockdowns during the Jewish holidays of Rosh Hashanah and Yom Kippur later this month.  "You want a lockdown during the High Holidays because you don't want people praying," Housing Minister Yaakov Litzman said to Gamzu, according to Israeli media reports. "We will not let this happen."  Gamzu says that his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overfed and underexercised, dogs putting on pandemic pounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Overfed-and-underexercised-some-dogs-are-putting-15545194.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When shutdowns to stem the spread of the novel coronavirus began last spring, Massachusetts retiree Lisa Allen took her state's stay-at-home guidance seriously. She holed up in her high-rise Boston condo with her 6-year-old Pomeranian, Desi.  She reduced walks from three to two a day - the better to avoid the elevator and lobby. She bought pee pads for Desi and gave him a treat when he used them.  By late June, Desi was having trouble breathing. A routine visit to the veterinarian revealed that the tiny dog had gained a pound.  "If I only gained a pound, I'd be very happy," Allen said. "But when you're 5 pounds, that's 20% of your weight. It was putting strain on him."  The problem, the vet said, was one familiar to millions of Americans and a growing number of their pet dogs: a routine upended by covid-19. In many cases, housebound humans are giving their dogs more attention and walks, boosting fitness for pets and people alike. But in others, veterinarians and professional dog walkers say, the changes have led to overfed and either underexercised or overwalked dogs - and to new joint problems and obesity.  Banfield Pet Hospital, which has more than 1,000 locations across the United States, surveyed pet owners at the end of May about how they were faring during the pandemic. Many reported pudgier pets.  "It's too soon to tell if the covid crisis has resulted in weight gain for the average pet," said Andrea Sanchez, a Banfield veterinarian and senior manager of operations support. But of 1,000 respondents, she said, "33% said they thought their pet had gained weight - and it was especially dog owners."  Tomika Bruen, who owns a dog-walking company in the Los Angeles area, said that when her clients began calling her back recently to take their dogs out, she detected not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside El Salvador's hell hole jails; Packed into overcrowded cells...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8700681/Gangsters-Guatemala-make-crew-signs-handcuffs-shaken-prison-guards.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities visited three Salvadorean prisons, some of them maximum security, to check on the inmates and to carry out searches amid the COVID-19 novel coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOKHARI: Everything You Post Online Will Be Scanned by 'Hate Speech Algorithms'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2020/09/05/bokhari-everything-you-post-online-will-be-scanned-by-hate-speech-algorithms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breitbart News technology reporter Allum Bokhari appeared on the Liz Callaway show on TALK 94.5 FM WTKN last week, to discuss revelations in his upcoming book, #DELETED: Big Tech's Battle to Erase The Trump Movement and Steal The Election, which features interviews with insiders from Google, Facebook, and other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Notion That US Debt Can Ever Be Paid Back is Ridiculous', Analyst Says...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/analysis/202009051080375191-the-notion-that-us-debt-can-ever-be-paid-back-is-ridiculous-analyst-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June, US Department of the Treasury data revealed that America's national debt had exceeded $26 trillion for the first time in the nation's history, as the country...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rochester rocked by another night of protests, counter-protests...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/05/rochester-rocked-by-another-night-of-daniel-prude-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence erupted on the third night of protests in Rochester against the death of Daniel Prude, with anti-police demonstrators terrorizing diners inside a restaurant and setting off what looked lik…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rush to rent 'winter houses' ahead of second wave...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/04/new-yorkers-scramble-to-rent-posh-winter-houses-ahead-of-second-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months before a possible second wave of the coronavirus, deep-pocketed locals are already looking for an escape route.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese pianist Lang Lang says Bach the remedy for troubled times...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinese-pianist-lang-lang-says-023017080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In times of crisis star Chinese pianist Lang Lang believes music is the best medicine, especially Bach, who he says penned the perfect soundtrack for these pandemic-troubled times more than 250 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENGINEERS TEST JETLINER WHERE YOU RIDE IN WINGS...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/test-jetliner-ride-wings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the first flight test for a model Flying-V, which has its seats and cargo inside its wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Number of Catholic Schools Shutting Down Forever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/05/a-growing-number-of-catholic-schools-are-shutting-down-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In more than four decades of coaching girls’ basketball at Lebanon Catholic High School in southeastern Pennsylvania, Patti Hower had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's loneliest elephant' okayed to quit zoo for new life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f09d3de7b5aad108678ec2e5f0d6bc55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — An elephant who has become a cause celebre for animal rights activists around the world will be allowed to leave his Pakistani zoo and transferred to better conditions, the animal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Hold Secret Edge If Too Close to Call...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-hold-secret-edge-if-election-is-too-close-to-call/ar-BB18JOdH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELANIA:  This is not journalism!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8699957/Melania-Trump-joins-fights-against-claims-Donald-Trump-called-WWI-Marine-heroes-losers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania Trump has joined the furious pushback following the release of an Atlantic article that reported Trump called deceased veterans 'losers' - as Fox News confirms the Atlantic's reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sentenced to 30 years for taking, sharing nude photos of 1-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article245498850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No denial from Mattis...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-allegations-leave-military-leaders-off-15544501.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior and former military leaders appeared to struggle Friday with how to respond to a report that President Donald Trump disparaged U.S. service members killed in combat as "losers," as the president attacked the allegations as "fake news."  The article elicited an array of reactions amid Trump's history with the military, which includes mocking Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., for being captured in Vietnam, belittling the parents of an Army officer killed in Iraq, and dismissing brain injuries suffered by U.S. troops in an Iranian ballistic missile strike as "headaches."  The report in the Atlantic, published late Thursday, focused in part on a presidential visit to Arlington National Cemetery on Memorial Day in 2017 and a canceled visit to the Aisne-Marne American Cemetery outside Paris in 2018.  In the first example, according to the magazine, Trump allegedly said, "I don't get it. What was in it for them?" while standing with retired Marine Gen. John Kelly at the grave of Kelly's son, Robert, who was killed in Afghanistan. At the time, Kelly was homeland security secretary.  In the second, the Trump administration canceled the visit to the cemetery in France in bad weather when helicopter travel was questionable and Trump seemingly dismissed the World War I veterans who are buried there.  "Why should I go to that cemetery?" Trump said, according to the report. "It's filled with losers."  The president vehemently denied the report, attacking the Atlantic as a "third-rate magazine" and criticizing Kelly for not doing a good job as his former chief of staff.  "This man was totally exhausted. He wasn't even able to function in the last number of months," Trump said. He added that he did not know whether Kelly served as a source for the Atlantic's story, "but it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland on edge after suspect in weekend killing is fatally shot by police... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Suspect-in-Portland-slaying-is-killed-during-15542831.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. - Eyewitnesses and video footage gave police investigators murky accounts of the fatal shooting of a far-right activist here a week ago, according to newly unsealed court documents that shed new light on the politically charged incident but offer little in the way of definitive answers.  Investigators interviewed at least five people who saw some portion of the shooting of 39-year-old Aaron "Jay" Danielson and reviewed video footage, according to an arrest affidavit unsealed Friday, but their accounts stopped far short of providing a cohesive narrative.  Police said they ultimately came to believe Danielson was shot by a far-left activist, 48-year-old Michael Forest Reinoehl. But Reinoehl claimed publicly that he acted to defend himself and others, while a man who was with Danielson said his friend was targeted for a hat he wore bearing the insignia of the far-right Patriot Prayer group.  Reinoehl was shot and killed by law enforcement officers as they tried to arrest him Thursday.  The affidavit is likely to do little to cool the tension gripping Portland. Dueling demonstrators are expected in the region in the coming days, as a racial justice protest is set for Saturday and a pro-Trump event honoring Danielson is planned on Monday.  Oregon Democratic Gov. Kate Brown said at a press briefing Friday that she remained concerned about more violence and urged calm.  "There needs to be a community-wide effort to stop the violence," she said. "Because the violence must stop. Period."  Portland has seen more than three months of consecutive protests against police brutality, some of them descending into destruction and mayhem. But the tension intensified a week ago when a caravan of Trump supporters drove through the city in trucks, sparking skirmishes with those...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One man's battle shows why covid and obesity are such toxic mix... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/one-man-s-battle-shows-why-covid-19-and-obesity-are-a-toxic-mix/ar-BB18IMXH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Fallout After President Reportedly Insulted Dead Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-faces-election-fallout-after-reportedly-insulting-dead-troops/ar-BB18IwSU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen: Trump Would Do Anything to Win, Even 'Starting a War'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-cohen-trump-would-do-anything-to-win-even-going-so-far-as-to-start-a-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump lawyer Michael Cohen sat down with NBC News' Lester Holt for an interview ahead of the release of his book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop receives life-saving transplant  -- from woman he jailed...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/she-saved-my-life-police-officer-receives-life-saving-transplant-from-woman-he-put-in-jail-8-years-ago</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jocelynn James, a recovered drug addict and former member of “Franklin’s Most Wanted,” saved the life of the police officer who put her in jail nearly a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman suffers severe burns after hand sanitizer on skin catches fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/round-rock-mother-suffers-severe-burns-after-hand-sanitizer-starts-house-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her home has dozens of hand sanitizers and cleaning products because one of her daughters has a compromised immune system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom says SOUTHWEST AIRLINES kept serving alcohol to drunken man who groped her daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/airlines/2020/09/04/texas-mom-says-southwest-airlines-kept-serving-alcohol-to-a-drunk-man-who-groped-her-teen-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas mother is suing Southwest Airlines after she said her teen daughter was sexually assaulted by an intoxicated passenger who was sold three beers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorothy Parker's ashes exhumed from longtime Baltimore resting place. But moved where?</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-dorothy-parker-ashes-exhumed-20200904-u5t6rvfzjjf2fc4qgbniqcbma4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 30 years in her Baltimore resting place, the ashes of famed Jazz Age writer Dorothy Parker are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION KICKOFF: VOTING BEGINS!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-vote-mail-begins-white-205036956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US election is officially open: North Carolina on Friday launched vote-by-mail operations for the November 3 contest between President Donald Trump and Democrat Joe Biden, which is getting uglier by the hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team pushes social media limits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-team-pushes-social-media-011145049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A message saying you &amp;quot;won&amp;#39;t be safe&amp;quot; in Joe Biden&amp;#39;s America. The former vice president shown &amp;quot;sleeping&amp;quot; during a television interview. Biden &amp;quot;hiding&amp;quot; -- alone -- in his basement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Tehran months away from nuke weapon...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-caught-stockpiling-enriched-uranium-needed-for-bomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has evidence that Iran is stockpiling enriched uranium, the key component in a nuclear weapon, in direct violation of international restrictions on Tehran’s use of the fissile material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat of power outages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-blackout-risk-rising-record-213737225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Another round of record-breaking heat hangs over California just weeks after searing temperatures pushed its electric grid to the brink, temporarily knocking out power to millions.Temperatures are forecast to top 100 degrees Fahrenheit (38 Celsius) across the state and reach as high as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing launches secret spacecraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/4/china-launches-reusable-robotic-spacecraft-mimics-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Friday launched a reusable spacecraft that appears to be Beijing’s answer to the secretive U.S. X-37 space plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  DUTY, HONOR, COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-camp-seizes-on-trumps-reported-military-scorn-says-we-understand-trumps-soul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Service members “have asked us if the president is simply waiting for them to die,” Rep. Conor Lamb, a former Marine and a Biden ally, said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Americans Who Died in War 'Losers', 'Suckers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/09/trump-americans-who-died-at-war-are-losers-and-suckers/615997/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has repeatedly disparaged the intelligence of service members, and asked that wounded veterans be kept out of military parades, multiple sources tell The Atlantic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS CONFIRMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/09/04/shocker-fox-newss-jennifer-griffin-confirms-atlantic-magazine-story-about-trump-disdain-for-military-and-mccain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News National Correspondent Jennifer Griffin says she has confirmed with two sources the gist of the Atlantic magazine story about Donald Trump’s disdain of the military and John McCain. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political party biggest factor in whether state has mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/newslocalpolitics/governors-political-party-is-biggest-factor-in-whether-a-state-has-imposed-mask-mandate-study-finds/ar-BB18GK82?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIA Soldiers Deserved Their Fate?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/washington-post-adds-new-reporting-trump-believes-vietnam-veterans-are-losers-and-mia-soldiers-deserved-their-fate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post confirmed and added to the Atlantic's reporting that President Donald Trump denigrated U.S. soldiers killed or captured in war, citing unnamed sources that included a "former senior administration official."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS KELLY SOURCE?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-john-kelly-troops-atlantic-chief-staff-white-house-a9706321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan downs Chinese fighter jet?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1331289/China-plane-crash-Taiwan-shoot-fighter-jet-world-war-3-missile-defence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN has been forced to publicly reject claims it shot down a Chinese military jet, after speculation spiralled out of control on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG'S CLAIMS ROIL DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edf5d17c4d41cfb69117f0cf97ef6ac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump defended himself Friday against accusations that he mocked American war dead as his Democratic rival, Joe Biden, intensified efforts to frame the election...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling versions of reality define fall campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/780b2edfd25af18c0107ee382356194f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — On the campaign trail with President Donald Trump, the pandemic is largely over, the economy is roaring back, and murderous mobs are infiltrating America's suburbs. With...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal border crossings surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/4/illegal-border-crossings-surge-coronavirus-fades-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents nabbed nearly 50,000 illegal immigrants along the southern border in August, marking the worst month in a year as the clampdown that had accompanied the coronavirus pandemic begins to fade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Dismisses 11 Students Who Gathered in Same Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/world/us/2020/09/04/northeastern-dismisses-11-students-who-gathered-in-same-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON - Northeastern University said Friday it has dismissed 11 freshman students for the fall semester for violating campus social distancing guidel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  Recovery To Take Long Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/09/04/909627932/feds-jerome-powell-jobless-rate-better-than-expected-recovery-to-take-a-long-tim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with NPR, Powell says it may take years before the economy has fully recovered. He says practicing social distancing and wearing masks is essential for the economy to rebound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's brother made $8 million selling TESLA shares -- days before buying them...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-brother-kimbal-made-more-than-8-million-selling-tesla-stock-2-days-before-he-bought-them-2020-09-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s younger brother, Kimbal, appears to have made more than $8 million on Tesla’s stock this week, as he exercised options to buy the stock, two days...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prof pretending to be black 'only confessed when black colleagues exposed her'
...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1422051/jessica-krug-george-washington-university-black-professor-exposed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PROFESSOR of African history who pretended to be black has only confessed because “black colleagues exposed her fake background.” Jessica A Krug – a 38-year-old white professor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mad dash -- for Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2020/09/03/texas-president-trump-bus-tour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's reelection campaign launched a bus tour of the state Thursday, though surrogates said — strenuously — that they still don't see Texas in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel crisis hits new milestone...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hotel-crisis-coronavirus-economy-travel-556b1f8d-9a12-4555-8a94-a790d78f9bd3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic-era travel drought has continued through major holiday weekends.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
