<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CARL BERNSTEIN:  White House chatter about throwing 2020 election to House...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/carl-bernstein-reports-white-house-chatter-about-throwing-2020-election-to-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran investigative journalist Carl Bernstein reported that President Trump is exploring various ways to hold onto power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson to beat Musk and Bezos in billionaire space race; Set to fly on GALACTIC ship next year!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1250514/branson-musk-bezos-space-race-virgin-galactic-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIT billionaire Sir Richard Branson will rocket into space aboard a Virgin Galactic spaceship next year, the company has announced. The launch promises to blaze a trail for commercial flights aboa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Trump's bag of tricks comes up empty against Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/04/trump-biden-bag-tricks-giuliani-391081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His untamed political instincts, once treated by Republicans with an almost mystical reverence, look increasingly unlikely to stave off defeat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RI added to NY quarantine list, 34 states now restricted as Cuomo blasts Feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/shame-on-all-of-you-more-states-may-land-on-ny-quarantine-list-as-cuomo-blasts-feds/2549231/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some states on the tri-state’s quarantine list have hit a plateau in coronavirus infections, and few of them have seen decreases in new cases — but the list remains almost as long as ever. California, Florida and Texas have all surpassed New York in most confirmed COVID-19 cases in the U.S. and they’re among the 34 states (plus Puerto Rico)…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spending Watchdog Presses Treasury for More Transparency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/virus-spending-watchdog-presses-treasury-for-more-transparency/ar-BB17wV27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive explosion rocks Beirut...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8592549/Massive-explosion-rocks-Beirut-destroying-buildings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic footage on social media shows people screaming as an enormous blast rocks the waterside area of Lebanon's capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends Ghislaine Maxwell well wishes: 'Do you know she was guilty?'</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-ghislaine-maxwell-jeffrey-epstein-1b313a9d-13c0-45f6-8975-26de2e1559aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"She's now in jail. Yeah, I wish her well."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Struggles to explain coronavirus charts, statistics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-coronavirus-under-control-5f114a16-9952-428c-bc07-3cfa360b0977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with "Axios on HBO," he said the virus is as well-controlled as it can be despite surging U.S. cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAST COAST STORM ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-04-tropical-storm-isaias-forecast-northeast-flooding-damaging-winds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the latest complete forecast briefing on Isaias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland, America's 'whitest' big city, an unlikely hub of Black Lives Matter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/portland-americas-whitest-big-city-113025189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland, Ore., where more than 72% of the population is white, has been transformed into a national center of the movement for racial justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaias tracks along I-95...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0d4583ecf2405caf0ab3713169787b0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTHPORT, N.C. (AP) — Tropical Storm Isaias spawned tornadoes and dumped rain along the U.S. East Coast on Tuesday after making landfall as a hurricane in North Carolina, where it smashed boats...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fumbles With Charts and Figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-axios-interview-coronavirus-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swan challenged Trump directly on the number of American coronavirus deaths in an interview that aired Monday night on HBO, earning praise online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC crime spree knocks on doorsteps of America's ultra-rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/nyc-crime-spree-americas-ultra-rich-robbery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking of the ultra-wealthy who left amid the COVID-19 pandemic, Gov. Cuomo said, "We're trying to get people to come back."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornadoes, fires, flooding, outages...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/isaias-tropical-storm-hurricane-tornadoes-flooding-fires-outages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It lost some punch after coming ashore as a hurricane but was hitting hard in North Carolina and Virginia. It's expected to hug the coastline as it moves north.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC producer pens scathing exit letter...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/510411-msnbc-producer-pens-scathing-exit-letter-ratings-model-blocks-diversity-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Producer Ariana Pekary recently resigned from MSNBC with an open letter accusing the news network of predicating its editorial process on ratings and alleging that its model "blocks diversity of thought and conte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEESE: 'Woke' Culture Killing Comedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/john-cleese-thinks-woke-culture-is-killing-comedy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this week’s episode of “The Last Laugh podcast,” Monty Python co-founder John Cleese talks “woke” comedy, laughing at Trump, and what he hopes his legacy will be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Find Best Place On Earth To See Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/best-place-on-earth-to-see-stars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Counting stars is pretty difficult in areas with lots of light, like New York City. A study says even in the clearest skies, you're still seeing turbulence in the atmosphere that makes stars twinkle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Dirty Secrets Of 'Clean' Electric Vehicles...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tilakdoshi/2020/08/02/the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-electric-vehicles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The widespread view that fossil fuels are “dirty” and renewables such as wind and solar energy and electric vehicles are “clean” has become a fixture of mainstream media and policy makers of all persuasions. But, in the case of EVs, the dirty secrets of “clean energy” should seem apparent to all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=765&amp;initrange=42.000000000000:-83.750000000000:33.500000000000:-69.750000000000&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUNSET BOULEVARD' at 70: We're all Norma Desmond now...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/aug/04/sunset-boulevard-at-70-were-all-norma-desmond-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunset Boulevard showed the damage wrought by fame. Seventy years on, popular culture is more obsessed than ever with being seen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas set to decide Kobach's fate -- and possibly the Senate's...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/04/primary-kansas-michigan-arizona-missouri-washington-391091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kansas GOP Senate contest leads the list of things to watch on a crucial primary day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives, establishment Dems set for major clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/guide-to-aug-4-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's your guide to the top stories ahead of (yet another) primary election day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/us/new-jersey/weather-radar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC: Branson space-bound early 2021...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/richard-branson-space-bound-early-2021-says-virgin-084900952.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Branson could shoot into space on his Virgin Galactic aircraft as its first passenger early next year, the company said, potentially blazing a path for commercial flights. The company has repeatedly pushed back the date it will take the first tourists outside earth&amp;#39;s atmosphere and said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men rescued from Pacific island after writing SOS in sand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1566b3c6a377ee907a0f2e143a5b26c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — Three men have been rescued from a tiny Pacific island after writing a giant SOS sign in the sand that was spotted from above, authorities say. The men had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pessimists Have Higher Risk of Heart Disease...</title>
      <link>/https://www.sciencetimes.com/articles/26712/20200802/pessimists-vs-optimists-whos-healthier.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Contagion' doctor predicts turmoil for years...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/08/03/covid-19-us-who-doctor-larry-brilliant/5574854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Brilliant, an ex-WHO doctor whose team helped eradicate smallpox, predicts the U.S. could battle COVID-19 for the next 3 to 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You Can't Do That': Stunning Exchanges from President's Interview With AXIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/you-cant-do-that-watch-the-most-stunning-exchanges-from-president-trumps-interview-with-axios-jonathan-swan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump sat down last week for an interview with Axios' Jonathan Swan for what turned out to be a wild and fascinating back-and-forth with heated exchanges on a number of issues ra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People live longer in blue states...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/people-live-longer-blue-states-040142664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study traces how the policies adopted by Democratic and Republican states over the last several decades have helped widen the gap in life expectancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries thought to have contained COVID face new waves of infection...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/around-world-countries-thought-contained-110429744.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh outbreaks from Australia to Spain underscore the relentlessness of the coronavirus as infections top 18 million worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: American Satisfaction at 13%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/316736/satisfaction-lowest-nine-years.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' satisfaction with the way things are going in the U.S. dropped seven percentage points last month, to 13% -- the lowest Gallup has measured since November 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three shot during wild party at Mulholland Drive mansion...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/08/03/lapd-responds-to-large-party-being-held-at-beverly-crest-mansion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a local health order prohibiting large gatherings, LAPD said it could not enter the premises to breakup the without a warrant. Police on scene were there for traffic and noise control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of evictions expected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/833d91877e2f0fa913c5258978a9e83c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — Kelyn Yanez used to clean homes during the day and wait tables at night in the Houston area before the coronavirus. But the mother of three lost both jobs in March because of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sobering' report shows hardening attitudes against media...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d27d2b01e6e4bb3c9dd2050e5afd70e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The distrust many Americans feel toward the news media, caught up like much of the nation's problems in the partisan divide, only seems to be getting worse. That was the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreaks in agricultural communities raise harvest fears...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/510371-covid-19-outbreaks-in-agricultural-communities-raise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREWSTER, Wash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Lockdown 2.0 Looks Like: Harsher Rules, Deeper Confusion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/04/what-lockdown-2-0-looks-like-harsher-rules-deeper-confusion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia’s second-largest city, Melbourne, grappling with a spiraling coronavirus outbreak in a country that once thought it had the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ASSAILS 'BALD-FACED LIES'</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden/biden-assails-trumps-bald-faced-lies-about-voting-by-mail-idUSKCN24Z2QW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden said on Monday that President Donald Trump was telling "bald-faced lies" about voting by mail to distract from his own failures, after Trump last week suggested it could be cause to delay the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VOWS EXECUTIVE ORDER ON MAIL VOTING </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d64defdd9960885f1fbe6be2f8714afe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump claimed Monday that he has the authority to issue an executive order on mail-in ballots, whose increasing use, he argues, could increase election fraud and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE POST OFFICE DELAYS AS ELECTION LOOMS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/666471269922a01ae792c79b991277e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Oversight Committee has invited the new postmaster general to appear at a September hearing to examine operational changes at the U.S. Postal Service that are causing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY TOPS AMAZON WITH FIRST BOOK IN 10 YEARS!</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2020-08-03/sean-hannity-live-free-or-die-fox-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In new book, Sean Hannity makes case for more Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA hunter who killed elephant is now PETA target in bid to end trophy hunting...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-08-03/peta-wants-to-ban-trophy-hunting-la-man-is-target</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California may soon pass a law to ban the import of "trophy" animal parts from Africa. Activists are targeting an L.A. hunter whose hunt was captured on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY MAIL leaks bodycam footage of George Floyd arrest, killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8576371/Police-bodycam-footage-shows-moment-moment-arrest-George-Floyd-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: DISTURBING CONTENT. DailyMail.com has obtained video from the body cameras of two officers involved in the arrest of George Floyd that ultimately led to his death on May 25 in Minneapolis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx is new target for Trump... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Top-virus-official-Birx-is-new-target-for-Trump-15456043.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump further disparaged his senior health advisers on Monday even as the pandemic deepened its hold on the nation, as the White House's top coronavirus coordinator, Deborah Birx, joined Anthony Fauci and other scientists on the receiving end of the president's ire.  Birx - who built a career leading public health efforts against HIV/AIDS - quickly garnered Trump's favor earlier this year for publicly championing the administration's coronavirus response, becoming a prominent figure inside and outside the White House.  But she soon lost support within swaths of the scientific and medical community for seeming to minimize the virus and to enable Trump's rosy view of the pandemic. This past weekend, Birx lost the backing of the nation's top Democrat, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi of California, who privately called Birx "the worst" and publicly said she had no confidence in her.  On Monday morning, Birx appeared to lose ground with perhaps her most important constituency, Trump himself, who dismissed her as "pathetic."  "So Crazy Nancy Pelosi said horrible things about Dr. Deborah Birx, going after her because she was too positive on the very good job we are doing on combatting the China Virus, including Vaccines &amp; Therapeutics," Trump wrote in a tweet. "In order to counter Nancy, Deborah took the bait &amp; hit us. Pathetic!"  Trump was especially incensed that she did not strike a more optimistic tone about states that are doing well and by her praise for Pelosi, an ardent Trump critic, said one senior administration official, who like others spoke on the condition of anonymity to share details of private discussions. When asked about Pelosi's lack of confidence in the handling of the pandemic, Birx replied, "I have tremendous respect for the speaker. And I have tremendous respect for her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded by virus, honeymooners hitch home on Antarctic boat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d0a26f48064a8a0a91556e10c8154b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — A New Zealand honeymoon couple stranded on the remote Falkland Islands in March because of the coronavirus has managed to return home by hitching a ride of more than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  George says  Trump's name should live in infamy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/george-conway-torches-trump-in-op-ed-for-attempt-to-defraud-his-way-to-re-election-he-must-lose-and-lose-badly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway went on a tear against President Donald Trump in another Washington Post op-ed for his recent attacks on mail-in voting and his floating of a potential election delay — something even a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=36.250000000000:-86.500000000000:27.750000000000:-72.500000000000&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daughter continues x-rated attacks, calls him  'f**king idiot'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1247890/claudia-conway-donald-trump-idiot-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAUDIA Conway has continued her rebellious attack on Donald Trump and called him a “f**king idiot” in an x-rated rant. The teenager reposted one of the president’s tweets with th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gambler removed in cuffs from Vegas casino for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1246656/las-vegas-four-queens-casino-face-mask-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAS Vegas gambler was removed from the famous 4 Queens casino in handcuffs after he went in without wearing a mask. The man was bundled out of the building and handed over to cops for flouting pu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  George says  Trump's name should live in infamy...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2020/08/george-conway-blasts-blundering-cheat-trump-in-new-op-ed-his-name-should-live-in-infamy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent conservative attorney George T. Conway III has written yet another Washington Post op-ed blasting President Donald Trump. “If there’s one thing we know about President Trump, it’s that he lies and he cheats. Endlessly,” Conway wrote. “And shamelessly. But still, mostly, incompetently.” “So it should have come as no surprise that Trump finally went […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Under FTC Investigation for Misuse of User Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/twitter-under-ftc-investigation-for-alleged-misuse-of-user-data/ar-BB17wu9o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://radar.weather.gov/lite/N0Z/LTX_loop.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radar.weather.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal spray approved for treating suicidal people...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-08-nasal-suicidal-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp; Johnson's Spravato has been approved as the first antidepressant for actively suicidal people, as doctors are becoming increasingly concerned about COVID-19's effect on the mental health of Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA probing Trump Organization for 'insurance and bank fraud'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/manhattan-da-probing-trump-organization-183900853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - President Donald Trump and his company face an investigation for possible "insurance and bank fraud," Manhattan District Attorney Cy Vance wrote Monday, asking a judge to uphold a subpoena for Trump's tax returns. The new filing in Manhattan federal court hinted at the scope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Protracted criminal conduct'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ffdad3a4983088224245dbf761c6d113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A New York City prosecutor fighting to get President Donald Trump’s tax returns told a judge Monday he was justified in demanding them because of public reports of “extensive and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline Food For Sale. No Plane Ticket Required...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/08/03/898647020/airline-food-for-sale-no-plane-ticket-required</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Chicken or beef?" A leading Israeli airline food company, which is struggling with most flights grounded, is selling its meals to the public as a low-cost delivery option during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Bombs Syria After Attempted Terror Attack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/syrian-air-defenses-respond-to-airstrikes-near-damascuss-637385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The targets hit in the strikes included lookout points, intelligence gathering mechanisms, anti-aircraft weapons and means of control and command at Syrian military bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female morgue workers fired after alleged porn, Black penis cake...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/08/03/macomb-morgue-scandal-sexual-harassment-racism/5567226002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Macomb County morgue workers have been fired in a race and sex scandal over claims that office staff mocked Blacks and bullied women for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continues to lose ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/03/politics/2020-election-map/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national political landscape has clearly and significantly shifted in Joe Biden's favor since he emerged as the Democratic Party's presumptive nominee back in March just as the public health emergency was taking hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation 'Racing Towards the Finish Line'...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/manhattan-das-investigation-into-trump-is-now-racing-towards-the-finish-line-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's secret home security superpower: Smart speaker always listening...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/google-smart-speaker-alarm-adt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google speakers are listening to more than just voice commands. Using them for home security could supercharge Google's $450 million ADT deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's August, but Lake Michigan 'dangerously cold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/weather/2020/08/it-might-be-august-but-lake-michigan-is-dangerously-cold-with-temps-below-50-nws-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water temperatures from Ludington to South Haven will be in the 40s to low 50s, according to the NWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60% of counties seeing 'uncontrollable spread'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8588147/Map-shows-60-counties-seeing-uncontrollable-COVID-spread.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data map shows that almost every state across the country has at least one county experiencing an 'epidemic trend', or uncontrollable spread, of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans divided over whether they'd fill Supreme Court vacancy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/510076-senate-gop-divided-over-whether-theyd-fill-supreme-court-vacancy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are conflicted about what to do if a Supreme Court seat becomes vacant during the remainder of President Trump's first term, a possibility that has come more into focus in recent weeks in light of Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC shakes up daytime lineup...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nicolle-wallace-gets-two-hours-193836826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an MSNBC programming shift, Nicolle Wallace&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Deadline White House&amp;quot; expands to two hours and Chuck Todd&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;MTP Daily&amp;quot; moves to midday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus-sniffing dogs dispatched at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Coronavirus-sniffing-dogs-dubai-15454175.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the United Arab Emirates, all arriving passengers must submit to COVID-19 testing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA player who stood for national anthem tears ACL...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/magic-jonathan-isaac-national-anthem-torn-acl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orlando Magic forward Jonathan Isaac was diagnosed with a torn ACL on Sunday night after going down with the injury in a game against the Sacramento Kings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of all furloughed workers now believe they'll be fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/03/nearly-half-of-workers-believe-temporary-layoff-will-become-permanent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April, roughly 2 in 10 households experiencing job loss considered their layoff permanent. Now, as states have stalled or reversed reopening plans and the coronavirus outbreak worsens, nearly half of unemployed workers think their job is not coming back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife Portia de Rossi breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/08/03/portia-de-rossi-breaks-silence-on-ellen-degeneres-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I stand by Ellen,” the “Arrested Development” star shared on Instagram on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's scandal-hit former king goes into exile...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/03/spains-scandal-hit-former-king-juan-carlos-to-move-abroad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 82-year-old says he is moving abroad to help son ‘exercise his responsibilities’ as king</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Emerging Middle Eastern Kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/israel-middle-east/articles/china-middle-eastern-kingdom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s drive for supremacy is now underway in the Middle East—and it won’t end there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President fires Tennessee Valley Authority chair, citing exec pay, foreign workers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0336437987fec77627c17ca9a4c781bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Monday that he had fired the chair of the Tennessee Valley Authority, criticizing the federal-owned corporation for hiring foreign...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROWNS WR Beckham Says NFL Season Should Be Canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/odell-beckham-says-the-2020-nfl-season-should-be-canceled-i-just-feel-like-it-shouldnt-happen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This probably isn't what the NFL wants to hear just before the start of training camp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's ex-king leaving country amid financial scandal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e7dda3c35a7953498964e3b8353c33d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain’s former monarch, Juan Carlos I, says he is leaving Spain to live in another, unspecified, country amid a financial scandal, according to a letter published on the royal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President fires Tennessee Valley Authority chair, citing exec pay, foreign workers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/03663ed28ac7f85818da0002b3c80249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Trump fires Tennessee Valley Authority chair, citing executive compensation, hiring of foreign workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice from a woman who survived 1918 flu, cancer and covid-19!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/lifestyle/article/Advice-from-a-woman-who-survived-covid-19-the-15454667.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are in a pandemic today that the world hasn't seen the likes of in 102 years.  Mildred Geraldine "Gerri" Schappals is one of the few people in the world who has survived both. The 102-year-old New Englander lived through a severe bout of the flu during the 1918 pandemic as a baby. And now, a century later, punctuated by two bouts of cancer, Schappals also has recovered from covid-19 in the pandemic of 2020.  Schappals - an Irish Catholic known for her witty one-liners - is the oldest resident at the Huntington at Nashua, a retirement and assisted-living community in Nashua, N.H.  "I don't think of myself as old," said Schappals, who is moderately deaf and provided an interview through her daughter, Julia Schappals.  Julia Schappals, 68, calls her mother feisty and tough and "an example of a good, fighting treasure."  She is an anomaly, and not just because of her age. The elder Schappals was not particularly health-conscious throughout her life, yet she seems to have a bulletproof immune system. She credits that to the 1918 flu pandemic, her daughter said.  Julia Schappals cannot recall a single time when her mother got sick with a respiratory ailment like the cold or flu. In fact, Gerri Schappals had disdain for anyone who did get sick.  "I really think that having the 1918 flu strengthened everything about me," she said. "I never had colds or illnesses until I got cancer, and even then I pulled through. It's either that or Mother Nature thinks I died in 1918, so she ignores me."  - - -  Gerri Schappals was born in Worcester, Mass., on Jan. 18, 1918, when World War I was raging, and women didn't have the right to vote. Eleven months after she was born - in November, the same month when the war officially ended - baby Gerri, her mother and her teenage brother, Joseph, came...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rails against 'illegal late night coup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8588043/Donald-Trump-rails-against-illegal-late-night-coup-claims-steal-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump launched another attack on mail-in voting as Republicans fret Trump's salvos could hurt them at the ballot box in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Biden's delay in announcing VP intensifies jockeying between potential picks...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-s-delay-in-announcing-running-mate-15453258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden has extended his vice-presidential search by as much as two weeks, intensifying the jockeying and lobbying between allies of the women who hope to join his White House. Even some longtime Biden allies worry that the process has become "messier than it should be," pitting women, especially Black women, against one another.  The dynamic threatens to undermine Biden's effort to use the vice-presidential search to spotlight some of the party's brightest female stars during the highly public vetting process. And it's already providing President Donald Trump's campaign an opening to dig up dirt and launch attacks on potential rivals.  "It's been relentless. It's been unfortunate. But I must say it's been predictable," said Donna Brazile, a former interim chair of the Democratic National Committee. "It's extremely disappointing, because many of these attacks . . . are being made by Democratic men who should know better."  "I would hope that in this selection process, we are mindful that Black women - and women of color - deserve respect," she added.  The increasing nastiness is fueled by a sense, even among Biden's closest advisers, that Biden is entering the final phase of the search without a clear favorite. Rather than a traditional "short list" of three candidates, people close to the process expect him to interview five or six finalists for the position.  The delay has intensified currents that have been swirling for weeks, said several people interviewed. The resulting backbiting risks inflaming divisions within the party that complicated the 2016 campaign - but that Biden has worked to coalesce since locking down the nomination in the spring.  A recent Politico report said former senator Chris Dodd, D-Conn., who is on Biden's vice-presidential vetting panel, told donors that Sen....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers protest across nation...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200803160440-yk1e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Teachers protest across U.S. over re-opening schools in pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some survivors suffer psychiatric disorders, Italian study says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200803145104-mqgw9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DISORDERS:Some COVID-19 survivors suffer psychiatric disorders, Italian study says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Companies Will Be Exempt From Liability Claims... </title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/red-flags-soar-big-pharma-will-be-exempt-covid-19-vaccine-liability-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 CEOs warn Congress of 'catastrophic' consequences without MORE bailout cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/more-100-ceos-warn-congress-catastrophic-consequences-small-biz-without-n1235613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The letter, spearheaded by Howard Schultz, chairman emeritus of Starbucks, was also signed by Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg and Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Slide Is Warning America Losing Grip on Virus Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/dollar-e2-80-99s-slide-is-a-warning-that-us-has-lost-grip-on-virus/ar-BB17uloo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh launches 'guaranteed income'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pittsburgh-launches-guaranteed-income-program-with-jack-dorsey-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eligible residents will receive $500 in monthly "guaranteed income."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land with no face masks: Holland's top scientists say no evidence coverings work...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8583925/The-land-no-face-masks-Hollands-scientists-say-theres-no-solid-evidence-coverings-work.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While 120 countries in the world, including much of Europe, have ordered citizens to wear masks in public places to prevent the spread of Covid-19, the Dutch are doing things differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAST COAST STORM ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-03-hurricane-warning-tropical-storm-isaias-forecast-east-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the latest complete forecast briefing on Isaias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed official says another full lockdown needed to save economy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/510235-top-federal-reserve-official-says-us-needs-another-lockdown-to-save-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government should again impose strict coronavirus-related lockdowns for a month or longer across the U.S. in order to boost the economy, a top Federal Reserve official said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://radar.weather.gov/lite/N0Z/CLX_loop.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radar.weather.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's new infections hits young, middle-aged...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/703d9d02ede92e29487a9a7c4c8ab47d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANT SADURNÍ D'ANOIA, Spain (AP) — Like most Spaniards, Emma Gaya thought the worst of the pandemic was behind her. Spain’s government had ended a three-month lockdown after an COVID-19...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
