<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dems plot to squeeze health care promises into social spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/05/dems-health-care-infrastructure-medicaid-502479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To squeeze as many of their priorities as possible in the budget resolution, lawmakers are discussing making some of the new health spending temporary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo spotted poolside with mystery blonde amid political storm...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/05/andrew-cuomo-lounges-poolside-as-sexual-harassment-scandal-swirls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo lounged poolside with a blonde pal at the Executive Mansion Thursday despite deafening calls for his resignation and almost-certain impending impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to scan U.S. phones for images of child abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-child-abuse-apple-inc-7fe2a09427d663cda8addfeeffc40196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is planning to scan U.S. iPhones for images of child abuse, drawing applause from child protection groups but raising concern among some security researchers that the system could be misused by governments looking to surveil their citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid surge hits hospitals: 'Only so many beds'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-38917e4fd073c8142df15de2d8102a24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Florida hospitals slammed with COVID-19 patients are suspending elective surgeries and putting beds in conference rooms, an auditorium and a cafeteria. In Georgia, medical centers are turning people away for lack of space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research finds people spend half their lives not focused on the present...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/05/health/practice-mindfulness-hate-sitting-still-wellness-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People spend nearly half of their waking hours thinking about something other than what is going on right in front of them. But there's good news --- we are not doomed to a life being incapable of paying attention to more than half of our day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt-Funded Researchers Sought Aborted Minorities for Organ Harvesting...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/policy/taxpayer-fund-aborted-babies-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government gave at least $2.7 million in taxpayer money to researchers who singled out minorities and harvested organs from full-term babies in an effort to fund a "pipeline" for experiments on aborted fetal organs, according to internal documents released Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm-on-Postcard Breakthrough Opens Door to Massive 'Sperm Books'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvqp9/sperm-on-a-postcard-breakthrough-opens-door-to-massive-sperm-books</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists mailed freeze-dried mouse sperm on a postcard and birthed pups on the other side, a major advance for affordable long-distance sperm transfer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quebec to introduce vaccine passport...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210805-canada-s-quebec-province-to-introduce-vaccine-passport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's Quebec province to introduce vaccine passport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers brace for renewed 'rebellion, anger'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/workers-brace-renewed-rebellion-anger-163724362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees of chains like Walmart, Starbucks, and IKEA appear split on whether masks and vaccines should be mandated in stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-Year-Old Girl Bitten By Shark Off Popular MD Beach...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/officials-believe-sandbar-shark-bit-12-year-old-girl-in-ocean-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocean City Beach Patrol said Thursday they believe a small sandbar shark bit a 12-year-old girl Monday on the surf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To break into kids TV, MARVEL met power players: Preschoolers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/break-kids-tv-marvel-met-120016673.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To make age-appropriate superhero TV, Marvel partnered with Disney Junior on research, pre-K focus groups and more. Here's how they did it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE mogul Larry Page allowed into New Zealand despite closed border...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9863993/Billionaire-Google-founder-Larry-Page-allowed-enter-New-Zealand-Fijian-island.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Larry Page, 48, has been living off the grid in Fiji for most of the pandemic but sought special permission to fly to New Zealand with the child, who is around 12-years-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman in San Fran leans out of car window in traffic brandishing AK-47...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/woman-in-san-francisco-leans-out-of-car-window-holding-ak-47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police on Wednesday released a photo of a woman leaning out of a moving car holding an AK-47 during an illegal speed event in San Francisco last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN clerk who shot at beer thieves charged with murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article253280283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The men took four cases of beer, and the armed clerk followed them outside to confront them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union boss Trumka dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/05/afl-cio-trumka-dead-502573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trumka had served as president of the federation for more than a decade and has been a close ally of the Biden White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  29% Have Lost Someone to Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/polls-show-20-of-americans-have-ended-friendships-over-covid-spats-and-29-have-lost-someone-to-covid-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling new polls show that significant numbers of Americans have ended friendships over disagreements about COVID-19 — and an even greater number have lost a friend or family member who died from the disease. In one survey released Thursday, YouGov asked respondents "Have you lost any friendships because of differences in opinion related to the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/greenville-dixie-fire-destroys-much-of-northern-california-mountain-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildfire that tore through a historic mountain town in Northern California left much of the downtown in ashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel 'ready to strike Iran'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-ready-to-attack-iran-as-defense-minister-says-we-need-to-take-military-action/ar-AAMXS2i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benny Gantz told Ynet that the world should act militarily against the Islamic republic which has been blamed for a drone attack on an Israeli-operated tanker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly venomous cobra on loose in Texas town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-west-african-banded-cobra-is-loose-in-grand-prairie-is-the-owner-allowed-to-have-it/ar-AAMWNSD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aug. 5—On Wednesday, a West African banded cobra was possibly slithering through a Grand Prairie residential neighborhood, prompting questions from residents about exotic snake permits and snake bite treatments. The cobra escaped from its owner's home on Tuesday, Grand Prairie officials said in a press release, and various agencies searched for the creature near the 1800 block of Cherry Street ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Fire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hot-gusty-weather-could-mean-054421092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California’s largest wildfire has leveled much of the downtown and some surrounding homes in a small Northern California mountain community. The Dixie Fire tore through the Greenville on Wednesday evening, destroying businesses and homes as the sky was cast in an orange glow. “If you are still in the Greenville area, you are in imminent danger and you MUST leave now!!” the Plumas County Sheriff’s Office posted on Facebook earlier Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Hospitals Fighting For Oxygen...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/coronavirus/florida-hospitals-fighting-to-get-oxygen-with-hand-tied</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida hospitals are struggling to get oxygen due to a rise in Covid-19 cases attributable to the delta variant and Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis’s decision not to declare another state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESANTIS AIMS FOR WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/04/ron-desantis-blasts-president-joe-biden-singling-out-florida-over-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is a guy who ran for president saying he was going to, quote, ‘Shut down the virus.’ And what has he done? He's imported more virus from around the world by having a wide open southern border."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Test Could Diagnose Alzheimer's Decades Before Symptoms Develop...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/blood-test-could-diagnose-alzheimers-disease-decades-before-sympttoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Alzheimer's blood test could lead to a screening program, enabling medications and lifestyle changes to be prescribed to vulnerable individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican official who mocked dies of virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article253276493.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In previous social media posts, he showed support for mask burning and called incentives to encourage vaccinations “disgusting.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT BY FALL?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/politics/cuomo-impeachment-looming-assembly-gives-1-week-deadline-for-evidence/3203142/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Assembly Judiciary Committee has given Gov. Andrew Cuomo an Aug. 13 deadline to provide any evidence he wants before the committee considers articles of impeachment against him. “We write to inform you that the Committee’s investigation is nearing completion and the Assembly will soon consider potential articles of impeachment against your client,” the committee’s lawyers wrote…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans poised to give Biden political victory...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/566441-senate-gop-poised-to-give-biden-huge-political-victory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are about to hand President Biden a huge political victory by voting for a historic $1 trillion infrastructure package that the president can then tout as fulfilling a campaign pledge to restore b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela to slash six zeroes from currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.gmanetwork.com/news/news/nation/798267/venezuela-to-slash-six-zeroes-from-currency-central-bank/story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gmanetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela will slash six zeroes off its inflation-battered currency the bolivar to make it easier to use, the central bank said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipping snags prompt US firms to mull retreat from China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-global-trade-a8992e7141013f0164d04476d637f0c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Game maker Eric Poses last year created The Worst-Case Scenario Card Game, making a wry reference to the way the coronavirus had upended normal life. He had no idea. In a twist that Poses never could have predicted, his game itself would become caught up in the latest fallout from the health crisis: a backlogged global supply chain that has delayed shipments around the world and sent freight costs rocketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock poll shows Newsom losing recall vote by double digits...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/poll-Gavin-Newsom-recall-losing-Elder-Paffrath-16364991.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll's other shocking finding is a new leader on Newsom's replacement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly venomous cobra on loose in Texas town...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/566471-highly-venomous-cobra-on-the-loose-in-texas-town</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly venomous cobra is on the loose in Grand Prairie, Texas, after it went missing from a home on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates says he regrets time spent with Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/08/05/business/bill-gates-regrets-jeffrey-epstein-relations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft founder Bill Gates regrets his gatherings with Jeffrey Epstein, the wealthy financial manager who was accused of child sex trafficking, he told CNN Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health System Ranks Last Among 11 High-Income Countries?</title>
      <link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/news/20210804/us-health-system-ranks-last-among-11-high-income-countries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.webmd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-income person in the U.S. was more likely to report financial barriers to needed health care than a low-income person in nearly all the other countries surveyed, the Commonwealth Fund reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Giuliani Went from 9/11's Hallowed Mayor to 2021's Haunted Ghoul...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/08/how-rudy-giuliani-went-from-911s-hallowed-mayor-to-2021s-haunted-ghoul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Bratton, Joe Klein, and former friends and aides weigh in on the colossal collapse of NYC’s ex-mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo isn't first NY gov to face impeachment. In 1913, another Dem removed...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Andrew-Cuomo-isn-t-the-first-New-York-governor-to-16366049.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo to resign piled up this week after state attorney...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skips work to strategize survival plan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/05/andrew-cuomo-hiding-in-governors-mansion-forming-survival-plan-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo didn’t show up at work but instead remained holed up in the Governor’s Mansion developing a strategy to salvage his political career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK exec helped smear accuser...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/facebook-exec-helped-cuomo-smear-sex-harassment-accuser-ag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top communications manager at Facebook helped Gov. Andrew Cuomo fight sexual misconduct allegations — including by helping leak confidential files about accuser Lindsey Boylan, according to the N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden approval slips...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/566461-biden-coronavirus-response-approval-slips-in-new-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approval of President Biden’s handling of the coronavirus has slipped in recent weeks, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOUTH PARK' Creators Sign Massive $900 Million Deal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/south-park-creators-sign-massive-115249786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The creators of “South Park” have signed a new deal with ViacomCBS Inc. that will pay them more than $900 million over the next six years, one of the richest deals in TV history.Trey Parker and Matt Stone will use the money to make new episodes of “South Park” for Viacom’s Comedy Central network and to create several spinoff movies for the company’s Paramount+ streaming service, the parties said Thursday. Their first project under the new deal will be a movie set in the world of “</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality shows sending people to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/05/tech/who-wants-to-be-an-astronaut-space-hero-reality-television-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hottest new reality show isn't set in a house, on an obstacle course, or on the Jersey Shore. Television producers are betting on a new location: the International Space Station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarmed Louisiana Residents Turn to Jabs in 'Darkest Days' of Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/05/alarmed-louisiana-residents-turn-to-vaccines-in-darkest-days-of-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMMOND, La. — Officials in Louisiana have been willing to try just about anything to jolt the state’s lagging Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sturgis bike rally revs back bigger, despite virus variant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-sd-state-wire-71bb16eee8ff6f9a4540405a3c69aba3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — Crowds of bikers are rumbling their way towards South Dakota's Black Hills this week, raising fears that COVID-19 infections will be unleashed among the 700,000 people expected to show up at the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON  MAYOR COMPARES MANDATE TO SLAVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/boston-mayor-janey-compares-vaccine-passports-to-slave-papers-birtherism/37213542#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There's a long history in this country of people needing to show their papers," said Janey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 CASES IN DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-covid-19-cases-hit-six-month-high-over-100000-reuters-tally-2021-08-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States hit a six-month high for new COVID cases with over 100,000 infections reported on Wednesday, according to a Reuters tally, as the Delta variant ravages areas where people did not get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA asks airports to monitor passenger alcohol intake, citing unruly behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/faa-asks-airports-monitor-passengers-alcohol-intake-citing-unruly-behavior-n1276015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Some airport concessionaires have offered alcohol 'to go,' and passengers believe they can carry that alcohol onto their flights," the agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy renouncing American citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wealthy-people-are-renouncing-american-citizenship-67fbada4-e2e4-4699-b106-c986839f209d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasons renouncing citizenship tend to be financial, not political.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Kamala Harris crisis dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/kamala-harris-press-coverage-crisis-dinner-7139cfc7-754b-42aa-a411-95716273dbb0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris has faced a torrent of bad press early in the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carl Lewis slams track team as 'embarrassment'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/05/carl-lewis-slams-us-track-team-as-embarrassment-after-relay-fail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An event that the United States previously dominated is now looking like “a total embarrassment” for Team USA – at least, that’s what one of its greatest legends thinks. Carl Lewis — who won nine g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Crash kills 10 in van carrying migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ten-killed-12-injured-texas-crash-involving-migrant-worker-van-local-media-2021-08-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A van overloaded with 30 people, many of them believed to be illegal immigrants, crashed in southern Texas on Wednesday, killing 10 occupants and critically injuring many of the others, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE mogul Larry Page allowed into New Zealand despite closed border...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/google-co-founder-larry-page-allowed-into-new-zealand-despite-closed-border-2503055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google co-founder Larry Page was allowed into New Zealand despite its closed border so his son could receive urgent medical attention, the government confirmed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driverless Semi Reaches Milestone in Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/driverless-semi-reaches-milestone-in-test-startup-plus-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Driverless Semi Reaches Milestone in Test, Startup Plus Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How G7 task force helps governments target critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-finance-fatf-consequences-specialrepo/special-report-how-a-little-known-g7-task-force-unwittingly-helps-governments-target-critics-idUSKBN2F616V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late 2020, when Ugandan President Yoweri Museveni faced a fresh challenge to his 35-year rule, a new tool helped to silence his critics: anti-money laundering legislation promoted by the G7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American stars fail to earn stripes in more athletics woe...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210805-usa-stars-fail-to-earn-stripes-in-more-athletics-woe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA stars fail to earn stripes in more athletics woe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police allege HILLSONG CHURCH founder concealed child sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-3418b25401fa5dac98efcfc74c7e6acd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — The founder of the Sydney-based global Hillsong Church, Brian Houston, has been charged with concealing child sex offenses, police said Thursday. Detectives served Houston’s lawyers on Thursday with a notice for him to appear in a Sydney court on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comFire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comFire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne plunges back into lockdown week after leaving it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/melbourne-plunges-back-into-coronavirus-lockdown-a-week-after-leaving-it/ar-AAMXGLs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mystery cases, suspected to be the delta variant, come as Sydney endures a lengthy shutdown amid a slow vaccine rollout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo logs record 5,042 cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-lifestyle-sports-coronavirus-pandemic-business-0b250f40128b0892863bc55067a4ba39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Tokyo reported 5,042 new daily coronavirus cases on Thursday, hitting a record since the pandemic began as the infections surge in the Japanese capital hosting the Olympics. The additional cases brought the total for Tokyo to 236,138, about a quarter of the national total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC launches its own health passport...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/new-york-city-launches-vaccine-passport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYC Covid Safe app is the new coronavirus vaccination app the city is rolling out for people to use to show they are vaccinated for indoor dining, gyms, and other places that will be forced to check.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic secret to age women start menopause discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/aug/04/genetic-secret-to-age-women-start-menopause-discovered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research could lead to doctors being able to tell women how long they have got left to start a family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes with White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/desantis-white-house-trade-barbs-as-florida-covid-cases-climb/ar-AAMWYGA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Governor Ron DeSantis had a heated exchange with the White House on Wednesday amid a surge of coronavirus hospitalizations and deaths in his state that’s prompted a political clash over mask mandates and vaccine requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to announce vax requirement for active-duty forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/sec-of-defense-austin-to-announce-mandatory-vaccine-policy-for-all-active-duty-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin is expected to announce a mandatory vaccine policy for all active-duty forces in the U.S. military Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some school districts push ahead with mask mandates, defying threat to cut funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Some-Florida-school-districts-push-ahead-with-16364677.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of Florida's largest school districts have announced they will either keep or issue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left wing complicates Pelosi's calculus...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Left-wing-complicates-Pelosi-s-calculus-16364819.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In July 2019, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., had a particularly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  WORSE THAN DELTA COMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fauci-delta-variant-covid-d1c0d550-6624-417d-bde6-33c8f56deaba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People who are not getting vaccinated mistakenly think it’s only about them. But it isn’t."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE FOREIGNERS TO JAB</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-a312ebaf72844c5b75246fb10b0f2ba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is taking the first steps toward requiring nearly all foreign visitors to the U.S. to be vaccinated for the coronavirus, a White House official said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark side of TIKTOK exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3410817/tiktok-star-deaths-timbo-the-redneck-anthony-barajas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIKTOK stars have become the latest set of celebrities but the dark side of the app has seen its rising talent die from suicide, addiction, shootings, and stunts for their account.  Timbo the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Zucker to stay at WARNERMEDIA at least until DISCOVERY deal closes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/04/cnn-president-jeff-zucker-will-stay-at-warnermedia-at-least-until-discovery-deal-closes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Zucker will stay at WarnerMedia at least until the AT&amp;T media unit merges with Discovery, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER linked to rare eye inflammation...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/pfizer-covid-19-vaccine-linked-to-rare-cases-of-eye-inflammation-study-675839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-one people developed anterior uveitis and two developed Multiple Evanescent White Dot Syndrome (MEWDS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Assembly Dems support impeaching...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/majority-of-assembly-democrats-support-impeaching-gov-cuomo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Democrats in the New York State legislature’s lower chamber support impeaching Gov. Andrew Cuomo after a state Attorney General probe that found the governor is a serial sexual harass…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA considers requiring proof at restaurants, gyms, indoor sporting events...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-consider-requiring-vaccine-proof-195454496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. City Council to consider requiring that people show their vaccination status to visit indoor places such as restaurants, stores and gyms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayhem for airline travel as summer turns into 'hot mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/mayhem-airline-passengers-crew-hot-vax-summer-turns-hot-mess-n1275947</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines took aggressive moves to cut overhead costs when the pandemic hit — but experts say they overshot the mark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Alone, Silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-alone-silent-after-ag-report-as-new-york-awaits-next-move/ar-AAMWgaj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo worked in the Executive Mansion in Albany on Wednesday, avoiding news cameras that he used to seek out as Democrats continued to call for his resignation over sexual-misconduct allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE FOREIGNERS TO JAB</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210804202933-qabl9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (EXCLUSIVE, URGENT):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. developing plan to require foreign visitors to be vaccinated -official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Giraffes highly complex social species, misunderstood...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/08/03/Britain-study-giraffes-socially-complex-species/6091628002986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giraffes are as socially complex as elephants, but their communication has been misunderstood, a new study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba Dumping Corpses in Backyards, Losing Bodies in Mass Graves...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2021/08/04/coronavirus-cuba-dumping-corpses-peoples-backyards-losing-bodies-mass-graves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent outlets published videos this week showing Cuban cemetery workers dumping suspected Chinese coronavirus victims in mass graves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Sues U.S. Gun Makers over Cartel Crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2021/08/04/mexican-government-sues-us-gun-makers-over-cartel-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government of Mexico is suing six U.S. makers, claiming "massive damage" created by "unlawful trafficking" of firearms to cartels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Fires Dozens of Employees for Data Misuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gk73/google-fired-dozens-for-data-misuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some allegations potentially center around accessing Google user or employee data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes sues MSNBC after 'spiteful' Maddow allegedly smeared him on air...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/rep-nunes-sues-msnbc-after-rachel-maddow-allegedly-smeared-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devin Nunes, 47, who has had three lawsuits against other outlets thrown out in the last year, filed the defamation lawsuit in Texas on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. comes out of hiding, announces tour dates...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/louis-c-k-announces-new-tour-dates-in-bizarre-email/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He will embark on a 24-city nationwide comedy tour, starting with gigs in New York City next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFSPRING drummer dropped from band for refusing vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/offspring-drummer-pete-parada-says-band-cut-him-loose-over-covid-19-vaccine-decision/ar-AAMWsN8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Offspring drummer Pete Parada explains why he decided against a vaccine. 'The hesitant population is not a monolithic group,' he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State spending billions to house homeless in hotels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-california-coronavirus-pandemic-835c2091c63c199d397346a497e7ae49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — When homeless outreach workers first visited her encampment under a Los Angeles highway overpass last fall, Veronica Perez was skeptical of their offer of not just a bed, but a furnished apartment complete with meals, counseling and the promise of some stability in her life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
