<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Wealth Tax Rakes in Cash as Covid Stokes Global Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/swiss-wealth-tax-rakes-cash-050000510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Switzerland’s wealth tax offers a rare real-world example of how a levy on assets can work, just as such ideas gain traction elsewhere in the wake of the coronavirus crisis.The measure forces residents in one of the world’s richest nations to tally the value of their investments, real estate, cars, fine art, Bitcoin, and even beehives and cows. A percentage is then skimmed off by cantonal governments, varying in size and method depending on the canton. Switzerland, among only a handful of countries with the levy, can make a claim that it has the most effective one.With the Covid-19 fallout causing government debt to swell, and hurting poorer people most, wealth taxes are being debated from California to the U.K. as a tool both to pay down debt and address inequality. U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren, Nobel laureate Joseph Stiglitz and economist Thomas Piketty are among proponents.Criticisms range from the view that it’s wrong to target assets accumulated through income that is already taxed, to more practical questions of how to fairly operate such a levy. The Swiss don’t seem to be very bothered by all of that.“It works for us,” said Stefan Kaufmann, a farmer from Wetzikon in the canton of Zurich, who describes the policy as a good Swiss compromise. “The wealth tax isn’t a lot. It doesn’t hurt.”On the final day of each year, Kaufmann -- who sits on the town’s local legislature for the nationalist Swiss People’s Party -- counts up his livestock and enters the totals on a tax return with the rest of his assets. His 50 bulls are worth about 2,000 francs ($2,239) each, according to the rules. His two donkeys are 500 francs a pop.Kaufmann’s untroubled attitude is common. Switzerland’s cantonal wealth tax just isn’t as emotive a matter as elsewhere. In January, a bid to cut the levy in Zug, the jurisdiction near Zurich known as a low-tax home for hedge funds and commodity giant Glencore Plc, was defeated by lawmakers.Switzerland is among very few countries left with a recurring annual wealth tax. The number of OECD countries imposing it dropped to four in 2017 from 12 in 1990.The coronavirus has prompted calls to change tack, often led by left-leaning politicians. The idea won endorsement from Germany’s Social Democrats, part of the ruling coalition. Argentina implemented a one-time wealth tax in December.“A lot of European countries have tried wealth taxes, certainly wealth taxes on an annual basis, and they’ve almost inevitably retreated from it because it’s highly complicated,” U.K. Conservative lawmaker Mel Stride told Times Radio on Monday. A one-off wealth tax is “nearer the end of the spectrum of the possible.”The most common riposte to the policy, also in Switzerland, is that it hits citizens again after they’ve already paid dues on their incomes.Christian Frey, deputy head of finances and taxes at pro-business group economiesuisse, says it particularly hurts some company owners, who face having to withdraw money from firms to pay the levy, suffering dividend tax in the process.“It’s an additional burden,” Frey said.Another criticism is that rich people can avoid it by shifting jurisdiction, just as Elon Musk announced his departure from California, the U.S. state with the highest income tax.Switzerland’s rationale is the constitutional principle of everyone paying according to their means. Inheritance tax is low, and there’s no capital gains levy on movable property such as equities.The measure also comes with safeguards. There’s a formula to ensure people who are asset-rich but with low incomes can still afford it. In Kaufmann’s case, the farmers’ association sets the valuation of livestock annually to help keep filing simple.The result is that Switzerland derives a bigger share of total tax revenue from the levy than any other industrialized country, according to OECD data.That’s not to say its effectiveness is unimpeachable. A study by University of Lausanne economics Professor Marius Bruelhart found that a cut in the wealth tax rate in Lucerne was followed by a rise in declared assets, hinting at prior evasion.Whatever the case, Switzerland appears comfortable with the policy.“It takes some of the tension out of that political debate around tax between the haves and the have-nots,” said David Wigersma, a Lausanne-based partner at Deloitte SA.(Updates with U.K. lawmaker in 10th paragraph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal courts demand double masking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wearing-2-masks-required-to-enter-federal-courthouses-in-ny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll need to double mask to go inside federal courthouses in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minor League Baseball Disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/minor-league-baseball-watch-2021-6121f637-4e7a-446c-995b-3ae79ec77132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Minor League Baseball starts its 2021 season, there will be 25% fewer teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION to Sue MYPILLOW Lindell...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dominion-says-it-will-sue-mypillow-ceo-mike-lindell-over-election-fraud-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominion sent letters to Lindell in December and January demanding that he retract false claims about their machines, instead the MyPillow CEO doubled down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit TV News Anchor Dies Day After Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/02/16/former-detroit-tv-anchor-dies-one-day-after-taking-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karen Hudson-Samuels’ career in broadcast journalism spanned over four decades in Detroit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bipartisan' earmarks come back...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/earmarks-coming-back-congress-469131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appropriators hope to recast the politically taboo spending practice as funding for “community projects."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please don't rush the border, White House asks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/16/white-house-asks-asylum-seekers-not-to-rush-the-us-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Tuesday urged potential Central American asylum seekers not to rush the US-Mexico border as President Biden ends former President Donald Trump’s “Remain in Mexico&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Star Dismisses Accusations Against Him as 'Recovered Memories'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-times-reporter-donald-mcneil-201006181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Torgovnik/GettyThe veteran New York Times reporter who resigned following reports that he said the “n-word” during a 2019 trip with students has privately dismissed the high-schoolers’ claims in an email obtained and reviewed by The Daily Beast.“I’m amazed at what's happening. I feel like I’m facing students ‘recovered memories’ from two years ago,” Donald McNeil Jr. wrote in the email sent this week to close friends. “And other papers are eating it up. I said ‘racism is over?’ Huh?”He continued: “I said ‘ghetto’? I don't think I’ve said ‘ghetto’ except 1. about Warsaw or 2. ironically, with air quotes, since Elvis released that ridiculous song in 1969. A teenager ‘corrected’ me and was upset that I failed to apologize to her/him? I don’t even know how to respond to that. Somehow I think I’d remember it if it had happened.”The note was sent following a report from Times media columnist Ben Smith, in which Sophie Shepherd, a student on the 2019 trip, recounted several uncomfortable conversations she had with McNeil.In one allegation, which McNeil referenced in his private email, Shepherd recalled the reporter saying: “It’s frustrating, because Black Americans keep blaming the system, but racism is over, there’s nothing against them anymore—they can get out of the ghetto if they want to.”Star NY Times Reporter Accused of Using ‘N-Word,’ Making Other Racist CommentsEarlier this month, McNeil, who’d become one of the most prominent American journalists covering the coronavirus pandemic, left the paper after The Daily Beast reported that several students complained that he made racist and offensive remarks, including saying the “n-word,” while accompanying the high-schoolers on a Times-sponsored trip to Peru.In public, the longtime reporter has stayed largely mum on the allegations. But following his resignation he joked in a note to friends and family that he “always knew my big mouth would be me into trouble one day.”And in a separate email to Times colleagues announcing his departure, he directly apologized for saying the “n-word,” and attempted to explain how the word came up during a conversation about one student’s classmate who’d been suspended for a video in which she used the racial slur.“To understand what was in the video, I asked if she had called someone else the slur or whether she was rapping or quoting a book title,” McNeil wrote. “In asking the question, I used the slur itself. I should not have done that. Originally, I thought the context in which I used this ugly word could be defended.”McNeil’s departure, and the way in which the paper wavered on how much “intent” matters in his case, set off a heated debate inside the paper. Numerous staffers called for additional investigation into the trip, while top editors attempted to assuage the concerns of prominent employees who were alarmed by the student complaints against McNeil, and by the paper’s initial handling of the ordeal.And while current and former staffers at the Times have been hoping the media conversation around McNeil’s departure will eventually subside, the science writer has other plans.In this week’s email, he told friends he has been “writing out long answers to everything” which he promised to have finished by March 1—the same day he is due to leave the Times.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France passes anti-radicalism bill that worries Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/polygamy-radicalism-secularism-elections-france-cbee2c916aa8c35380562277f0025c2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Lawmakers in the French parliament's lower house on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a bill that would strengthen oversight of mosques, schools and sports clubs to safeguard France...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas at One U.S. Hub Trading at $999. Last Week It Was $4...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/gas-one-u-hub-trading-173155074.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A polar blast in the central U.S. has pushed natural gas prices at one trading hub up 24,000% from a week ago.Supply for next-day delivery at the Oneok Gas Transportation hub in Oklahoma traded at $999 per million British thermal units for two contracts on Tuesday, according to David Hoy, a trader at Dynasty Power in Calgary. That compares with $4.19 a week earlier.Gas at the Henry Hub in Louisiana, the benchmark for futures in New York, traded at $19 at about 11:45 a.m. in New York after earlier soaring to $30, Hoy said. Supply at the hub traded at $3.24 a week ago.Production of gas in the Lower 48 states has plummeted to a three-year low as frigid weather triggers blackouts and causes liquids to freeze inside pipes, forcing wells and processing plants to shut. Underpinning the rally is the prospect of tighter inventories by the end of the winter as heating demand soars. Liquefied natural gas export terminals shut or curtailed operations amid a disaster declaration in Texas.“It’s a shocking situation,” said Cody Moore, head of gas and power trading at Mercuria Energy America LLC. “It’s chaos. It’s crazy with the prices.”Gas futures also rose, though they didn’t fully reflect the turmoil in the day-ahead market. Contracts for March delivery rose 10% to a three-month high before settling up 7.5% at $3.129.The spread between March and April futures -- essentially a bet on how well supplied the market will be at the end of winter -- rose to the highest since November.The cold ravaging the central U.S. should persist for days to come, with temperatures from South Dakota to Texas remaining well below average at least through Saturday, according to private forecaster Commodity Weather Group.“With bitterly cold air dropping all the way down to the Gulf Coast, the natural gas market is experiencing some of its most chaotic conditions ever,” Andy Weissman, chief executive officer of EBW AnalyticsGroup, said in a note to clients. “Massive amounts of production are offline, but so is a huge number of gas-fired power plants.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOURNALISM: Kudlow Caught on FOXNEWS Hot Mic Berating Kamala Harris...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/bullsht-fox-news-hot-mic-catches-larry-kudlow-raging-at-kamala-harris-for-claim-about-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump economic adviser Larry Kudlow was caught on a hot-mic profanely screaming about Vice President Kamala Harris' recent comments on the federal government's vaccine distribution plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Ending Use Of Term 'Illegal Alien'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/hamedaleaziz/illegal-alien-uscis-biden-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigrants and advocates say it represents a shift away from “dehumanizing” language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA opens mass vax sites...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fema-opens-mass-vaccination-sites-4cd95c115ac455169b63ae109d179f4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEMA opened its first COVID-19 mass vaccination sites Tuesday, setting up in Los Angeles and Oakland as part of an effort by the Biden administration to get shots into arms more quickly and reach...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cuomo Aide Is Top Candidate to Replace CNN Zucker...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/media/zucker-lieutenant-top-candidate-replace-cnns-helm-rcna287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allison Gollust, a CNN executive and top lieutenant to Jeff Zucker, has emerged as the leading internal candidate to take over the network if Zucker steps down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai princess claims being held 'hostage' in new videos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/16/dubai-princess-says-she-is-being-held-hostage-in-new-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Latifa Al Maktoum made the whispered pleas for help in a series of clandestine videos recorded on a phone that was smuggled to her in her villa “prison” in the Kingdom, the Fre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain betting on vaccine passports to revive summer visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-spain-tourism/spain-betting-on-vaccine-passports-to-revive-summer-tourism-idUSKBN2AG2CW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain hopes the introduction of vaccination passports combined with pre-travel COVID-19 testing will allow British tourists to return to Spanish destinations this summer, a tourism ministry source told Reuters on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black church having a moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/16/us/black-church-pew-pbs-moment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pew is publishing a major study on African Americans' attitudes towards religion on Tuesday, the same day PBS premieres a two-part special on the history of the Black church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printed in days, a house: 3D printing hits next level...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tech-3d-printed-house/printed-in-days-a-house-new-york-firm-takes-3d-printing-to-the-next-level-idUSKBN2AG2CA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most homes are built block by block, or brick by brick. But a demo house in Calverton, New York, was constructed scan by scan - its walls made using a giant three-dimensional printer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle woman, 90, walks 6 miles through snow for jab...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seattle-storms-coronavirus-pandemic-2527c61138a14a5229c03bd221419196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A rare winter storm that dumped a foot of snow on Seattle couldn’t keep a 90-year-old woman from her first appointment for the coronavirus vaccine. The Seattle Times reports...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th wave looms if USA fails to contain variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/02/16/covid-19-us-fourth-wave-variants-coronavirus/4460958001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts urge continued vigilance against the spread of coronavirus variants as some state officials lift mask mandates and ease restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA restricts edits...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/wikipedia-lincoln-project-edits-john-weaver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wikipedia is classifying The Lincoln Project's page on its site as "semi-protected," meaning many users are restricted from editing the page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners At Firm Hired to 'Review' Scandal Are Donors...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/paul-hastings-lincoln-project/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Hastings, the law firm hired to conduct a "comprehensive review" of the Lincoln Project's "operations and culture," could be hard-pressed to deliver a credible result given several of its senior partners have donated to the scandal-plagued super PAC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates: All rich countries should move to 100% synthetic beef!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/16/bill-gates-all-rich-countries-should-move-to-100-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft cofounder Bill Gates said in a new interview that all rich countries should transition to 100% synthetic beef in order to significantly curb the greenhouse-gas emissions driving climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Escape Confines of Time, Space According to CIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7k9qag/how-to-escape-the-confines-of-time-and-space-according-to-the-cia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 80s, the spy agency investigated the "Gateway Experience" technique to alter consciousness and ultimately escape spacetime. Here is everything you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing off limits' in Oprah interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14064983/meghan-markle-prince-harry-determined-not-upset-queen-oprah-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE will be “nothing off limits” in Meghan Markle’s sit down interview with Oprah, Gayle King said today. The Duke and Duchess of Sussex will appear in a bombshell 90-minute spe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA reports back-to back days of more than 1 million travelers over Presidents' Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/TSA-reports-back-to-back-days-of-more-than-1-15954004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two days in a row over the holiday weekend, the Transportation Security...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echos rhetoric from the 1930s...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/spain-probes-anti-semitic-speech-at-neo-nazi-rally-01613495105?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in Madrid on Tuesday said they had opened an investigation into anti-Semitic comments made at a neo-Nazi rally held at the weekend which drew ire from Spain's Jewish community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain probes anti-Semitic speech at neo-Nazi rally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-media-social-media-barcelona-crime-9babe2c97e7be859f139789be3a0ea22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Prosecutors in Spain have launched two separate investigations involving a far-right party and extremist neo-Nazi sympathizers for possible hate crimes against Muslims and Jews,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID FADING AWAY?  India's dramatic fall in cases leaves experts stumped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-dramatic-fall-coronavirus-cases-199585f8d5cb023abe241c4c463d88ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — When the coronavirus pandemic took hold in India, there were fears it would sink the fragile health system of the world’s second-most populous country. Infections climbed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside chilling torture dungeons run by Putin-backed sadist 'The Maniac'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14027442/ukrainian-basement-torture-cells-putin-the-maniac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORTURE dungeons where victims are mutilated with surgical tools, beaten with hammers and shocked with electricity are being run by Putin’s thugs in war-torn Ukraine, civil rights groups clai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare snow blankets Acropolis!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-athens-greece-be193363451279cc4d105d025d0fb2b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Heavy snowfall blanketed the Acropolis and other ancient monuments in Athens and halted COVID-19 vaccinations in the Greek capital Tuesday as the weather brought many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle meeting with Newsom sparks talk about her political potential...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/meghan-markle-s-meeting-with-gov-newsom-sparks-talk-about-her-political-potential/article_82df15c1-05a0-5407-9fb3-10e2e784b326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle may be pretty busy these days, expecting her second child with Prince Harry while handling the demands of her new career as a philanthropist, Netflix producer, Spotify podcaster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'ALLEN V. FARROW' Horrifying Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/allen-v-farrow-horrifying-indictment-150000019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBOWarning: Graphic descriptions of alleged child sexual abuse.As Judge Elliott Wilk, who presided over the shocking custody case between Mia Farrow and Woody Allen in New York State Supreme Court concluded, “We will probably never know what occurred on August 4, 1992.” But the new four-part documentary series Allen v. Farrow makes a thoroughly convincing argument that Allen indeed molested his 7-year-old daughter, Dylan Farrow, that fateful day in their Connecticut home. Premiering Feb. 21 on HBO, the shot-in-secret series took three years to make, and comes from the directorial team of Kirby Dick and Amy Ziering, who most recently helmed On the Record, a powerful documentary highlighting the brave women—Drew Dixon, Sil Lai Abrams, Sheri Sher, and others—who came forward with allegations of abuse against hip-hop mogul Russell Simmons. Seven years ago, I reported on the findings of the custody case between Farrow and Allen, researching all the documents I could find, and conducted an awkward interview with Allen during the press tour for his film Magic in the Moonlight in which he dodged questions about the Farrow allegations until his publicist threatened to end the interview.But what Dick, Ziering, and their producing partner Amy Herdy have accomplished here is far more exhaustive, featuring internal documents as well as interviews with Dylan, Mia, and Ronan Farrow, members of the Previn clan, a number of family friends, officials involved in the cases, and childcare experts, all of whom echo the other portion of Judge Wilk’s ruling, “That Mr. Allen’s behavior toward Dylan was grossly inappropriate and that measures must be taken to protect her.”Mariel Hemingway Reckons With Mental Health, Woody Allen, and ‘Manhattan’: ‘I Was a Kid’ According to then-partner Mia Farrow, it was Allen who’d suggested the family adopt a cute blond girl—and so Farrow adopted six-month-old Dylan in 1985. Almost immediately, Allen is said to have developed an obsession with Dylan. She recalls him constantly “hovering” around her, explaining, “I was always in his clutches. He was always hunting me.” Casey Pascal, a close family friend, would bring her kids over but “there was no point” because Allen would always go off with her; Priscilla Gilman, Dylan’s friend at the time, remembers how Allen “followed Dylan wherever she went,” and would often be caught standing nearby silently watching her. “He would come, and she would run away from the door, and say, ‘Hide me! Hide me! At first, I thought it was like a game, but then I realized she actually sensed this kind of smothering energy from him,” Gilman says in the film.Around this time, Dylan would start locking herself in bathrooms. Her family describes how a once-effervescent and talkative girl became incredibly withdrawn, resembling “a dead animal.”Allen’s behavior toward Dylan became increasingly affectionate and, Mia and others maintain, began crossing the line into creepy, as Allen would allegedly cuddle with Farrow in bed in their underwear. “I remember sitting on the edge of his bed. The light in the room, the satin sheets,” says Dylan. “I have memories of getting into bed with him. He was in his underwear, and I’m in my underwear cuddling. I remember his breath on me. He would just wrap his body around me very intimately.“The first time that I saw it, I was coming into the room and he was getting out of the bed, and so I saw that he was only wearing underwear,” adds Gilman. “And I just kind of turned around and walked the other way, because I didn’t want him to know that I had seen it.”Mia Farrow recounts how Allen would “kneel in front of [Dylan] or sit next to her and put his face in her lap, which I caught a couple of times, and I didn’t think it was right.” Her sister Tisa Farrow offers even more damning testimony, revealing that during a visit to their Connecticut country home in the summer, as the young kids were running around naked by the beach, “Mia handed Woody a thing of sunscreen to put on, and he was rubbing Dylan’s back… His hand went down between her buttocks and kind of lingered there and suggestively—I have to say suggestively, because that’s what it was—went between her buttocks’ cheeks with his finger and then came back. And Mia saw it too and snatched the sunscreen away.”Allen also apparently had a habit of having Dylan suck on his thumb. “I remember sitting on the steps with him in the country house. There was nobody else around, and he was directing me on how to suck his thumb—telling me what to do with my tongue, and I think that lasted a while. It felt like a long time,” Dylan says in the film. “I saw her sucking his thumb, which was really, really weird. He said, this helps her, this calms her down,” adds Priscilla.We are shown home video footage of young Dylan, in a diaper, with her hand resting on the inside of Allen’s thigh. Inside the Shocking Custody Case Court Documents that Shed Light on the Dylan Farrow-Woody Allen Saga Due to all the strange behavior, Mia says she eventually confronted Allen about it, and he became enraged. Still, Mia couldn’t believe that the man she loved, her life partner and collaborator, was a pedophile. So, she had Allen see a clinical psychologist concerning his behavior with Dylan, who subsequently determined that Allen was being “inappropriately intense” with Dylan, but that it “wasn’t sexual.” In light of that, Mia said she let Allen formally adopt Dylan and Moses, a young boy Mia had adopted from Korea, since she felt he was her “life’s partner.”Allen v. Farrow makes the case that Allen has a predilection for young women. In addition to clips of his films, often pairing older men with barely of-age women, the docuseries features Christina Englehardt, the supposed inspiration for Mariel Hemingway’s character in Manhattan, who met Allen when she was 16, and says the two became romantic when she turned 17 (“It’s taken a toll on how I’ve been in relationships,” she maintains of Allen). There are the Woody Allen Papers at Princeton University—a comprehensive archive of letters, scripts, and papers by Allen, that journalist Richard Morgan examined for The Washington Post. “The thing that kept on showing up was this sort of focus he had on very young women,” he reveals.And then there is the matter of Mia’s adopted daughter Soon-Yi. When Mia famously found a stack of nude Polaroid pictures of Soon-Yi—then a college freshman—on Allen’s nightstand, the family was thrown into chaos, with all the children siding against Allen. “My opinion of him changed completely. He went from a father figure to a person who is a predator who we have to keep out of the house and protect ourselves from,” attests Fletcher Previn, Mia’s child from a previous marriage who was partially raised by Allen.The film intimates that Allen “groomed” Soon-Yi over a period of years, and that his sexual interest in her may have actually began when she was in high school, providing the following carefully worded text:Allen claims his relationship with Soon-Yi began after her first semester of college in December 1991. According to court testimony, their relationship had begun years earlier. Both Allen’s doorman and the building maintenance man testified in court to having seen Soon-Yi visit Allen dozens of times during her junior and senior years in high school. Allen’s housekeeper testified she found what she believed to be semen stains on the sheets and condom wrappers in the wastebasket after Soon-Yi’s visits, while Soon-Yi was still in high school.“I remember my mom told me and Ronan, ‘Daddy took naked pictures of Soon-Yi.’ And that was sort of the first instance where I thought, ‘Oh… it’s not just me,’” says Dylan.Still, Dylan claims that she could not yet bring herself to come forward about Allen’s uncomfortable behavior toward her—both because she still felt it was the way fathers treated their daughters, and that she feared his wrath.“At one point, we were all sitting at the dinner table and we were eating spaghetti. And I thought I was being funny by calling him ‘Woody’ instead of ‘Daddy.’ And he was getting progressively more agitated by it,” Dylan remembers. “And he grabs me by the back of my neck and shoves my face down into my plate of hot spaghetti, and that was sort of when I realized that that’s what happens if I say no. Doing what he says is the only way to protect myself.”Then came the alleged incident on Aug. 4, 1992, which Dylan says changed everything.That day was a rather busy one at the Farrow-Allen home in Connecticut. Casey Pascal’s children were over, along with their babysitter, Allison Stickland; Mia’s babysitter, Kristi Groteke, was around to watch over her flock; and Sophie Berge, Dylan and Ronan’s French tutor, was also there. Not long after Mia and Casey went off to the store, Berge says that Allen arrived. But then, according to Berge and Groteke, Allen and Dylan went missing for “about 20 minutes.” When Mia returns, she notices that Dylan isn’t wearing any underwear.The next morning, Mia received a disturbing call from Pascal. “I called Mia and said, ‘Allison said that she saw Dylan sitting on the couch with Woody kneeling on the floor with his head buried in her lap. And she said that she felt that she had walked in on a very adult situation, and she realized that it was a child—it was a child she was seeing. And she was horrified to the core. She said Dylan was staring off into space, and Woody’s face was in her lap,” Pascal says in the film. Woody Allen holding Dylan Farrow, and other members of the Previn-Farrow clan HBO An alarmed Mia asked Dylan if that had happened, and she said yes. Then, since Dylan’s therapist was away for the summer, Mia decided to make a video of 7-year-old Dylan discussing what she says had happened with Allen. Clips from the grainy home video, dated Aug. 5, 1992, are shown in Allen v. Farrow, and they are incredibly upsetting. In the video, Mia can be heard asking Dylan what happened that day, and she replies, “We went into your room, and we went into the attic. Then he started telling me weird things. Then secret he went into the attic [inaudible] went behind me and touched my privates.” When Mia asks where Allen touched her, she points to her vaginal area. “Well, when I was in the attic, he said, ‘Do not move. I have to do this.’ But I wiggled my bum, to see what he was doing, he said, ‘Don’t move, I have to do this! So if you stay still, then um… we can go to Paris,” Dylan remarks later on in the video.“We were in the TV room, and he reached behind me and he touched my butt. And then he told me to come up to the attic with him,” recalls a present-day Dylan in the film. “I remember laying there on my stomach and my back was to him, so I couldn’t see what was going on. I felt trapped. He was saying things like, ‘We’re gonna go to Paris together. You’re gonna be in all my movies.’ Then he sexually assaulted me. And I remember just focusing on my brother’s train set. And then… he just stopped. He was done. And we just went downstairs.”Mia brought Dylan to their pediatrician the following day, and Dylan told him what had happened. The doctor then, unbeknownst to Mia, reported it to the police. Shortly thereafter, both the NYC Child Welfare Administration and the Connecticut State Police opened investigations into the alleged child sexual assault at the hands of Allen.Each episode of Allen v. Farrow ends with the text, “Woody Allen denies ever having been violent or sexually abusive with Dylan. He also denies ever having been sexually inappropriate with any teenaged girl.”Following the news of the investigations into his alleged child sexual abuse, Allen decides to hold a packed press conference at the Plaza Hotel in Manhattan, where he declares his love for Soon-Yi and argues that Farrow concocted the Dylan abuse story to get back at him for it. Then, Allen unleashed a press blitz, appearing on 60 Minutes and the covers of Time, Newsweek, and People magazines, to hammer home his side of the story and drown out Dylan and Mia’s. And the press were all too ready to side with the filmmaker over Mia, who fought to keep the matter private for the safety of her children. Allen is also accused of having a team of private investigators trail the Farrow clan—scaring the kids—in search of any possible dirt that would help their case.The few journalists who weren’t complicit in Allen’s PR campaign were women, including Maureen Orth of Vanity Fair, whose piece detailing the Farrows’ side didn’t make the cover of the magazine, though she did find out that Allen had refused to submit to Connecticut State Police’s polygraph test, and instead opted for a private polygraph by a hired calligrapher. Meanwhile, a news report at the time by Rosanna Scotto of local Fox 5 NY alleges, “Here at the Episcopal School on Manhattan’s East Side, sources tell us exclusively that Woody Allen was so obsessed with Dylan, who was then 3 years old, that parents and teachers began talking about how Allen would sit in the doorway, positioned, to watch Dylan in the classroom.”Allen v. Farrow also contains a series of taped phone calls (by Mia) between Mia and Allen, since the two were taping each other’s calls during this period. In one eye-opening exchange, Mia pleads with Allen to tell her what happened the day of Aug. 4. “If I have a shred of belief left in you, then help me now. Tell me where you were for those 20 minutes,” she asks, her voice cracking in distress. “All the details when the time comes…” replies Allen, rather ominously.When Mia presses again and again as to why he can’t just tell her where he was, he coolly repeats it: “All the details when the time comes, and the truth will come out.”Over the years, Allen’s defenders have often cited the report by the Yale New Haven Child Abuse Sex Clinic, which was commissioned by Connecticut state prosecutor Frank Maco. The team overseeing Dylan’s case was led by John Leventhal, who was joined by social workers Julia Hamilton and Jennifer Sawyer. The New Haven report ultimately contended there were “inconsistencies” in Dylan’s story; that she had “difficulty distinguishing fantasy from reality”; and that the allegations “were likely reinforced and encouraged by her mother who was enraged with Mr. Allen.” Without informing Maco, the team notified Farrow and Allen of the results, which allowed Allen to then hold a rather tasteless victory-lap press conference outside of the New Haven hospital. In Allen v. Farrow, a number of childcare professionals—from child psychologists to case workers—break down the New Haven report, and find a number of perceived oddities, including the fact that Hamilton and Sawyer interviewed Dylan a staggering nine times over the course of three months—unheard of for an alleged victim of child sexual abuse. “The more I was asked the same question over and over, the more I started to wonder: What do they want from me?” says Dylan in the film. “And feeling like the more I said the same thing, it was the wrong answer. Like, I was being treated like I was lying.” Mia Farrow and Dylan Farrow attend 2016 Time 100 Gala, Time's Most Influential People In The World red carpet at Jazz At Lincoln Center at the Times Warner Center on April 26, 2016, in New York City. Dimitrios Kambouris/Getty The New Haven report also reasoned that Dylan was “delusional” because she would occasionally refer to “the magical hour,” a phrase she’d commonly heard on film sets, and called mannequins “dead heads,” which both seemed like reasonable descriptions for a 7-year-old. Furthermore, in another head-scratcher, Hamilton and Sawyer decided to destroy all of their contemporaneous notes.As for the NYC Child Welfare Administration, investigator Sheryl Harden assigned the case to Paul Williams, a star employee who’d been awarded “Caseworker of the Year” by the City of New York. Williams found Dylan to be credible, and per his contemporaneous notes—which were obtained by the filmmakers—concluded that there was sufficient evidence to open up a case of child sexual abuse against Woody Allen, and included an exchange with Sawyer where she told Williams that she “believes Dylan.” But then Williams was mysteriously fired for “insubordination,” causing the case to die. When Williams’ firing was contested, a judge determined that Williams shouldn’t have been fired, reinstated him, and awarded him backpay.“In the end, the result was that people with power were able to get the case removed,” Gloria Steinem, who supported Williams’ case, says in the film. “It just seemed to me, like everything I could glean as a reporter, to be a case of great injustice.”Harden, who appears in Allen v. Farrow, was so disgusted with the process that she quit the NYC Child Welfare Administration about a year after the Dylan case.Just when it looked as though Allen might get away scot-free, the show alleges that his vindictiveness took hold and he decided to sue Farrow for custody of their children. The child-custody trial in New York State Supreme Court dealt several blows to Allen’s credibility, as Allen claimed he was never alone with Dylan on Aug. 4—testimony that was contradicted by babysitters Groteke and Stickland, as well as French tutor Sophie Berge. Stickland testified that “Dylan was sitting upright on the couch and Woody was kneeling directly in front of her with his face in Dylan’s lap… His face was very close to her private area.” Mia’s videos of Dylan discussing Allen’s alleged abuse were entered into evidence in the trial, while Judge Wilk poured cold water on the New Haven report, saying, “The unavailability of the notes, together with their unwillingness to testify at this trial except through the deposition of Dr. Leventhal, compromised my ability to scrutinize their findings and resulted in a report which was sanitized and, therefore, less credible.” Judge Wilk ruled that Farrow was “a caring and loving mother”; that there was “no credible evidence to support Mr. Allen’s contention that Ms. Farrow coached Dylan”; and that “Mr. Allen’s behavior toward Dylan was grossly inappropriate and that measures must be taken to protect her… It is unclear whether Mr. Allen will ever develop the insight and judgment necessary for him to relate to Dylan appropriately.” Allen was ordered to pay Farrow’s $1 million in legal fees, and to only be allowed to meet with Dylan during supervised visits. Woody Allen attends the Midnight In Paris photocall at the Palais des Festivals during the 64th Cannes Film Festival on May 11, 2011, in Cannes, France. Pascal Le Segretain/Getty The Connecticut State Police investigation, meanwhile, discovered that Allen was inconsistent about whether he’d ever been in the attic with Dylan, and three childcare specialists from separate agencies found that Dylan’s testimony was “consistent,” “honest,” and believed “the victim was telling the truth.” The investigators concluded that “an arrest warrant be issued for the accused” on the charges of 1st- and 4th-degree sexual assault of a minor. But Maco declined to file charges against Allen out of a concern for young Dylan’s safety. “My concern was the further traumatization of the child,” Maco says in the film. “She had already been through so much. Was it truly in her best interest to put her on the stand?”In addition to the media, Allen v. Farrow points a finger at Hollywood for continuing to support Allen and strengthen his mystique. There’s footage of Allen receiving a standing ovation at the 2002 Academy Awards, and a montage of A-list actors who worked with Allen after 1992 singing his praises, from Scarlett Johansson and Javier Bardem to Penelope Cruz. Then there was Emma Stone, who presented a lifetime achievement honor to Allen at the 2014 Golden Globes, which was accepted by Diane Keaton on his behalf. Dylan, Mia, and Ronan looked on in horror as Hollywood continued to celebrate a man they saw as a monster.In 2014, after her brother Ronan tweeted about the molestation allegation during those Golden Globes, Dylan says that she submitted an op-ed to both the Los Angeles Times and The New York Times. The Los Angeles Times rejected Dylan’s essay, as did The New York Times’ op-ed page, so Ronan went to his family friend Nicholas Kristof, who was allowed to publish it on his New York Times blog (the Times’ op-ed page opted instead for Allen’s lengthy rebuttal).“I am that little girl on the tape,” Dylan shares in the film. “So… it’s a very vulnerable part of me, and a very… a very hurt part of me. There’s a lot of… That little girl is in a lot of pain.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: LINCOLN PROJECT founders knew about sex allegations in March...</title>
      <link>https://19thnews.org/2021/02/lincoln-project-founders-march/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;19thnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelation comes as the political group’s domestic and international associates cut ties, including an Israeli prime ministerial hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAACP files litigation against The Don, Giuliani...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/naacp-trump-giuliani-capitol-riots-469077</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit claims that the former president and his personal lawyer violated the Ku Klux Klan Act by conspiring with white supremacist groups to incite the insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN: NASA Mars rover aims for dicey landing to search for ancient life...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/nasa-e2-80-99s-mars-rover-perseverance-aims-for-dicey-landing-to-search-for-ancient-life/ar-BB1dJbcQ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: World's first flying car that can travel 100mph cleared for take-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/cars/worlds-first-flying-car-can-23509563</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Terrafugia Transition 'roadable aircraft' has been given the all-clear by the Federal Aviation Authority in the USA. It's the world's first flying car</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman sues Trump over role in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-joe-biden-donald-trump-lawsuits-presidential-elections-7eb83edae942014d4a6e4a047ef641a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Democratic congressman accused Donald Trump in a federal lawsuit on Tuesday of inciting the deadly insurrection at the U.S. Capitol and of conspiring with his lawyer and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists from all over world flocking Mexico nudist paradise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nudist-mexican-paradise-zipolite-is-great-business-for-tourism-but-bad-for-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists from all over the world are flocking to the Oaxacan coast, but some locals worry they will be the ones paying a price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shot at Dubai? Saudi's ultimatum to pull global HQs into kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/16/targeting-dubai-saudi-arabias-ultimatum-to-pull-hq-offices-to-kingdom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What began as a pitch for investment from international head offices appears to have become something much more aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G phones may interfere with aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/5g-phones-may-interfere-aircraft-131736200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest generation of smartphones, 5G, can interfere with aircraft altitude instruments, the French Civil Aviation Authority warned Tuesday as it recommended they should be turned off during flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48 hours of border chaos: Inside CBP crackdown on Iranian Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/customs-border-protection-iranian-americans-468851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the U.S. killed a top Iranian general in 2020, it stopped and held 277 people — dozens of them American citizens or legal permanent residents — at the border during “heightened security measures.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL, CA took opposite approaches -- with same result...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9262397/How-California-Florida-took-different-approaches-ended-result.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historically, Florida has had 8,306 cases and 117 deaths per 100,000 residents and California has had about 8,499 cases per 100,000 residents and 130 deaths per 100,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: Biden confronts leadership moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/16/politics/joe-biden-coronavirus-vaccine-schools/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exhausted and impatient nation needs the kind of clarity and leadership only a president can provide as the coronavirus pandemic reaches a potentially decisive stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of his followers being sought by FBI. It's not stopping leader of Oath Keepers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/15/politics/capitol-riot-oath-keepers-stewart-rhodes-soh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is investigating some of his followers. Others are already in custody and facing decades in prison if convicted of federal charges connected to the January 6 insurrection at the US Capitol. But the national leader of the extremist Oath Keepers group is carrying on as before. He might even be emboldened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico eyes biometric phone registry, sparking privacy fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-telecoms-focus-idUSKBN2AG1AK?taid=602bc450a77dbd00013d27fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plan by Mexican lawmakers to put millions of cell phone users' data in a biometric registry, billed as a tool to fight kidnapping and extortion, has sparked a backlash from telecoms companies and rights groups who warn it could lead to stolen data and higher costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK plan for campus free speech champion draws praise, alarm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/higher-education-9ec7da0e825e16b7570afa3d12d9bf13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The British government said Tuesday it will appoint a “free speech champion” for universities to protect against attempts to silence academics and speakers with unpopular...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin breaks $50,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/16/bitcoin-btc-price-hits-50000-for-the-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin's price broke above $50,000 for the first time in history Tuesday, continuing its blistering rally as major companies appear to be warming to cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Inflation Deepens...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-pay-more-meat-food-050000496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- There are signs that the food inflation that’s gripped the world over the past year, raising prices of everything from shredded cheese to peanut butter, is about to get worse.The Covid-19 pandemic upended food supply chains, paralyzing shipping, sickening workers that keep the world fed and ultimately raising consumer grocery costs around the globe last year. Now farmers -- especially ones raising cattle, hogs and poultry -- are getting squeezed by the highest corn and soybean prices in seven years. It’s lifted the costs of feeding their herds by 30% or more. To stay profitable, producers including Tyson Foods Inc. are increasing prices, which will ripple through supply chains and show up in the coming months as higher price tags for beef, pork and chicken around the world.Feed prices “go up and down, and you tend to take the rough with the smooth,” said Mark Gorton, managing director at the British chicken and turkey producer Traditional Norfolk Poultry. “But when it rallies as much as it has, it starts to impact massively on the business.”The last time grains were this expensive was after the U.S. drought of 2012, and meat prices saw a dramatic run-up. Now, meat is again poised to become a driver of global food inflation, and part of the intensifying debate over the path of overall inflation and exactly what central banks and policymakers should do to aid economies still working to recover from the pandemic.Vaccinations promising a return to normal life and fiscal stimulus programs amounting to trillions of dollars are already expected to unleash pent-up demand and drive a surge in consumer prices. U.S. and European bond markets are sending signals that inflation is back. Americans’ one-year inflation expectations last week rose to the highest since 2014.As for what’s driving the feed prices, that’s due to bad crop weather shrinking world harvests. Demand is also increasing. China, the biggest buyer of commodities, is scooping up record amounts of the available supplies to feed its expanding hog herds.Meat producers across major exporting countries are feeling the impact of the higher grain costs. In Brazil, the biggest poultry shipper, the cost of raising chickens jumped 39% last year due to feed, according to Embrapa, a state-owned agricultural research agency. Costs rose again last month by around 6%, said Itau BBA bank.In Europe profitability of livestock operations has plunged due to the combination of high feed expenses and stifled demand from Covid-19 lockdowns. Some smaller hog farmers may be forced to exit the market, according to Rabobank senior analyst Chenjun Pan.The United Nations’ Food &amp; Agriculture Organization said global meat prices in January climbed the fourth straight month.Since Dec. 1, corn futures in Chicago have risen 28% and soybeans 18%.Animal disease outbreaks could also push meat prices higher, with parts of Europe and Asia seeing avian influenza outbreaks. A deadly hog virus called African swine fever is still spreading in some countries after decimating Chinese herds, and recently caused a Philippine hog company to exit the industry.Shrinking HerdsMeat prices at retail grocery stores rise the most after farmers shrink their herds due to declining profits. That’s a process that takes time, which means there’s a lag between the feed-cost inflation and rising consumer prices, said Will Sawyer, animal protein economist at farm lender CoBank ACB.In the U.S., livestock and poultry operations have already started contraction due to slim profits amid the pandemic. The American hog herd in December fell 0.9% from the previous year and the cattle herd in January by 0.2%, according to government data.Cattle profits are already down. CRI Feeders in Oklahoma, a feedlot with 42,000 animals bulking up on corn, is breaking even, said co-owner Scott Anderson. Expanding drought is withering pastures and feed prices have shot up 30%.The market and weather challenges likely will prompt ranchers to scale back, according to Clayton Huseman, executive director of the Kansas Livestock Association.“Over the next couple of years, we do expect the supply to get tighter,” Huseman said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's Next Problem Could Come From People Like 'Mr. Sweepy'...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/big-tech-next-big-problem-mr-sweepy-7191120/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operator of a website called Sweepstakes Today, Mr. Sweepy — a nickname used by Craig McDaniel — says Google used its power over online advertising to bleed his website dry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid wars launch DeSantis into GOP 'top tier'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/covid-ron-desantis-2024-469071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor’s clashes with the media and reluctance to embrace coronavirus restrictions are fueling conservative chatter about a 2024 presidential bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mariachis' 'Hand of God' touches patient on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mariachis-hand-god-touches-covid-012220387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wife of an ailing Anaheim locksmith hires a band to lift his spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Soothing, Digital Rooms of YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/16/the-soothing-digital-rooms-of-youtube/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picture this: You’re in the Hogwarts library. Rain falls outside, a fire crackles across the room, and somewhere offscreen, quills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Debt Prisons...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/16/the-new-debt-prisons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While controversial calls to “defund the police” have grabbed headlines, we urgently need to examine how we fund the police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While rest of country freezes, Florida's sunny beaches overflow with crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/while-the-rest-of-the-country-freezes-floridas-sunny-beaches-overflow-with-crowds/ar-BB1dIfJV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As a massive, historic winter storm swept across the U.S. on Monday, unloading dangerous snowfall, freezing rain and piercing wind chills, South Florida’s scorching beaches served as a hot destination for hundreds of tourists and the usual crowd of locals who enjoyed the long holiday weekend by the water, despite the coronavirus pandemic. Wearing little to no masks and barely keeping ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep's family DISOWNS him:  Relatives call him 'disappointment to God' and member of 'devil's army'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9264005/Kinzinger-releases-letter-family-saying-joined-devils-army-backing-Trumps-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam Kinzinger told the New York Times he received the pejorative note just two days after he called for Trump to be removed from office following the Capitol riots on January 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Mardi Gras canceled, New Orleans residents are making their homes into floats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mardi-gras-is-canceled-so-residents-are-making-their-homes-into-floats-e2-80-98new-orleans-doesn-e2-80-99t-know-how-to-do-anything-halfway-e2-80-99/ar-BB1dGVFd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It started on Twitter: "Turn your house into a float and throw all the beads from your attic at your neighbors walking by. #mardigras2021.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media video leads police to suspect in Chihuahua's death...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/social-media-video-leads-riverside-police-to-suspect-in-chihuahuas-death/ar-BB1dHq7m?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Riverside Police Department said a call about a video of a small Chihuahua with a large laceration on its neck led to an arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians accuse Israel of blocking vaccines to Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210215-palestinians-accuse-israel-of-blocking-vaccines-to-gaza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians accuse Israel of blocking vaccines to Gaza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed in freak accident at car wash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/customer-killed-by-suv-at-queens-car-wash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 54-year-old woman was killed in a freak accident at a Queens car wash on Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donor gave millions for 'voter fraud' investigation. Now he wants his money back...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/02/15/a-republican-donor-gave-25-million-for-a-voter-fraud-investigation-he-wants-his-money-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s campaign and the Republican Party collected $255 million in two months, saying the money would support legal challenges to an election marred by fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway moves mountains to bring skiing to the people...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/norway-moves-mountains-bring-skiing-015228337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegians, the saying goes, are born with skis on their feet. But with a lack of snow and the pandemic this year leaving many in despair, authorities are bringing snow and ski trails to downtown Oslo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
