<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm brings flooding rainfall to Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-claudette-hits-gulf-coast/965344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communities near the Gulf Coast are taking the brunt of Tropical Storm Claudette with roads underwater and some homes damaged by suspected tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLCE &amp; GABBANA 'light therapy' collection celebrates life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-health-coronavirus-pandemic-arts-and-entertainment-1b19ef45352408683580b6daf411a54d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana are coaxing men off their sofas and back into the world with a resplendent collection inspired by the extravagant lighting installations of southern Italian street festivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral Rivals Team Up, Aiming to Weaken Race's Front-Runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/nyc-elections-2021/ny-nyc-andrew-yang-kathryn-garcia-mayor-campaign-trail-20210619-pwwwn5b52vftbe5ygu256qb62a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pair planned to barnstorm across the city as they seek out voters in each others strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden struggles to sell democracy abroad when it faces challenges at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-struggles-to-sell-democracy-abroad-when-it-faces-challenges-at-home/ar-AALdy15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has made promoting democracy central to his role on the world stage. That’s complicated by events in the United States stemming from falsehoods about the last election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American breaks shot put world record that stood for decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/19/sport/ryan-crouser-shot-put-world-record-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Crouser toppled the men's shot put world record on Friday with a 23.37-meter throw on the first night of the US Olympic Track and Field Trials in Eugene, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records fall as heat continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/records-fall-as-heat-wave-continues-for-fathers-day-weekend/965582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dozens and dozens of heat records fell the past week, AccuWeather forecasters say relief is on the way for some, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan City Council candidate caught with dominatrix in leaked video...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/nyc-council-candidate-caught-with-dominatrix-in-leaked-bdsm-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was filmed at Parthenon studio in Midtown — which is known for its high-quality BDSM dungeons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Challenger crew likely survived explosion before plunge to earth...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/challenger-crew-likely-survived-explosion-before-fatal-plummet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book reveals how Christa McAuliffe was chosen as the first civilian in space, and why the Challenger crew likely survived the explosion before their fateful plunge to earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ties with Gulf Arabs may hinge on nuke pact...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619153729-d2ie7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ELECTION/GULF (PIX):As Iran veers right, ties with Gulf Arabs may hinge on nuclear pact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinking straw device 'instant cure for hiccups'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/18/drinking-straw-device-is-instant-cure-for-hiccups-say-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sipping water through an L-shaped ‘suction and swallow tool’ cured 92% of attacks, according to study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Rockefeller Heir Eaten by Cannibals?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/was-this-rockefeller-heir-eaten-by-cannibals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockefeller heir Michael Rockefeller disappeared in 1961. Some believe he drowned. Others say he was eaten by cannibals. The truth may be more complex and mysterious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had pregnant women tortured?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3115267/iran-new-president-ebrahim-raisi-butcher/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRANIAN hardline cleric Ebrahim Raisi has won a landslide victory to be declared the country’s next president – but he has a bloody history steeped in murder and executions, activists c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pack of wolves chases actors on stage at theater...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3113514/video-wolves-chasing-actors-chinese-theatre-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TERRIFYING video of a live stage show in China has gone viral after it appeared to show a group of actors being chased by THIRTY wolves. The clip, filmed in a theatre in the city of Xi’an, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INDIANA JONES' filming '24/7 hell' for residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3113220/indiana-jones-nimby-filming-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANA Jones has been caught up in a Nimby row after filming of the new movie took over a street. Producers paid one neighbour a reported £50,000 to let cameras into their home. The homeowner then…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans, spurred by unlikely figure, see political promise in critical race theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-spurred-by-an-unlikely-figure-see-political-promise-in-critical-race-theory/ar-AALd4W9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Rufo, once a documentary filmmaker, has become a go-to activist for the GOP in a political fight over race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians reject doses...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/vaccine-exchange-deal-between-israel-and-pa-has-been-announced-671413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came after Israel delivered a first shipment of Pfizer COVID vaccine to the Palestinian Authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMNESTY calls for investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210619-amnesty-calls-for-iran-s-raisi-to-be-investigated-over-rights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amnesty calls for Iran's Raisi to be investigated over rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My battle to save Princess Diana: Doctor gives first ever account...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9702355/First-minute-minute-testimony-doctors-fight-save-Princess-Diana.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview, MonSef Dahman recalled how he was summoned to the emergency department of the Pitié-Salpêtrière Hospital, Paris, to attend to Diana, Princess of Wales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral Rivals Team Up, Aiming to Weaken Race's Front-Runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-19/nyc-mayoral-rivals-team-up-aiming-to-weaken-race-s-front-runner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move to shake up the race to become New York City’s next mayor, former Sanitation Commissioner Kathryn Garcia and celebrity entrepreneur Andrew Yang agreed to campaign together Saturday in each other’s political strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Boasts Sour Amid Explosive Rise in Infections...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/europe/putins-covid-19-boasts-sour-amid-explosive-rise-in-infections/articleshow/83663038.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe News: Already among the pandemic’s worst-hit countries, Russia’s experiencing a resurgence of the deadly virus aided by the rapid spread of the highly-conta</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: CDC can't regulate cruises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/559248-cdc-cant-regulate-cruises-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal in Florida judge on Friday ruled that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's (CDC) coronavirus-era sailing orders were an overreach of power, issuing a preliminary injunction temporarily barring the CDC from enforcing the guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taser-wielding madman sparks mayhem in park...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/taser-wielding-man-sparks-mayhem-in-washington-square-park-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was left covered in blood after she was “run over” in the stampede to safety, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombies, Semen, Big Racks: Inside Deer Breeding Industry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zombies-semen-big-racks-inside-130649327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Photos via GettyTexas-bred deer are currently infected with an incurable, highly contagious, zombie-like disease, and as if that weren’t bad enough, the likelihood that the disease has spread across the state among the wild population is increasing by the minute. And while the disease has been found in several other states prior, grassroots groups are pointing the finger at Texas deer breeders, who they believe, through political-will have skirted regulation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-person marches, music and reflection as Americans mark Juneteenth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619090141-6yv50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrations and activism planned for Juneteenth holiday after a year that sparked a reckoning over racism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Severe' Blood Shortage Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/06/18/severe-blood-shortage-nationwide-impacting-minnesota-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At one of the Red Cross donation sites in Bloomington, they say some of their most common donors are frontline healthcare workers, who are seeing this shortage firsthand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Move Here, You Make Deal With Nature': Life in Fire-Prone Canyon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/19/if-you-move-out-here-you-make-a-deal-with-nature-life-in-a-fire-prone-canyon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPANGA, Calif. — The Palisades Fire that forced hundreds to evacuate last month on the outskirts of Los Angeles never</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memphis erases Confederate general from public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tn-state-wire-memphis-racial-injustice-race-and-ethnicity-7e5941b9a05b0e01247b1bc89d7da348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Confederate Gen. Nathan Bedford Forrest’s polarizing presence has hung over Memphis since he moved here in 1852 — his legacy cemented by a giant statue that loomed over all who passed his gravesite in a popular park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit by ransomware attack? Payment may be deductible...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-government-and-politics-d8c1e9958ad1e89eab83f44e6ca70a94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As ransomware attacks surge, the FBI is doubling down on its guidance to affected businesses: Don't pay the cybercriminals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-line judiciary head wins Iran presidency..</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-judiciary-4d60554fd608a5dea2c76a303ec352d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran's hard-line judiciary chief won a landslide victory Saturday in the country's presidential election, a vote that both propelled the supreme leader's protege into Tehran's highest civilian position and saw the lowest turnout in the Islamic Republic's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 inches?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/la-state-wire-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-storms-2a55717d3441af8d128a476932aeaca2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Thunderstorms and high winds on the east side of Tropical Storm Claudette battered the Florida panhandle and much of Alabama on Saturday, as the weather system moved toward the North Carolina coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partygoers, police injured at curfew-busting rave in France...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-097cff85c058bfadf6dcb3a4f4637828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French police clashed with party-goers as they tried to break up an unauthorized rave in western France, authorities said Saturday. A 22-year-old man lost his hand and several others were injured amid the violence, including police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMART THERMOSTATS 'MANIPULATED' IN TEX</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/texas-remote-controlled-smart-thermostats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Power companies in Texas are remotely raising temperatures inside of some customers' homes amid the state's ongoing energy shortage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST BAKED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/heat-wave-raises-fears-western-us-states-could-face-severe-fire-season/ar-AALchP9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high temperatures and a worsening drought have parched vast tracts of brush, timber and grasses, leaving an abundance of potential fuels for the flames to consume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global study claims atheists are just as happy as those with a faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9702653/Religion-ISNT-secret-happiness-global-study-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers from Cologne University, Germany, found that all except those who were 'weakly religious' showed similar levels of life satisfaction (file photo).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SET TO MISS JULY 4 VAX TARGET...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210618202053-3gtnc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Biden, Harris urge vaccinations as U.S. looks likely to miss July 4 target</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse plague continues in Oz...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15321058/mouse-plague-australians-trouser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSSIES are being told to tie string around the their trousers to stop scurrying rodents running up their legs. The country has been gripped by a plague of mice – the worst outbreak in more t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes' pro-Obamacare decision spurs both parties to new strategies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-e2-80-99s-pro-aca-decision-spurs-both-parties-to-new-strategies/ar-AALahWJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Cases Surge Even as 8 in 10 Have Received Shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/uk-virus-cases-surge-even-as-8-in-10-have-received-shots-11623958350491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by Public Health England showed infection rates increasing across all age groups, but are highest among people aged 20 to 29.More than 11,000 new cases of the disease were reported on Thursday, along with 19 deaths, according to the Department Health</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Puerto Rico, 2 major power outages in week fuel fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-Puerto-Rico-2-major-power-outages-in-a-week-16258546.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Gustavo Irizarry walked the dark streets of Adjuntas, Puerto Rico, he thought of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Trump Lawyers Find Washington's Revolving Door Turns Slowly...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/ip-law/slower-revolving-door-what-trumps-top-lawyers-are-doing-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 80% of top lawyers in Trump’s administration have landed somewhere since he left office, even if their roles are part time or not their first choice, according to an analysis by Bloomberg Law. Some of those lawyers—and legal recruiters—say they’re having a harder time finding work than in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Snap Up Private-Jets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bankers-see-private-jet-party-133326251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The coronavirus pandemic has created an overhang of pent-up travel demand and left unspent money burning holes in the pockets of the well-to-do. Put the two together and the result is a hunger for private jets.Buyers have scooped up so many of the good used planes out there that they’re now getting on waiting lists to purchase new aircraft, said bankers at this week’s Corporate Jet Investor conference.“There’s been quite a party in the private aviation business in the last 18 mont</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  MSNBC Execs Push Back Against Staff Unionization Despite Support From High-Profile Anchors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/msnbc-brass-push-back-against-staff-unionization-drive-despite-support-from-high-profile-anchors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pushback came just a day after staff announced plans to form a union, and after network stars publicly expressed support for the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid counts hit zero in hospitals once overrun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/covid-counts-hit-zero-in-us-hospitals-once-overrun-by-victims/ar-AALbE91?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first pandemic surge flooded Boston Medical Center with coronavirus patients: 229 at last spring’s peak, filling nearly two-thirds of its beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -533 to close out worst week since October...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/17/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blue-chip Dow lost 3.5% this week, its worst weekly performance since October. The S&amp;P 500 dropped 1.9% over that time period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VOWS NO NEW LOCKDOWNS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-new-lockdowns-biden-promises-201834771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden vowed that the U.S. would not see new lockdowns in the coming months, even as he warned about the new Delta variant of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPUBLICA Has Tax Info on Thousands More. Will Anyone Sue?</title>
      <link>https://www.futureofcapitalism.com/2021/06/propublica-has-tax-info-on-thousands-more-will</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.futureofcapitalism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ProPublica, the nonprofit news organization that recently published what it said was the tax information of the 25 richest Americans, is now out with the tax information of a candidate for Manhattan district attorney, "Tali Farhadian Weinstein, who is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure on PORNHUB grows after 34 women sue...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210618-pressure-on-pornhub-grows-after-34-women-sue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure on Pornhub grows after 34 women sue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico fans banned from World Cup qualifier for homophobic slurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/mexico-fans-hit-with-fifa-ban-at-world-cup-qualifier-for-homophobic-slurs-671432</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires Receive Stimulus Checks...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/gop-megadonors-puzzled-to-receive-stimulus-checks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops! The Internal Revenue Service is typically in the business of taxing the rich, but two Republican megadonors were surprised in May to find $1,400 payments from the tax man deposited directly in their bank accounts—coronavirus stimulus payments gone awry, people close to those donors tell the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas empties prison to prepare to detain illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/06/17/immigration-prison-border-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prison — Dolph Briscoe Unit in Dilley — will have capacity for about 1,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California unveils digital 'vaccine records' system...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressdemocrat.com/article/news/california-unveils-system-to-provide-digital-covid-19-vaccine-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressdemocrat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccinated Californians can now access a digital version of their COVID-19 vaccine record.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
