<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Results not known until mid-July?!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm/2021/06/22/why-nycs-instant-runoff-could-take-weeks-to-decide-493332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the For the People Act heads for defeat in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US planes launch first airstrikes from foreign ship since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/06/22/u-k-u-s-f-35bs-launch-anti-isis-strikes-from-hms-queen-elizabeth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British and American F-35B Lighting II Joint Strike Fighters flew anti-ISIS strike missions from the U.K. Royal Navy aircraft carrier HMS Queen Elizabeth (R08) – a first for the U.K. in a decade, defense officials confirmed to USNI News on Tuesday. The F-35s from the embarked Royal Air Force 617 Squadron, “The Dambusters” flew combat …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Star's Suit: Pastor Slept With My Wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.wjbf.com/news/lawsuit-former-mlb-star-ben-zobrist-says-wife-had-affair-with-their-pastor-sues-him-for-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wjbf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Major League Baseball star Ben Zobrist claims his wife was having an affair with their pastor, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as Seattle Pride charges white people $50 'reparations fee' to attend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3132240/seattle-pride-event-charging-white-people-50-reparations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIDE event has been accused of “reverse racism” after charging white people up to $50 in a “reparations fee” to attend. Seattle Human Rights Commission officials dismisse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NYC guidelines: 'Make it kinky' at summer 'sex parties'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/22/make-it-kinky-at-summer-sex-parties-nyc-health-dept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic memo touts glory holes, synchronized masturbation and more new health department guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why single people smell different...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210621-why-single-people-smell-different</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a wealth of psychological and biological information stored in our scent, but for some reason we choose to ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900 Secret Service employees were infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-22208672ed5c0bb126c00e0f6e91a7d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roughly 900 U.S. Secret Service employees tested positive for the coronavirus, according to government records obtained by a government watchdog group. Secret Service records show that 881 people on the agency payroll were diagnosed with COVID-19 between March 1, 2020 and March 9, 2021, according to documents obtained by Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-the-clock officers acting as on-duty cops: Father's death in Austin shows need for restraint, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/off-the-clock-officers-acting-as-on-duty-cops-alex-gonzales-death-shows-need-for-restraint-experts-say/ar-AALgO6j?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As investigations into Alex Gonzales' Austin police shooting death continue, focus is on peril of officers taking official action while off-duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area has become more segregated over decades, report says...</title>
      <link>https://thesantaclaramail.com/politics/bay-area-has-become-more-segregated-over-decades-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesantaclaramail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big Tech created data 'treasure trove' for police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/how-big-tech-created-data-treasure-trove-for-police-e8a664c7814cc6dd560ba0e0c435bf90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — When U.S. law enforcement officials need to cast a wide net for information, they’re increasingly turning to the vast digital ponds of personal data created by Big Tech companies via the devices and online services that have hooked billions of people around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Britney Quietly Pushed for Years to End Her Conservatorship... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/22/arts/music/britney-spears-conservatorship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidential court records obtained by The Times reveal that the singer has urged changes to the arrangement that controls her life, and her father’s role in leading it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant Industry Crippled By Staffing Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/06/21/many-restaurant-job-applicants-arent-showing-up-for-interviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While fully open, many Twin Cities bars and restaurants are having trouble filling their staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa doctor did surgery on wrong testicle, state says. He tried to fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article252274043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tampa urologist marked a patient’s right testicle for removal of enlarged veins and did the procedure on that testicle. But the September 2019 procedure was supposed to be done on the left testicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER vaccine linked to rare blood disease, claims Israeli study...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/pfizer-covid-19-vaccine-linked-to-rare-blood-disease-israeli-study-671694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson from the hospital stressed that this study, which was very small, should in no way deter people from vaccinating and encouraged anyone who has not yet been inoculated to get the jab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  44% Of Americans Hit 'Lowest Emotional Point' Of Lives During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pandemic-lowest-emotional-point-doctors-telehealth-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While 72 percent agree mental health care is just as important as physical health care, only 18 percent are currently enrolled in therapy sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PONNURU TOP AT NATIONAL REVIEW; LOWRY STEPS DOWN  AFTER 23 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/national-review-editor-rich-lowry-e152aee4-5d06-4f58-af9a-93d826cd1833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'll focus on more strategic long-term initiatives as National Review's editor-in-chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL BE FIRST?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/branson-bezos-space-tourism-billionaire-battle-81f7e1e5-eb54-425f-910e-bd8e63deb398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race to make suborbital space tourism a viable business is heating up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1 million nonbinary adults in USA, pioneering study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/more-than-1-million-nonbinary-adults-live-in-the-us-a-pioneering-study-finds/ar-AALjqdz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The final frontier: Doing laundry in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210622114952-o3bpi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCTER GAMBLE-NASA/ (PIX):The final frontier: doing laundry in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High stakes and high stress, forecasting tornadoes can take psychological toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/high-stakes-and-high-stress-forecasting-tornadoes-can-take-psychological-toll/ar-AALjnSW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornadoes can have profound impacts on the meteorologists who warn for them, especially when lives are lost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/china-s-troop-deployment-along-disputed-border-worries-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising violent crime poses new challenge for White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/559467-rising-violent-crime-poses-new-challenge-for-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will detail his administration’s crime prevention strategy on Wednesday in a high profile address that comes as a series of major cities see spikes in crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Strawberry Moon to dazzle in last full moon of year...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3125408/strawberry-supermoon-june-full-moon-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE LAST Supermoon of the year will brighten up the night sky this week. June’s full Moon is called the Strawberry Moon and it will be at its fullest on Thursday June 24. The “Super Str…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'unprecedented' challenge to homophobia law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-vatican-in-unprecedented-challenge-to-italy-homophobia-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vatican in 'unprecedented' challenge to Italy homophobia law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doge down 70% since Musk on SNL...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/dogecoin-price-elon-musk-snl-cryptocurrency-crash-china-bubble-2021-6-1030542208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Buyout Just the Start as Wealthy Flee Tax Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/record-buyout-just-start-wealthy-120000843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For 110 years, four generations of Mills family members earned their money by expanding their great-grandfather’s Chicago apron business into a medical supplier that ranked among the nation’s largest private companies.But soon after Democrats turned their attention toward raising taxes for the wealthy this year, the family signed a deal to cash out billions.It was no coincidence, according to people close to the more-than $30 billion transaction, which sold part of Medline Industr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China crypto crackdown wipes $300 billion off market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/china-crypto-crackdown-wipes-nearly-300-billion-off-market-btc-slides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Friday, China has stepped up its efforts to rein in the country's cryptocurrency industry from mining bans to warnings to financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin below key $30,000 level...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/bitcoin-falls-again-breaking-below-key-30000-level-that-traders-say-could-lead-to-more-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecocide: Fast-growing movement to put environmental destruction on par with war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/how-a-growing-movement-plans-to-put-ecocide-on-a-par-with-war-crimes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecocide is an umbrella term for all forms of the mass damage of ecosystems, from industrial pollution to the release of micro plastics into the oceans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No one gonna steal election from me': Echoes of 2020 in NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2021/06/22/no-one-is-gonna-steal-the-election-from-me-echoes-of-2020-in-nyc-mayors-race-1386767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A racially-tinged battle has erupted over the process, with the leading candidate&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;leveling accusations of voter disenfranchisement&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;after two of his opponents formed a last-minute alliance to bolster their own campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse plague forces Oz prison evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mouse-plague-forces-australian-prison-evacuation/ar-AALi9Qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mouse plague ravaging Australia's farmlands forced the evacuation of hundreds of inmates from a rural jail on Tuesday, as the rodents broke in and chewed through essential infrastructure. "The health, safety and wellbeing of staff and inmates is our number one priority, so it's important for us to act now to carry out the vital remediation work," said Peter Severin od Corrective Services NSW. Up to 420 inmates and 200 staff from the Wellington...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia struggles to quash persistent outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-australia-struggles-to-quash-persistent-coronavirus-outbreaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia struggles to quash persistent coronavirus outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210622034933-9gsj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCIALMEDIA-DATING/ (GRAPHIC, PIX):FOCUS-Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything in a post-pandemic world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fleet off Hawaii practices sinking aircraft carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9711403/Russian-fleet-35-miles-Hawaii-practices-sinking-aircraft-carrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Monday announced that they had carried out an exercise simulating the sinking of an aircraft carrier, off the coast of Hawaii. The war games are the largest since the Cold War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel tests digital shekel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/jpost-tech/israel-has-already-tested-a-digital-shekel-cryptocurrency-671639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept of issuing such a currency has been in discussion since 2017, but it decided to accelerate its research and preparation for the potential issuance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garland tries to untangle Trump legacy at Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/garland-tries-to-untangle-the-trump-legacy-at-the-justice-department/ar-AALgBAO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC paid Mar-a-Lago $175K for spring donor retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/21/rnc-paid-trumps-mar-a-lago-over-175000-for-donor-retreat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's private club was paid over $175,000 in May by the RNC to host its donor retreat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA BORED...</title>
      <link>https://w3-lab.com/instagram-reach-is-down-is-instagram-dying-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;w3-lab.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the Instagram trends for 2021? Why is Instagram`s reach and engagement rate declining? Is Instagram dying in 2021? Find out here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside dog 'factory farm' from hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/panicked-dogs-bred-factory-farms-24368423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING IMAGES: EXCLUSIVE: Footage shows beagles being piled onto overcrowded trolleys and whimpering before being force fed chemicals for 90 days in what comedian Ricky Gervais called 'terrible cruelty'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASSIB FIRST OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.instagram.com/p/CQZXu_8nyy_/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instagram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;93.1k Likes, 8,563 Comments - Carl Nassib (@carlnassib) on Instagram: “For more information on the life-saving work and resources of The Trevor Project click the link in…”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAY IN NFL</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31682318/carl-nassib-las-vegas-raiders-announces-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders DE Carl Nassib became the first active NFL player to come out as gay, announcing the news in an Instagram post Monday while pledging $100,000 to the Trevor Project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SUES NYC... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-organization-sues-york-city-wrongful-termination-contracts/story?id=78408860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s company sued New York City Monday for allegedly wrongfully terminating contracts the Trump Organization had to operate city facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency services scramble to rescue drowning SEX DOLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3128026/emergency-services-rescue-drowning-woman-sea-discarded-sex-doll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMERGENCY services scrambled to save a drowning woman washed out to sea before discovering the damsel in distress was actually a discarded SEX DOLL. Crowds gathered to watch the dramatic rescue of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiCaprio's multi-million-dollar eco-friendly resort years behind schedule...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3091472/leonardo-dicaprio-eco-friendly-resort-belize-behind-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEONARDO DiCaprio’s plan to “change the world” by building the greenest luxury resort off the coast of Belize is running YEARS behind schedule after angry protests by fishermen an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDER becomes NFL's only openly gay player...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/06/21/raiders-carl-nassib-comes-out-as-openly-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders defensive end Carl Nassib came out today, making him the NFL’s only openly gay player. “I just want to take a quick moment to say that I’m gay,” Nassib said in a video he posted on his verified Instagram account. “I’ve been meaning to do this for a while now but I finally feel [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS ARRESTED OUTSIDE TED CRUZ HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article252262438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were arrested outside Sen. Ted Cruz’s home, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIZEN app told LA residents plane had crashed -- it was training drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/citizen-plane-crash-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off sending a mob after the wrong person, Citizen accidentally misreported that a plane crashed in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Atlanta went from nearly defunding police -- to boosting funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/atlanta-news/atlanta-almost-withheld-73m-in-police-funding-last-year-whats-changed-since-then/FEZOTN3G7NFCDFAMAI5BBBTVYY/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discussions at City Hall over this year’s budget, which followed a citywide rise in violent crime, highlight how the discourse over policing has shifted in the last year, among elected officials and some members of the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte threatens those who refuse vaccine with jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-duterte-threatens-those-who-refuse-covid-19-vaccine-with-jail-2021-06-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Rodrigo Duterte threatened to jail people who refuse to be vaccinated against the coronavirus as the Philippines battles one of Asia's worst outbreaks, with over 1.3 million cases and more than 23,000 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado sweeps through suburban Chicago, causing damage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/suburbs-naperville-chicago-environment-and-nature-us-news-606ad68e325f0074102786a17a1bcbcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A tornado swept through communities in heavily populated suburban Chicago, damaging more than 100 homes, toppling trees, knocking out power and causing multiple injuries, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books Already 'Burning'...</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/the-books-are-already-burning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question is only: How long will decent people stand by quietly and watch it happen?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms used in health care nationwide rife with bias...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/21/algorithm-bias-playbook-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report finds bias is pervasive in algorithms used by hospitals and insurers. It also offers a playbook on how to fix those flaws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th presidential candidate detained in Nicaragua...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/21/americas/nicaragua-fifth-candidate-detained-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicaragua's National Police have detained a fifth presidential candidate, bringing the total number of opposition leaders so far detained to 15 ahead of the November general election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Woman who claims she gave birth to 10 babies admitted to psych ward...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/21/south-african-woman-who-says-she-birthed-10-babies-now-in-psych-ward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gosiame Thamara Sithole, who made headlines for the alleged record-breaking birth, was taken to the psychiatric ward last week at Tembisa Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardline Iranian President Refuses Biden Meeting...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iranian-president-elect-rejects-biden-refuses-negotiations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s newly elected hardline president, Ebrahim Raisi, said in his first press conference on Monday that he will not allow negotiations to take place on the country’s contested missile program, which includes long-range ballistic missiles capable of carrying a nuclear warhead.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
