<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Appeals judge found shot dead behind home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/25/stephen-goss-appeals-judge-found-shot-dead-behind-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An appeals judge in Georgia was found Saturday shot dead behind his Albany home, but officials do not believe it was a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows NYPD struggling to arrest man as onlookers taunt them...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/video-shows-nypd-struggling-to-arrest-man-as-onlookers-taunt-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republican New York state assemblyman retweeted a video that depicts four New York Police Department officers struggling to arrest a man resisting to get into a police car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci appears at Biden event...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/scaramucci-appears-at-biden-campaign-event-and-says-trump-will-lose-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTHAMPTON, N.Y. — President Trump's wayward former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci appeared at a Southampton, New York, campaign stop where Joe Biden addressed well-heeled Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's deepest hole dubbed 'well to hell' revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9786114/worlds-deepest-hole-well-to-hell/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EARTH’S deepest artificial hole stretches 40,000 feet below the surface – but it’s only covered by a rusty metal lid. Russia’s Kola Superdeep Borehole was created by the Soviets i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitos Deadliest Hunter on Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-deadliest-hunter-of-humans-on-the-planet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this introduction to his book “The Mosquito,” Timothy C. Winegard profiles the creature that has changed the course of war and empire, and survived every attempt to wipe it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: More Dangerous Than WMDs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/amazon-fires-show-limits-sovereignty/596779/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person shouldn’t have the power to set policies that doom the rest of humanity’s shot at mitigating rising temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollution Linked To Psychiatric Disorders?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smog-sadness-study-suggests-link-between-air-pollution-psychiatric-disorders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they have identified a possible link between exposure to environmental pollution, specifically polluted air, and an increase in the onset of psychiatric and mental health problems in a population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arpaio seeks to reclaim mantle as 'America's toughest sheriff'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-sheriff/ex-arizona-lawman-seeks-to-reclaim-mantle-as-americas-toughest-sheriff-idUSKCN1VG0AD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Arpaio, the former Arizona sheriff who built a national reputation as a stau...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, French officials reach deal on digital tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g7-summit-digital-tax/french-u-s-officials-strike-draft-compromise-on-french-digital-tax-idUSKCN1VG0N5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French and U.S. negotiators have reached a compromise agreement on France's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change in politics with more black voters in Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/08/12/a-change-in-politics-with-more-black-voters-in-the-deep-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-tropical-storm-dorian-update-20190825-koiaunm2zfcajj527oupyj6dyu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Dorian is expected to continue to strengthen, National Hurricane Center forecasters said, and they still predict it will become the first hurricane of the season by late Tuesday or early Wednesday. Some computer models have the storm tracking to Florida by next weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football's Consequences Weigh Heavily...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/25/sports/football/andrew-luck-retirement-injuries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luck belongs to a young generation more carefully weighing the dangers of the game against the financial rewards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/refresh/AL052019_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/205313_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens who lived in same neighborhood diagnosed with brain tumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dozens-who-lived-in-same-neighborhood-diagnosed-with-brain-tumors/ar-AAGhbtr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Allies Target Journalists Over Coverage Deemed Hostile to White House... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-allies-target-journalists-over-coverage-deemed-hostile-to-white-house/ar-AAGjq3C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONCERN, CONFUSION</title>
      <link>https://www.morningstar.com/news/dow-jones/20190825882/us-companies-greet-latest-trump-tweets-with-concern-and-confusion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.morningstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third dengue fever case confirmed in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article234329597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Floats Own Hotel as Site for Next Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-floats-his-own-doral-hotel-as-site-for-next-g7-summit-its-very-big-great-conference-rooms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has suggested that next year's G7 summit should happen in Miami, specifically at his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's assault on China, Fed hits American consumers with hidden tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trumps-assault-on-china-and-the-fed-will-be-a-stiff-tax-on-every-american-consumer-2019-08-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Misguided White House leaves investors on the rocks and in a hard place, writes David R. Kotok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTION OVER BEIRUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Lebanese-Army-Two-Israeli-drones-downed-over-Beirut-599623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hezbollah leader Hassan Nasrallah expected to talk after 5 pm following two alleged Israeli drones downing Beirut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump denies he suggested nuking hurricanes. But govt once studied idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-denies-that-he-suggested-nuking-hurricanes-14378268.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In October 1935, roughly six weeks after a devastating hurricane laid waste to the Florida Keys, a group of frustrated chamber of commerce executives from the storm-battered Florida cities of Miami, Fort Lauderdale, and Hollywood got together to figure out what could be done about storms that mercilessly pounded the state's coast every fall, threatening the burgeoning tourist economy.  The solution they landed on was a novel one, and, conveniently, it didn't require anyone to move out of harm's way. Instead, the executives suggested, the government should simply try bombing hurricanes before they got to Florida.  "These storms are not only local menaces," reasoned Clyde Elliot, the secretary of the Hollywood, Florida, Chamber of Commerce. "They reach Newfoundland frequently before they disburse, hence this control is really of national importance."  While their proposal didn't gain any traction, it wasn't the last time the idea would come up. On Sunday night, Axios reported that President Donald Trump has repeatedly urged senior Homeland Security and national security officials to explore the possibility of using nuclear bombs to weaken hurricanes before they reach the United States, which would make him the latest in a long line of politicians (and coastal property owners in Florida) who have suggested fighting storms with military force.  Early Monday, Trump denied ever pushing for the use of nuclear bombs against hurricanes, tweeting that the Axios story was "ridiculous" and "Just more FAKE NEWS!"  Regardless of Trump's feelings on the subject, the idea of hurling bombs in the path of incoming storms was once given serious consideration. Just weeks after the U.S. dropped the first atomic bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki in 1945, Floridians started wondering if the same destructive force that had ushered in the end of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex bots with coding errors prone to violence and could strangle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robots-coding-errors-prone-18992240</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doll collector Brick Dollbanger fears what could happen if robots are not regulated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius monkey sharpens rock before smashing it against zoo window in escape bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/genius-monkey-sharpens-rock-before-19007139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The monkey's enclosure window shattered as the rock was smashed against it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRETS OF PRINCE ANDREW'S SIX DAYS WITH EPSTEIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391369/Prince-Andrew-spent-six-days-Jeffrey-Epsteins-home-two-years-convicted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York stayed over a period of six days with shamed financier Jeffrey Epstein in 2010. This was two years after the businessman was convicted of having sex with a child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Stephanopolous went to lavish party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391265/Woody-Allen-pictured-leaving-Jeffrey-Epsteins-mansion-lavish-party-royals-honor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial film director, 83, and his wife Soon-Yi, 48, attended the New York party. They left Epstein's house midway through Prince Andrew's visit, at 11.30am on December 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia test fires 2 missiles from nuke subs in Arctic Ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/24/europe/russia-test-fires-ballistic-missiles/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missiles launch took place from two nuclear-powered submarines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantasy of being disconnected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/the-fantasy-of-being-disconnected/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overactive world is hard to break away from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRADE WAR 'EMERGENCY'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/25/trump-on-us-china-trade-war-i-could-declare-a-national-emergency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clouding the G-7 gathering, which represents the world's major industrial economies, are the tit-for-tat tariffs between Washington and Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual deal keeps shrinking Ohio city's newspaper going...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2019/08/26/vindicator-unusual-deal-keeps-shrinking-youngstowns-newspaper-going/2118333001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agreement appears to save the essence of a hometown newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Fallout: COLTS Plummet To 60/1 Super Bowl Longshots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/andrew-lucks-retirement-leads-to-colts-afc-title-and-super-bowl-odds-plummeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vegas is now questioning if the Colts have the firepower to make the postseason without Luck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Tropical Storm forms over Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/forecasters-tracking-tropical-disturbance-as-it-moves-closer-to-florida/70009155 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh sex assault allegatons could delay Weinstein trial...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/harvey-weinstein-faces-fresh-sexual-042143785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fallen movie mogul Harvey Weinstein, indicted over two sexual assault allegations, is to be informed of new allegations against him Monday that could delay his trial and complicate his defence. New York prosecutors announced on Thursday that they had filed a new indictment against the 67-year-old former</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN:  YOU GOTTA LAY OFF TWITTER!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/458740-mark-penn-trump-should-push-china-but-drop-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has to learn that governing by Twitter is self-defeating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin built hypersonic arsenal -- while Pentagon slept...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/458769-putin-built-a-hypersonic-arsenal-while-the-pentagon-slept</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is almost certain to introduce almost all of its new hypersonic weapons well before they will appear in the American arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters, Protestors Clash At Straight Pride Event In CA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/24/approximately-200-people-gather-at-straight-pride-event-in-modesto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 200 people gathered, including protestors, at a Straight Pride event this afternoon in Modesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam taxing robots as companies invest in advanced tech...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/25/brave-new-world-uncle-sam-is-taxing-robots-as-companies-invest-in-advanced-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a brave new world for the IRS: taxing robots. Uncle Sam is padding the Treasury with millions of dollars to assess bots at the same time that corporations invest more in advanced technology an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Reunited With Lost Cat -- 11 Years Later!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/23/new-york-cat-returns-home-11-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was found wandering, seemingly living in plain sight, just a few miles from his Dutchess County home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbados braces...</title>
      <link>https://newsday.co.tt/2019/08/25/barbados-braces-for-tropical-storm-dorian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsday.co.tt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARBADOS is bracing for the impact on Monday of Tropical Storm Dorian which, on Saturday, was upgraded from from a tropical depression by the National Hurricane Centre in Miami. Other areas of the Eastern Caribbean especially St Lucia are expected to feel the effects of Dorian on Tuesday. The TT Met Office said the storm … Continue reading Barbados braces for Tropical Storm Dorian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right surge rattles guardians of Nazi era remembrance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/far-surge-rattles-guardians-nazi-era-remembrance-042905806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tour group handpicked by the far-right party Alternative for Germany touched off a scandal last summer while visiting the former Nazi concentration camp Sachsenhausen north of Berlin. "As our horrified colleague told me, the comments by obviously rhetorically trained people culminated in them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Draws Record Crowd of 15,000 in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elizabeth-warren-draws-record-crowd-005435054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elizabeth Warren drew the largest crowd of her presidential campaign Sunday in Seattle, as an estimated 15,000 people turned out to support what she calls a movement for change.When touting her wealth tax of 2 cents on every dollar of assets above $50 million, Warren drew chants of “2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Seeks to Avoid 2016 Repeat But Some Fear Gone Too Far...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dnc-seeks-avoid-2016-repeat-080000545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders railed against a “rigged” Democratic primary during the 2016 election, but as he campaigns this year, his team has no complaints.That’s because the Democratic National Committee has taken pains to fix the problems that some said plagued the last nominating process. There</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's army fights Amazon fires after hundreds more flare up...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-army-fights-amazon-fires-hundreds-blazes-ignite-003334696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil on Sunday deployed two C-130 Hercules aircraft to douse fires devouring parts of the Amazon rainforest, as hundreds of new blazes flared up and thousands protested over the destruction. Heavy smoke covered the city of Porto Velho in the northwestern state of Rondonia where the defense ministry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Long Journey From Trump Hater to Best Friend...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnsons-long-journey-trump-135221894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Follow @Brexit on Twitter, join our Facebook group and sign up to our Brexit Bulletin.In December 2015, Boris Johnson joked that he wouldn’t go to some parts of New York because of the risk of meeting Donald Trump, a man of “stupefying ignorance.”How times change.Johnson was London’s popular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Athens mayor pledges revamp of crisis-hit capital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/athens-mayor-pledges-revamp-crisis-hit-capital-024532988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly-elected Athens mayor Costas Bakoyannis, scion of one of Greece's most powerful political families, took his oath of office Sunday pledging to turn the crisis-battered capital into "a safe, clean and bright" European metropolis. "Over the next four years I pledge to be a servant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>182 pigs killed en route to slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/182-pigs-killed-en-route-french-slaughterhouse-090709312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 180 pigs were killed when a lorry that was transporting them to the slaughterhouse overturned at the weekend in northeastern France, rescuers said Monday. "A heavy goods vehicle (HGV) which was transporting 205 pigs overturned" at a roundabout in Etain, about 50 kilometres (30 miles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bracing for nastiest contest in modern era...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff2f787aceb34498bde8f6f948d5c471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMPTON, S.C. (AP) — President Donald Trump told American congresswomen of color to "go back" to where they came from. He vowed to revive a racial slur to tear down Elizabeth Warren, promoted a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracks emerge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f19d28009bc94db387ac238dffa27348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — A top Iranian official paid an unannounced visit Sunday to the G-7 summit and headed straight toward the heart of the city where leaders of the world's major democracies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>