<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Police Use of Driver's License Databases to Nab Crooks Spurs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-use-of-drivers-license-databases-to-nab-crooks-spurs-privacy-concerns-1529233200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law-enforcement officials who advocate for using facial recognition searches of driver’s license photos argue that it is a valuable tool; civil liberties advocates say it infringes on privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moped thieves steal UK Home Secretary's phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6550824/ive-been-robbed-by-a-moped-crook-says-sajid-javid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOME Secretary Sajid Javid has revealed he was a moped mugging victim — as he launches a blitz on street crime. He admits it left him fearing for his kids’ safety when they go out. The Tory, 48, wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama gas station clerk shoots customer as he walks out of store...</title>
      <link>http://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article213196489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a man was shot at the Obama gas station on Farrow Road, police have arrested the store's clerk, according to a Columbia police statement. Antar Daralhaj was arguing with a customer Saturday afternoon about overcharging for gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue ships dock in Spain as migrant debate roils Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3eeb4671542a40b39ded7b736cd685ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VALENCIA, Spain (AP) — Ships in the Aquarius aid convoy docked Sunday at the Spanish port of Valencia, ending a weeklong ordeal for hundreds of people who were rescued from the pe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NBA player charged for home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/former-nba-player-charged-with-armed-robbery-coweta-county/RKsjSFosvDioSvzq2AkqzO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former NBA player who went to high school in Cobb County was arrested Friday night in connection w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How string of violent sex crimes traced to ex-NFL star...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/17/how-a-string-of-violent-sex-crimes-were-traced-to-former-nfl-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eagle-eyed neighbor helped crack the bizarre case of a former NFL star now accused in a slew of attacks on women. It was just after 2:30 p.m. on June 7 when the Encinitas, Calif., resident spott…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Likens Abortion to Nazi Eugenics...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-francis-likens-abortion-to-nazi-eugenics-1529178587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In unusually blunt language, Pope Francis said that “to have an easy life, one does away with an innocent.” The pope also said the only real families are those based on marriage between a man and a woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria's entire 200 million population plunged in to darkness by power grid meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6551013/nigerias-power-grid-meltdown-world-cup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGERIA has suffered a power cut across the entire country. A power grid melt down comes on the same day the national team played Croatia in the first World Cup fixture. The Super Eagles lost 2-0 o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce and Jay Z Drop Surprise Album...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/16/beyonce-and-jay-z-drop-surprise-album-everything-is-love-plus-video-watch-here-apesht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprise! Beyonce and Jay Z have dropped a surprise album and single. It’s available on their Tidal service, but the single and video are here. “Ape-sh*t” is terrific. What a nice…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local billionaire to take control of the LA TIMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/local-billionaire-control-l-times-190522470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A biotech billionaire who purchased the Los Angeles Times with an eye toward restoring its independence and vigor will officially take control of the news organization Monday, the newspaper reports .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump keeps his promises on trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-keeps-promises-trade-144239362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By inflicting tariffs on the steel and aluminum of his allies, and then on tens of billions of dollars in goods from China, US President Donald Trump has quickly moved to fulfill the tough campaign pledges he made on trade. During his first year in office, Trump and his top economic aides made repeated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets Palestinians launching 'fire balloons' from Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-targets-palestinians-launching-fire-balloons-gaza-194205932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli army on Saturday wounded two Palestinians in the Gaza Strip attempting to launch incendiary balloons across the border into Israel, officials said. An Israeli military spokeswoman said an "aerial device" had fired at a group near the Gaza border that was launching "fire balloons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA dilemma: Notify people carrying cancer genes?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/article213014904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iceland, with extensive DNA databases, has the ability to identify citizens with deadly breast-cancer genes, and notify them. But government so far refuses to do so. That infuriates Kári Stefánsson, a brilliant but polarizing geneticist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reiner denounces De Niro, celebrities for anti-Trump remarks...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/media/392574-rob-reiner-denounces-robert-de-niro-and-other-celebrities-for-anti-trump-remarks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Rob Reiner denounced Robert De Niro and other celebrities for their remarks against President Trump, saying it only helps the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow taxi driver mows down fans...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5851807/Seven-injured-taxi-ploughs-World-Cup-fans-Moscow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among those injured included Mexican fans who were gearing up to watch their nation's opening World Cup game against Germany tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'ROSEANNE' Spinoff Clears Key Hurdle as Negotiations Heat Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/abcs-roseanne-spinoff-hinges-barr-relinquishing-fee-1120723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should a new take on the successful revival move forward, the WGA has made it clear any series will retain the comedian's credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TEAM PREDICTS MUELLER REPORT SOON...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-mueller-trump-russia-20180616-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's lawyers and special counsel Robert Mueller are hurtling toward a showdown over a yearlong investigation into the president's conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to colonize ASTEROIDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/710067/asteroid-nasa-cities-space-mining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Officials Rush to Support U.S. Envoy After Death Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-16/canadian-officials-rush-to-support-u-s-envoy-after-death-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Canadian officials, led by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, rushed to express support for Ambassador Kelly Craft after a package containing a suspicious substance and a death threat was mailed to the U.S. diplomat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican to Host Conference on 'Xenophobia, and Politically Motivated Populism'...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/06/16/vatican-host-conference-migration-xenophobia-politically-motivated-populism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Council of Churches (WCC) has announced a joint venture with the Vatican to co-host a meeting next September on "migration, xenophobia, and politically motivated populism."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 killed after nightclub brawl in Caracas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/906d30f06bfa47d69433ed7865d697bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS,Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's government says 17 people were killed Saturday after a nightclub brawl in the capital led to a stampede.        Interior Minister Nesto</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite cancer, McCain's maverick ways press on in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/despite-cancer-mccains-maverick-ways-press-tweets-154857911--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain's legacy was thrust into focus nearly one year ago when he announced his brain cancer diagnosis. The six-term Senator and decorated Vietnam War veteran is now fighting the illness from his beloved Arizona, and filling the role of one of the few Congressional Republican voices to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuelas-interior-minister-says-17-dead-nightclub-brawl-160758668.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL'S LAST WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/975166/Angela-Merkel-Germany-Bundestag-EU-migration-crisis-Kai-Whittaker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMAN Chancellor Angela Merkel could lose her powerful seat in the heart of Europe as soon as next week amid clashes within her coalition Government over EU migration policies, claimed German MP Kai Whittaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists and tech bring resilient Iceland back from the brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/16/iceland-tourists-tech-resilient-bank-from-brink-financial-crisis </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the country lets its banks go bust 10 years ago, there seemed to be no timetable for recovery. Things have changed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest stabbed in Bethlehem as religion shrinks in conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/974431/christian-persecution-christianity-bethlehem-palestine-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST in Bethlehem has been stabbed while protecting his congregation from thugs in the latest example of Christianity in Palestine coming under threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme body modification: Amputees risk DEATH by cutting off OWN limbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/703655/body-modification-mods-amputee-extreme-cutting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE: Break Up GOOGLE! Competitors banished into oblivion...</title>
      <link>https://apps.bostonglobe.com/opinion/graphics/2018/06/break-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case for ending Google's Internet domination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Deal Making Could Free CBS From VIACOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/why-media-deal-making-could-free-cbs-from-viacom-1529157600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viacom may have given up on CBS and now that media deals are in the air, CBS could get bought by another company, leaving Viacom all alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Saudi increasingly chummy; Big implications for OPEC, oil prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/16/russia-saudi-arabia-get-chummy-ahead-of-opec-may-affect-oil-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Saudi Arabia reinforced their partnership as OPEC is set to grapple with some thorny issues, like declines of supply from Venezuela and the effect of renewed U.S. sanctions on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast of U.S. Open  picks up rough sex talk...</title>
      <link>http://www.sportingnews.com/golf/news/fox-sports-us-open-2018-audio-rough-sex-shinnecock-hills-joe-buck-on-course-microphones-usga-headbutted/yc1ix2umw4b915c9d4jyfg4w5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportingnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the network&amp;#39;s omnipresent on-course microphones at Shinnecock Hills gets the network in trouble; it eavesdrops on a private conversation that wasn&amp;#39;t suitable for even cable television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'd rather wake up next to severed horse head'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/15/gotti-flick-is-the-worst-mob-movie-of-all-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’d rather wake up next to a severed horse head than ever watch “Gotti” again. The worst movie of the year so far, the long-awaited biopic about the Gambino crime boss’ rise from made man to top do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23-foot-long python swallows woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/7-meter-long-python-swallows-indonesian-woman-111050649.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7-meter-long (23-foot-long) python has swallowed a woman in central Indonesia, a village official said Saturday. The victim, 54-year-old Wa Tiba, went missing while checking her vegetable garden near her village on Muna island in Southeast Sulawesi province on Thursday evening, according to the village</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian supermarket giant says 'yes' to mass nude photograph...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/australian-supermarket-giant-says-yes-mass-nude-photograph-075347154--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 11,000 Australians who rushed for the chance to strip for American photographer Spencer Tunick will soon wear only smiles after a national supermarket chain changed its mind about allowing the shoot to go ahead on a suburban rooftop carpark. "We're over the moon," John Lotton</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Seeks Macron's Help as Asylum Crisis Threatens EU Unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/16/merkel-seeks-macron-s-help-as-asylum-crisis-threatens-eu-unity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Seeks Macron's Help as Asylum Crisis Threatens EU Unity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Over for Nevada's Legal Brothels? Possibility of Ban Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/is-the-party-over-for-nevadas-legal-brothels-possibility-of-a-ban-looms-1529146800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 20 Nevada brothels where prostitution remains legal face possible bans amid November ballot measures and increased scrutiny of working conditions in the #MeToo era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Ultrasonic Noise Make Sick? Devices Trigger Headaches, Dizziness...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/can-ultrasonic-noise-make-you-sick-1529147100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultrasonic signals from sensors and other devices are all around us and the health effects of their interactions aren’t clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great INTERVIEW Magazine Caper...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/the-great-interview-magazine-caper/17631047/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In November, Fabien Baron was trying to collect $498,000 in back pay for his work as editorial director of Interview. The magazine’s owner, Peter Brant, was in Kentucky buying a $2 million horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine Used to Subdue Dozens at Request of Minneapolis Police...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/at-urging-of-police-hennepin-emts-subdued-dozens-with-powerful-sedative/485607381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings of a draft report prompted the Minneapolis Police Department to tell officers that it's not their role to encourage sedation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover at Bilderberg: Reporter infiltrates secret society...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5850053/Undercover-worlds-elitist-secret-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in its 66-year history a journalist penetrated security to go undercover at the hotel where the secretive Bilberberg conference was held in Turin, Italy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
