<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Fountain Of Youth' Substance May Reverse Aging In Bones...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fountain-of-youth-aging-bones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds adding acetate to specific bone marrow stem cells can reverse the aging process that weakens bones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reopening of 3 monster Broadway shows signals 'wait over'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-entertainment-lifestyle-bruce-springsteen-arts-and-entertainment-4459e4ef46f4c7617a2b2046c274763c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A digital marquee in Times Square says it all: “The Wait Is Over.” Eighteen months after the global pandemic shuttered live theater in March 2020, Broadway takes a big step forward Tuesday when three powerhouse shows — “The Lion King,” “Hamilton” and “Wicked” — rev their engines again with new safety protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Concerned Citizen' At Holmes' Trial Turns Out To Be Family...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/14/1036835868/elizabeth-holmes-trial-hotelier-bill-evans-goes-incognito</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious attendee at Elizabeth Holmes' fraud trial derided the case against her to reporters. Turns out, he was not whom he claimed to be, but was the father of Holmes' partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 ex-U.S. intel, military operatives admit to providing hacking technology to UAE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-united-states-hacking-5700a1fa8b1b4612477658b883e58f31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three former U.S. intelligence and military operatives have admitted providing sophisticated hacking technology to the United Arab Emirates and agreed to pay nearly $1.7 million to resolve criminal charges in an agreement that the Justice Department described Tuesday as the first of its kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slaughter of dolphins sparks debate on traditions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-denmark-dolphins-0a6d669d0742e56e575ed6849f1dd45b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — The slaughter of 1,428 white-sided dolphins over the weekend, part of a four-century-old traditional drive of sea mammals into shallow water where they are killed for their meat and blubber, has reignited a debate on the small Faeroe Islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BART passenger tethered to dog dies after being dragged onto tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/bart-train-drags-woman-to-death-as-shes-tethered-to-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BART passenger was dragged and killed by a train departing the Powell Street station as she was on the platform but her leashed dog remained inside the car, authorities said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Household Income Fell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/income-americans-2020-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first two stimulus payments lifted 11.7 million people out of poverty, the analysis found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion house in backlash over 'racist' $1,190 sweatpants...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-58563242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics say the $1,190 pants, which come with a built-in pair of boxer shorts, rip off US hip hop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College sports under siege -- and want K Street to save them...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/14/ncaa-college-sports-athletes-511700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NCAA is tasking seasoned D.C. hands to help it figure out a world in which college athletes can earn cash off their name and likeness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alanis Morissette Rips 'Salacious Agenda' Of HBO 'JAGGED' Doc...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/alanis-morissette-slams-jagged-film-hbo-alison-klayman-1234833230/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alanis Morissette has torn into the documentary about her landmark Jagged Little Pill album that’s set to world premiere Tuesday night at the Toronto Film Festival. On a short break in her tour wit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi mocked 'fat butt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9990487/Nancy-Pelosi-mocked-Donald-Trumps-fat-butt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi slammed then-President Donald Trump in the days following the January 6th riot on Capitol Hill, mocking him for having a 'fat butt' and saying he's 'crazy,' new book reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's Congress's Leading Progressive -- Just Not In Her Own Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/addybaird/pramila-jayapal-staff-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former staffers who worked for Rep. Pramila Jayapal, a House Democrat who built her reputation on being a champion of workers, say her treatment of her staff was often inconsistent with her public image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House encouraging state, local mandates...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914191542-rov9q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-BIDEN (URGENT):White House says it is encouraging state, local COVID vaccine mandates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56% of Young People Think Humanity Doomed...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88npnp/fifty-six-percent-of-young-people-think-humanity-is-doomed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major study of 10,000 young people across 10 different countries lays bare the scale of climate crisis-related anxiety felt around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNKIN' Opens First 'Digital-Only' Restaurant In Boston...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/dunkin-digital-only-restaurant-boston-common/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new kind of Dunkin' has just opened in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' star, stand-up comedian with cult following...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/awards/norm-macdonald-former-saturday-night-live-player-stand-comic-dies-n1279164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stand-up comedian had been privately battling cancer for nearly a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long private battle with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/norm-macdonald-dead-obituary-comedian-saturday-night-live-weekend-update-anchor-was-61-1234833212/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norm Macdonald, whose laconic delivery of sharp and incisive observations made him one of Saturday Night Live’s most influential and beloved cast members, died today after a nine-year private…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking arm amputation surgery makes 'phantom' hand seem real...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/09/14/i-can-still-feel-it-new-arm-amputation-surgery-makes-a-phantom-hand-seem-real/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The procedure aims to restore proprioception, the ability to sense where our limbs are in space and how fast and forcefully they’re moving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE unveils iPhone 13...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/apple-event-iphone-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple announced the new iPhone 13 and iPhone 13 Pro phones, new iPads and the Apple Watch Series 7 during its fall event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving boosters to healthy people 'not right,' WHO says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/giving-covid-booster-shots-to-healthy-people-is-not-right-who-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are countries with less than 2% vaccination coverage, most of them in Africa, who are not even getting their first and second dose" Tedros said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing purging celebrities, tech billionaires. Problem bigger than 'sissy men'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-purging-celebrities-tech-billionaires-100047948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the economy slows, China's crackdown on the rich and famous may be an attempt to distract from ordinary families' anxiety over their children's future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top intel officials say Al Qaeda rebuilding for USA attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/sep/14/al-qaeda-rebuilding-us-attacks-one-two-years-cia-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defeat of the American-backed government in Afghanistan has increased the danger that the al Qaeda terrorist group will launch another attack on the United States very quickly, the director of the Defense Intelligence Agency said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Jassy: 'Still early days for us in media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/amazon-ceo-andy-jassy-its-still-early-days-for-us-in-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of his first interviews since ascending to the CEO role, Amazon's Andy Jassy said the company has big ambitions in media and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  General Milley thought Trump had declined mentally in aftermath of election... MORE</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/14/fears-that-trump-might-launch-a-strike-prompted-general-to-reassure-china-book-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff twice called his Chinese counterpart in the final months of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers in CO Could Face Criminal Charges If Don't Enforce Mask Mandate; Punishable By Prison...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/tri-county-health-teachers-could-face-criminal-charges-if-they-dont-enforce-school-mask-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some parents are planning to sue Tri-County Health Department over its mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarborough Hits Republicans Crying Fraud:  What whiners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/scarborough-msnbc-larry-elder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC morning host says claiming fraud and being "losers" is now just part of Republicans' election "strategy"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spyware firm targeted APPLE devices via iMessage, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/sep/13/nso-group-iphones-apple-devices-hack-patch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery was shared with Apple, which on Monday released a patch to fix the vulnerability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNET KILLED THE VIDEO STAR:  MTV Music Awards Draws Less Than Million Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/14/mtvs-video-music-awards-scored-less-than-a-million-viewers-on-mtv-and-not-much-more-anywhere-else</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know things are bad when MTV’s Video Music Awards barely score ratings on MTV. Sunday’s show had 900,000 viewers on the main channel, and a smattering elsewhere on channels like VH1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Senate Dems strike deal with Manchin on voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-senate-democrats-get-deal-with-manchin-on-voting-rights/ar-AAOqKLZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Senior Senate Democrats have reached agreement with moderate Senator Joe Manchin on a broad overhaul of U.S. voting rights law, a development that should unify all Democrats in the chamber behind a single plan for the first time. The measure would create an automatic voter registration system through each state’s motor vehicle agency, make Election Day a public holiday and provide voters with at least 15 days of early voting for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVED BY ELDER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/14/politics/larry-elder-covid-newsom-recall/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this year, when California Gov. Gavin Newsom was searching for the right message to convince disengaged Democrats to vote against the effort to oust him in Tuesday's recall election, it would have been impossible to imagine a more perfect foil than conservative talk radio host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 BODIES FOUND IN CREEPY WISCONSIN CORN FIELD; SITTING IN BLACK SUV...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/nation-world/national/article254229133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s like something out of a horror movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hand Sanitizer Poisoning In Children On Rise; Kids Getting Drunk...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/moon-township-elementary-school-hand-sanitizer-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Moon Township mother has a warning for every parent out there about hand sanitizer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why TV Producers Are STILL Betting on Broadcast in Streaming Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/can-broadcast-tv-survive-in-the-streaming-era-these-shows-are-betting-on-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of another fall TV season, showrunners tell TheWrap what it's like to launch a new broadcast series in a world dominated by Netflix</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANDSLIDE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/newsom-is-up-big-in-california-heres-why-pundits-got-fooled-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today’s climate, motivating the base isn’t enough to win on enemy turf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reputed Colombo crime family boss among a dozen mobsters snared in bust... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/investigations/reputed-nyc-mob-boss-among-a-dozen-snared-in-fraud-corruption-bust-sources/3270937/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD and FBI arrested a dozen alleged mobsters, including a reputed Colombo crime family boss, early Tuesday on charges connected to healthcare fraud allegations and union-related corruption, law enforcement sources said. The arrests, which sources say include reputed 87-year-old Colombo street boss Andrew Russo, also known as “Mush,” and an underboss, 83-year-old Benjamin “Benji” Castellazzo, were conducted in the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pulled from BMW in Manhattan carjacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/driver-pulled-from-bmw-assaulted-and-robbed-in-manhattan-carjacking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were searching for a group of motorcyclists who carjacked and assaulted a man driving a BMW in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm leaves Texas town underwater...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/live-tropical-storm-nicholas-updates-texas-louisiana-flooding/1016769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic drone images show the town of Seabrook, Texas, surrounded by storm surge after Nicholas made landfall early Tuesday. Plus, hundreds of thousands were without power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecution witness in Netanyahu trial killed in plane crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/prosecution-witness-in-netanyahu-trial-and-his-wife-killed-in-greek-plane-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haim Geron was a former deputy director of the Communication Ministry; light plane he was piloting went down after apparent technical fault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poverty Rate Rose From 60-Year Low, Incomes Fell Amid Virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-poverty-rate-rose-from-60-year-low-incomes-fell-amid-virus/ar-AAOqYyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. household income fell in 2020 while the national poverty rate rose from a 60-year low as the Covid-19 pandemic upended the U.S. economy and threw millions out of work. Median, inflation-adjusted household income decreased 2.9% last year to $67,521 according to annual data released Tuesday by the U.S. Census Bureau. The poverty rate rose one percentage point to 11.4% after having dropped for five straight years and reaching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's 'Mad Max' stokes anti-vax rage -- and could help Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914141144-0bh3k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA-ELECTION/BERNIER (PIX):Canada's 'Mad Max' stokes anti-vax rage - and could help Trudeau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists Smoking Toad Venom in Mexico Hipster Town Tulum...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx53e5/tourists-are-now-smoking-toad-venom-in-mexicos-hipster-town-tulum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Observers are split on the consequences of “speed-toading” using the venom, called bufo, as a cure for the ills of the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Enyart, Anti-Vax 'Real Science Radio' Host, Dies of COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bob-enyart-anti-vax-real-science-radio-host-dies-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Denver radio personality was also known for "gleefully" mocking those who died from AIDS on his defunct TV show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Unmanned Vessel Spotted In San Diego Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42358/this-mysterious-unmanned-vessel-was-just-spotted-in-san-diego-bay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The low-slung drone-ship catamaran is equipped with solar panels, various antennae, and camera systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Warships Sailing Near Alaska; Shadowed By Coast Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42352/chinese-warships-sailing-near-alaskas-aleutian-islands-shadowed-by-u-s-coast-guard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pictures of the Chinese vessels off Alaska emerged after criticism of similar American naval activity from one of China's main state media outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAY OR GO?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-california-climate-elections-a590782877be099d44f1766b2d138394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONG BEACH, Calif. (AP) — After a year of debate that laid bare divisions in America's most populous state, Californians on Tuesday will be deciding whether Gov. Gavin Newsom keeps his job, or if the state goes in a more conservative direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving biggest name for last, Biden joins Newsom to campaign on eve of recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/saving-the-biggest-name-for-last-biden-joins-newsom-to-campaign-on-eve-of-recall/ar-AAOpbpt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two campaigned on covid-19 restrictions as the key to ending the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gavin team: No scenario where we lose...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-team-no-scenario-where-we-lose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom's team seems to be striking a confident tone just a day before Tuesday's California recall election, and said that there's no "scenario where we lose."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Jim Breuer won't perform at venues requiring vax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/572113-comedian-jim-breuer-wont-perform-at-venues-requiring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Jim Breuer says he's "absolutely not" performing shows at venues that require proof of COVID-19 vaccinations, calling the public health measures "segregation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overeating doesn't cause obesity? Scientists claim all about what you're eating...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/overeating-doesnt-cause-obesity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team adds that despite years of public health messaging about eating less and exercising more, cases of obesity continue to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Order Sparks Price-Gouging for Fake Vax Cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joe-biden-mandate-sparks-price-gouging-for-fake-vax-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s clear to us they’re using current events to galvanize the market,” researchers at cybersecurity firm Check Point found, said spokesperson Ekram Ahmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran could build nuke in month?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3657650/iran-month-away-from-building-first-nuclear-bomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN is a “month away” from having enough lethal uranium to build a nuclear bomb in a chilling threat to the West, experts claim. Tehran is closer than ever to reaching bomb-grade level…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrifying tale of prostitute orangutan chained to bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3657105/prostitute-orangutan-pony-tragic-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHAINED to a wall and lying on a dirty mattress with a full face of make-up, Pony the orangutan waited for her next client. Men working in the nearby palm oil farm in Borneo would come into the bro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3,586,456,000,000: Federal Tax Collections Set Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/3586456000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $3,586,456,000,000 in total taxes through first eleven months of fiscal 2021 (September through August), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer price index rises 5.3% in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/consumer-price-index-august-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index was expected to increase 5.4% from a year ago in August, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fence back up...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/571981-capitol-fence-is-going-back-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fence surrounding the U.S. Capitol is set to return ahead of the pro-Trump rally on Sept. 18, the head of the Capitol Police confirmed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400,000 without power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914103355-vgwdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-NICHOLAS/CENTERPOINT-POWER (URGENT):Storm Nicholas knocks out power to over 400,000 customers in Texas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians to decide gov's fate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914095923-0szuz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-RECALL/ (PIX, TV):Californians to decide governor's fate in Republican-backed recall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Thirds of Businesses Around World Struggling to Hire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/two-thirds-of-businesses-around-the-world-are-struggling-to-hire/ar-AAOpHcP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Businesses around the world want to hire but face a similar dilemma: attracting workers. A survey of nearly 45,000 employers across 43 countries showed 69% of employers reported difficulty filling roles, a 15-year high, according to employment-services provider ManpowerGroup Inc. At the same time, 15 countries -- focused in Europe and North America -- reported their highest hiring intentions since the survey began in 1962....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man roams Galveston beach dressed as 'HALLOWEEN' Michael Myers...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/halloween-michael-myers-tropical-storm-nicholas-galveston-beach-costume/11018578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh, you know, no big deal. Just Michael Myers roaming Galveston beach as a hurricane heads toward Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human remains found inside 504-pound gator suspected in Ida attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article254213953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sunherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities captured the animal early Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deaths of despair' worsen among Americans lacking college degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/deaths-of-despair-worsen-among-americans-lacking-college-degrees/ar-AAOoWKl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the U.S., a four-year degree is increasingly a “talisman” against deaths related to suicide and economic hardship, according to a new research paper that offers a stark verdict on the current economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin self-isolates after Covid cases in inner circle...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210914-putin-self-isolates-after-covid-cases-in-inner-circle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin self-isolates after Covid cases in inner circle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Palm Reader Launches at Ampitheatre in Sneak Peek of Biometric Future...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazons-palm-reader-launches-at-first-non-amazon-venue-1847670790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Red Rocks Amphitheatre in Denver will use the new tech for ticketed events.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
