<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Trans more politically conservative than straight men...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/study-finds-transgender-people-more-politically-conservative-than-straight-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Trans men and women have a different relationship with liberalism.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacation -- to live longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/comment/why-go-on-a-holiday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Ramps Up Attacks on FOXNEWS For Poll Showing Him Losing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/trump-ramps-up-attacks-on-fox-news-for-poll-showing-him-down-to-biden-no-way-im-losing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is President Donald Trump's long-standing love affair with Fox News waning? Judging by Friday morning tweets, he's certainly disgruntled with the network. Trump has long been an enormous fan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Border agents give illegals hand up hill, around wall -- into USA...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-border-agents-give-illegals-hand-up-hill-around-wall-into-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When did Customs and Border Patrol become the welcoming committee to America? Video published by KOLD shows Border agents standing at the top of a hill, waiting for a group of illegal aliens to approach. The agent crosses past the end of the border wall and extends his hand to assist a woman scaling the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida officials clarify stance on green iguanas: Don't shoot them...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/25/green-iguanas-florida-clarifies-message-kill-whenever-possible/1833420001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission is asking residents to seek help from professionals if they can't safely remove green iguanas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN SPIRAL: BART elevator attendants attempt to stop urinators...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/resources/transit/article/bart-elevator-attendants-powell-civic-dirty-14135435.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the years, BART has tried a variety of strategies to keep people from behaving badly in station elevators (including one memorable poster campaign in which sad, anthropomorphized elevators dolefully declared, "I'm not a bathroom").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 3% Growth Feat Undone by Data Revisions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-26/trump-s-3-growth-feat-in-2018-undone-by-annual-data-revisions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 cats fatally mauled by 2 pit bulls at shelter...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/29-cats-fatally-mauled-pit-bulls-alabama-shelter-64584606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two city officials say an Alabama animal shelter's outdated equipment allowed two pit bulls to fatally maul 29 cats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joaquin Phoenix descent into 'JOKER' madness...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/movies/2019/07/25/joker-new-photos-show-joaquin-phoenix-full-descent-into-madness/1832969001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three new photos for Todd Phillips' "Joker" chart the complete course of Joaquin Phoenix's descent into villainous madness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Beijing takes over Hollywood blockbuster; Studios adapting to censored market...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/times2/how-china-is-influencing-hollywood-movies-and-tom-cruises-new-top-gun-jacket-2rcwq773v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yay, Top Gun is back! Did you see the trailer for the sequel, Top Gun: Maverick, which “dropped” last week? It shows Tom Cruise, as everyone’s favourite flying ace Maverick, going supersonic in jets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Thinks About Sex 8 Times Per Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/adults-think-about-sex-8-times-per-day-on-average-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people do a pretty good job of pushing sexual thoughts out of their heads until the appropriate time and place, but a new survey has found that sex still pops into most adults heads eight times per day on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undead take DC in zombie thriller...</title>
      <link>https://www.slashfilm.com/zombieland-double-tap-trailer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.slashfilm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's time to nut up or shut up again with the Zombieland Double Tap trailer, teasing the sequel that is arriving 10 years after the first movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Editor Celebrated Deaths of 'Jewish Pigs' in Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/nicholas-fondacaro/2019/07/25/cnn-photo-editor-celebrated-deaths-jewish-pigs-anti-semitic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, CNN photo editor Mohammed Elshamy was exposed as an anti-Semite after numerous political operatives and news outlets dove into his Twitter history and discovered his hatred. Elshamy has since made his Twitter account private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: A.I. Predictive Policing Could Lead to Mass Incarceration...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7287341/AI-experts-release-statement-slamming-predictive-policing-digitizing-stop-frisk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say predictive algorithms have a tendency to overestimate accused peoples' risk of violence when in fact, the likelihood of crimes committed during trials is small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSI: GOOGLE 'Almost Total Control' over Key Election Elements...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/07/25/tulsi-gabbard-lawsuit-google-has-almost-total-control-over-key-elements-of-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate and military veteran Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-HI) is suing Google, claiming in her lawsuit that the company as "almost total control" over key elements of elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protests Become Global Problem as Tensions Escalate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-protests-become-global-110005325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tensions between Hong Kong and the government in Beijing are increasingly spilling outside China’s borders.China’s foreign ministry this week accused the U.S. of being a “black hand” behind protests that have rocked Hong Kong since early June, while Secretary of State Michael Pompeo urged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Outlines Space War Plans...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/china-outlines-space-war-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's strategy for developing advanced space weapons were disclosed this week in Beijing's first defense white paper issued in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says missile test was warning to South 'warmongers'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef8e8e174c8b42a496b84484b2b58c74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busiest day in aviation history; 225,000+ flights!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/flightradar24/status/1154399755075751936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Yesterday, we tracked over 225,000 flights in a single day for the first time. Follow more than 20,000 flights right now at https://t.co/A4mWRJu9Vi.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon tax shows new signs of life in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/454819-carbon-tax-shows-new-signs-of-life-in-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Congress on both sides of the aisle are introducing competing bills that aim to put a tax on carbon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Biden: 'You can't let people say bullshit and not respond to it'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/454802-team-biden-fires-back-you-cant-let-people-say-bullshit-and-not-respond-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is ready to scrap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems divided on path forward... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Democrats-second-guess-calling-Mueller-divided-14152728.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats are struggling to figure out their next move against President Donald Trump after their highly anticipated hearing with Robert Mueller III fell flat, forcing some Democrats to second-guess their strategy while aggravating divisions in the party over impeachment.  Several centrist Democrats seized on the absence of a major revelation to argue it was time to end House investigations into whether Trump tried to obstruct the former special counsel's probe and pivot to legislation.  "Anyone who was looking for the smoking gun yesterday didn't get it," said Rep. Anthony Brindisi, D-N.Y., who ousted a Republican incumbent by fewer than 500 votes in last year's midterm elections. "It's time to move on and focus on getting some bills passed here that can get signed into law."  But that plea had no effect on the pro-impeachment Democrats, who dug in, insisting that House oversight of Trump and his administration has been ineffective and pressed for launching proceedings.  In a closed-door caucus meeting Wednesday night, after Mueller's testimony, proponents tried to convince House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., to move ahead on impeachment, a step she has resisted.  "There's no question that if we're serious about accountability, we put our strongest foot forward to get information and enforce subpoenas to shape this narrative," said Rep. Jared Huffman, D-Calif., who complained that the House's current strategy was a "slow-walk."  He said it was a mistake for Democrats to rely on Mueller - a 74-year-old reluctant witness who had made clear that he would not provide the blockbuster moment the party craved - to make their case to the public.  "We are not potted plants. We can actually shape some of this public sentiment," Huffman said. "We're not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK co-founder campaigning to break up tech 'monopoly' he helped create...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Facebook-co-founder-campaigning-to-break-up-tech-14149729.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Facebook co-founder Chris Hughes has become one of the company's biggest problems.  In recent weeks, Hughes, who left the social media giant in 2007 and cashed out his nearly $500 million worth of stock, has been making the rounds in the nation's capital, visiting a dozen lawmakers and regulators at the Department of Justice, the Federal Trade Commission and other agencies which are all interested in examining whether Facebook has amassed too much power. He's talked with the attorney general of New York.  In those meetings, which he sometimes attended on his own, he has presented a 39-page slide deck that makes a point-by-point legal case for breaking up the social network drawing on decades of antitrust law precedent.  The crux of the case, designed with the help of two antitrust scholars: Facebook's wealth and power and massive user base have pushed it into monopoly territory, and its acquisitions of rivals have squashed competition. More than 2.7 billion people use Facebook or its other platforms, which include Instagram and messaging service WhatsApp, at least once a month, Facebook said Wednesday.  "I hope that my speaking out provides cover to a lot of other folks, whether former employees or current ones, to express ambivalence or concern about what's going on," Hughes said in an interview Thursday. "And I think there's a lot to be concerned about."  Hughes, who helped develop the social media giant with Mark Zuckerberg in their Harvard University dorm, has become a critical weapon to trust busters in a fight that keeps expanding in scope, threatening tech giants including Amazon, Apple and Google with potential new regulation or even a breakup. Just this week, the Justice Department said it was launching a new, expanded probe targeting "market-leading online platforms," And on Wednesday, Facebook...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Changing CBP Operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/07/how-facial-recognition-changing-cbp-operations/158704/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech is freeing up Customs and Border Protection employees—once they learned to trust it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON BROIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7284247/Europe-heatwave-Hottest-day-forecast-continent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soaring temperatures are expected to peak today, breaking heat records across the continent and putting lives at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Intelligence panel releases first chapter of report into Russian interference...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/election-security-report-on-russian-meddling-released-by-senate-intelligence-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee says that though the country was unprepared in 2016 for the Russian attacks on its election infrastructure, the U.S. has learned "much more" about the nature of Russian cyber meddling and better understands the threat it poses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cooler filled with male genitalia' found in raid of Phoenix body-donation company...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-health/2019/07/19/cooler-penises-frankenstein-head-found-phoenix-body-donation-company/1720254001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-three plaintiffs have sued Biological Resource Center, saying the company lied to families and treated bodies with a lack of dignity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEWART:  Tarantino's exploitation has no place anymore...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/25/quentin-tarantinos-exploitation-has-no-place-in-hollywood-anymore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino’s new movie, “Once Upon a Time in . . . Hollywood,” is a love letter to the film industry days of yore — the late ’60s, to be exact. Men were men, female actors were “starlets” an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILLEGALS BY THE NUMBERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cbba8ede5436460ab4f792f981ee32e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans aware of Mueller 'frailty' ahead of hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/25/robert-mueller-frailty-known-republicans-ahead-tes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans had expected former special counsel Robert Mueller’s feeble testimony and some even strategized around that fact as they prepared their questions, Rep. Matt Gaetz said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL TALK:  Dem Presidential Hopefuls Have Made 1,200 Podcast Appearances...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/democrats-podcast-presidential-primary-marianne-williamson-andrew-yang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marianne Williamson and Andrew Yang have spent more time on podcasts than most 2020 Democratic presidential contenders. Has it helped?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran test fires ballistic missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9587313/iran-fires-ballistic-missile-test-tanker-row-us-uk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has reportedly test fired a ballistic missile amid escalating tensions with the US and UK in the Gulf. The Shahab-3 missile travelled 1,000km, but did not pose a threat to shipping or US bases…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of designer proteins; Turns cells on and off... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-scientist.com/news-opinion/designer-protein-acts-as-a-switch-for-cellular-circuitry-66200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-scientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike biotech tools adapted from nature, the invention was entirely conceived by humans and represents one of the few proteins made from scratch in the lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS turned over Nixon's tax returns same day congressional panel asked for them...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/IRS-turned-over-Nixon-s-tax-returns-same-day-that-14146359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Internal Revenue Service turned President Richard Nixon's tax returns over to a congressional committee the same day in 1973 that the panel requested them for a review, according to letters released by House Democrats on Thursday.  The newly released documents appear to contradict the Trump administration's claims that House Democrats' demands for the president's tax returns are "unprecedented," and suggest a split between this administration and prior IRS officials over the interpretation of the law.  On Dec. 13, 1973, Laurence Woodworth of the Joint Committee on Taxation asked the commissioner of the IRS to review Nixon's tax returns from 1969 through 1972, according to the documents. Nixon had asked the congressional committee to review the documents amid the widening Watergate scandal.  In a letter to the committee also dated Dec. 13, 1973, IRS Commissioner Donald Alexander said that enclosed in his response were attachments of "true copies of the original joint federal income tax returns filed by Richard M. and Patricia R. Nixon" for the years requested.  House Ways and Means Committee Chairman Richard Neal, D-Mass., has requested six years of Trump's personal and business tax returns, from 2013 to 2018, a period that includes several years before Trump became president.  Neal recently sued the Trump administration in federal court to obtain the records, after Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin argued in a May letter that Neal's "unprecedented request" should be denied.  The Ways and Means Committee voted in executive session to make the documents public. In a memo sent Thursday to other members of the committee, Neal said the letters confirm his interpretation of code section 6103, which pertains to congressional requests for private taxpayer information.  "Section...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denial of bail stunned billionaire... </title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-jeffrey-epstein-jail-20190725-magu4viicrczbgr65pe6qjcw3y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexual predator Jeffrey Epstein was found semi-conscious inside his MCC cell earlier this week with possibly self-inflicted marks on his neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS 'MONITOR' MIGRANTS IN TEX</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/active-duty-u-s-troops-are-now-just-feet-away-n1034416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The troops "monitor" migrants at a Texas facility. One congressman said they shouldn't be prison guards, and are close to breaking the posse comitatus law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government expands on Trump watch...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/854622/gops-stupid-swoon-big-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative nationalists are now selling the virtues of industrial policy. Big mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 108&amp;#176;  PARIS!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/europes-record-setting-heatwave-spike-even-higher-032037783.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris on Thursday baked in an all-time high temperature of 42.6 degrees Celsius (108.7 Fahrenheit) as a ferocious heatwave smashed records across northern Europe, sparking concerns about public health and causing new misery for rail travellers. As records also tumbled in Belgium, the Netherlands and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON BROIL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/352387083bf7459797046f2306b2794b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White professor sues black university for racial discrimination...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/white-professor-sues-black-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white professor at a historically black university in Alabama has filed a federal lawsuit against the school&amp;nbsp;for age and racial discrimination after he claims they have denied him the salary he deserves, despite his tenure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg: Kavanaugh 'Very Decent' Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/ruth-bader-ginsburg-brett-kavanaugh-is-a-very-decent-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The liberal star of the Supreme Court praises the character and intellect of Neil Gorsuch and Brett Kavanaugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodstock 50 fest will go on -- in Maryland...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190725-woodstock-50-fest-will-go-maryland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woodstock 50 fest will go on -- in Maryland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Philippines, content moderators see worst of web -- and suffer silently...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/In-the-Philippines-content-moderators-at-14130284.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines - A year after quitting his job reviewing some of the most gruesome content the internet has to offer, Lester prays every week that the images he saw can be erased from his mind.  First as a contractor for YouTube and then for Twitter, he worked on a high-up floor of a mall in this traffic-clogged Asian capital, where he spent up to nine hours each day weighing questions about the details in those images. He made decisions about whether a child's genitals were being touched accidentally or on purpose, or whether a knife slashing someone's neck depicted a real-life killing - and if such content should be allowed online.  He's still haunted by what he saw. Today, entering a tall building triggers flashbacks to the suicides he reviewed, causing him to entertain the possibility of jumping. At night, he Googles footage of bestiality and incest - material he was never exposed to before but now is ashamed that he is drawn to. For the last year, he has visited a mall chapel every week, where he works with a church brother to ask God to "white out" those images from his memory.  "I know it's not normal, but now everything is normalized," said the 33-year-old, using only his first name because of a confidentiality agreement he signed when he took the job.  Workers such as Lester are on the front lines of the never-ending battle to keep the internet safe. But thousands of miles separate the Philippines and Silicon Valley, rendering these workers vulnerable to exploitation by some of the world's tech giants.  In the last couple of years, social media companies have created tens of thousands of jobs around the world to vet and delete violent or offensive content, attempting to shore up their reputations after failing to adequately police content including live-streamed terrorist attacks and Russian disinformation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Baltimore Police Dept Employee Brutally Attacked, Carjacked...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/07/25/brazen-attacks-caught-on-camera-around-baltimore-another-family-carjacked-exclusive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazen attacks caught on camera around Baltimore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move on? No thanks. Both sides to keep talking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a1c69423ca894fc49541791230b6b269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA hopes to resume talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/u-s-calls-for-no-more-north-korean-provocations-hopes-to-resume-talks-idUSKCN1UK2SG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States on Thursday urged North Korea to refrain from further provocat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Founder Working With Gov to Break It Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/25/technology/chris-hughes-facebook-breakup.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Hughes has joined two leading academics to argue to government officials that Facebook has engaged in anticompetitive behavior for almost a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flyboard hero fails in attempt to cross English Channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/franky-zapata-flyboard-channel-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French inventor Franky Zapata failed in his attempt to cross the English Channel on his jet-powered Flyboard, after missing a platform mounted on a boat as he tried to land midway for refueling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Journalists Demanding Entertainment, Not Doing Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/public_editor/msnbc-chuck-todd-mueller-testimony.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fired off 'new type' of missile in defiance of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/north-korea-launched-new-type-of-missile-in-latest-test-2019-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have suggested that the weapons North Korea has been testing this year could be the key to a first strike, one that could evade defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedate charity lunch with Warren Buffett turning into bizarre affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/25/normally-sedate-charity-lunch-with-warren-buffett-is-turning-into-bizarre-affair-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Sun, a Chinese cryptocurrency entrepreneur who paid a record $4.57 million to dine with Warren Buffett, abruptly apologized for his "out-of-control, excessive self promotion."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bright Fireball' Spotted Streaking Across Northeast Skies...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/07/25/meteor-video-newton-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Meteor Society said it received more than two-hundred reports about a “bright fireball over the East Coast” Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stem cells, 3-D printing could make baldness obsolete...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/07/hair-for-all/594826/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New uses of stem cells and 3-D printing could make baldness obsolete (for the wealthy).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Marines Arrested for Human Trafficking, Drug Smuggling...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2019/07/25/16-camp-pendleton-marines-arrested-by-ncis-during-battalion-formation-for-alleged-human-smuggling-and-drug-offenses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrests follow the July 3 detention of two Marine grunts near the U.S.-Mexico border by Border Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused wife killer claims powerful group infected him with mayonnaise...</title>
      <link>https://www.kget.com/news/crime-watch/man-accused-of-killing-wife-claims-powerful-group-infected-him-with-mayonnaise-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAKERSFIELD, Calif. (KGET) — Arrested in the death of his wife, Nathaniel Robertson admitted during an interview with sheriff’s detectives to beating her with a concrete block. But Robe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RATINGS BUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/robert-mueller-hearings-draw-13m-viewers-fox-news-msnbc-lead-1226985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel's testimony before Congress brings in a smaller audience than some other recent televised hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall-like air breaks record lows in southern USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/fall-like-air-to-threaten-record-lows-from-early-1900s-in-parts-of-southern-us/70008881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Buyouts at NEWSDAY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/25/patrick-dolans-newsday-offers-voluntary-buyouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Dolan’s Newsday took staffers by “surprise” Thursday when executives of the largest newspaper on Long Island said it is offering voluntary buyouts, The Post has learned. “They called everyo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How USA Could Lose War With China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/07/china-us-war/594793/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not that the Chinese Communist Party would take over Washington. But in its own region, China has the advantage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Marines arrested for alleged crimes including human smuggling...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/25/politics/us-marines-arrested/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen US Marines were arrested Thursday for alleged involvement in various illegal activities ranging from human smuggling to drug-related offenses, according to a statement from the Marine Corps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi sues GOOGLE over censorship claims...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/454746-tulsi-gabbard-sues-google-over-censorship-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-Hawaii), a 2020 presidential contender, is suing Google over claims that the tech behemoth violated her right to "free speech."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Tourist Savagely Beaten, Stomped, Spit on by Gang of Youths...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/07/shock-video-dc-tourist-savagely-beaten-stomped-spit-on-by-gang-of-youths-at-hilton-hotel-where-reagan-was-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Mother Teresa aide killed in bar brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/former-assistant-mother-teresa-killed-bar-brawl-n1034436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Bloomfield, 54, died Sunday from injuries he suffered in Swansea, Wales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper A$AP Rocky to be tried for assault in Stockholm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sweden-decide-rapper-ap-rocky-charge-030550356.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Swedish prosecutor said Thursday that US rapper ASAP Rocky will be tried for assault over a June street brawl in a decision likely to infuriate fans already indignant over his three weeks in custody. "Today I have pressed charges against the three suspects for assault, because in my judgement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 61,000 migrant children surge over border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/record-61-000-migrant-children-surge-over-border-230m-spent-for-snacks-diapers-baby-formula</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 61,000 unaccompanied migrant children have surged over the U.S.-Mexico border and been handed to federal care facilities since October, and there are still over two months left in the fiscal year, according to immigration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTV rolls dice with serious documentaries... </title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/07/25/mtv-documentary-slate-with-legendary-producer-sheila-nevins-announced-can-she-make-vapid-channel-important-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MTV at present is mired in a schedule of junk. It’s all reality programming on the low end, a tribute to vapidity. But now comes Sheila Nevins, an actual legend of documentary filmmaking, hir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans balk as budget vote looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/25/house-gop-budget-vote-1433848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measure is expected to pass, but GOP support remains thin despite Trump's backing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper circulation lowest level since 1940...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/07/23/key-takeaways-state-of-the-news-media-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newspaper circulation in the U.S. reached its lowest level since 1940, and the audience for local TV news has steadily declined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Plastic Surgeons React to Breast Implant Recall: 'Don't Panic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/beverly-hills-plastic-surgeons-react-breast-implant-recall-dont-panic-1226768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FDA recall on Allergan's Biocell textured implants may affect some cross-fit trainers and yoga instructors in Los Angeles, but only about five percent of breast implants sold in the U.S. are textured, as opposed to smooth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy victory dance after Mueller mess...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/robert-mueller-hearings-rudy-giuliani-reaction-04c5ce69-cf13-4a68-8e24-da4cfcd22942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Soon it will be The End and credits will appear."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dog Who Was Shot 17 Times Becomes Therapy Dog...</title>
      <link>http://news.animalchannel.co/blind-dog-shot-17-times-becomes-therapy-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.animalchannel.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This dog's spirit and strength are incredible!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Site to Charge $3.99 Per Month for Twice Daily News Texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cleveland-website-to-charge-3-99-per-month-for-twice-daily-news-texts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the future of paywalled journalism?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY Gamble...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/can-once-a-time-hollywood-deliver-an-original-adult-tentpole-1226843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino's latest undertaking stars two of the world's biggest movie stars — Leonardo DiCaprio and Brad Pitt — but is a sizeable risk for Sony and the maverick filmmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General orders first federal executions in two decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/25/william-barr-orders-first-federal-executions-in-nearly-two-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government will resume executing death-row inmates after nearly two decades without doing so, the Department of Justice announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Stirs Controversy With Only Two Women Directors, Place For Polanski...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/venice-women-directors-roman-polanski-twitter-1202653389/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Venice Film Festival has soared in recent years but the 2019 lineup could provoke the festival’s biggest polemic yet after artistic director Alberto Barbera revealed a 21-strong competiti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Punishes Whistleblowing Engineer with Administrative Leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/corinne-weaver/2019/07/25/google-punishes-whistleblowing-engineer-administrative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hive known as Google is quick to punish those who undermine its authority. Hours after Google engineer Greg Coppola appeared with James O’Keefe in a Project Veritas video, he was put on administrative leave by his company. In the video, Coppola said that he believed that Google News and Google’s search engine algorithms were biased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Frail' Performance ...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/this-is-painful-pundits-question-muellers-frail-performance-at-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of pundits this morning have been questioning former special counsel Robert Mueller's performance at the hearing thus far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain sends warships to escort tankers in Hormuz...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Britain-sends-warships-to-escort-tankers-the-14128080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates - Britain has begun sending navy ships to accompany vessels traveling through the narrow Strait of Hormuz following the seizure of a British-flagged tanker by Iranian forces.  In a statement, Britain's Department of Defense said that "the Royal Navy has been tasked to accompany British-flagged ships through the Strait of Hormuz, either individually or in groups, should sufficient notice be given of their passage."  HMS Montrose, a Royal Navy Type 23 frigate, became the first navy ship to offer an escort overnight on Wednesday into Thursday in the narrow waterway, Sky News reported on Thursday, citing shipping industry sources.  Britain made the decision just days after the seizure of the Stena Impero by Iran's Revolutionary Guard Corps, a British-flagged tanker, as it as it passed through the Strait of Hormuz on Friday.  Iran subsequently claimed that the Stena Impero was passing through the wrong channels of the strait and had also turned off its signals for longer than allowed.  However, the seizure was widely interpreted as a tit-for-tat measure in response to British marines taking part in the seizure of an Iranian-flagged tanker near Gibraltar, a British overseas territory off the coast of Spain.  Britain said it sent Royal Marines to board and take control of the Grace 1 tanker because it was suspected of transporting oil to Syria, a violation of European Union sanctions targeting Syria's government.  On Wednesday, Iranian President Hassan Rouhani appeared to suggest that Tehran would consider releasing the Stena Impero if Britain released the Grace 1.  Britain has previously suggested that seizure of the Iranian tanker needed to be resolved by Gibraltar's courts and called on Iran to provide evidence that the tanker was not en route to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machines 'so intelligent' will be 'like gods'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/792485/killer-robots-artificial-intelligence-transhumanism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen from prison: 'American people deserve more'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/454664-michael-cohen-from-prison-american-people-deserve-more-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen on Wednesday weighed in on former special counsel Robert Mueller’s congressional testimony, saying that "The American people deserve more" in a statement issued from the federal correctio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pit Bulls Fatally Maul Entire Alpaca Herd...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/07/24/alpaca-owner-devasted-as-pit-bulls-maul-her-herd-in-soquel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Soquel neighborhood is on edge after two pit bulls mauled and killed a herd of alpacas that have brought joy to a local preschool of kids for several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas district to begin drug testing students as young as 12...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/07/25/texas-school-district-drug-testing-students-as-young-as-12/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A school district in Texas will begin drug testing students as young as 12 years old who are interested in playing sports or participating in other extracurricular activities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
