<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Obamas ready to debut their first film...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/8/hollywood-regulars-obamas-ready-to-debut-their-fir/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama and Michelle Obama, who signed an exclusive production deal with Netflix some 15 months ago, are now readying their first release, a documentary titled “American Factory,” which debuts Aug. 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun activists warn could lose their votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/gun-rights-supporters-say-trump-could-lose-their-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week before calling for more gun control laws, President Trump invited boos at a massive Ohio campaign rally, warning 17,000 supporters that if Democrats reclaim power, “there is no Second Amendment.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To keep Texas county red, Republican says time to become politically intolerant...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/sns-tns-bc-texas-gop-intolerance-20190809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas There's a new political battle cry in Tarrant County, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missle test gone wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1163716/Russia-latest-news-Putin-military-explosion-nuclear-missile-radiation-leak-world-war-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN naval base is on a mysterious month-long lockdown after an accidental missile explosion at the base was linked to a sudden radiation spike in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armie Hammer calls out MARVEL exec Trump contributions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/456834-armie-hammer-calls-out-marvel-chairmans-trump-contributions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armie Hammer on Friday called out one of the most powerful men in entertainment over his politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER explosion...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/russia/201908091076515014-new-explosion-hits-military-facility-in-russias-south-five-injured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, a fire erupted at a military depot located near the Siberian city of Achinsk, which caused multiple explosions and left 12 people injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson lost 40 pounds through starvation in jail...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/tommy-robinson-40-pounds-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDIDATE FATIGUE IN IOWA</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/too-many-candidates-iowans-tired-051716837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jake Poorman is exhausted. Iowans treasure the national attention that shines on them every four years when presidential candidates descend on the state, whose caucuses mark the beginning of an election year. The concern isn't limited to Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man reports Glock stolen during weekend-long orgy at home...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/gun-stolen-during-weekend-gathering-274938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 8--In the midst of a weekend-long orgy, a 9mm handgun was stolen from the host's bedroom, according to Florida police who are not confident in catching the thief since guests at the gathering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sleep loss 'breathalyzer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7338853/Scientists-identify-way-spot-brain-impaired-lack-shut-eye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from the NASA Ames Research Center in California says that tracking eye-movements were significantly impaired from people who didn't get enough sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME FOR A BREAK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/955b8436cd084f58a42ff96ee78330ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Hoarding Food, Gold In Anticipation Of Global Collapse?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/is-china-hoarding-food-gold-and-other-commodities-in-anticipation-of-a-global-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does China believe that we are on the verge of a major global crisis?  The communist Chinese government has always been very big into planning, and it appears that they have decided that now is the time to hoard food, gold and other commodities.  Of course in recent days the fact that China is compl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TACO BELL hotel in Palm Springs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/food/story/2019-08-08/taco-bell-hotel-palm-springs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We got a room at the Taco Bell hotel in Palm Springs. This is our story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS OF PUTIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/after-20-years-is-vladimir-putins-untouchable-image-crumbling/a-49953706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During Vladimir Putin's two decades in power, polls have often shown Russians blame their government rather than their president for their problems. Amidst a new wave of domestic tension, that could be changing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Alligator Eats Woman's 100-Pound Dog...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/florida-woman-alligator-ate-her-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman says an alligator ate her 100-pound dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Asks Clerk For 'Anything That Would Kill 200 People'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/florida-man-walmart-employee-anything-kill-200-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man ran into some trouble with police on Thursday, after he reportedly asked a Walmart clerk for "anything that would kill 200 people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban voters in red states threaten GOP grip on power...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Suburban-voters-in-red-states-threaten-GOP-s-grip-14292534.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKHAVEN, Ga. - Republicans face a reckoning in the red-state suburbs that have long been a bedrock for the party, propelled by the stormy confluence of President Donald Trump's searing racial attacks, economic turbulence and frustration with government inaction after last weekend's deadly mass shootings in Texas and Ohio.  The GOP lost its House majority in 2018 after it fared poorly with suburban voters, particularly women. Party leaders are increasingly alarmed that they have made little progress winning them back. Instead, Trump's incessant feuds, his hard-line position on immigration - including federal raids that left children without their parents - and the stock market's tumult amid his trade standoff with China threaten to further alienate suburban voters ahead of the 2020 campaign, even in states that have traditionally elected Republicans.  Republican leaders also worry that Trump's dramatic policy moves and Twitter outbursts - such as last month's racist tweets about four minority women in Congress - could prod more suburban GOP lawmakers to head for the exits rather than mount a defense, following in the footsteps of several Texas Republicans and others who have decided not to seek reelection.  "There is so much angst with these retirements and there is so much hope that President Trump would just talk about the economy for three days straight," said Scott W. Reed, the U.S. Chamber of Commerce's senior political strategist. And he warned that the Republican-controlled Senate could be at risk if the GOP does not make an "aggressive effort" to win the suburbs.  Democrats, meanwhile, are making inroads in places such as Atlanta's northern suburbs, a longtime Republican enclave that once sent Republican former House speaker Newt Gingrich to Washington, by making targeted appeals on the economy, health care...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first for Arab world, openly gay candidate runs for Tunisia presidency...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/first-arab-world-openly-gay-065339903.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal Party leader Mounir Baatour, an openly gay lawyer, announced on Thursday he would stand in Tunisia's presidential elections, marking a first for the Arab world. Baatour's candidacy marks "a first which will without doubt be a benchmark in history", his party said.A lawyer at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAGA ACCUSED OF STEALING 'SHALLOW'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/08/lady-gaga-accused-of-stealing-shallow-from-unknown-songwriter/?_ga=2.131603271.953003245.1565208591-1370560762.1565208591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaga’s team is branding as a “brazen shakedown.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Biden blunder: 'Poor kids' just as bright as 'white kids'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/08/latest-biden-blunder-poor-kids-are-just-as-bright-as-white-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaffe-prone presidential hopeful Joe Biden put his foot in his mouth during an Iowa campaign stop on Thursday when he told a group of predominately Asian and Hispanic voters that “poor kids a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Hong Kong Airport Braces for Sit-In Protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-airport-braces-sit-035632042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hong Kong’s airport bolstered security as protesters began a three-day sit-in at the arrivals hall of its main terminal, kicking off a 10th straight weekend of anti-China demonstrations.Only departing passengers with tickets or boarding passes and valid travel documents will be allowed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians rush to buy iodine after blast causes radiation spike...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190809093035-01tbh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-BLAST/:Russians rush to buy iodine after blast causes radiation spike - reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second black trans killed in SCarolina in two weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/a-second-black-transgender-woman-is-killed-in-south-carolina/article_473a10a5-cacd-5f57-8c0b-8d5dd0f93c27.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pebbles LaDime Doe was killed in rural Allendale, S.C., on Aug. 4, making her the second black transgender woman murdered in the state in two weeks, advocates say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: ILLEGAL USE OF CHINESE CHILDREN TO MAKE AMAZON ALEXA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/aug/08/schoolchildren-in-china-work-overnight-to-produce-amazon-alexa-devices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked documents show children as young as 16 recruited by Amazon supplier Foxconn work gruelling and illegal hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida raking in billions as Americans abandon high-tax states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/florida-income-american-movers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's low taxes and high levels of affordability are drawing movers in droves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic gridlock at LaGuardia forces travelers to walk to terminals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/08/gridlock-at-laguardia-forces-travelers-to-walk-to-terminals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LaGuardia Airport’s roads filled to capacity on Thursday, with travelers reporting that they were forced to hop out of cars and buses and walk to catch their flights. Video posted to Twitter …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions, tigers found dead in freezer at 'hunting' farm...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/08/08/lions-and-tigers-found-dead-in-freezer-at-south-african-hunting-farm-10541165/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A harrowing video also shows two fatally ill lion cubs locked inside a metal crate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arquette 'White Shame' Tweet Turns Toxic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rosanna-arquette-fbi-twitter-account-white-shame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rosanna Arquette said the FBI told her to make her Twitter account private after tweeting she was ashamed of being "white and privileged."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun nut films himself walking into WALMART with assault weapon and 100 rounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9685741/walmart-springfield-missouri-man-assault-weapon-el-paso/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GUN nut dressed in fatigues filmed himself walking into a Walmart in the US carrying an assault weapon and 100 rounds. The man, described as white and aged in his twenties, was detained by an off…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Store manager pulled alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.ozarksfirst.com/local-news/springfield-police-arrest-armed-man-at-walmart-on-republic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ozarksfirst.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Mo.– The Springfield Police Department tweeted out Thursday that an armed man was arrested at the Walmart Neighborhood Market on W. Republic Road. His intent was not to cause pea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-duty firefighter stops him...</title>
      <link>https://www.ky3.com/content/news/Heavy-police-presence-at-Walmart-Neighborhood-Market-in-south-Springfield-528602951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ky3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Springfield Police Department says it responded to a potential threat at the Walmart Neighborhood Market on Republic Rd. near Golden Avenue, Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Pulls Video Game Tournament... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/espn-abc-pull-apex-legends-esports-tournament-mass-shootings-1230344 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Apex Legends' EXP Invitational was scheduled to air this weekend on the networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk flight attendant slurs safety speech, passes out, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/state/illinois/article233658102.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline pilot flies dad's remains home from Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/08/vietnam-vet-airline-pilot-flies-mia-dads-remains-home-texas/1956770001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Air Force Maj.Â Roy Knight, Jr., left Dallas for VietnamÂ 52 years ago, his 5-year-old son, Bryan, came to Dallas Love field to see him off. On Thursday, Bryan, now a captain for Southwest Airlines,Â  brought back his father's remains aboard a flight to the same Dallas airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL: GUN CONTROL 'FRONT &amp; CENTER'</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/politics-government/article233630997.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayton killer's demonic notebook scrawls... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7337373/Dayton-shooters-chilling-notebook-scrawls-reveals-fantasized-hunting-humans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connor Betts, 24, killed nine people in Dayton, Ohio, on Sunday. Ian Himes claims to have been with friends with Betts and revealed Betts' sickening notebook scrawls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techlash Has Come to STANFORD...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/technology/2019/08/stanford-tech-students-backlash-google-facebook-palantir.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in the famed computer science program, students are no longer sure they’d go to work for Facebook or Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER reports largest-ever loss at $5.2 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/08/uber-earnings-q2-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber has worked to keep riders, and drivers, loyal with membership offerings and loyalty rewards, while battling competitors like Lyft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Survives on COCA-COLA for 5 Days After Falling at Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.arlnow.com/2019/08/07/arlington-man-survived-on-coca-cola-for-five-days-after-falling-at-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arlnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly resident who lives in Arlington's Williamsburg neighborhood was rescued by an attentive mail carrier, neighbors, and first responders after falling at home and not being able to get up. The man survived on his kitchen floor for five days by drinking Coca-Cola that was within arm's reac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Woman Claims Meth Found Hidden In Vagina Isn't Hers...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/police-woman-claims-meth-found-hidden-vagina-isnt-hers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana woman told investigators the methamphetamine allegedly found inside her vagina did not belong to her, according to the Ouachita Parish Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio-warfare experts question why Canada sent lethal viruses to China...</title>
      <link>https://beta.canada.com/health/bio-warfare-experts-question-why-canada-was-sending-lethal-viruses-to-china/wcm/fce2a521-4ce1-4eb0-8ccf-43f165713c0b/amp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;beta.canada.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eisner says TV giants lining up for battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thisismoney.co.uk/money/news/article-7292779/Michael-Eisner-tells-giants-TV-lining-expensive-battle-Netflix.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thisismoney.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Disney boss Michael Eisner says a major battle is looming in the world of television broadcasting - and Netflix will end up being challenged from all sides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  SHOOT-'EM-UP VIDEOGAMES DON'T WARP MINDS -- BIG TECH DOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/shoot-em-up-videogames-dont-warp-minds-big-tech-does/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It takes a lot of effort, research, and efficiency to manipulate people online and influence their behavior in the real world. Silicon Valley has it down to a science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Above-normal hurricane season now more likely, NOAA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/hurricane/2019/08/08/above-normal-hurricane-season-now-more-likely-with-el-ninos-end-noaa-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency predicts five to nine hurricanes this season, two to four of them at the level of Category 3 or higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-No. 1 NHL pick homeless again -- refusing help...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/in-depth/sports/columnists/jeff-seidel/2019/08/08/joe-murphy-homeless-detroit-red-wings/1878370001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force halts flights for 123 C-130s over 'atypical' cracking...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2019/08/08/air-force-pauses-flight-ops-for-more-than-a-hundred-c-130s-after-atypical-cracking-found/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a quarter of C-130 Hercules in service at Air Mobility Command will be temporarily grounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds disallow DELTA ban on pit bulls as service animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/business/dot-disallows-delta-ban-pit-bulls-service-animals/dRlCBpjo37xeAUEiBWQy5O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Transportation says Delta's ban on pit bulls as service animals is not allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing next AOC, House Dems hoard campaign cash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd4f4ea8481e4bc9a8bb7a1be77fc740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing files and exorcism: Guam's clergy abuse scandal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8442f05def44d1ea79b9e6805da4e0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball's future: Shrinking attendance, stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/08/08/mlb-attendance-stadiums-future/1941614001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As attendance dips around baseball, teams are compensating by shrinking their stadiums and finding ways to attract the new generation of fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 bodies hung from bridge or hacked up in Mexico gang feud...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de294939aa834fa29e18ed2d4a599c3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ICE released 300 of 680 detained in Mississippi raids...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/2019/08/08/ms-ice-raids-300-detainees-released-wednesday-680-detainees-tuesday/1955772001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of the 680 people detained in Wednesday's U.S. Immigrations and Customs Enforcement raid were released the same day,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman In Hijab Killed, Another Injured In Stabbings At Pittsburgh Bus Shelter...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/burlington-coat-factory-store-downtown-pittsburgh-stabbing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women were stabbed, one fatally, right in front of a police officer late Thursday morning in the middle of downtown Pittsburgh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman fired shots at plane spraying for mosquitoes, thought was drone...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/louisiana-drone-ranger-275903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 7--A Louisiana woman who fired several shots at a small airplane spraying for mosquitoes claimed that she thought that the manned aircraft passing over her home was a hobbyist’s drone, accordi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pure evil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/08/california-stabbings-police-call-suspect-4-killings/1952759001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect killed four people and injured two in a stabbing and armed robbery rampage over two hours in Southern California,Â police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession Odds Pick Up as Economists Cut Growth Estimates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/recession-odds-rise-as-economists-cut-growth-estimates/ar-AAFwDzK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Tried Hiding From Silicon Valley in Pile of Privacy Gadgets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2019-08-08/i-tried-hiding-from-silicon-valley-in-a-pile-of-privacy-gadgets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
