<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New NPR Ethics Policy:  OK For Journalists To Demonstrate...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/publiceditor/2021/07/29/1021802098/new-npr-ethics-policy-its-ok-for-journalists-to-demonstrate-sometimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR opens the door for journalists to publicly advocate for fairness, justice and other human values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return Of Long Lines: 'Crazy' Wait Times At FL Testing Sites...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/south-florida-covid-test-sites-long-lines-cases-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long lines for coronavirus tests are back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Sues DISNEY Over 'BLACK WIDOW' Streaming Release...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/scarlett-johansson-walt-disney-co-black-widow-lawsuit-1234802440/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson filed a lawsuit on Thursday against The Walt Disney Co., claiming that the studio breached her contract by releasing the Marvel movie Black Widow on Disney+ at the same time it w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:   If you don't fall asleep, there's plenty to look at...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/07/jungle-cruise-disney-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how to drag a 20-minute theme-park ride into nearly two hours of cinematic tedium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman Found Beheaded On MN Sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/suspect-arrested-after-woman-found-stabbed-to-death-on-shakopee-sidewalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An arrest has been made after a woman was found beheaded on a Shakopee sidewalk Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Chasing Extra Vaccine Dose, While Scientists Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-are-chasing-extra-vaccine-shots-while-scientists-debate/ar-AAMI68p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many scientists say that vaccinated people probably won’t need booster shots anytime soon. Some are getting them anyway. They are going to local pharmacies, other states or even other countries — anywhere where there is no record of them having been vaccinated — to get extra doses out of concern about the Delta variant or because they are worried their protection may be wearing off. The news on Thursday that Israel would give them to some older...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major universities have more diversity staff than history professors...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2021/07/28/diversity-bloat-many-major-universities-have-more-diversity-staff-than-history-professors-n405278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"legislators should consider reducing and restructuring DEI staffs"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military looks for secret to GPS-free navigation in bird's eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/07/28/military-funded-research-looks-for-the-secret-gps-free-navigation-in-a-birds-eye/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers can synthesize DNA that could be used for future navigation applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman With Only J.D. Salinger Recording To Burn It...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-only-known-recording-j-125755616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woman with only known recording of J.D. Salinger's voice to have tape burned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police ordered to arrest bareface...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/capitol-police-ordered-arrest-staff-visitors-not-wearing-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Capitol Police were ordered to start arresting visitors and staff who refuse to wear a mask on the House side of the Capitol complex starting Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cardinal charged with sexually assaulting teen...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2021/07/ex-cardinal-mccarrick-charged-with-sexually-assaulting-teen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, who was defrocked after a Vatican investigation confirmed he had sexually molested adults and children, is charged with sexually assaulting a teenage boy during a Massachusetts wedding reception in the 1970s, court records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL QB Says He Only Jabbed After Pressure From League: 'They'll Make Your Life Miserable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/nfl-qb-says-he-only-got-vaccinated-because-of-league-pressure-if-you-dont-fall-in-line-theyll-make-your-life-miserable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;85 percent of NFL players have reportedly received at least one dose of the Covid-19 vaccine, but a hesitancy lingers among the remaining 15 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Forces soldier drowns in Key West pool during underwater combat training...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9839637/Special-Forces-soldier-drowns-underwater-combat-training.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday, a Green Beret drowned in a pool at the Special Forces Underwater Operations School in Key West, Florida, during a conditioning exercise on Tuesday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feelings Of Deja Vu Growing Amid More Mandates, Return Of Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/amid-covid-setbacks-and-mask-mandates-some-feeling-sense-of-deja-vu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City restaurateur Danny Meyer, behind hot spots including Union Square Cafe and Gramercy Tavern, is requiring all staffers and diners inside his restaurants to be vaccinated, starting Sept. 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prolonged shaking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-alaska-hawaii-tsunamis-2a5af8987548ead7182d21f87cca7557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERRYVILLE, Alaska (AP) — A powerful earthquake which struck just off Alaska’s southern coast caused prolonged shaking and prompted tsunami warnings that sent people scrambling for shelters. Residents reported only minor damage, but officials said that could change after sunrise and people get a better look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN OLYMPIC BUBBLE HOLD?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/29/as-covid-cases-hit-record-high-in-tokyo-can-the-olympic-bubble-hold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — Outside the Tokyo Olympics bubble, the coronavirus situation in Japan has never been worse. Both the city and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Trump youth group stokes vaccine resistance as covid surges again...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2021/07/29/vaccine-mandates-charlie-kirk-tpusa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlie Kirk’s Turning Point USA and its affiliates are urging students to resist mandates and spreading baseless claims about “medical raids,” part of a bid for donations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing stages 'Taiwan invasion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3372974/ww3-fears-china-stages-taiwan-invasion-drills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEARS of World War Three have been sparked after China staged massive military drills “invading Taiwan”. Beijing also boasted about defeating the US and the UK in any conflict – a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: Where WWIII likely to explode...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3367846/map-world-war-three-likely-explode-next-frontier-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPECULATION is growing where the next global conflict may break out in 2021 as global powers modernize their nuclear arsenals and tensions between nations mount. It comes as a Council of Foreign Po…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida county to require in schools, defying DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/565415-florida-county-to-require-masks-in-schools-defying-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida county school board voted on Wednesday to require students, staff and visitors to wear masks inside its schools, directly conflicting with Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: RICH PEOPLE OF HAMPTONS NEW HEADACHE -- EVEN RICHER PEOPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/07/hamptons-new-headache-even-richer-people </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers: NBA players profiting from Beijing 'slave labor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/politico-china-watcher/2021/07/29/lawmakers-nba-players-profiting-from-slave-labor-in-china-493767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN BIZARRE TWIST, ASTRONOMERS DETECT LIGHT COMING FROM BEHIND BLACK HOLE...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/astronomers-detect-light-behind-black-hole</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Any light that goes into that black hole doesn't come out, so we shouldn't be able to see anything that's behind the black hole."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunisa Lee wins gold, filling void left by Biles...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/gma/sunisa-lee-jade-carey-compete-080004367.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunisa Lee has won gold in the gymnastics all-around at the Tokyo Olympics. With Simone Biles withdrawing from the individual all-around, American gymnasts Lee and Jade Carey picked up the mantle Thursday in an event the U.S. has won at four straight Olympics. An event initially thought to be a showcase for the all-time great, the all-around field was blown wide open with Biles' withdrawal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT: The Invisible Tech Behemoth?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/07/microsofts-antitrust/619599/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How has Microsoft escaped the scrutiny of reinvigorated antitrust regulators?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beltway Can't Stop Talking About Him. Voters He Needs Barely Know Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/07/29/jd-vance-senate-election-rob-portman-ohio-501384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In conversations with Ohio voters, it seems J.D. Vance's national brand hasn’t broken through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China to hold joint military drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210729120607-npfof</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-CHINA/DRILLS (URGENT):Russia, China to hold joint military drills in mid-Aug - Ifax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating foods high in flavonoids could slow down cognitive decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/28/health/flavonoid-cognitive-decline-study-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flavonoids are commonly found in fruits and vegetables and have been shown to have anti-inflammatory properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer who had heart attack during Capitol riot received threatening voice mail for testifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-officer-who-had-a-heart-attack-during-capitol-riot-received-vulgar-threatening-voice-mail-for-testifying/ar-AAMH4cl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a voice mail left for D.C. police officer Michael Fanone, a man accused Fanone of lying about the events on Jan. 6 and said he wished the rioters killed the officers defending the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in Tracing Alerts Reveals Scale of UK 'Pingdemic'...</title>
      <link>https://businesshala.com/rise-in-covid-tracing-alerts-reveals-scale-of-u-k-s-pingdemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businesshala.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Businesshala) - About 690,000 people in England and Wales were told to isolate by official COVID-19 mobile phone apps in the week ending July 21,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS: USA breaks world record -- and loses...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/us-breaks-world-record-and-loses-042725207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Katie Ledecky-led U.S. relay broke the world record in the 4x200-meter freestyle here on Thursday ... and lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attendees in hospital as COVID cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210729114105-a20t3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Two Games attendees in hospital as Japan COVID-19 cases surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biles makes mental health talk of Games...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-athletes-mental-health-7c7dad85a3ded5d3fce07055f5387d37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Brittney Griner has long been open about her ongoing battle with depression, an ailment that triggered suicidal thoughts when she was younger and last year drove her out of the WNBA bubble because the isolation was too much to handle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yelling, Throwing, Tweeting: Day Coverings Returned to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/yelling-throwing-tweeting-the-day-masks-returned-to-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The lack of basic human decency being exhibited in the House is a stain on our country,” said Rep. Dean Phillips (D-MN).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-headed snake eats two mice at same time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/two-headed-snake-named-ben-24641772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Barczyk said it was rare to see each head of the snake eat a mouse each at the same time. He works at a reptile zoo which also houses two-headed turtles and albino creatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: PEOPLE QUICK TO BELIEVE WORST WHEN STRESSED...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/people-b948131.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stress can make us jump to undesirable conclusions, new research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 8.2 mag largest quake to hit Alaska since 1965...</title>
      <link>https://www.alaskapublic.org/2021/07/28/major-quake-hits-near-alaska-peninsula-triggers-tsunami-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.alaskapublic.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala bad polls trigger Dem worries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/565336-harriss-bad-polls-trigger-democratic-worries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris has some ground to make up in order to be perceived more favorably by the public, a complicating factor for the Biden administration as it maps out its midterm strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL APPROVES 3RD SHOT</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/israeli-health-ministry-panel-recommends-third-covid-shot-for-older-people-1.10049085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDACE OWENS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/show/candace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us weekly as Candace Owens delves into the political and cultural issues of the day with her signature blend of intelligence and humor. CANDACE features celebrity interviews and panel discussions with the world’s most influential thought leaders and cultural mavens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fines for breaching Sydney lockdown doubled; Police given extra powers to shut down businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9837589/Fines-breaching-Sydneys-lockdown-doubled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fines for Covid rule breakers in NSW have doubled and police can shut down businesses and construction sites that under wide-ranging new powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE ROGAN</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/show/4rOoJ6Egrf8K2IrywzwOMk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;open.spotify.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to The Joe Rogan Experience on Spotify. The official podcast of comedian Joe Rogan. Follow The Joe Rogan Clips show page for some of the best moments from the episodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAWKER begs readers to have an 'open mind and heart' in quiet relaunch...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/gawker-quietly-relaunches-asks-readers-for-an-open-mind-and-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picked up at a bankruptcy auction by Bustle Digital Group, Gawker reappeared in a third iteration after Bustle’s headstrong CEO Bryan Goldberg attempted to resuscitate the site twice before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds releasing infected migrants into communities...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/07/28/la-joya-covid-migrants-whataburger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The undocumented migrant family at Whataburger told a police officer that Border Patrol had released them because they had COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong's urban farms sprout gardens in the sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbesindia.com/article/forbes-lifes/hong-kongs-urban-farms-sprout-gardens-in-the-sky/69083/1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbesindia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their heads in the clouds and their hands in the soil, a group of office workers are busy harvesting the fruits of their labour on the roof of a Hong Kong skyscraper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks on. Masks off. Masks on again at White House...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/masks-masks-off-masks-again-150227895.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden made adherence to COVID guidelines a cornerstone of his campaign to defeat Trump. He beat Trump, but beating the pandemic may be harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY sails into new LGBT waters with 'JUNGLE CRUISE' film...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/disney-sails-lgbt-waters-jungle-015845392.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Jungle Cruise," Disney's new nostalgia-soaked adventure film based on a 1950s theme park ride, has an unexpectedly modern twist -- one of its main characters comes out as gay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports highest number of new cases in world...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/covid-delta-variant-surge/?id=79058271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pandemic of the novel coronavirus has now infected more than 195 million people worldwide and killed over 4.1 million of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand rated best place to survive global societal collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/28/new-zealand-rated-best-place-to-survive-global-societal-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study citing ‘perilous state’ of industrial civilisation ranks temperate islands top for resilience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors of California's deadliest wildfire haunted as new blaze nears: 'I can't do it again'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivors-of-california-e2-80-99s-deadliest-wildfire-haunted-as-new-blaze-nears-i-can-e2-80-99t-do-it-again-e2-80-99/ar-AAMFNsT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As California’s biggest blaze of the year raged toward a haven for survivors of the 2018 Camp Fire, residents relived a nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK, GOOGLE will require...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/google-and-facebook-to-require-vaccines-for-in-office-employees-paving-the-way-for-rivals-to-follow/ar-AAMFtGw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's shift on masking creates new political difficulties, policy challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-shift-on-masking-creates-new-political-difficulties-policy-challenges/ar-AAMFr09?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s allies say his new message is a commendable response to the findings of scientists and health experts. But critics call it confusing and possibly damaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  Bring Vision of Metaverse to Life!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/facebook-q2-2021-1234989781/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s ad revenue increased 56 percent year over year for a total of $28.58 billion in the second quarter of this year, according to earnings reported on Wednesday. The majority of the co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25% of new cases in LA fully vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/over-25-of-new-covid-19-cases-in-los-angeles-county-are-fully-vaccinated-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June fully vaccinated people accounted for 20% of all the new cases diagnosed in LA County, while unvaccinated and partially vaccinated people accounted for 80% of the cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significance of breakthrough infections remains unclear; CDC hides data...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Experts-ask-to-see-data-behind-new-policy-16347545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - New recommendations from federal health officials this week on when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelina Jolie son 'may NOT have been orphan,' agent claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3361292/angelina-jolie-son-maddox-not-orphan-adoption-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angelina Jolie’s son Maddox may not have been an orphan like the actress once claimed, the agent who investigated a Cambodian “baby buying” scandal told The Sun in an exclusive in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How wealthy, Wall Street ruined housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/housing-market-prices-expensive-millennials-wealthy-rich-americans-wall-street-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buyers waiting for cheaper houses are out of luck. The wealthy, investment firms, and millennials are creating a permanently higher price floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK,</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/28/facebook-requiring-us-employees-to-be-vaccinated-to-return-to-work.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company will continue to evaluate its approach outside of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Private Schools Have Gone Woke...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/why-private-schools-have-gone-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dalton School hosts an annual conference for New York City private schools on diversity, equity, and inclusion. This May, it was Rodney Glasgow’s turn to deliver the keynote address. Glasgow, a longtime school administrator who has founded multiple DEI consultancies, used his speech to address the elephant in the room: the parental pushback to "antiracism" at Dalton and other elite private schools, which made national headlines after Dalton headmaster Jim Best resigned amid the uproar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: DISCOVERY 'Shark Week' -- Harmful To Sharks?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/shark-week-missed-opportunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors argue that these problems undermine the greater purpose of Shark Week, hindering efforts of shark scientists and harming the sharks themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema opposes $3.5 trillion price tag or Dems' sweeping social safety net bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/sinema-opposes-3-5-trillion-price-tag-democrats-sweeping-social-n1275330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona Democrat said she will, however, vote in favor of the budget resolution that begins the legislative process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Republicans Ready to Take Up Infrastructure Spending Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/key-republicans-say-theyre-ready-to-take-up-an-infrastructure-deal/ar-AAMFmCy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House and a bipartisan group of senators agreed on Wednesday on a far-reaching infrastructure bill, with a vote to advance it set for as soon as Wednesday evening, paving the way for action on a crucial piece of President Biden’s agenda. “We now have an agreement on the major issues, and we’re prepared to move forward,” said Senator Rob Portman, Republican of Ohio and a lead negotiator for his party on the infrastructure measure....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gymnast skirts protest ban with BLM raised fist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/costa-rican-gymnast-raises-fist-for-black-lives-matter-during-floor-routine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luciana Alvarado wrapped up her performance in the Olympic qualifying rounds in Tokyo by kneeling on the floor and looking up with a raised fist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player cut for 'stealing food' to take home...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/falcons/news/new-york-giants-cut-kelvin-benjamin-for-stealing-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first-round pick of the Carolina Panthers Kelvin Benjamin was cut by the New York Giants for the strangest reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Israel has 2 week window to halt 4th wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israels-two-week-window-to-halt-the-4th-covid-19-wave-675199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new daily cases has surpassed 2,000 for two days in a row and hospital heads say they are starting to feel the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Says No Jab, No Job!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/netflix-to-require-covid-vaccinations-for-all-actors-on-us-productions-1234801577/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Netflix has become the first major Hollywood studio to implement a blanket policy mandating vaccinations for the casts of all of its U.S. productions, as well as those who come into cont…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Star On Life Support, Friend Shot to Death Inside CA Movie Theater...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/28/rylee-goodrich-anthony-barajas-corona-movie-theater-fatal-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 18-year-old woman was killed and a 19-year-old man was taken to the hospital with life-threatening injuries after a shooting at a Corona movie theater, police said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floyd Mayweather 'TARGETED' in drive-by; Bodyguard wounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3366508/floyd-mayweather-targeted-drive-shooting-bodyguard-hurt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLOYD Mayweather’s bodyguard was shot protecting the retired boxing star from a “targeted” drive-by shooting that left him with a horrific wound. Greg La Rosa, 39, exclusively rec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA CONSIDERS 'DRASTIC ACTIONS'</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/national/coronavirus-surge-worsening-in-california-as-officials-consider-more-drastic-actions/article_ff6feae9-b4a7-59a9-8c9e-ecf697e83015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Faced with sustained increases in coronavirus infections and COVID-19 hospitalizations, California officials are considering new measures to hopefully cap the spike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers flare in House over new rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/565286-tempers-flare-as-some-in-gop-ignore-new-house-mask-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several GOP lawmakers refused to comply with the newly reinstated mask requirement on the House side of the Capitol on Wednesday, putting themselves at risk of having to pay hefty fines as punishment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
