<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Leprosy Next Public Health Crisis To Hit Los Angeles?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-09-06/leprosy-could-be-next-public-health-crisis-hit-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAILER...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5UijUOy0MmE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SPY, starring Sacha Baron Cohen, is inspired by the real-life story of former notorious Mossad agent, Eli Cohen, who successfully goes undercover in Syri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure grows to release health records...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/pressure-grows-on-biden-to-release-health-records-as-campaign-stonewalls-on-bloody-eye-mishap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic front-runner Joe Biden was speaking at a televised town hall Wednesday when the corner of his left eye appeared to fill with blood, bringing attention away from the issue of climate change at a time when his campaign is already batting back scrutiny about his age and health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAINTS QB Drew Brees defends self after appearing in Bible video...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/saints/2019/09/05/drew-brees-new-orleans-saints-focus-family-video-lgbtq/2226844001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drew Brees appeared in a video promoting National Bring Your Bible to School Day. That video was tied to the anti-LGBTQ group Focus on the Family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spate of clinical trials has scientists hopeful about HIV vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/spate-of-clinical-trials-has-scientists-hopeful-about-a-vaccine/article_aedbf626-41ad-5141-91bb-c531e1923ed8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First there were the drugs that could knock back HIV to undetectable levels, and the virus was no longer synonymous with a death sentence. Then came a treatment that allowed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARKS IN FLOODED WATERS</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9877387/hurricane-dorian-bahamas-floodwaters-sharks-as-dad-is-forced-to-throw-son-5-on-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DAD has told of how he was forced to fling his son onto a roof to save him from sharks that had swum inland after Hurricane Dorian decimated the Bahamas. Adrian Farrington was trying frantically …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Top Progressive News Site Shuts Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/thinkprogress-a-top-progressive-news-site-is-shutting-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A search had been underway for a new publisher. But none was found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT Media Lab Rocked by New Epstein Revelations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mit-media-lab-rocked-by-new-jeffrey-epstein-revelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Yorker’s Ronan Farrow says paperwork indicates the accused sex trafficker “directed” a $2 million donation from Bill Gates to the lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Alarming Number Of Seniors Go Entire Week Without Talking To Anyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/lonely-lives-alarming-number-of-seniors-go-entire-week-without-talking-to-anyone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of British seniors sheds light on this sad, but true effect of aging, noting that hundreds of thousands of people often go a week without speaking to a single person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sexually assaulted on flight got no help from crew, suit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/business/aviation/article234704067.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More people traveling world than ever. But number coming to America is dropping...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/lifestyle/travel/article/More-people-are-traveling-the-world-than-ever-14420066.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers can't get enough of globe-trotting. But have they had enough of the United States?  According to the World Tourism Organization, a United Nations agency, the number of international tourist arrivals around the world reached 1.4 billion last year. That represented a 6% increase, and the organization forecast the number to grow by another 3 or 4% in 2019.  But in the first half of 2019, the number of international visitors coming to America has actually dropped nearly 1.7%. That's according to preliminary data from the Department of Commerce's National Travel and Tourism Office, which shows slightly more than 37 million foreign travelers came to the country between January and June.  According to a forecast from the U.S. Travel Association, an industry trade group, the outlook for 2019 is for visitor numbers to remain just about the same as last year. Even if that holds true and the country doesn't see a dip for the full year, the news is not good.  "It's generally going to be under-performing global travel," says David Huether, the group's senior vice president of research.  There's a grab bag of reasons for the downturn, observers say. The latest version of a monthly report from the U.S. Travel Association, out this week, warns that foreign visits to the country remain vulnerable.  "Ongoing global economic cooling, prolonged and expanding trade tensions, and uncertainty surrounding the Trump administration remain major risks to international traveler sentiment," the report says.  The value of the U.S. dollar also remains strong, making travel more expensive for visitors from other countries, Huether says.  Trade wars with China could cost the country 1.9 million inbound visitors and $11 billion in spending between 2018 and 2020, according to research from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC blocks virtual caucuses in Iowa and Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/campaigns/dnc-blocks-virtual-caucuses-in-iowa-and-nevada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee formally decided Friday not to move forward with virtual caucuses in Iowa and Nevada amid cybersecurity concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red flag laws spur debate over due process...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/09/04/red-flag-laws-spur-debate-over-due-process</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC:  They Survived Dorian but Wonder How Many More Hurricanes They Can Withstand...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/09/06/us/dorian-north-carolina-hurricane-victims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most residents in eastern North Carolina, where people rattle off the names of storms like old enemies, were spared the worst from Dorian. But they haven’t all recovered from last year’s flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODY HELL: NETS SPIKE BIDEN EYE DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2019/09/06/joe-bidens-bloody-eye-cnn-somehow-spiked-everyone-fox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA spy to publish book about undercover exploits without agency approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/ex-cia-spy-readies-publish-book-without-approval-agency-n1050456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some former CIA agents question the veracity of "Life Undercover: Coming of Age in the CIA," by Amaryllis Fox, which hits stores in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Plan to Drop Presidential Primaries in 4 States to Impede Trump Challengers... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gop-plans-to-drop-presidential-primaries-in-4-states-to-impede-trump-challengers/ar-AAGV0kQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man whose cancer 'cured by holy water' to have claims tested by doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-whose-cancer-cured-holy-19784219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kazik Stepan, from Kent, will appear on Songs of Praise, on which doctors will carry out incredible tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City diocese names priests in 'the dreadful scourge of sexual abuse of minors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article234792262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILITIA ON PATROL</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/in-dorian-ravaged-bahamas-armed-militias-stop-people-from-looting-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survivors provide example of why it's important to have a well-armed populace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE:  Sacha Baron Cohen Amazing in 'SPY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/spy-1237183</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this Netflix limited series' true-life spy story, Sacha Baron Cohen delivers his best dramatic work yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT: CHAPTER 2' Set For Biggest Opening In Horror History?</title>
      <link>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/it-chapter-2-set-to-have-biggest-opening-weekend-i/1100-6469653/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gamespot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how much money It Chapter 2 is expected to make at the box office during its opening weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's oldest mom' gives birth to twins at age 74...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/worlds-oldest-mom-gives-birth-twins-ivf-hospital-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The title was previously held by a 70-year-old woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>