<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>High Society Bracing for Ghislaine Maxwell Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-high-society-1258165/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What will be revealed? Who might she name? Jeffrey Epstein’s right-hand woman is going on trial for their alleged crimes — and those who used to know her can’t stop talking about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA wants 55 years to process FOIA request over data...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/wait-what-fda-wants-55-years-process-foia-request-over-vaccine-data-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freedom of Information Act requests are rarely speedy, but when a group of scientists asked the federal government to share the data it relied upon in licensing Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine, the response went beyond typical bureaucratic foot-dragging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi on $550 billion climate spending: 'Religious thing'...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/pelosi-550-billion-climate-spending-me-its-religious-thing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's Build Back Better Act is estimated to cost $4.79 trillion if its policies are made permanent, according to the Committee for a Responsible Budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Jury ends THIRD day of deliberations with no verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-verdict-watch-11-18-21/h_87dc3885421105e20787bd01af3fbdbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in the trial of Kyle Rittenhouse will continue deliberations today. Follow here for live updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeking strength in numbers, U.S.-bound migrants form new caravan...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118214502-s84as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Seeking strength in numbers, U.S.-bound migrants in Mexico form new caravan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Starts Using Drones In New Delivery Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/walmart-starts-using-autonomous-drones-in-new-delivery-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News got an exclusive look at a new on-demand delivery service, which uses autonomous drone technology, outside a Walmart headquarters in Pea Ridge, Arkansas. Errol Barnett reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star accused of obtaining fake card...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/sports/bucs/2021/11/18/bucs-antonio-brown-accused-of-obtaining-fake-vaccine-card/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former live-in chef also says Brown, who missed one game this season after testing positive for COVID, owes him $10,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland city council votes to INCREASE police funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/portland-city-council-votes-to-increase-police-funding-crack-down-on-homeless-camping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$500,000 is allocated to install benches to prevent the homeless from setting up camp near city parks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88% of Americans worried about inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/inflation-has-88percent-of-americans-worried-heres-how-they-will-cut-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worries about rising prices are at the top of most American consumers' minds as we head into the holiday season, a new Country Financial survey shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man banned from all-you-can-eat BBQ for eating too much...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-59331975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A live-streamer has been banned from a buffet restaurant in China after multiple food binges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million Americans May Have Permanently Lost Sense of Smell...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/over-a-million-americans-may-have-permanently-lost-thei-1848082265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study estimates that up to 1.6 million Americans have experienced covid-related smell loss for longer than six months, with little chance of recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem retirements spark worry over holding House majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democratic-retirements-spark-worry-over-holding-house-majority-2548f85b-ab8d-4cb1-b191-3afe2a25dee5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;15 House Democrats and 10 Republicans are not running again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Known Covid Case Was Vendor at Wuhan Market, Scientist Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2298195-analysis-of-earliest-covid-19-cases-points-to-wuhan-market-as-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fresh look at what we know about the first covid-19 cases shows that the earliest known case was in a person who worked at the Huanan Market in Wuhan, which was suspected as the source from the start of the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 'Great Resignation' may not last very long...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/why-the-great-resignation-may-not-last-very-long.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4.4 million people quit their jobs in September, but there’s more to the “Great Resignation” than just worker dissatisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE pushes fully autonomous car forward...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/tech/bloomberg-apple-plans-to-launch-fully-autonomous-car-as-soon-as-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple’s electric autonomous car will have no steering wheel or pedals, with a new chip managing the vehicle’s self-driving abilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black pastors rally outside trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-georgia-brunswick-al-sharpton-6daf56b12c4fa58da89d1424d5ba090c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — Hundreds of pastors both rallied and prayed Thursday outside the trial of three white men in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery , gathering in response to a defense lawyer's bid to keep Black ministers out of the courtroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France bans wild circus animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211118-france-bans-wild-circus-animals-and-mink-farms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French parliament voted Thursday to end wild animals being used in live circus shows and outlawed mink farming, in new animal-rights legislation hailed as a step forward by campaigners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wargame Tests Navy's Mettle...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/are-naval-forces-right-path-leaders-run-wargame-check/186924/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis of the classified, Pacific-focused “Global 14” will continue for weeks or months, a Navy official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limit public life for unjabbed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118164736-9c3im</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Germany to limit public life for the unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who raped 4 teens gets no jail time: 'Incarceration isn't appropriate'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/man-who-raped-four-teenagers-gets-no-jail-time-judge-says-incarceration-isnt-appropriate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who fatally shot Arbery says he feared for life in struggle for gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/man-who-fatally-shot-ahmaud-arbery-says-he-feared-for-his-life-in-struggle-for-gun/ar-AAQPfX9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis McMichael testified Wednesday that he feared for his life when Arbery grabbed his gun, setting up a potential battle over the prosecution’s ability to grill him on alleged “racial animus.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Ejects MSNBC...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/live-trials/live-trials-current/kyle-rittenhouse/judge-ejects-msnbc-from-kyle-rittenhouse-courthouse-after-extremely-serious-incident-of-person-following-jury-bus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Bruce Schroeder has ejected cable news organization and website MSNBC from the Kenosha County Courthouse for the remaining duration of the Kyle Rittenhouse homicide trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Longest lunar eclipse in 580 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/longest-partial-lunar-eclipse-nearly-100142484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longest partial lunar eclipse in nearly 600 years will grace the night sky late Thursday night and early Friday morning across the entire country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:  'SIMPSONS' reveal plans for last episode...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/4086616/the-simpsons-boss-last-ever-episode-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Simpsons boss has revealed plans for the last ever episode – and it’s a major tear-jerker. The hit animated sitcom has been running since 1989 and shows no signs of slowing down. Ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DIANA' Broadway Musical Opens to Scathing Reviews, Teeters on Closing...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/11/17/broadway-diana-musical-opens-to-scathing-reviews-teeters-on-closing-almost-immediately</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer once bragged about thinking 'like a criminal' in viral ad. Now, he's convicted felon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-lawyer-once-bragged-about-thinking-e2-80-98like-a-criminal-e2-80-99-in-a-viral-ad-now-he-e2-80-99s-a-convicted-felon/ar-AAQR9ts?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Muessig made a viral 2014 ad that Slate magazine called "the best (or worst) lawyer commercial ever made."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mile from Auschwitz, restored synagogue recalls thriving Jewish life...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/a-mile-from-auschwitz-restored-synagogue-recalls-thriving-jewish-life-in-oswiecim-685313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New space tax proposal!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/bezos-blue-origin-hires-lobbyist-with-ties-to-obama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin recently hired a lobbyist with ties to former President Barack Obama as new tax legislation looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In post-Roe world, California preparing to become nation's abortion provider...</title>
      <link>https://californiahealthline.org/news/article/california-abortion-access-out-of-state-patients-roe-v-wade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiahealthline.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While other states dramatically restrict abortion and the conservative-leaning U.S. Supreme Court weighs Roe v. Wade, California is preparing to absorb the country’s abortion patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS, AMAZON open cashier-less store in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/starbucks-amazon-open-cashier-less-store-in-manhattan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks and Amazon are teaming up on a grab-and-go store format. The Seattle-based companies will open their first Starbucks Pickup with Amazon Go location on Thursday in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  BRITNEY READY FOR OPRAH...</title>
      <link>https://www.bustle.com/entertainment/what-will-britney-spears-do-after-conservatorship-ally-oprah-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bustle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a video posted to Instagram on Nov. 16, Britney Spears said she wants to be an ally to others under conservatorships and hinted at an interview with Oprah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna's Former Miami Home on The Market for $32M -- And it's Owned by A Dog!</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/miami-real-estate-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pampered pooch, Gunther III, acquired the mansion as part of an $80 million inheritance from a German countess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATER WARS:  California, Arizona and Nevada in talks on Colorado River water...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-arizona-nevada-talks-plan-130057269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water officials from California, Arizona and Nevada are discussing plans to take even less water from the shrinking river and leave it in Lake Mead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs, Slovaks Join European Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/health/2021/11/18/czech-republic-targets-unvaccinated-with-new-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Czech and Slovak governments have approved new coronavirus restrictions that specifically target unvaccinated people amid a record surge of infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% TSA agents lack shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/11/17/breaking-news/tsa-screeners-face-vaccine-deadline-with-up-to-40-lacking-shots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 40% of U.S. airport security screeners haven’t been vaccinated for COVID-19 as an immunization deadline for federal employees and the busy holiday travel season converge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey trap: Dems, Biden careen toward rocky -- and pricey Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/11/18/turkey-trap-democrats-biden-careen-toward-rocky-and-pricey-thanksgiving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden and Democrats remain focused on trillions more in domestic spending while voters are concerned about rising prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should women be eligible for draft? Defense bill stirs up debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/military/vp-nw-women-draft-defense-bill-20211118-5zukka7nznbujne5yjxbrnxkme-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A provision that would require college-aged women to sign up for Selective Service is included in the annual defense spending bill that passed in the House and is up for a vote in the Senate this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BIDEN APPROVAL DROPS TO 36%...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/582109-bidens-approval-dips-to-36-percent-in-new-quinnipiac-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s job approval rating is down to just 36 percent in a new Quinnipiac University poll, signaling trouble for Democrats as they head into 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How VON DUTCH Trucker Hat Empire Ended in Chaos and Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/von-dutch-trucker-hat-empire-103053173.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vince Bucci/GettyIn the aughts, it was impossible to miss the sensation that was Von Dutch.What started out as a small counter-culture brand intent on creating high-quality denim suddenly exploded onto the scene.The Venice Beach-based label was known for its iconic trucker hats stamped with the scrawly signature logo, popularized by the likes of Ashton Kutcher, Jay Z, Madonna, Britney Spears, and of course: it girls of the era Paris Hilton and Nicole Richie, who almost exclusively wore Von Dutch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irreversible Overdoses, Robberies, Sex Assaults: Rise of Benzo Dope...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awv3d/rise-of-benzo-laced-fentanyl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irreversible overdoses, robberies, and sex assaults. The next phase of the drug poisoning crisis is here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are We About to Find Life on Venus?</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/life-venus-102808303.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Kelly Caminero/The Daily Beast/GettyPhosphine is a colorless, flammable, toxic gas that smells like rotting fish. Humans manufacture it to use in pest control and the production of computer chips. But it’s also a waste product from a certain kind of “abiotic” microbe that lives in oxygen-free environments. Its presence is a potential sign that there’s something alive.The gas with the chemical name PH3 has been at the center of a passionate debate among scientists concerned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad of DISNEY Star Accused of Grooming Underage Girls...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/dad-disney-star-peyton-clark-103148171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Photos Getty ImagesThe father of Disney actor Peyton Clark and influencer Acacia Kersey has been accused of grooming teenagers, using his child photography business to get alone time with young girls in order to pressure them into taking risqué and explicit photos, several sources told The Daily Beast.Seven women who had previously modeled for Rich Clark detailed the 52-year-old’s alleged predatory behavior, including how he would encourage young girls to po</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says West not taking Russia 'red lines' seriously enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-says-west-not-taking-russias-warnings-red-lines-seriously-enough-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday that the West was not taking Russia's warnings not to cross its "red lines" seriously enough and that Moscow needed to obtain serious security guarantees from the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey-brain study with link to China's military roils top European university...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/exclusive-monkey-brain-study-with-link-chinas-military-roils-top-european-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese professor at the University of Copenhagen conducted genetic research with the Chinese military without disclosing the connection, the university told Reuters, in the latest example of how China's pursuit of military-civilian technology is tapping into Western academia in the strategically sensitive area of biotechnology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takes swings at GOOGLE, FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-chairman-rupert-murdoch-takes-swings-google-facebook-2021-11-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch renewed his attacks on Google and Facebook during News Corp’s annual shareholder meeting on Wednesday, accusing the tech giants of trying to silence conservative voices and calling for "significant reform."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of Healthcare Workers Not Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/11/18/nearly-one-third-of-healthcare-workers-in-us-hospitals-are-still-not-vaccinated-against-covid-19-cdc-study-finds-as-vaccine-mandate-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 70% of healthcare workers in U.S. hospitals were fully vaccinated against Covid-19 as of September 15, according to the CDC study, with higher rates found among workers in children’s hospitals and urban areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel to Usher in Tighter Rules With Germany Engulfed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/merkel-to-usher-in-tighter-covid-rules-with-germany-engulfed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Pushes For Tighter Covid Rules With German Infections Rising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan deploys advanced fighter jets amid tensions with China...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/582095-taiwan-deploys-advanced-fighter-jets-amid-tensions-with</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan reportedly deployed advanced fighter jets on Thursday in a show of strength and cooperation with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don vs. DeSantis: Let the war games begin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/582043-trump-vs-desantis-let-the-war-games-begin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surely DeSantis wants to avoid a higher ranking on Trump’s enemies list, but it’s doubtful that the governor will acquiesce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: For Anti-Aging, Nothing Beats Diet -- Not Even Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/healthy-diet-beats-drugs-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show calorie intake and the balance between protein, fats, and carbohydrates have a stronger impact on liver function than pharmaceuticals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Airlifted Out Of State Due To Hospital Bed Shortage In Boston...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/17/boston-medflight-out-of-state-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston MedFlight is being forced to bring patients to hospitals in Connecticut and Rhode Island because there aren't enough beds in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock After Parishioner Found Stabbed To Death Inside Baltimore Church...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/evelyn-player-baltimore-church-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Police confirm to WJZ Thursday that a person of interest is being sought in the murder of Evelyn Player, the 69-year-old Baltimore woman found dead Tuesday morning inside Southern Baptist Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Junk Spreads, Creating Risk of No-Go Zones for Satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/space-junk-spreads-creating-risk-of-no-go-zones-for-satellites/ar-AAQRas3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian missile test that shattered a dead satellite this week highlights a growing threat of space debris just as companies such as SpaceX and Boeing Co. make plans to launch as many as 65,000 commercial spacecraft into orbit in coming years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer boots, more slippers: Shortage of containers changing what shows up on shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/fewer-boots-more-slippers-how-a-shortage-of-shipping-containers-is-changing-what-shows-up-on-shelves/ar-AAQRbrr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retailers and manufacturers are prioritizing merchandise that’s lightweight and pliable to maximize every cubic inch of these massive steel boxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German hospitals sound alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211118-last-resort-german-hospitals-sound-alarm-in-pandemic-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With intensive care beds filling up and health staff running short, a hospital in Bavaria's Freising made an unprecedented decision to transfer a coronavirus patient to northern Italy for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church under fire over 'Let's go Brandon' chant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-church-under-fire-over-lets-go-brandon-chants-caught-on-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas church is coming under fire over a video showing people inside the place of worship chanting the viral anti-Biden phrase, "Let’s Go Brandon."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflicts mount on easing restrictions amid infection spikes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/582080-conflicts-mount-on-easing-covid-19-restrictions-amid-autumn-case-spikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in COVID-19 cases as winter approaches is setting off a debate about if a new era of living with the virus has arrived or whether heightened restrictions and caution are still needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems question whether Biden will actually run in '24...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/582071-democrats-question-whether-biden-will-actually-run-in-2024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of Democrats are privately questioning whether President Biden will run for reelection amid anemic approval ratings and rising worries about next year’s midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Jury in Rittenhouse murder trial deliberate for third day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118105806-8k733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/WISCONSIN (PIX):Jury in Rittenhouse murder trial to deliberate for third day in Wisconsin court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile execution looms in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/executions-oklahoma-oklahoma-city-baker-mayfield-1e212e0db47f598ccb9c97fd611df929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Students at high schools across Oklahoma City walked out of their classes. Prayer vigils were held at the state Capitol, and barricades were erected outside the governor's mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of homes for sale continues to plague housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/shortage-of-homes-for-sale-continues-to-plague-housing-market/ar-AAQQHbX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOWN SQUARE | A recent report by Redfin real estate brokerage found that one-third of homes in more than 400 metro areas went under contract within one week of being listed for sale during the four weeks that ended Oct. 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Tells Trump He Needs to Leave Past Behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rupert-murdoch-tells-trump-he-needs-to-leave-the-past-behind/ar-AAQPEyk </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media baron Rupert Murdoch told former President Donald Trump that he needed to leave the past behind and focus on the future to address problems the country faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican National Guard deploying troops in Cancun following rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/581996-mexican-national-guard-deploying-troops-in-cancun-following-rise-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico is sending at least 1,500 National Guard troops to Cancun following a rise in violence in the southeastern corner of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Rittenhouse jury ends DAY 2 of deliberations without verdict...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jury-rittenhouse-murder-trial-deliberate-110736753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (Reuters) -Jurors in the Wisconsin murder trial of Kyle Rittenhouse ended their second day of deliberations without reaching a verdict, after reviewing a series of videos on Wednesday of the teenager's deadly encounters at racial justice protests last year. Defense lawyers made a new request for a mistrial, saying prosecutors withheld the high-definition version of a drone video in evidence and enhanced it in order to portray Rittenhouse as a threat. Rittenhouse, 18, is charged with killing Joseph Rosenbaum, 36, and Anthony Huber, 26, and attempted homicide in the wounding of Gaige Grosskreutz, 28, during a chaotic night of protests in Kenosha, Wisconsin on Aug. 25, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $750 million 'ASTROWORLD' lawsuit names APPLE alongside Travis Scott, Drake, LIVE NATION...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/750-million-astroworld-lawsuit-names-234316307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Tony Buzbee filed suit on behalf of 125 victims of the Astroworld tragedy, including the family of 21-year-old Axel Acosta, who died at the concert.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
