<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>COMEDIAN JACKIE MASON DEAD AT 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/jackie-mason-who-turned-kvetching-into-comedy-gold-dies-at-93/600081181/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former rabbi, Mason made comic capital as a Jew feeling his way — sometimes nervously, sometimes pugnaciously — through a perplexing gentile world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z 'nowstalgia' leading to thrifting explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/gen-z-s-nowstalgia-y2k-fashion-leading-thrifting-explosion-n1274720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iconic fashion trends of the early 2000s like bucket hats, low-rise jeans, and babydoll T-shirts are all having a resurgence among younger consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans Enduring Day-Long Waits to Fill Gas Tanks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/venezuelans-enduring-day-long-waits-220448641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Venezuela’s capital city is once again rationing gasoline after output at state-owned refineries slumped, forcing motorists to endure day-long queues to top off tanks.Shortages have returned to Caracas, prompting drivers to prowl the streets for open filling stations as lines stretch for blocks in some areas. Because of breakdowns at Petroleos de Venezuela SA fuel-making plants, gasoline output has crashed by more than 40% since the end of June, according to two sources with knowl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASK MANDATES RETURN...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/cities-revive-covid-19-mask-mandates-sparking-backlash-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mask mandates have provoked outrage. One town councilman in California even called the policy "BS" and vowed not to enforce it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man used AI to bring back deceased fiance. Tech creators freak...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/man-used-ai-to-talk-to-late-fiance-experts-warn-tech-could-be-misused-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man used artificial intelligence (AI) to mimic speaking to his late fiancé. The creators of the technology warn that it could be used for misinformation campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians threaten to prolong...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australians-may-face-longer-lockdown-022624032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE (Reuters) -Australia's New South Wales logged its second-highest daily increase of the year in locally acquired COVID-19 cases on Sunday amid fears of a wave of new infections after thousands of people joined an anti-lockdown protest. There were 141 COVID-19 cases reported, down from 163 a day earlier. Under fire for a slow vaccine rollout, Prime Minister Scott Morrison said more vaccine supply was not going to ensure New South Wales gets out of lockdown, but what was needed was an effective, properly enforced lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Pyramid-sized asteroid to fly close to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/great-pyramid-sized-asteroid-to-fly-close-to-earth-674818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The asteroid is considered potentially hazardous, with a possible height of 220 meters (720 feet), but it is expected to fly safely without impacting the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many rappers are being killed as gun violence spirals in 'warzones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3332480/rappers-kts-dre-indian-red-boy-pop-smoke-killed-gun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE brutal shooting death of KTS Dre earlier this month added the rapper’s name to a growing list of stars wiped out by gun violence. His death – along with the killings of Indian Red Bo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears' agent breaks silence on 'abusive conservatorship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3345355/britney-spears-longtime-agent-cade-hudson-speaks-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of Britney Spears’ oldest friends and agent has broken his silence on the singer. Cade Hudson took to his Instagram to say “enough is enough” and he got “thousands of de…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands join Budapest Pride march against anti-LGBTQ law...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/thousands-march-for-lgbtq-rights-in-budapest-e2-80-99s-biggest-pride/ar-AAMwsWr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of about 200 counter-demonstrators along the route held banners reading ‘Stop LGBTQ paedophilia’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With first posthumous album, Prince pierces American condition...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-posthumous-album-prince-pierces-011533353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince's estate will soon issue a completed record from the mercurial artist's storied music vault, the first never-before-heard album released since the musician's shock death five years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETS ON A HIGH:  Stock Bulls Look Toward $17 Trillion Burning Hole in Pockets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-bulls-look-toward-17-162752226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the stock market, the refusal of retail investors to back down from every macro threat has become the only story. When will it end? Judging by the size of all the pools of cash lying around, it could be a while.Among all the economic stories of the pandemic, the one about money piling up in people’s accounts has been the most significant in the stock market, where the S&amp;P 500 just notched its seventh gain in nine weeks. Money market accounts, viewed in some circles as a “dry po</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Critical race theory' debate is fiercely dividing the Christian church, Texas pastors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article252897943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the CRT turmoil continues to overwhelm school board meetings across the country, Fort Worth pastors say the shock waves are destabilizing the Christian church, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former rabbi who turned to stand-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3345684/jackie-mason-dead-age-93-comedy-legend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKIE Mason – a comedian famed for his one-man Broadway shows – passed away on Saturday at the age of 93. Mason died at a hospital in Manhattan, his long-time lawyer friend Raoul Felde…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built his career out of political incorrectness...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/tv/tv-news/jackie-mason-comic-dead-1201848/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stand-up who built his career out of political incorrectness found multiple generations of fans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He refused to give up his coveted TWITTERr handle. Then he was 'swatted' and died of heart attack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/refused-coveted-twitter-handle-then-193345633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international scheme to obtain a coveted Twitter handle ended on a sleepy, country road in Tennessee when police surrounded the home of Mark Herring and ordered him to come out with his hands up. Authorities were called to the Sumner County address in April 2020 in response to a report that a woman had been fatally shot and pipe bombs would go off if officers arrived, according to court records.Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stories from The Wash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States scale back reporting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-f9c58c50f565e707be9bedfa9a82319e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — Several states scaled back their reporting of COVID-19 statistics this month just as cases across the country started to skyrocket, depriving the public of real-time information on outbreaks, cases, hospitalizations and deaths in their communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEDIAN JACKIE MASON DEAD AT 93... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/24/arts/jackie-mason-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He kept the borscht belt style of comedy alive long after the Catskills resorts had closed and eventually brought it, triumphantly, to Broadway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURSED OLYMPICS:   TV RATINGS CRASH TO 33 YEAR LOW</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-tokyo-olympics-opening-drew-231950728.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC's broadcast of the Tokyo Olympic Games opening ceremony drew 16.7 million viewers, the smallest U.S. television audience for the event in the past 33 years, according to preliminary data from Comcast-owned NBCUniversal on Saturday. Across all platforms, including NBCOlympics.com and the NBC Sports app, 17 million people watched the ceremony, the company said in an email. The streaming audience on those platforms grew 76% from the 2018 PyeongChang opening ceremony and 72% from the 2016 Rio opener, reflecting a change in viewing habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Ice Baths to Oxygen Chambers: New Wellness Centers Offer Recovery From Grueling Workouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lifestyle/style/hollywood-wellness-centers-recovery-workout-1234984889/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From cryo chambers and float tanks to infrared saunas and old-fashioned naps, you cannot go wrong if you add a recovery protocol to your curriculum,” says trainer-to-stars Gunnar Peterson, whose cu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrations in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210724-french-protesters-against-covid-19-health-restrictions-clash-with-police-in-paris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French anti-riot police fired teargas on Saturday as clashes broke out during protests in central Paris against COVID-19 curbs and vaccination, local television reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic trips soon part of therapy. What sessions look like...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/24/how-psychedelic-assisted-therapy-with-mdma-and-psilocybin-works.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In as soon as two years, tripping on mind-altering drugs like MDMA and psilocybin could become a regular part of therapy to treat conditions from depression to post-traumatic stress disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Luria's pro-Navy, centrist identity may get Jan. 6 test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-government-and-politics-capitol-siege-navy-cead205203b284a27184b83a99620dbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORFOLK, Va. (AP) — When members of Congress head home to connect with their constituents, some hit tractor pulls. Others might stop by mom-and-pop stores. For Democratic Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Apocalypse Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/24/opinion/sunday/climate-change-floods-wildfires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mother Nature called. She's had it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team USA gets no medals to open Olympics first time in decades...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/564653-team-usa-gets-no-medals-to-open-olympics-for-first-time-in-decades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Team USA athletes suffered multiple upset losses in the first official day of competition at the Tokyo Olympics on Saturday, the first time in decades the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Officials Warn Healthcare System Crisis 'Highly Possible'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/japan-covid-cases-surge-olympics-1234799395/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world’s athletes gather in Japan for the Summer Olympics the country is experiencing a fourth wave of Covid-19 infections. Country-wide, case numbers have risen 20% in the past week, w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALASKA: State That Lives Up to Hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alaska-the-state-that-actually-does-live-up-to-the-hype</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s the thing about Alaska: There are no wrong decisions, only decisions to be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More Money You Make, Longer You'll Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-longer-life-net-worth-longevity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money may not buy happiness, but it could buy you a longer life. New research concludes that being wealthy can add years to your lifespan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian anti-lockdown protestors violently clash with police...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9820691/Australian-anti-lockdown-protestors-clash-police-amid-new-restrictions-just-176-new-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests are a response to harsh Covid lockdowns in New South Wales, Victoria and South Australia, with more than half the country's 25million people ordered to stay at home over the outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Promised Online Fame. She Says They Leaked Her Nudes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/promised-her-online-fame-influencer-144842600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyWith the likes of influencer Tana Mongeau, YouTuber Daisy Keech, Too Hot to Handle cast member turned TikTok provocateur Harry Jowsey, the Clermont Twins, and dozens of other social media stars and models on its roster, the Unruly Agency seems to be the place that could take an influencer’s brand to new heights.But clients and contractors who worked with Unruly and Behave Agency—Unruly’s spinoff for smaller influencers—are warning others agains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Most Influential Spreader of Virus Misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/24/the-most-influential-spreader-of-coronavirus-misinformation-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — The article that appeared online on Feb. 9 began with a seemingly innocuous question about the legal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican reveals it owns more 5,000 properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/24/vatican-reveals-it-owns-more-than-5000-properties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real estate holdings published for first time show it owns 4,051 properties in Italy, 1,120 abroad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana farmers blamed for water theft as drought grips west...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/23/water-theft-marijuana-farmers-california-american-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California official says ‘Water stealing has never been more severe’ as water taken from hydrants, homes, rivers and wells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts express concerns for animal safety as heat waves rip through Pacific Northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/experts-express-concerns-for-animal-safety-as-heat-waves-continue-to-rip-through-the-pacific-northwest/ar-AAMvT59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes chant 'Dr. Biden' as first lady cheers swimmers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/564659-us-athletes-chant-dr-biden-as-first-lady-cheers-swimmers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athletes on the U.S. swimming team chanted first lady Jill Biden's name as she sat in attendance for their competition at the Tokyo Olympics on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands join Budapest Pride march against anti-LGBTQ law...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210724130301-kijdh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNGARY-LGBT/MARCH (UPDATE 1, PIX/TV):UPDATE 1-Thousands join Budapest Pride march against anti-LGBTQ law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-based 'shadow financial market' spooks regulators...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/24/shadow-financial-market-spooks-regulators-500696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watchdogs are warning that some DeFi activities are probably illegal under federal law and pose serious danger to consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China digital yuan could pose challenges to dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/24/the-us-is-deciding-how-to-respond-to-chinas-digital-yuan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are digging into Central Bank Digital Currencies and what a CBDC could look like in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of delta variant poses new political threat to Biden and his agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/surge-of-covid-delta-variant-poses-new-political-threat-to-biden-and-his-agenda/ar-AAMvWbq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has sought to place blame elsewhere, calling the resurgence “a pandemic of the unvaccinated” and scolding social-media platforms for misinformation that leads people to refuse vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Green Bank, West Virginia -- quietest place in America...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/24/inside-green-bank-west-virginia-quietest-place-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside Green Bank, West Virginia, the most silent place in America, where 8,000 residents aren’t allowed to use cellphones or Wi-Fi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athens' Old Airport Rivaling New York in Property Prices...</title>
      <link>https://businesshala.com/athens-old-airport-is-rivaling-new-york-in-property-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businesshala.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Businesshala) -- The redevelopment of Athens' old airport offered a unique opportunity to secure ancient seaside homes close to a major city, and even</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With workers in high demand, teens filling void...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-504f6e207d8914070f315225adb58c17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — As businesses have taken “closed indefinitely” signs out of their windows and reopened their doors, the landscape of a post-pandemic workforce is changing and depending on an unexpected demographic — teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfing debut making clear wave riders masters of science...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-surfing-sports-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-f76fb9c41535bff7c65727830d3ddc79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICHINOMIYA, Japan (AP) — Olympic surfing’s debut is making clear that these wave riders are unsung masters of science -- in climatology, meteorology and oceanography to be exact. Serious wave chasers are by default atmospheric science junkies because there are few, if any, sports that are both dependent on an uncontrollable variable — the weather — and defined by a literal uneven playing field — the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New LAMBO cleans house, cooks dinner, entertains kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3341535/lamborghini-huracan-evo-spyder-alexa-tested-interior-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you were going to spend £180k on a Lamborghini, you’d want the ruddy thing to clean your house. And the new Huracan Evo does just that…plus it’ll sort your dinner out and keep the kids entertain…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China criticises NBC broadcast for 'incomplete map'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/china-criticises-nbc-olympics-broadcast-incomplete-map-2021-07-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China criticised NBC Universal for showing an "incomplete map" of the country in its broadcast of the opening ceremony of the Tokyo Olympics, after a map displayed during the arrival of Chinese athletes included neither Taiwan nor the South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA exceeds 3,000 daily cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/la-county-exceeds-3000-daily-coronavirus-cases-as-surge-worsens/ar-AAMuZLh </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives riled up over registering women for draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/07/23/conservatives-riled-up-over-registering-women-for-draft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives oppose a Senate bill that would require women to register for the military draft next year and plan to make it an election issue in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Frustration mounts over vax holdouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98patience-has-worn-thin-e2-80-99-frustration-mounts-over-vaccine-holdouts/ar-AAMuLoH </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest lockdown in Sydney...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-sydney-arrests-coronavirus-pandemic-ff50971322d56dc9ce9ec92ea7e940c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (AP) — Thousands of people took to the streets of Sydney and other Australian cities on Saturday to protest lockdown restrictions amid another surge in cases, and police made several arrests after crowds broke through barriers and threw plastic bottles and plants.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
