<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Era of anti-Covid pills begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211106-the-era-of-anti-covid-pills-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if a simple pill could help heal from Covid-19?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleeing passengers shut down busy Spanish airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59191108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palma de Mallorca Airport closes for four hours after 21 people run from a plane across the tarmac.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Apologize to Arab Royal Families for Leaking Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nw8m/conti-ransomware-hackers-apologize-to-arab-royal-families-for-leaking-their-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Bluntly, UAE sends assassination teams to deal with people they don’t like. [...] Even ransomware groups are subject to political pressure."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety link to irritable bowel syndrome seen in DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-57821848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have been studying more than 50,000 people with IBS to better understand the condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knife attack on German train severely injures 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-germany-nuremberg-2f7cd4d47381d35a515e86ef17849322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A knife attack on a high-speed train in Germany left three people severely wounded, the Bavarian Red Cross said Saturday. Police said a man has been arrested in connection with the morning attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Jan. 6 Rioter Tries to Sell Home on ZILLOW, Inadvertently Reveals Cache of Explosives...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alleged-jan-6-rioter-jeremy-brown-tries-to-sell-home-on-zillow-accidentally-reveals-cache-of-explosives-fbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Green Beret and onetime congressional candidate Jeremy Brown's operational security has apparently gotten a little sloppy of late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan City Council will be all Muslim, likely first in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/11/05/hamtramck-first-muslim-city-council/6288652001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All six members of the Hamtramck City Council will be Muslim starting in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easing of travel restrictions lets loved ones reunite...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-travel-relationships-528d66c448c9b6fc7dd50ac5ddef03fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Erin Tridle and her boyfriend, it was love at first sight. They met while the American was traveling in France in the summer of 2019. They said, “I love you,” on day two. “People tell us it's like something from a movie,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid size of Eiffel Tower heading for Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/asteroid-the-size-of-eiffel-tower-heading-for-earth-in-december-684133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed 4660 Nereus, or 1982 DB, this vaguely egg-shaped asteroid has a size of approximately 330 meters. But while considered potentially hazardous, it also has potential for exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raids PROJECT VERITAS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-searches-project-veritas-personnel-173750571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department conducted two searches on Tuesday in the New York City area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where's Gavin? Newsom disappears from public for 10 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10172023/Wheres-Gavin-California-Governor-Newsom-disappears-public-view-10-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom was last seen in public on October 27, receiving a COVID-19 booster shot in Oakland. He said it was painless and then flexed in celebration, urging others to get boosters as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Politics Rotting Brains, Making Everyone Mad...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/05/politics-is-rotting-brains-and-making-everyone-mad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As exciting as it may sound to grab power and vanquish enemies, the only way to save America is to recommit to its original principles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Dems warn party: Growing Republican wave real...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pennsylvania-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-philadelphia-elections-3420f14ee42f95907b316438585ed4a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW HOPE, Pa. (AP) — The Democrats of Bucks County, Pennsylvania, felt the red wave building over the summer when frustrated parents filled school board meetings to complain about masking requirements and an academic theory on systemic racism that wasn't even taught in local schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA director dispatched to Moscow to warn over troop buildup near Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/05/politics/bill-burns-moscow-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden dispatched CIA Director Bill Burns to Moscow earlier this week to warn the Kremlin that the US is watching its buildup of troops near Ukraine's border closely, and to attempt to determine what is motivating Russia's actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  HALF SAY NOTHING WITH CHANGE MIND...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-unvaccinated-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;18 percent think COVID vaccinations are more dangerous than the virus itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe slams...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/fbi-searches-project-veritas-associates-in-probe-over-diary-purportedly-belonging-to-biden-s-daughter/ar-AAQmUtl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The probe is centered on how a right-wing website ended up with and published contents of the diary just before the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>228-206 vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/congress-approves-12-trillion-infrastructure-bill-sending-measure-to-biden-for-enactment/ar-AAQmcP7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vote marked the final milestone for the first of two pieces in the president’s economic agenda, sending to Biden’s desk a sprawling initiative that grew out of his 2020 campaign pledge to rejuvenate the economy in the aftermath of the coronavirus and “build back better.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Axes Estevez From 'MIGHTY DUCKS' Over Status...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/emilio-estevez-leaving-the-mighty-ducks-game-changers-season-2-gordon-bombay-covid-vaccine-mandate-1234868978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Mighty Ducks franchise will continue without Gordon Bombay. Emilio Estevez, who reprised his role from the 1992 movie and its 1994 and 1996 sequels in Season 1 of The Mighty Ducks: G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 DEAD AT HOUSTON MUSIC FESTIVAL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/8-dead-after-panic-houston-astroworld-music-festival-n1283397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventeen people were transported to the hospital after the crush, and 11 who were taken by ambulance were in cardiac arrest, Houston officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANIC, STAMPEDE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10171759/Multiple-injuries-reported-Astroworld-Festival-Houston.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people are dead and 'hundreds' more injured during a crush and stampede on the opening night of rapper Travis Scott's sold-out Astroworld Festival in Texas on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA developing most powerful laser weapon to blast missiles from sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4007773/us-laser-weapon-missiles-chinas-nuke-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US is developing its most powerful laser weapon yet capable of blasting missiles and drones out of the sky following China’s “round the world” nuke test. Boeing and General At…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Alone Boosts Risk Of Heart Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-alone-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older women eating alone had lower intakes of energy, carbohydrates, dietary fiber, sodium, and potassium in comparison to those eating with others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson accusers detail alleged abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2021-11-05/marilyn-manson-esme-bianco-sexual-abuse-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court records reviewed by The Times and nearly two dozen interviews portray Manson as a transgressive artist who mistreated and isolated women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria bans unjabbed from cafes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211105-austria-bans-those-unvaccinated-against-covid-19-from-caf%C3%A9s-amid-surge-in-new-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria said on Friday it is barring those not fully vaccinated against Covid-19 from cafes, restaurants and hairdressers as infections approach the record set a year ago and the government struggles…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camels escape circus, wander Madrid streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59186294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight camels and a llama were found, with managers blaming their escape on animal rights activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New coronavirus, likely from dogs, infects people...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2021/11/05/1052961177/new-coronavirus-likely-from-dogs-infects-people-in-malaysia-and-haiti</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could turn out to be the 8th coronavirus known to spread humans. Some scientists think doctors and researchers should start actively looking for this virus in patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX REBELLION</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-ripped-for-bonkers-anti-vax-interview-citing-joe-rogan-and-mlk-touting-ivermectin-and-suggesting-the-vaccines-cause-sterility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodgers is just the latest athlete railing against the vaccines, and he was roundly criticized for using his platform this irresponsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi strategy at risk of collapsing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/05/politics/house-votes-infrastructure-build-back-better/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's plan to pass a $1.9 trillion economic package and a $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill, two pillars of President Biden's agenda, is at risk of collapsing as leaders struggle to unify the progressive and moderate wings of the party, a dynamic that has consumed Democrats for the past several months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Axes Estevez From 'MIGHTY DUCKS' Over Vax Status...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/emilio-estevez-leaving-the-mighty-ducks-game-changers-season-2-gordon-bombay-covid-vaccine-mandate-1234868978/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Mighty Ducks franchise will continue without Gordon Bombay. Emilio Estevez, who reprised his role from the 1992 movie and its 1994 and 1996 sequels in Season 1 of The Mighty Ducks: G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR denounces 'Let's go, Brandon' conservative rally cry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-sports-business-united-states-f9bb6c6cb77a78f1302f4f08640cc973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVONDALE, Ariz. (AP) — NASCAR denounced its association with the “Let's go, Brandon” political cry being used across the country as an insult directed at President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Multiple' bomb threats at YALE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/05/yale-university-bomb-threats-forces-student-evacuations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police evacuated students at Yale University after several bomb threats were called in around campus Friday, police said. Eight buildings were evacuated out of an abundance of caution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Sex-Crime Charge May Be 'Defective,' DA Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/05/cuomo-sex-crime-charge-may-be-defective-d-a-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sex-crime case against former Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo was thrown into doubt on Friday after the Albany County district</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin's Underage Son Tried to Vote in VA Election, Officials Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/glenn-youngkins-underage-son-tried-to-vote-in-virginia-governors-election-officials-say/2870695/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 17-year-old son of Virginia Governor-elect Glenn Youngkin twice tried to cast a ballot on Election Day even though he is not yet eligible to vote, election officials confirm to News4. He was unsuccessful in his attempt to vote. News4 is not naming Youngkin’s son because he is a minor and has not been charged with a crime. Fairfax County…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Woke Meet Their Match -- Parents...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/the-woke-meet-their-match-parents-d7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenn Youngkin's mix of populist policy and moderate style is a breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulted With Joe Rogan For Medical Advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/aaron-rodgers-said-he-consulted-with-joe-rogan-for-medical-advice/ar-AAQn2xv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Packers quarterback Aaron Rodgers made headlines earlier this week when he tested positive for COVID-19. On Friday afternoon, he appeared on “The Pat McAfee Show” to share his side to the story. Rodgers revealed that he’s unvaccinated because he’s allergic to an ingredient in the mRNA vaccines. “I have an allergy to an ingredient that […] The post Aaron Rodgers Said He Consulted With Joe Rogan For Medical Advice appeared first on The Spun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Draft Women Advancing in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/policy/2021/11/plan-draft-women-uniting-unlikely-political-allies/186667/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-war activists and conservative hawks both want women to stay out of the Selective Service System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOY BORN WITH TAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9997843/The-boy-born-TAIL-Brazilian-baby-gets-12cm-long-appendage-chopped-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian baby born with a rare 12cm-long tail, ending in a 4cm ball, has had it surgically removed. The tail is a rare example of true human tail being left from one the baby grew one inside the womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Bill Gives Special Tax Handout to Media Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/dem-bill-gives-special-tax-handout-media-companies-1500-local-journalists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAKE ACTION: Reject Democrats Reckless Tax-and-Spend Bill &amp;#13;&amp;#13;The reconciliation bill working its way through the U.S. House calls on the American taxpayer to subsidize Democrats' media allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan to pay $300K to only staffer fired over Flint water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-environment-michigan-flint-d52c97713e59647ccce70f754ef3a114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The state of Michigan said Friday it agreed pay $300,000 to settle wrongful discharge claims by the only employee who was fired as a result of lead-contaminated water in Flint. The deal with Liane Shekter Smith, who was head of the state’s drinking water division, came weeks after an arbitrator said she was wrongly fired in 2016 by officials who were likely looking for a “public scapegoat” in one of the worst environmental disasters in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARCLAYS subpoenaed over connections to Jeffrey Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/barclays-subpoenaed-over-jeffrey-epstein-connections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of the subpoenas came days after Barclays announced its CEO, Jes Staley, would quit following an investigation into his relationship with Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Religious Exemptions Granted in Air Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/zero-religious-exemptions-granted-covid-vaccines-air-force-deadline-passes/186601/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 5,000 religious exemptions are still pending approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT:  Schools will start requiring vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/05/1051902361/covid-vaccine-schools-history-comic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first vaccine required for school was for smallpox, over 200 years ago. And for decades, all states have required that kids be vaccinated against contagious diseases like polio to attend school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Hollywood is shunning sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20211029-why-hollywood-is-shunning-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While society becomes more sexually open, there are fewer sex scenes in mainstream cinema than ever. Has film really entered a newly Puritan age, asks Christina Newland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers Addresses Vax Fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/11/05/aaron-rodgers-vaccination-status-woke-mob-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers has broken his silence on his vaccination status. He hit back at his critics during an interview with Pat McAfee.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
