<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Stillborn' baby being prepped for burial found to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/04/brazilian-stillborn-baby-prepped-for-burial-found-to-be-alive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A baby was declared stillborn by a Brazilian doctor was being prepared for burial at a funeral home — then was miraculously found to still be alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron vows to 'p*ss off' France's unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20220104/macron-causes-stir-as-he-vows-to-pss-off-frances-unvaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator details 27-hour nightmare commute...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/snarled-snow-sen-tim-kaine-trapped-nearly-27-hour-nightmare-n1286955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaine, D-Va., a former Democratic vice presidential candidate, was one of the unlucky drivers trapped on I-95 for more than an entire day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC to launch plant-based fried chicken...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/kfc-to-launch-meatless-fried-chicken-made-with-beyond-meat-nationwide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KFC restaurants nationwide will add Beyond Meat's plant-based chicken to their menus, starting Monday for a limited time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd great niece shot in bed in attack at family home...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4395458/george-floyds-great-niece-arianna-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Floyd’s four-year-old great-niece was shot while in her bed in an attack at their Houston family home after she paid tribute at protests. According to ABC13, the bullet was fired by an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 straight days of record-setting cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/map-united-states-covid-records-january-2022-n1286953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-thirds of the states have set Covid case or hospitalization records since Dec. 28, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley watches next steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/jan/04/elizabeth-holmes-conviction-silicon-valley</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the fraud charges could open up tech industry to further scrutiny, making startups tread more carefully</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania Trump to auction off hat, NFT from Macron visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220104-melania-trump-to-auction-off-hat-nft-from-macron-visit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Melania Trump announced Tuesday she will auction off a famed white hat she wore in 2018, with accompanying physical and digitized NFT drawings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee positivity rate: 34%...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/health/2022/01/04/tennessee-covid-19-omicron-positive-tests/9071546002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The omicron variant has lifted Tennessee's COVID-19 test positivity rate faster and higher than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Aide Leaving Kamala's Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/kamala-harris-aide-leaves-for-capitol-hill-on-heels-of-other-departures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another aide is leaving Vice President Kamala Harris' office soon after two other advisors departed late last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After backlash, Quebec exempts dog-walkers from 10 p.m. curfew...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/quebec-updates-curfew-exemptions-to-include-dog-walking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To request Sean Hannity's cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jan-6-committee-sean-hannity-d454ed9f-bec1-4d72-a160-6d742f3c3cb5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hannity is one of the most prominent media figures in America and was a close adviser to Donald Trump throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TAMPS DOWN ALARM</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/588214-biden-tamps-down-omicron-alarm-urges-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden on Tuesday sought to tamp down worries about the omicron coronavirus variant, underscoring that COVID-19 vaccines protect against severe illness from the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside DC's Rowdy New Progressive Scene...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/164814/washington-dc-rowdy-new-progressive-scene</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The town’s lefties might not be notching a lot of wins, but they’re having a lot more fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Network Cuts Top Reporter Over Criticism of Commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/mlb-network-cuts-ties-with-ken-rosenthal-over-criticism-of-commissioner-rob-manfred/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Rosenthal, one of baseball's most prominent reporters, is out at MLB Network, stemming from criticism of commissioner Rob Manfred. Rosenthal, 59, had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA to stop seeking prison for many...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/04/manhattan-da-alvin-bragg-to-stop-seeking-prison-in-some-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first memo to staff on Monday, Alvin Bragg said his office “will not seek a carceral sentence” except for in homicide and a handful of other cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panel Quietly Ramps Up Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-the-capitol-s-shadow-the-jan-6-panel-quietly-ramps-up-its-inquiry/ar-AASpMyZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Behind closed doors inside a nondescript office building at the foot of Capitol Hill on a recent chilly morning, the House inquiry into the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol was in full swing. As congressional staff aides shuffled through the halls going about their normal business, investigators quietly pulled shades over the windows in conference rooms on several different floors and posted “Do Not Disturb” signs. In one such room sat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK passengers trapped 30-plus hours on train...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/neighborhoods/north-fulton/atlanta-amtrak-passengers-trapped-30-plus-hours-on-train/77QSQTWQDNEW5F7WEC6KCIDR6M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A midnight train from Georgia has been trapped on the tracks in Virginia for more than 30 hours. They are not alone, the rail provider is reporting delays of several hours for trains across the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police called out to break up fights at testing centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/milwaukee-covid-testing-sites-security-increased-due-to-altercations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Milwaukee Police Department will be present at testing facilities to assist with the line and keep everyone safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health experts criticize TSA security checks as virus spreads...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2022/01/04/ignoring-omicron-risk-tsa-still-requires-travelers-remove-masks-airport-checkpoints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mask-wearing on planes reduces the risk of Covid infection, but in airports every traveler is still required to remove their mask during security screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Defy God, Teach Goldfish to Drive on Land...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7v7g4/scientists-defy-god-teach-goldfish-to-drive-on-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goldfish were pretty good at piloting a Fish-Operated Vehicle, or FOV, the scientists report in a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Backdoored Phones Secretly Harvested GPS Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93b3ay/fbi-backdoor-anom-phones-gps-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents reviewed by Motherboard, including thousands of pages of Anom messages, show that the FBI's backdoored Anom phones collected more data than the content of messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religous Sect, Burning Shed Focus of Deadly Colorado Fire Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/christian-sect-burning-shed-focus-of-deadly-colorado-fire-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people are missing and presumed dead in a fire that sent 10,000 people from their homes and appears to have started on land owned by the Twelve Tribes group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida train kills 5th person in month...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-florida-fort-lauderdale-7dd0e7ec2435468d685918b92a0d2bf2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A Brightline higher-speed train fatally struck a pedestrian who walked into its path Tuesday, the fifth death involving the railroad since it recently resumed operations after being shutdown because of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood trade wars heat up...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/culturefiles/hollywood-trade-wars-heat-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Noah's Ark' underground doomsday bunker on moon could save humanity in apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/noahs-ark-underground-doomsday-bunker-25852569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A storage unit on the moon could work as a 'global insurance policy' says Professor Jekan Thanga who believes 250 rocket launches are needed to complete the project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan ER doc:  Omicron making people really sick in different way...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/omicron-variant-symptoms-latest-covid-making-people-really-sick-in-a-different-way/3477882/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As COVID-19 infections with the omicron variant of the virus surge out of control nationwide, emergency rooms are filling up again — and one well-known New York City doctor says what they’re seeing now is much different than the last two years of the pandemic. Manhattan emergency room physician Dr. Craig Spencer took to Twitter late Monday night to explain…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC cuts subway service...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/some-nyc-subway-service-suspended-due-to-crew-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MTA has suspended multiple subway lines through Friday, Jan. 7, 2022, because COVID-19 is hitting the workforce hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 4.5 MILLION QUIT JOBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/04/economy/us-job-openings-november/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon declares enough room in space for billions of satellites!</title>
      <link>https://spacenews.com/op-ed-is-there-enough-room-in-space-for-tens-of-billions-of-satellites-as-elon-musk-suggests-we-dont-think-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spacenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's stance is overly optimistic. Space is big, but LEO is not big enough to safely accommodate tens of billions of satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence flares at protests in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-pandemics-germany-ac28ee41bfe23856bd3f8df7f070fbca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Police in Germany have reported sporadic violence at demonstrations against the country’s pandemic restrictions, with one protester in the eastern town of Lichtenstein biting an officer and another attempting to steal a service weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Life-Changing Realizations People Have on Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg9a5/the-life-changing-realisations-that-people-had-on-psychedelics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New year, new you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Damon Viral Crypto Ad Is Embarrassing Cash Grab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/matt-damons-viral-crypto-ad-is-an-embarrassing-cash-grab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor’s commercial for Crypto.com (tagline: “fortune favors the brave”) compares investing in crypto to the bravery of space exploration or summiting Mount Everest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top suspect in Haiti assassination probe in custody in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/haiti/article257029817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key suspect in the assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse is in U.S. custody in Miami after being arrested Tuesday morning by Homeland Security agents upon arrival from Panama, multiple U.S. government sources familiar with the matter told McClatchy and the Miami Herald.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'needs to be in prison' for Jan. 6 riot, says partner of fallen Capitol Police officer Sicknick...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-needs-to-be-in-prison-for-Jan-6-riot-16748063.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The partner of Capitol Police officer Brian Sicknick, who died after trying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TO ADDRESS NATION</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/588146-biden-to-address-nation-on-omicron-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will address the nation on Tuesday afternoon about the current wave of the omicron coronavirus variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARLINK Internet Dishes Attracting Cats...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/starlink-dishes-cats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's Starlink internet dishes are attracting local cats on cold days, apparently to stay warm and take advantage of the heat it produces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leftists Ascendant in Latin America as Key Elections Loom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/04/leftists-are-ascendant-in-latin-america-as-key-elections-loom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO — In the final weeks of 2021, Chile and Honduras voted decisively for leftist presidents to replace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo artist anger over new EU rules goes beyond skin deep...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-lifestyle-amsterdam-european-union-tattoos-7cd5d66056cbd1d8405f41238a4946f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Tattoo parlors say their art will lose a lot of its vibrancy after European Union rules banning thousands of chemicals in their coloring ink kick in on Wednesday. The 27-nation bloc answers back that public health will be much better served with tougher restrictions on elements in ink that may cause cancer or allergies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN DIES AFTER FALLING INTO HAWAII VOLCANO...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4393808/hawaii-kilauea-volcano-man-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 75-YEAR-old man has died after he plunged 100ft into Hawaii’s Kilauea volcano. The man, who has only been identified as a Hilo resident, disappeared at the Hawaii Volcanoes National Park la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Cybermen: Nimble robot can open bottle, give injection, lift 65lbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10366023/his-hi-tech-invention-looks-just-like-Doctor-villain-dont-worry-help.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beomni 1.0, is set to be unveiled for the first time in public at the 2022 Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas this week. It is so nimble it can pick up a pinch of salt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SET NEW RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/03/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average and S&amp;P 500 closed at records on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER DRONE ATTACK ON AMERICAN FORCES IN IRAQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4389676/us-stops-second-armed-drone-iran-revenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US stopped a second armed drone attack on its forces in Iraq after Iran vowed revenge for the 2020 killing of Qasem Soleimani. A similar attack was attempted on Monday after two armed drones we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZONGOOGLE deploy armies to thwart antitrust bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/04/amazon-google-thwart-antitrust-bills-526460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small businesses that rely on the tech giants are signing petitions and joining Zoom calls with lawmakers to warn against legislation aimed at promoting competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Epstein settlement with accuser bail him out?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article257015497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein paid Virginia Roberts Giuffre $500,000 in November 2009 to dismiss a lawsuit she had brought against him alleging that that he and Ghislaine Maxwell had sexually abused her and directed her to have sex with their powerful friends, according to a newly unsealed settlement document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variant NOT 'worth worrying about; Fails to take off...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10367101/French-Covid-variant-NOT-worth-worrying-scientists-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virologists say the strain predates Omicron but has yet to cause chaos, bolstering hopes that it may fade into the background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden disapproval hits new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/biden-disapproval-rating-high-voters-blame-him-on-economy-cnbc-poll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's disapproval rating reached a new high in December as more voters signaled their unhappiness with his handling of the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Raises Coup Clashes in Warning Rivals Against Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-04/erdogan-raises-coup-clashes-in-warning-rivals-against-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of prayer site in doubt under Israel's fragile govt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-jerusalem-israel-prayer-04a68f9f0baafa813fb0dfab3485e896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — When Israel's new government took office last June, it indicated it would press ahead on an egalitarian prayer site at Jerusalem's Western Wall — a sensitive holy site that has emerged as a point of friction between Jews over how prayer is conducted there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarkets Shelves Bare in Sydney as Virus Isolates Staff...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/supermarkets-shelves-bare-sydney-covid-053706230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sydneysiders are facing empty shelves at some supermarkets as exploding coronavirus cases force a range of staff from truck drivers to warehouse workers into isolation. Most Read from BloombergOmicron Cases Are Hitting Highs, But New Data Put End in SightU.S. Sets Global Daily Record of Over 1 Million Virus CasesPolice Pinpoint Starting Point of Historic Colorado WildfireIvanka Trump, Donald Trump Jr. Subpoenaed in Asset ProbeU.S. Catches Kremlin Insider Who May Have Secrets of 20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOTS FILL IN FOR STAFF</title>
      <link>https://abc7news.com/robots-robot-hotel-silico-valley/11421841/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, customers say they like it, especially now while COVID anxiety is high. It's one less person to make contact with as a robot brings room service orders to your door, instead of a person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Grapes Key To Healthy Heart? 'Cleans Up' Cholesterol...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/grapes-heart-attack-cholesterol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study found just four weeks of eating grapes led to significant health boosts among people who rarely eat fruit and vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ:  Republicans Will Impeach Biden If Win House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/ted-cruz-says-republicans-will-likely-impeach-biden-over-border-policy-if-they-win-house-majority/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Weather it's justified or not, the democrats weaponized impeachment. They used it for partisan purposes to go after Trump because they disagreed with him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Superyacht Dispute Pits CREDIT SUISSE Against Gulf Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/saudi-superyacht-dispute-pits-credit-suisse-against-gulf-prince</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Superyacht Dispute Pits Credit Suisse Against Gulf Prince</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Meme Twin Brothers Die Days Apart From COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/french-tv-star-igor-bodganoff-dies-from-covid-19-complications-days-after-twin-brother-grichkas-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grichka Bogdanoff reportedly succumbed to complications from COVID-19. Six days later, so did Igor Bogdanoff. Both had refused to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew set for court showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-andrew-set-court-showdown-25845863</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for the 61-year-old Duke of York will argue that the lawsuit should be dropped due to a secret deal Victoria Guiffre made with billionaire paedophile Jeffrey Epstein in 2009</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorists trapped overnight on I-95 as winter storm causes icy, snowy havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/04/weather/winter-weather-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers have been stranded for hours on a major interstate in eastern Virgina -- some stuck from Monday into Tuesday morning -- after a severe winter storm caused massive backups, sending authorities scrambling to clear a path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News engagement fell off cliff in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/media-ratings-traffic-2021-a6be4d72-ba5f-4f8a-ae3e-0872ecd87677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It doesn't look like 2022 will be much better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In historic first, aircraft carrier Abraham Lincoln deploys under command of female captain...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2022-01-03/abraham-lincoln-strike-group-deploys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strike group's deployment to the western Pacific comes amid hostile rhetoric between China and Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown remains on BUCS roster as Tampa Bay discusses next steps with NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/antonio-brown-remains-on-buccaneers-e2-80-99-roster-as-tampa-bay-discusses-next-steps-with-nfl/ar-AASoLFg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech, finance firms buying up homes doesn't bode well for everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/opinions-tech-and-finance-firms-buying-up-homes-doesn-t-bode-well-for-everyone-else/ar-AASpXOc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew launches legal gambit to derail sex suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/prince-andrew-launches-legal-gambit-derail-virginia-giuffre-sex-abuse-rcna10751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew’s lawyers tried again Monday to block a lawsuit by Virginia Giuffre who says he sexually assaulted her when she was 17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Catches Kremlin Insider Who May Have Secrets of 2016 Hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/01/03/world/crime-legal-world/us-kremlin-insider-secrets-2016-hack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extradited from Switzerland in December, Vladislav Klyushin has been accused of illegally making millions of dollars trading on hacked corporate-earnings information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA MILLION CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/us-counts-over-1-million-new-daily-covid-cases-in-global-record-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. also has the highest 7-day average of new cases in the world, according to Johns Hopkins University's rankings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betty White agent denies she died from booster...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/01/03/betty-whites-cause-of-death-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Golden Girls” and “Mary Tyler Moore Show” star died at the age of 99 on Dec. 31 at her home in Brentwood, Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE RELAXES</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/france-relaxes-quarantine-rules-as-europe-adapts-to-omicron-s-spread-11641224120777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European countries try to avert the threat of labor shortages resulting from mass self-isolation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1918 flu even more relevant in 2022 thanks to omicron?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/opinions-the-1918-flu-is-even-more-relevant-in-2022-thanks-to-omicron/ar-AASnEOY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How safe are indoor gyms?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/wellness/how-safe-are-indoor-gyms-during-omicron-surge-what-experts-say/ar-AASoa9k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames feds for shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/desantis-blames-feds-for-covid-treatment-testing-shortages-as-omicron-spreads/ar-AASoigB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark Silicon Valley case...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/elizabeth-holmes-theranos-trial-verdict-guilty-fraud-001725594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Homes, the former CEO and founder of Theranos, has been found guilty on charges of wire fraud and conspiracy to commit wire fraud..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell Attended 'VANITY FAIR' Party After Editor Graydon Carter Killed Damning Exposé...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/ghislaine-maxwell-vanity-fair-party-photos-graydon-carter-killed-jeffey-epstein-farmer-sisters-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted sex trafficker enthusiastically attended the magazine's parties after getting her way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron upends return to schools and workplaces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-education-milwaukee-dce5cae3226eb78ebf074383a2d8135b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some school systems around the U.S. extended their holiday break Monday or switched back to online instruction because of the explosion in COVID-19 cases, while others pressed ahead with in-person classes amid a seemingly growing sense that Americans will have to learn to co-exist with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG:  Ivanka Trump, Don Jr. Subpoenaed in Asset Probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-donald-trump-subpoenas-ivanka-trump-072e02a5bf16faa89a7f496d16536893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York attorney general’s office confirmed Monday that it has subpoenaed former President Donald Trump and his two eldest children, Ivanka and Donald Trump Jr., demanding their testimony in an investigation into the family’s business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Slams 'Hysteria' as Florida Shatters Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-governor-ron-desantis-blames-the-feds-slams-hysteria-as-florida-shatters-covid-records-with-omicron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor gave his first press conference in weeks, railing against COVID mitigation measures like masking, which he erroneously claimed “hasn’t worked period.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the influencer scam crimewave flooding INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4386757/inside-influencer-scam-crimewave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SHOCKING crimewave is flooding social media – with celebs plugging scams where Brits are conned out of thousands of pounds of their hard-earned cash. Celebs including Joey Essex, Katie Pric…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4386697/chinese-authorities-raid-homes-midnight-quarantine-camps-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINESE authorities reportedly raided dozens of homes in the middle of the night and forced people onto buses to quarantine camps under the world’s strictest lockdown. The country is racing t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Final' interview faked?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/03/exclusive-people-magazines-betty-white-cover-story-final-interview-conducted-by-email-no-one-spoke-to-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARES CONTINUE... THOUSANDS STRANDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10363979/Flightmare-slows-2-680-flights-canceled-270-delayed-Monday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest was the hardest hit of all US airlines on Monday with 481 cancellations. By late morning, 2,133 domestic flights or international ones starting or finishing in the US had been canceled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds THERANOS founder Elizabeth Holmes guilty on multiple charges in criminal fraud trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/03/jurors-in-holmes-trial-remain-deadlocked-on-three-of-11-fraud-counts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors reached a verdict in the Elizabeth Holmes criminal trial after seven days of deliberations. They found the Theranos guilty on four counts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
