<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Even in face of surging grocery prices, retail beef and pork prices cause sticker shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/even-in-the-face-of-surging-grocery-prices-retail-beef-and-pork-prices-cause-sticker-shock/ar-AAKvANC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beef and pork prices hover at near record high due to labor shortages, high grain and energy costs and just plain old demand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warships 'swarmed by 100 UFOs' over month period...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/nine-navy-warships-were-swarmed-24203067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Investigative filmmaker Jeremy Corbell, who has released various authentic UFO videos seen by US Navy vessels, claimed anti-drone technology was completely ineffective</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Hamptons Booms, World of Luxury Problems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/29/as-the-hamptons-booms-a-new-world-of-luxury-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was 4 p.m. last Friday and a 30-something New Yorker who’d just flown into the East Hampton airport was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam detects highly contagious new virus variant as infections surge...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/556076-vietnam-identifies-new-highly-transmissible-variant-of-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vietnam has detected a new, highly transmissible variant of the coronavirus, the Vietnamese Health Ministry announced Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Prosecutors Zero In On Trump's Real-Life Wayne Manor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prosecutors-zero-trump-real-life-004618943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyAs two separate investigations into the Trump Organization heat up, a series of subpoenas issued by the New York attorney general and the Manhattan district attorney shows how prosecutors are probing one particular land deal.The subpoenas, which have not been publicly released until now, have been issued during the past 18 months to three towns just north of New York City.Investigators asked for a trove of documents related to Donald Trump’s failed attempts to develop a luxury golf course on a 212-acre, forested estate that spans across those three towns and includes several mansions. The requested documents and subsequent court filings show that investigators are examining whether the Trump Organization inflated the value of the property for a charitable tax write-off.The Daily Beast has learned the state Attorney General’s Office issued a round of subpoenas in November 2019. Investigators demanded copies of “zoning, property planning, or other building and construction permissions” sought by Trump’s firm for the property, Seven Springs LLC. At question is the dense forest that surrounds a towering, 60-room, century-old, sandstone chateau that includes three pools, carriage houses, and is imposing enough to justify its own forecourt and fountain.Think: Bruce Wayne. (There’s even a massive suspected bat population on the grounds of the estate.)When locals fought Trump’s building plans, Trump decided to give away his land rights to a conservation group—allowing him to take a hefty $21.1 million tax deduction in 2015, according to a filing made by investigators last August.But the pivotal question remains: Was the gifted land really worth that much if nothing was built on it?The towns of Bedford, New Castle, and North Castle handed over dozens of documents, according to records The Daily Beast obtained.At that time in late 2019, the AG’s office had already issued a subpoena seeking records and communications to see if the Trump Organization and its officers committed bank fraud—again, essentially a case concerning lying about asset values. Nearly a year later, the team would acknowledge in court filings that it hadn’t yet “reached a determination” whether it had found “violations of any applicable laws.”Meanwhile, Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance Jr. was busy trying to get then-President Trump’s tax returns in order to examine his “hush money” payments to the porn star Stormy Daniels. As that investigation expanded into a criminal probe of Trump’s property valuations in cities across the country, that office also sent subpoenas for the Seven Springs conservation deal to the same three towns in December 2020.Except this time, investigators demanded a much larger collection of records. They asked for items like planning board meeting minutes, which would help show whether Trump ever really stood a chance at building on the land, and they sought records dating back more than 15 years in some cases—items that one clerk said should have been destroyed.Another town clerk said that, as recently as two months ago, DA investigators were still picking up boxes of documents and loading them onto a truck.The Daily Beast received a copy of the DA’s more recent subpoenas to Bedford, New Castle, and North Castle, as well as the documents they turned over.Those subpoenas, tied to a 2018 case called “Investigation into the Business and Affairs of John Doe,” demanded copies of a dozen different types of records, as well as “appraisals, engineering reports, and environmental impact statements.”Where those two separate probes overlap, their efforts have now merged.Ever since news of a grand jury broke, Trump reacted in his standard, bitter fury. He publicly denounced the New York investigations as politically motivated, and he claimed they were trying to harm his potential 2024 presidential run.In the past few days, lawyers and other advisers close to the twice-impeached former president have personally reassured Trump they do not believe New York prosecutors will ever actually indict him, according to two people familiar with the situation.“I told him that he has nothing to worry about,” one of these advisers said.Still, Trump’s attorneys have already discussed possible legal maneuvers in the event that the ex-president is eventually indicted as a result of these probes. According to a person with direct knowledge of the conversations, Trump’s lawyers would argue, for instance, that the investigation was tainted due to New York Attorney General Letitia James’ openly “partisan” rhetoric about Trump’s alleged criminality and her remarks about Trump being an “illegitimate” president.Former Manhattan Assistant District Attorney Alissa Marque Heydari, who now runs the academic Institute for Innovation in Prosecution, sounded more hopeful.“Using the grand jury to focus on the acts of the most powerful will help restore trust in the criminal justice system,” she said. “Too often, those tools are brought to bear on the last powerful in our society. But the investigations of the AG and DA buck this norm.”But one source of Trump’s palpable anger with the New York investigations isn’t the possible legal peril; it’s the ballooning financial cost to him and his business empire.The ex-president has recently complained repeatedly about how he feels the investigators could drag this out for years, and that the hefty legal bills are becoming “such a pain in the ass,” one of these sources recounted.Indeed, a motion delivered by Trump’s lawyers earlier this month alleged that a lawsuit filed against him by the NAACP over the Jan. 6 Capitol riot was “frivolous,” and stated that the Democratic plaintiffs and their lawyers “should be ordered to pay President Trump’s fees and costs.”Last week, the AG’s office confirmed that its civil case had recently become a criminal one. James later revealed that two of her prosecutors have been deputized to work alongside the Manhattan DA’s team. And on Tuesday, The Washington Post reported that the DA has already convened a grand jury to make the historic decision of whether or not to indict Trump and others involved.“It’s relatively rare to partner up to this extent on an investigation together,” said Tess Cohen, a criminal defense lawyer who presented cases before grand juries for years when she was at the Special Narcotics Prosecutor's Office in New York City.Given the circumstances, Cohen said it’s likely that both prosecution teams are now presenting to the same grand jury, which is an even rarer development that could indicate a few things. Either one investigation team has access to a key cooperating witness that the other side needs, or the unprecedented act of targeting a former president is such a political minefield that bringing two government offices together strengthens their case.Neither office would confirm the existence of a sitting grand jury, as such proceedings are secret by state law, nor would they provide comment for this story.Another reason to team up might be differences in jurisdiction, said Dan Feldman, a law professor at John Jay College of Criminal Justice who worked at the AG’s office for six years until 2005. Feldman, who as a state legislator also wrote New York's mob-busting anti-racketeering law, said the AG’s office also has greater ability to use that against the many entities and players in the Trump world on this deal.“Because the AG has the organized crime task force, they are particularly well-equipped to pursue an Organized Crime Control Act indictment because they have the expertise, the background, and statewide jurisdiction,” he said.The attorney general has the ability to prosecute crimes that occurred outside of Manhattan. Although the Trump Organization and its Seven Springs LLC subsidiary are based in New York City, the property being appraised is in Westchester County and any meddling in that deal may have occurred outside the city.Trump’s second son, Eric Trump, hired the real estate firm Cushman &amp; Wakefield in June 2015 to appraise the property, according to material gathered by the AG’s office. That firm determined that the property was worth $56.5 million as of Dec. 1, 2015, just days before Trump gave away development rights on a huge chunk of that land.When Trump did sign the agreement, he turned over rights to the North American Land Trust. The conservation easement, as it’s called, bestows power on this nonprofit to protect the 158 acres of red oaks, sugar maples, and huckleberry bushes. An environmental assessment in the document says “it is likely that the Conservation Area provides critical habitat for some of the rarest bat species of the region,” like the little brown bat.One person involved in that conservation deal told The Daily Beast they were questioned by the AG’s office more than two years ago about the land’s value and how it was appraised. The person said they had not spoken to investigators since or been brought before any current grand jury as a witness. The AG’s office would not confirm their account.Another person who was ordered to turn over documents was Charles Martabano, the land-use attorney who represented Seven Springs and tried to develop the property. State investigators used a subpoena to obtain hundreds of pages of emails, although he successfully kept many of them from prosecutors by declaring them subject to attorney-client privilege.“From his point of view, there is absolutely, positively nothing inappropriate here,” said Martabano’s attorney, George J. Calcagnini.One town clerk, who turned over documents to investigators, lambasted the investigation as a waste of time and said the town shouldn’t have kept the documents long enough to turn over to investigators.“They're not going to find what they're looking for,” she said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hollywood 'Jesus' Went Full Q...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-jesus-jim-caviezel-went-000054592.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyJim Caviezel, best known for playing Jesus in Mel Gibson’s The Passion of the Christ and his starring role in CBS’ Person of Interest, made people do a double take when he appeared at a right-wing conference in April to promote his forthcoming anti-child trafficking movie.It wasn’t entirely shocking that Caviezel was at the Health and Freedom Conference, which was attended by former President Donald Trump’s usual posse, including the conspiracy theory-loving trio of MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, attorney Lin Wood, and former Trump lawyer Sidney “release the Kraken” Powell. The actor has proudly been one of few outspoken conservative Christians in Hollywood, counting Steve Bannon as a good friend and often closing out interviews by reciting one of Ronald Reagan’s speeches.But while talking about his new movie Sound of Freedom, Caviezel went on a wild tangent about a QAnon conspiracy theory called “adrenochroming.” The event’s 4,500-strong crowd had a decent showing of raised hands when asked if they were familiar with the term. Essentially, it’s an insane theory rooted in anti-Semitism (and the Pixar film Monsters, Inc.) that liberal elites and members of Hollywood are secretly killing children in order to harvest adrenochrome from their blood for psychedelic experiences, satanic rituals, and even to extend their lifespan. How QAnon Became Obsessed With ‘Adrenochrome,’ an Imaginary Drug Hollywood Is ‘Harvesting’ from KidsHere’s how Caviezel explained it. “I’ll just simplify it,” he began. “When you are scared, you produce adrenaline. You’re an athlete, you get in the fourth quarter, you have adrenaline that comes out. If a child knows he’s going to die, his body will secrete this adrenaline. They have a lot of terms that they use that [Tim Ballard] takes me through, but it’s the worst horror I’ve ever seen. The screaming alone, even if I’d never, ever, ever, ever saw it, it’s beyond.”“These people that do it,” he paused, seeming to hold back tears. “There’ll be no mercy for them.”The crowd burst into applause.So how did Caviezel wind up getting sucked into one of the more fringe conspiracy theories of QAnon? Normally, it’d be easy to track a person’s fall down the rabbit hole of QAnon, starting with their social media behavior, which often involves sharing questionable posts from questionable profiles on Facebook and Twitter.However, Caviezel doesn’t have a very active presence online, apart from his Instagram account that he started in September 2020. Describing the page as his only social media account, he has a sprinkling of posts that include some behind-the-scenes moments at work and photos of scripture. There did seem to be a convincingly real Twitter account belonging to Caviezel that went inactive right when he started his Instagram, which posted about his upcoming projects, praise for Mel Gibson, support of Donald Trump, and dozens of tweets about being pro-life.But it seems that Caviezel could have been brought into the QAnon fold through working on his new movie Sound of Freedom, which is based on the life story of Tim Ballard, who runs the controversial anti-child sex trafficking organization Operation Underground Railroad (OUR). Ballard handpicked Caviezel to play him in the movie, explaining that he was moved by his performances in The Passion of the Christ and The Count of Monte Cristo.Caviezel did not respond to The Daily Beast’s requests for comment.Ballard claims his decade in the U.S. government included a stint as a CIA agent and as an undercover agent with Homeland Security; he was later tapped by Trump to be a council member of the Public-Private Partnership Advisory Council to End Human Trafficking. He spouts off unverified statistics about child trafficking, some of which were repeated by Trump while he was in office.Ballard’s group OUR frequently finds itself entangled with QAnon conspiracy theorists, sometimes by Ballard’s own doing. Last summer, when a since-debunked claim that online furniture retailer Wayfair was secretly promoting the sale of children through its site, Ballard seemed to give credence to the claim, reportedly talking about it at a QAnon-heavy conference and on social media.“With or without Wayfair, child trafficking is real and happening,” he said in a video message. “This is not a small thing or a conspiracy theory, this is the fastest growing criminal enterprise in the world. The children need us.” Ballard did not return The Daily Beast’s requests for comment.That last phrase is a familiar rallying cry for QAnoners, who are often lured into the web of deep state rumors and promises of armed uprisings by claims of a global child sex trafficking ring filled with billionaires, powerful politicians, and members of Hollywood.The slogans #savethechildren and #saveourchildren have become so associated with the QAnon community that when Trump incited a mob to storm the Capitol on January 6th, several insurrectionists carried signs with variations of the phrases, including “Protect the Children'' and "The Children Cry Out for Justice.” In an attempt to stop the spread of disinformation, Facebook has tried to redirect users from the hashtags, instead providing links to reputable groups that work to stop child sexual exploitation. OUR is not among the organizations listed.So it’s no surprise that when Ballard was mentioned several times by Caviezel during his address to the ultra-right-wing conference, the crowd erupted into cheers and applause, already familiar with his work. And when Caviezel suggested that he learned about “adrenochroming” from Ballard, the concept was not new to them.When video of Caviezel’s remarks posted to YouTube, the comments were flooded with talk of “save the children,” declarations of how the “evil Satanic cult will be defeated by the Lord,” and how many believe that “this is common in the dark backrooms of the elite.”Sound of Freedom seems to have leaned into its QAnon fanbase, using both #freethechildren and #savethechildren in its promotional marketing, with fans responding in kind. At a screening for the movie, Caviezel was photographed with former heavyweight boxer David Niño Rodriguez, who has turned into a vocal QAnon supporter and, as of May, still believes a “Trump revival is coming.”Last May, he was on a podcast talking about pizzagate and adrenochrome, saying “they traumatize the kid until you fucking can’t pull out any more adrenaline and then they kill him.”“They drink that shit up,” he added. “It’s a fucking fact bro, everyone knows it. I’m confident to say, ‘Yeah it’s happening.’ All the most powerful people in the world are doing it, you got to remember the elite control shit and they only bring in like minds. So, I don’t have names, I just know this.” Timothy Ballard, Jim Caviezel and director Alejandro Gomez Monteverde on the set of Sound of Freedom Instagram Caviezel also claims that Hollywood doesn’t want a film about the evils of child trafficking, resulting in Sound of Freedom’s delayed release, even though many films’ release dates were pushed due to the ongoing pandemic.“Obviously you understand the content of this, once the world sees this film, once they see the ships that they transport the children in, all that stuff…,” he told the conference. “There’s no other film like this. Our industry can’t make this film right now because a lot of people who are involved in this all over the world, many of these people are very famous.”“So, in the fourth quarter, that’s when we hope [the movie will come out],” he added. “We are going to need your prayers.”Caviezel has long believed he’s up against the forces of Hollywood given his religious beliefs, even claiming that taking the role of Jesus in 2004’s The Passion of the Christ made him a pariah in the industry. Yet he managed to land roles throughout the years, including on CBS’ primetime crime drama Person of Interest in 2011, playing the character of John Reese alongside Michael Emerson and Taraji P. Henson.His time on the show and his connection to QAnon was explored at length in the popular podcast QAnon Anonymous earlier this month, as hosts Julian Feeld, Travis View, and Jack Rockatanksy devoted a whole episode to Caviezel, with featured guest Dave Anthony.Feeld spoke with three anonymous people who worked on Person of Interest with Caviezel who described numerous instances of bizarre behavior from the actor, with the men later summing him up toward the end of the 80-minute episode as “perfect for QAnon!”They said he was “profoundly consumed by a jumble of bizarre religious, military and nationalistic fixations,” initially refusing to participate in an episode where he had to rescue a same-sex couple because it went against his morals. “All of them told me they felt Caviezel was homophobic and believed members of the LGBTQ community were going to hell,” the sources claimed.Another claim was that Caviezel would often make snap judgements of what someone’s ethnicity and race was based on their skin color or appearance, then mimic the language he believed they spoke. He allegedly bowed to an Asian executive and attempted to speak in Chinese to him, later waving off concern because he had adopted two Chinese children.The sources claimed that he would talk in a “blaccent” when around Black crew members and later refused to let his character have a romantic relationship on screen with his Black female co-star because “people shouldn’t have interracial relationships.”He allegedly had an “obsession with identifying Jewish people that was accompanied by a pretty clear hatred for Islam,” and the source said he once walked up to a demonstration where people were planning to burn the Quran in Washington, D.C, and allegedly said, “I know Islam, Islam is evil all the men want Sharia [law].”The sources also mention how Sound of Freedom director Alejandro Monteverde is also a devout Catholic and, like Caviezel, anti-abortion. Caviezel has been very vocal about his pro-life stance, saying in 2010 that he regards it as the “greatest moral defect of the western world.” Discussing how Attila the Hun “raised the bar to another level” when he began killing women and children during wars, he said “abortion goes much further.” Bill O'Reilly and actor Jim Caviezel attend the 30th Annual Great Sports Legends Dinner. Bryan Bedder/Getty “When the mother herself kills her son she goes against her own nature, against her own instinct,” he said. “People talk about ‘choice,’ but when a woman does that, when she destroys the life of her unborn child, then we have arrived at the limit. The level cannot go higher regarding evil.”Speaking to a church congregation in 2014, he spoke about abortion at length, telling the crowd, “Some of you had abortions. Some men and women are adulterers. Some have committed murder. Some of you didn’t have the abortion but you paid for it, so you have contributed to this. Many people are a part of this great sin in this country.”QAnon expert Jack Bratich, an associate professor of journalism and media studies at Rutgers, explained to The Daily Beast how it can often be a slippery slope into QAnon for those who believe they are trying to protect the unborn and vulnerable children when their belief is rooted in religion, because they are sometimes already predisposed to believe that those who think otherwise are evil.“In 2020, when you started seeing that kind of Save the Children hashtag, almost more prominent than QAnon, it was kind of a gateway. You would have these protests for Save the Children and a lot of people would want to ‘save the children,’ right? So, they would show up to these protests or watch a video, and then the more extreme components of QAnon would enter, like adrenochrome and a satanic pedophile ring at the highest levels of government in Hollywood.”“They’re not just predisposed to save children or even save fetuses, but they think there’s a vast enemy that’s out to destroy children. If they already have that kind of framework, that people who are pro-choice are actually evil, that it’s not just a policy matter that they’re actually evil, then it’s a pretty easy slide to go there when it comes to child trafficking and cannibalism.”A recent poll found that roughly one quarter of Republicans believe in some form of the QAnon conspiracy, while QAnon is now as popular in the U.S. as some major religions.Currently, Sound of Freedom does not have an official release date. Its Instagram account has not posted since last September. It appears some of the movie’s producers are still working to get it distributed on a larger scale, hosting small word-of-mouth screenings around the country, most recently in Houston. Ballard appeared to announce a firmer premiere date in April, claiming it would be coming out in the fall of 2021, but the post has since been taken down.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do deficits matter anymore? Biden's first budget signals they don't...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/do-deficits-matter-anymore-biden-s-first-budget-signals-they-don-t/ar-AAKuHYg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s first budget predicts a $1.8 trillion deficit for 2022 and deficits of $1.3 trillion for years to come to fund big investments in education, infrastructure and the social safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer drones 'hunted down humans without being told to'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/killer-ai-drones-hunted-down-24203431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The explosive-carrying quadcopters, which were deployed during an engagement between rival factions in the Libyan civil war, are thought to have deliberately crashed into targets without being ordered a human controller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUGHT ON RADAR:  Moment USS Omaha Swarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9627489/Moment-USS-Omaha-SWARMED-14-UFOs-radar-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video (right) showing UFO splashing into Pacific Ocean off coast of San Diego two years ago appears to have been corroborated by military radar (left) - footage of which was released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers held experimental indoor concert in Spain with no social distancing. No one contracted virus!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Researchers-held-an-experimental-indoor-concert-16210285.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In December, hundreds of people packed into a Barcelona arena to dance and sing along to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:   Boy charged as an adult after cheerleader stabbed 114 times!</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/breaking-news/2021/05/28/florida-boy-14-charged-as-an-adult-after-cheerleader-stabbed-114-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charged in the case is 14-year-old Aiden Fucci, a schoolmate in St. Johns County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba rolls out homegrown vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-bets-on-biotech-prowess-as-it-rolls-out-homegrown-covid-19-vaccine/ar-AAKuiTM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soberana, or sovereign, is how Cuba baptized its top COVID-19 vaccine, which just completed the last phase of clinical trials. Other shots are called Abdala, named after a poem by independence hero José Martí, and Mambisa, the word for 19th Century insurrectionists in the fight against Spanish rule. The names reveal a lot about the island's political and economic strategy to focus on a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman known as 'Neighbor from Hell' again charged with two counts of stalking...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/weddings/minn-woman-known-as-neighbor-from-hell-again-charged-with-two-counts-of-stalking/ar-AAKuCYY?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS – A White Bear Lake, Minnesota, woman dubbed as the "Neighbor from Hell" for years of menacing her neighbors was charged Thursday with two counts of stalking after she harassed real estate agents and prospective buyers who came to look at the property next door that had recently been put up for sale. Lori E. Christensen, 57, took photos of and videotaped clients, put up "No ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pledges to tackle supply shortages as prices rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527222243-0lyxr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/BIDEN (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Biden pledges to tackle monopolies, supply shortages as prices rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin: Ground zero for hesitancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/may/28/wisconsin-coronavirus-vaccine-hesitancy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid vaccine take-up varies widely between rural and urban counties but many of those yet to get a shot remain open to it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYPILLOW CEO flew Kristi Noem to governors conference. And then left...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/28/mike-lindell-kristi-noem-private-jet-491348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Lindell was then kicked out of the RGA event after threatening to confront certain governors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Michael Lewis' teen daughter dead after head-on collision...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/28/author-michael-lewis-teen-daughter-dead-after-head-on-collision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Moneyball” and “The Big Short” author Michael Lewis’ 19-year-old daughter Dixie Lewis was killed in a California car crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUTGERS apologizse after speaking out against anti-Semitism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rutgers-university-chancellor-provost-apologize-164750273.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chancellor and provost of a satellite campus of Rutgers University apologized for an email they sent out condemning anti-Semitism as the U.S. sees a dramatic rise in anti-Jewish hate crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's New Stamps To Call Out Racism Draw Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/05/28/1001228126/spains-new-postage-stamps-were-meant-to-call-out-racism-instead-they-drew-outrag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's postal service issued a set of four stamps in different skin-colored tones. The darker the stamp, the lower the price. The controversial effort was meant to highlight racial inequality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Eyeing Vaccine Passports for Travel Abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-covid-vaccine-passport-mayorkas-travel-546fec90-3b6d-4d84-afff-64c1514ad295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There’s an underlying point here, of course, which is everyone should get vaccinated."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse spotted trying veal in WHOLE FOODS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/28/mouse-spotted-feasting-on-high-grade-veal-at-nyc-whole-foods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mouse was spotted chowing down on a raw slab of Osso Bucco Veal, priced at $22.99 a pound — at the Columbus Circle store — making shoppers squeak with dismay, according to a TikTok video.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infighting Plagues Democrats Before Critical Virginia Primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.virginiamercury.com/2021/05/26/va-house-democratic-caucus-oks-mailers-portraying-top-democratic-donors-as-dark-money-billionaires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.virginiamercury.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Virginia House Democratic Caucus authorized and funded attack mailers that falsely imply two of the state’s top donors to Democrats are right-wing “dark money billionaires,” according to an image of the mailer obtained by The Virginia Mercury. The caucus-backed messages were sent in support of new Del. Candi King, D-Prince William, who has accepted […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Frank Luntz Created Mess Inside LATIMES...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frank-luntz-created-mess-inside-193806884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyWell-known Republican pollster Frank Luntz’s work is causing headaches for the Los Angeles Times.Recent revelations that he conducted undisclosed, behind-the-scenes partisan consulting while also doing unpaid work for the paper came as little surprise to staffers, who have previously raised concerns about conflicts-of-interest in his work.Earlier this month, The Washington Post reported that Luntz, a veteran political strategist who has worked in Republican politics for decades and conducted focus groups on behalf of television networks and other media organizations, had been paid by a political action committee controlled by House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy to conduct surveys last year.The revelation created editorial issues for the Los Angeles Times, which had enlisted Luntz to conduct several focus group surveys during the 2020 election under the condition he was not also working with candidates or partisan organizations.The Post’s story pushed the Times to update several items from last year about the focus groups, noting that the paper “incorrectly stated that the public opinion expert who convened the panel, Frank Luntz, did not work for a political party in the 2020 election cycle.”The embarrassment also opened up an old wound within the newsroom, where Luntz’s public-opinion surveys had previously been the subject of internal tension and concerns voiced by newspaper staffers.A famed public-opinion analyst with decades of experience, Luntz has been a fixture of Republican politics since the early 1990s, when he helped House Speaker Newt Gingrich draft the Contract With America and advised other Republican figures like former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani and Pat Buchanan. For years, Luntz interspersed his political work with media appearances, hosting focus groups and regularly appearing on Fox News and CBS News, where he had contributor contracts.While his paid TV work has seemed to slow in recent years, Luntz—who did not respond to a request for comment on this story—has continued to partner with major media outlets during election seasons to hold small focus groups designed to explore what supposedly motivates the average American voter. Just last week, he conducted a session on conservative views of George Floyd, published in The New York Times opinion section; and another recent Luntz session with vaccine-resistant Republicans was prominently featured on This American Life and in The Washington Post.LA Times Billionaire’s Daughter Is Tinkering With the Paper. And Staffers Welcome It.Last year, the Los Angeles Times commissioned Luntz to conduct a round of such group sessions following one of the 2020 Democratic presidential primary debates. Multiple sources with knowledge told The Daily Beast that the paper’s owner, Patrick Soon-Shiong, was interested in focus groups run by Luntz, who Salon noted was personal friends with the LA-based pharmaceutical-industry billionaire (both Luntz and McCarthy were part of a clinical trial for the COVID vaccine that Soon-Shiong is pursuing, Salon further reported). The move sparked concern among some Times staffers, particularly some of the unionized journalists covering the election, who felt his consultation for political organizations—including Trump administration officials—gave an inherently right-leaning partisan slant to his surveys.Newspaper staffers brought their concerns to Norm Pearlstine, then editor-in-chief, as well as top deputies Scott Kraft and Shani Hilton, informing management that unionized staffers refused to put their bylines on Luntz-related content, citing wariness of the analyst’s political work and methodology (Luntz’s questions have occasionally publicly irked survey participants, who felt he was biased toward particular candidates and ideas).The paper, which had already recorded a focus group with Democratic primary voters, decided last summer to move the content from its news section to its opinion vertical. Staffers thought the matter was largely settled.But many journalists and some newsroom leaders were taken aback when, just a few months later, the paper decided to conduct a second round of focus groups with Luntz, this time following the presidential and vice-presidential debates.In messages posted to an internal Slack channel dedicated to journalistic ethics, reporter Michael Finnegan wrote that he and other staffers were frustrated that the paper enlisted Luntz to host yet another round of focus groups given his work advising top Trump administration officials on messaging for a variety of political issues. More specifically, Finnegan—who did not respond to a request for comment—said he was concerned about the language in the story claiming Luntz was not working for any candidate or party during the 2020 election. The pollster had advised the Trump administration informally during the president’s time in office, the Times reporter noted for his colleagues.“It’s a conflict of interest for him to advise top Trump administration officials on how to talk about immigration, trade, education, and other topics,” Finnegan wrote, “and then hold himself out to be an unbiased vehicle for assembling an LA Times focus group of independent voters to evaluate a Trump-Biden debate.”Others on staff pointed out that Luntz’s survey group didn’t include enough diverse perspectives, which had been a source of frustration in the newsroom all year after a heated and public reckoning over the paper’s failure to adequately cover non-white communities in Southern California. Some felt that Luntz was encouraging survey participants to engage in what they felt were racial and gendered stereotypes about then-Sen. Kamala Harris, including comments on her facial expressions and how likeable she was.“It’s bad enough his panelists tend to trot these stereotypes out unchecked, but it’s hard to be surprised when they’re the same ones frank tweets and says himself (and then prompts them on in questions),” another Times staffer added in the Slack chat at the time.The paper was unaware of Luntz’s partisan work during the 2020 election cycle. Times opinion editor Sewell Chan told colleagues that Luntz told him he had not been paid by any candidate, party, or committee during the election cycle. But as Salon noted this week, Luntz’s firm was paid by the Republican leader’s PAC multiple times in the days before and after the focus groups held in partnership with the SoCal-based paper. (Salon also reported that Luntz had failed to disclose work for Sen. Ted Cruz’s 2018 re-election campaign while hosting several focus groups for Vice News.)In a note sent to staffers on Friday, Chan defended the decision to host the focus groups, claiming they offered “interesting insights into the minds of undecided voters,” and said that the paper did not present Luntz’s studies as scientific samples. Still, he seemed to express frustration with the pollster and said he acted swiftly to update the past content. Further, he suggested the pollster would likely would not return as a contributor to the opinion section due to his failure to disclose his work for GOP leadership.‘I Trolled Trump at a Frank Luntz Focus Group’“It is most unfortunate that Luntz failed to disclose his ties to McCarthy’s PAC, and his ethical lapse will certainly factor into our thinking should he ever wish to be an opinion contributor again,” Chan wrote.In a statement, the Times noted that the focus groups were not conducted by the paper itself, but that the paper had provided production support and hosted the video on its website.“While we regret that Luntz did not originally disclose his work for a political action committee led by Rep. Kevin McCarthy (R-Bakersfield), the House minority leader, at the time the focus groups were conducted, we believe that the discussion with voters during the campaign was valuable,” spokesperson Hillary Manning wrote. “We have added the disclosure where the videos are published.”While many on the left have been critical of Luntz and his focus groups for years, the veteran strategist has come under increased scrutiny in recent weeks from conservatives.Earlier this month, Fox News primetime host Tucker Carlson used his show to rage against Luntz as being increasingly beholden to “liberal causes” by offering advice to large companies. The right-wing media star additionally reported that the House minority leader once rented a room in the veteran pollster’s lavish D.C. home.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORVETTE Driver Arrested For Going 150 On NH Highway...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/28/corvette-driver-rochester-nh-clocked-150-mph-route-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Corvette driver was arrested by New Hampshire State Police for allegedly going 150 miles per hour on the highway in Rochester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex allegations rock LA's largest LGBTQ theater company...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/sexual-misconduct-allegations-rocking-l-120004992.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael A. Shepperd, artistic director of Celebration Theatre, was fired after allegations of sexual misconduct. What he and his accusers tell The Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA using cabin cameras to spy on drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/28/tesla-starts-using-cabin-cameras-for-driver-monitoring.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technical changes come amid regulatory scrutiny of Tesla vehicle safety in the U.S. and abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common pain reliever may increase risk of autism, ADHD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/28/common-pain-reliever-linked-to-risk-of-autism-adhd-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research found that unborn children exposed to acetaminophen, compared to non-exposed fetuses, were 19% more likely to land on the spectrum of autism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke flash cards: US secrets exposed on learning apps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nuclear-flash-cards-us-secrets-190918744.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US troops charged with guarding nuclear weapons in Europe used popular education websites to create flash cards, exposing their exact locations and top-secret security protocols, according to the investigative site Bellingcat Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Lightfoot sued for limiting interviews to reporters of color...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/il-state-wire-business-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-2b7119002e31896293abcaaa14787559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A white reporter for a conservative media outlet is suing Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot over her decision to grant interviews at the midpoint of her first term only to journalists of color , saying she discriminated against him because of his race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plexiglass Barriers Everywhere, but Probably Useless...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/05/27/plexiglass-barriers-are-everywhere-but-theyre-probably-useless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a good chance they haven't been preventing the spread of COVID, and they might even be counterproductive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci once argued viral experiments worth risk of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/28/fauci-once-argued-viral-experiments-worth-the-risk-of-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci once argued that conducting experiments on contagious viruses to increase their potency was worth the risk — even if the work could accidentally lead to a pandemic, it was r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Building 2 Secret Nuke Reactors. Scientists Freak...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/energy/a36517874/china-mysterious-nuclear-reactors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These aren't your average reactors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver Shortage Only Compounding Supply Issues...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/truck-driver-shortage-impacting-gas-stations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Twin Cities-area gas stations have been running out of gas ahead of the Memorial Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC eases summer camp guidance: Kids can [at times] go bareface...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2021/05/28/camp-mask-guidelines-cdc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cafe to charge mask-wearing patrons $5 fee...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/fiddleheads-cafe-vaccines-mask-policy-sign-16206085.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When asked if he believed it fair to charge customers the extra fee, the owner said he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas demand may hit record...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/u-s-gasoline-demand-may-hit-a-record-this-summer-gasbuddy-11622223671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer gasoline demand is nearly back to normal and any disruptions to the fuel flow could lead to more pain the pumps, with drivers already facing their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept Worker Committed 'Corporate Espionage' for Tens of Thousands in Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/state-department-worker-committed-corporate-224852780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. District Court for the District of ColumbiaA federal construction contractor that worked for several U.S. agencies bribed a State Department worker to commit “corporate espionage” and steer contracts worth more than $100 million to his company in exchange for tens of thousands of dollars in cash, federal investigators allege in a newly-unsealed search warrant affidavit.Iranian-born May Salehi, who was assigned to the State Department’s division of Overseas Buildings Operations (OBO), had a security clearance and a mountain of debt, according to the document. To get out of her financial hole, special agents working for the State Department’s Inspector General believe Salehi, 65, illegally helped steer what might have amounted to more than $100 million in State business to a Washington, D.C.-based company as part of a “multifaceted fraud scheme” that spanned several years and at least half a dozen countries.Salehi began working for the State Department in 1996, according to her LinkedIn profile. A State Department spokesperson told The Daily Beast that Salehi is still employed there. She does not have a lawyer listed in court records, and did not respond to a message seeking comment. No arrests have yet been made, according to the affidavit.The origins of the case can be traced back to 2014, when Montage, Inc. of Chevy Chase, Maryland, won a $26.1 million State contract to renovate the U.S. Consulate in Lagos, Nigeria. But the project went two years over deadline, and nearly bankrupted the firm, the affidavit states. That’s when something strange happened: Instead of avoiding State Department projects following the Nigeria “debacle,” the affidavit says Montage “transformed its business model so that it relied almost exclusively on State Department projects thereafter—indeed, the exact type of overseas, complex, U.S. embassy/consulate project that Montage had just been nearly decimated by.”Over the next three years, Montage mysteriously won six major contracts with the State Department to build U.S. embassies or consulates overseas. This “seemingly counterintuitive” development can be “explained by the existence of a State Department insider who had an illegal relationship with Montage,” according to the affidavit. From that point on, roughly 95 percent of Montage’s revenue came exclusively from State Department contracts—$106.5 million of $111.4 million to date—nearly double what it had taken in previously.Who’s the Mole?In September 2020, State Department agents raided Montage’s offices on suspicion of, among other things, bank fraud, money laundering, and unauthorized removal and retention of classified materials. There, they seized numerous documents, nearly 40 computers, several cell phones, and a 96-terabyte server.One office was the D.C. headquarters Montage lists publicly as its primary place of business. The second was what investigators describe in the warrant as the company’s “secret” office suite in Chevy Chase, Maryland. The space was purchased through a shell company and had a sign by the door identifying it as the American Society for Addictive Medicine.There, agents encountered Montage founder and principal Sina Moayedi. In the affidavit, Special Agent Christopher Swenson states he told Moayedi that if he happened to have “information about a Government insider, that it would be something we would be very interested to hear.”“Moayedi’s demeanor and expression changed immediately, as he raised his head and made direct eye contact with me, stating in substance, ‘I think I understand what you’re asking: You want to know if I’m paying someone in the State Department?’” the agent recalled.Investigators suspected Moayedi had forged business licenses and credentials for Montage employees he said would be working on government projects. A resume he submitted to the State Department for a project manager on one job claimed the employee had “years of full-time complex work in the construction field in various capacities.” However, the affidavit states the person “had actually sold meat as a door-to-door salesman, was a landscaper, and built swimming pools for several years during the same time period.”Agents interviewed two unnamed Montage executives, who blamed the company’s troubles on its former CFO, claiming he had embezzled money from the firm. But when they visited the ex-CFO at his home in Maryland, a different story emerged.During the interview, Swenson read the former CFO an email in which a Montage bookkeeper painted him as an alcoholic, and said he had mental health problems. The CFO had covered up his alleged theft by “creating an entire phony universe of Quickbooks, payroll, receivables, payables and bank account statements,” the bookkeeper claimed in the message, and said the CFO “took payroll under assumed names.”Upon learning that he was being set up as Montage’s fall guy, the former CFO turned on Moayedi, describing him as a “master forger” who electronically altered bank balances, forged resumes, and kept at least four sets of books that Moayedi not only used to dupe lenders but also to significantly reduce his own personal tax burden.That’s when the CFO dropped a bombshell. He told agents that Moayedi “had cultivated a career employee at the State Department” and paid this person “bribes in exchange for intelligence regarding Government contracts,” the affidavit states. The CFO didn’t remember the State Department insider’s name, but recalled that she was a female “Iranian friend” of Moayedi’s whom he met through a “community group relating to Iranian heritage.”The CFO told agents that he had met the insider at a pre-bid conference for a State Department project in Slovenia a few years back. She had also helped Moayedi and Montage win a State Department contract in the Caribbean in exchange for a $60,000 kickback, the CFO said. To hide the transaction, the CFO claimed Moayedi cut a check which the CFO cashed and provided to a middleman, who passed the cash to the corrupt State Department employee. To further obfuscate the truth, the insider was told to give the middleman a $2,000 Persian rug in exchange for the cash “in case ‘anyone asked’” about it.Follow the MoneyA search of State Department travel records identified the insider as May Salehi, an engineer in the State Department’s OBO Project Development and Coordination Division. Passport records confirmed that Salehi, who lived less than a mile from Montage’s “secret” office, was in fact born in Iran.Salehi’s position requires a security clearance, so investigators analyzed her official paperwork for clues. One red flag involved Salehi’s 2007 divorce, which took place shortly after she secured a $1.5 million mortgage for a home in Great Falls, Virginia. The mortgage payments on the house ran approximately $10,000 a month—exceeding Salehi’s gross salary at the time of $9,333 a month. Another detail that raised agents’ suspicions was a Porsche Boxster convertible Salehi purchased in 2014, paying off $15,000 of a 60-month, $25,000 loan in a lump-sum the following year. U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia A review of phone records found that Salehi had “significant, sudden telephonic contacts with Moayedi in the precise period that Montage’s fortunes suddenly changed,” the affidavit says. Financial records subpoenaed by investigators turned up numerous transactions, each worth tens of thousands of dollars, including one with a memo line that read, “Final payment for Anna’s house.”Investigators then dug into Salehi’s State Department email account. They found that Salehi “likely knew of Montage and Moayedi (in her professional capacity) by 2006, as Montage was bidding State Department projects at that time in New Delhi, India and Abuja, Nigeria,” the affidavit says, noting that agents found at least one official document in her email archive listing Sina Moayedi as Montage’s point of contact. She had also forwarded numerous internal State project documents from her work email to her personal email, all of which pertained to contracts Montage later won. Many of them were sent at odd intervals, furthering investigators’ suspicions.“In particular, forwarding trip reports so long after the conclusion of the trip itself tends to negate any suggestion that Salehi was merely ‘taking her work home with her,’ and therefore forwarded these emails for the purpose of finishing up State Department business from home,” states the affidavit. “On the other hand, transferring these documents from her State Department account to Salehi Personal Email Account-1 would have certain benefits for someone engaged in selling Government information. For example, such transfers would allow Salehi to print hard copies for later dissemination without any State Department oversight.”A review of Salehi’s search history on her State Department computer revealed further evidence against her. According to the affidavit, Salehi searched for “SCI clearance,” “herb for anxiety,” “Kratom herb for anxiety,” “Montage construction company litigations,” “what is litigation,” YouTube videos about litigation, and “Shiva Hamidinia,” who was Montage’s longtime legal counsel. Investigators subpoenaed cell phone records from a Montage employee and found a text from Moayedi that said: “Nela please conf call me 1/2 through your meeting with Shiva and May.” Agents also discovered Salehi’s contact info within Moayedi’s cell phone contacts and his Telegram, Skype, and iCloud accounts.The feds now want to seize further documents they believe will bolster the government’s case against Salehi.“[A]mong the materials we are requesting permission to seize are Salehi’s tax-related documents and filings, which are likely to contain either (implicit) admissions of her having received bribe payments, or false statements in an attempt to conceal the bribery scheme, just as she appears to have done in her State Department financial disclosure forms,” the affidavit says. U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia Investigators asked a judge to let them search Salehi herself, including “any and all clothing and personal belongings, backpacks, briefcases, purses, bags, and electronic devices that are within Salehi’s immediate vicinity and control, wherever Salehi is located within the federal judicial district of the District of Columbia.”According to court filings, agents executed two warrants at 6:12 a.m. on May 20 and seized Salehi’s Apple Watch, three iPhones, a Macbook Pro, a micro SD card, a Dell laptop, an iPad, and a letter-size manila folder with a gray folder inside.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donna Brazile canceled at FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-and-donna-brazile-quietly-part-ways</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic pundit confirmed to The Daily Beast that she is no longer with Fox, and that the split was amicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spy ship operating off Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/05/26/breaking-news/russian-spy-ship-operating-off-kauai-navy-confirms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian spy ship parked in international waters off Kauai for several days has delayed a Missile Defense Agency missile test, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED ALERT: Chinese Military to Overtake US by End of Biden Term...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/politico-china-watcher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s next in U.S.-China relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortions in Illinois up 10%...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-illinois-abortion-numbers-increase-20210528-s5ddpbvcw5dk3ckwx5p5xv2d5m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of abortions performed in Illinois recently increased by almost 10%, with about 4,000 more terminated pregnancies reported in 2019 than the previous year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donna Brazile Exits FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/28/fox-news-intensifies-its-pro-trump-politics-as-dissenters-depart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News once devoted its 7 p.m. and 11 p.m. time slots to relatively straightforward newscasts. Now those hours are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans block creation of commission to investigate Jan. 6 riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/was-attack-our-capitol-murkowski-criticizes-gop-colleagues-opposing-jan-n1268906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House-passed legislation hit a dead end in the Senate due to Republican opposition led by Sen. Mitch McConnell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIGITAL COVID PASSPORT DEBUT IN COPENHAGEN</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/danes-present-digital-coronavirus-passport-113245238.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Danish government on Friday presented its digital coronavirus passport enabling people to travel abroad or, in Denmark, go to the hairdresser, a tattoo parlor, dine inside a restaurant or wherever else it is needed. “The corona passport we present today can be used from July 1 when you can travel within the EU,” said Finance Minister Nicolai Vammen. During a press conference outside the Copenhagen airport, Health Minister Magnus Heunicke held up his phone to show the app, which only features a QR code and a green bar if the person has been vaccinated twice or recently tested negative for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rtsHNQeqAA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the Carlos Watson Show: a new breed of talk show where we're having meaningful conversations with the game-changers and change-makers who are ahea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey Lays Out Political Goals: No Bandaid Solutions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/555944-mcconaughey-face-masks-a-short-term-inconvenience-for-long-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew McConaughey is blasting the politicization of wearing face masks amid the coronavirus pandemic, calling the practice a "short-term inconvenience for long-term freedom."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy parks try reservations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/parks-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-philanthropy-health-86f8554cf2c3a95d8462f5ecb440967c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. HUBERTS, N.Y. (AP) — Nick and Matthew Golebiewski climbed to the summit of Gothics mountain in the Adirondacks with packs, water, good boots and a new must-have item: advanced reservations. The free reservation system went online recently to handle the fast-growing number of visitors to the privately owned Adirondack Mountain Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry blasts world as 'depressing' and believes is 'making us sicker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/prince-harry-blasts-world-depressing-24202310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex also said that 'parents aren't equipped' to help their children growing up in the world in a new episode of The Me You Can't See: The Path Forward with Oprah Winfrey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia imposes near-total lockdown after virus soars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/malaysia-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-2ed4ca58354171e33646d72a93e2f834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — Malaysia's prime minister announced on Friday a near-total coronavirus lockdown in the country, with social and economic activities to be halted for two weeks to contain a worsening outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO pay rises to $12.7 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ceo-pay-rises-again-b1d87eb36ac921a159268a6b830fc308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — As COVID-19 ravaged the world last year, CEOs’ big pay packages seemed to be under as much threat as everything else. Fortunately for those CEOs, many had boards of directors willing to see the pandemic as an extraordinary event beyond their control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Box office could be first to top $100 million since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/28/memorial-day-box-office-could-be-first-to-top-100-million-during-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Memorial Day weekend could break the $100 million mark at the box office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: New era of frivolity and decadence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ok-state-wire-migration-immigration-coronavirus-pandemic-business-361a9bf86ea3175194957b7550bb6051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — History repeats itself. But do decades duplicate? As hopes rise that the pandemic is ebbing in the United States and Europe, visions of a second “Roaring Twenties” to match last century’s post-pandemic decade have proliferated.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
