<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Beijing takes aim at USA, Taiwan in new military blueprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/China-takes-aim-at-U-S-Taiwan-in-new-military-14118706.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - China sharpened its hostility toward the United States and Taiwan in a new high-level report on its future military strategy that accused Washington and its allies of undermining global stability.  Releasing the document on Wednesday, officials of the People's Liberation Army repeatedly warned that Beijing would be willing to deploy military force to assert its claims over Taiwan. The self-ruled island has pulled closer to the Trump administration and agreed this month to buy $2.2 billion in weapons, including M1A2T Abrams tanks and Stinger missiles.  Taiwan's incumbent Democratic Progressive Party favors declaring formal independence from China, a move that could spark confrontation in the Taiwan Strait, one of the world's most heavily militarized flash points. China's navy this month sailed its sole aircraft carrier into the strait in a show of force reminiscent of similar U.S. operations two decades ago that showcased American military dominance in Asia.  "If anyone dares to separate Taiwan from China, the Chinese military would not hesitate to go to war," Chinese military spokesman Wu Qian said as he laid out what officials called a revised national defense policy for "the New Era" - a catchphrase that denotes the imprimatur of China's assertive leader, Xi Jinping.  The military blueprint comes as tensions simmer in the western Pacific and China moves to enforce its strategic aims across the region, including in the disputed South China Sea. Beijing views democratically ruled Taiwan, which separated from the Communist-ruled mainland in 1949, as a renegade province.  Global military competition was rising, with the United States "strengthening its Asia-Pacific military alliances" and engaging in "technological and institutional innovation in pursuit of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER TAKES STAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f109a539220b41218860fa68176a9c98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside reports of deaths, sickness that have consumed Dominican Republic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/24/inside-the-reports-of-deaths-sickness-that-have-consumed-dominican-republic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s fear surrounding the Dominican Republic these days. In just the past few months, the beach oasis has been battered by a steady stream of disturbing reports about tourist deaths, sudde…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>