<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Al-Baghdadi will 'still be alive in deepfake' to recruit new ISIS terrorists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/al-baghdadi-still-alive-deepfake-20841470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: US President Donald Trump said Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi had been wiped out but deepfake material could be used by ISIS to cast doubt on his claims among potential recruits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI INVITES TRUMP TO TESTIFY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nancy-pelosi-face-the-nation-trump-has-every-opportunity-to-present-his-case-in-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi told CBS News that "what the president did was so much worse than even what Richard Nixon did"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong braces for more disruption as violence escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/hong-kong-braces-for-more-disruption-as-violence-escalates/article_88e5bfe7-9bb4-530c-b267-03dcd6d8b0fe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG — Hong Kong police and protesters hardened their battle lines over the weekend as violent clashes showed no signs of abating, leaving the city bracing for a second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE:  Conservatives seek to stifle new 'alt-right' movement...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/470687-conservatives-seek-to-stifle-new-alt-right-movement-seeped-in-anti-semitism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fringe group of far-right activists have been disrupting conservative and pro-Trump events in recent weeks, drawing rebukes from mainstream Republicans who are eager to separate the party from white nationalists and alt-right racists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM GOV WINS LA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b65e73cbb2304514997d073a36e5bcbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Deep in the heart of the conservative South, Louisiana’s voters reelected Democratic Gov. John Bel Edwards to a second term, shocking Republicans who had hoped to reclaim...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastated Venice hit with third major flood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/343886375fcb49e58ee188ddab0fbb0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE, Italy (AP) — Venice was hit Sunday by a record third exceptional tide in the same week while other parts of Italy struggled with a series of weather woes, from rain-swollen rivers to high...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader warns 'thugs' as protests reach 100 cities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0a1699c5fa1549f9b3ef239a19427d70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran’s supreme leader on Sunday cautiously backed the government’s decision to raise gasoline prices by 50% after days of widespread protests, calling those who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How FEDEX Cut Its Tax Bill to $0...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/how-fedex-cut-its-tax-bill-to-0/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the 2017 fiscal year, FedEx owed more than $1.5 billion in taxes. The next year, it owed nothing. What changed was the Trump administration’s tax cut — for which the company had lobbied hard. The public face...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House preps sweeping homeless crackdown in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-administration-ousts-top-homelessness-official-as-white-house-prepares-broad-crackdown/ar-BBWRIpI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambassador discussed sensitive matters from Kyiv restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sondland-discussed-sensitive-matters-with-trump-on-phone-from-kyiv-restaurant-as-waiters-circled/ar-BBWRNHp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Looking for Next Generation of Stars -- Ages 9-12...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/nfl-looking-for-next-generation-of-stars-ages-9-12-111719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is wrapping up its 100th season celebration by searching for the next generation of stars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Braun-Taylor Swift feud just took wild turn...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/17/the-scooter-braun-taylor-swift-feud-just-took-a-wild-turn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Braun’s company, Ithaca Holdings, bought the masters of Swift’s first six albums and her former record label Big Machine for $300 million in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTROS emails reveal more evidence in cheating scandal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/16/astros-emails-reveal-how-deep-cheating-scandal-went-in-2017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sign-stealing case against the Astros continues to grow. In August 2017, as Houston prepared for the playoffs, a front office executive expressed the organization’s desire to steal signs in an …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 Muslim candidates won election across USA this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/national/muslim-candidates-faced-hatred-in-political-races-this-year-won/article_9e503468-6abc-503c-9baf-9793342b86f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT — When Abdul El-Sayed announced in February 2017 he was running as a Democrat to be Michigan’s next governor, it was just a few weeks after President Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong campus protesters fire arrows as unrest spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests/hong-kong-campus-protesters-fire-arrows-as-unrest-spreads-across-kowloon-idUSKBN1XQ0OJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong protesters shot bows and arrows and hurled petrol bombs from a barrica...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm bankruptcies at highest since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-stock-market-at-record-but-farm-bankruptcies-at-highest-since-2011-2019-11-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While U.S. stock market is soaring to new records, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average hitting 28,000 on Friday, farmers are having trouble paying their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalpers selling tix for $500...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7693287/People-selling-free-Kanye-West-Sunday-Service-tickets-online-500.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People on social media have been trying to practice their own prosperity theology and resell tickets for Kanye West's Sunday Service at Joel Osteen's Lakewood Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence aide tells inquiry President's call was 'unusual and inappropriate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7693221/White-House-budget-official-testifies-impeachment-probe-Saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Williams, who serves as Pence's special adviser for Europe and Russia, was listening in on the call which is now at the heart of the impeachment inquiry into President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Barbarians' go to war with Warren...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/17/elizabeth-warren-popeyes-2020-071237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator’s latest elite target tries to fend off her attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans accuse Janet Jackson of lip-syncing concert, walk out in protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/janet-jackson-lip-syncing-concert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Janet Jackson fans are not happy with the singer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Win a Baby' radio sweepstakes winners have boy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox4now.com/news/local-news/win-a-baby-contest-winners-have-a-boy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox4now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A once-in-a-lifetime radio sweepstakes helped a Cape Coral couple start their own family. B1039 held a 'Win a Baby' contest in which the winner gets a round of in vitro fertilization treatments and required medication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President makes 'unscheduled' Walter Reed visit for medical exam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/16/politics/trump-annual-physical-walter-reed/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump underwent a "quick exam and labs" as part of his annual physical exam on Saturday, out of anticipation of a "very busy 2020," the White House said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton, Trump Met Privately Over Withheld Aid, White House Official Testified...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/bolton-and-trump-met-privately-over-withheld-aid-white-house-official-testified/ar-BBWRFYl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY's oldest boy's club may finally allow female members...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/16/new-yorks-oldest-charity-to-vote-on-allowing-female-members-after-235-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, the city’s oldest charity, will vote on a resolution this week to allow women to become members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Justin Bieber's VIP, Sex Joke-Filled Celebrity Megachurch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-churchome-justin-biebers-vip-and-sex-joke-filled-celebrity-megachurch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We venture inside the Beverly Hills house of worship, where the Biebers and Kardashians take in sermons by the charismatic Pastor Judah Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Stents no better than drugs for many heart patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-heart-stent/stents-no-better-than-drugs-for-many-heart-patients-u-s-study-idUSKBN1XQ0MR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many patients with severe but stable heart disease who routinely undergo invasiv...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Saudi Arabia, TWITTER becomes more useful to repressors than the repressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/opinion/article/In-Saudi-Arabia-Twitter-becomes-more-useful-to-14840969.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This editorial appears in The Washington Post:  - - -  Omar Abdulaziz is only one person, but his story offers a way to better understand 9.9 million more. That's the number of Saudis on Twitter, a platform that has been at the center of Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's efforts to stamp out dissent and promote the misleading story that it's doing just the opposite.  Abdulaziz wrote in The Post this week that more than 30 Saudi citizens influential on the social media site told him they were blackmailed with material gained from hacking their phones - just as Abdulaziz's own phone was breached using spyware sold by the Israeli company NSO Group. These efforts were payback not only for speaking out against the regime generally but also for speaking out against the regime on Twitter in particular. Of the three most influential Saudis on Twitter, Abdulaziz wrote, one has been arrested, a second has disappeared, and he is in exile.  The ultimate aim of the blackmail Abdulaziz identifies was focused on the platform once again. The targets were ordered to tweet propaganda, or else the government would release their private communications and pictures. Complying would align them with the virtual army assembled by Saud al-Qahtani, the former royal court adviser known by activists as the "minister of flies." Abdulaziz had been amassing a counterforce called the "electronic bees" with the aid of Post contributing columnist Jamal Khashoggi. Khashoggi, when he learned regime officials had discovered their attempt, wrote to Abdulaziz: "God help us." He was murdered by the regime two months later.  Twitter is popular among Saudis as a public square because protesting in a physical public square has rarely been an option. Abdulaziz's experience first of "living democratically" online and then watching that democracy get strangled -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Say Ditching Smartphones For Week Changed Their Lives...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/students-ditch-phone-changed-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They survived! Nearly two dozen Adelphi University students made it a full week without their cell phones!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM GOV WINS</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/elections/article_2b7c0b7c-08a5-11ea-bcfe-1bd7f6b19e9d.html?1573962442332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Gov. John Bel Edwards will win a second term as Louisiana governor, defeating his Republican opponent Eddie Rispone, WWL is projecting tonight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President cast Louisiana vote as impeachment referendum...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-casts-louisiana-vote-as-impeachment-referendum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will it be enough?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUISIANA RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://voterportal.sos.la.gov/static/2019-11-16/resultsRace/Statewide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;voterportal.sos.la.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUISIANA RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2019/11/16/20963502/louisiana-election-results-live-edwards-rispone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lone Democratic governor in the Deep South is trying to hang onto his seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Denver Radio Host Fired Midshow After Criticizing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/conservative-denver-radio-host-fired-midshow-after-criticizing-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Denver radio station 710 KNUS fired host Craig Silverman during his broadcast Saturday after he criticized Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick holds his own workout, and NFL calls him a no-show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/sports/former-nfl-quarterback-colin-kaepernick-doing-workout-least-11-teams-n1084171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaepernick's former teammate, Eric Reid, expressed concern that the NFL arranged the workout primarily for publicity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 teams watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28095462/colin-kaepernick-throws-passes-40-minutes-workout-urges-nfl-stop-running</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick completed his workout for what his agent said were eight NFL teams at an Atlanta-area high school on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  MAYOR PETE POPS TO 9-POINT LEAD IN IOWA... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/16/politics/iowa-poll-cnn-pete-buttigieg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a new Democratic front-runner in Iowa, and his name is Pete Buttigieg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDSOR WILD!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/16/prince-andrew-says-he-couldnt-sweat-in-attempt-to-debunk-epstein-accusers-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive BBC interview, Prince Andrew delivered a tense, sometimes bizarre denial of ever bedding his pal Jeffrey Epstein’s sex slaves — claiming his royal disdain for hugging, and his body’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN TEAM TRUMP FLIP LA?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ecad2990a83b4d84af821ba6cbdb7d91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — In a race that has become a nail-biter, Louisiana Gov. John Bel Edwards battled Saturday to defy the partisan odds in the ruby red South and win reelection to a seat that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Shooting Leaves 5 Dead, Including 3 Children... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/Multiple-People-Injured-in-Shooting-in-Paradise-Hills-SDPD-565039022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people are injured in a shooting that occurred in Paradise Hills, said San Diego Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate in UK elections poses in S&amp;M leather and whip for TV ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10359922/uk-general-election-canterbury-liberal-democrat-candidate-claire-malcomson-sm-gear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAST minute candidate for the Lib Dems in a marginal seat has previously featured in an S&amp;M-style television ad, complete with a whip, suspenders and stockings. Claire Malcomson was parachute…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARLIE'S ANGELS' Crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/16/box-office-kristen-stewart-updated-charlies-angels-a-total-loss-with-3-1-mil-friday-including-thursday-previews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bosley must be turning in his grave. Columbia Pictures’ latest installment of “Charlie’s Angels” is a total write off at the box office. Last night the Kristen Stewart versi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a CIA analyst triggered an impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-a-cia-analyst-alarmed-by-trumps-shadow-foreign-policy-triggered-an-impeachment-inquiry/ar-BBWRhvT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of 5G weapons system on streets... after conspiracist takes apart light...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/fears-5g-weapons-system-uk-20893384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conspiracist deconstructed a light he claims a council worker whistleblower sent him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Progress in Audit Undercut by Worsening Shortfalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/pentagon-progress-in-new-audit-undercut-by-worsening-shortfalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon Progress in New Audit Undercut by Worsening Shortfalls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Protesters March to Revive Flagging Anti-Maduro Revolt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-protesters-march-revive-flagging-170505718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Supporters of Juan Guaido protested in Caracas in their first major showing in months as Venezuela’s opposition leader seeks to revive his campaign to oust President Nicolas Maduro.A week after Maduro’s ally Evo Morales was toppled in Bolivia, Guaido is seeking to boost thinning crowds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'FORD V FERRARI' Speeds to No. 1...'</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/charlies-angels-bombs-at-box-office-reasons-why-1202787938/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Terminator: Dark Fate’s failure at the B.O., and Paramount’s recent decision to make Beverly Cops 4 for Netflix, we have the further breakdown of cinema IP in Sony’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters head to polls in critical Louisiana gubernatorial race...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191009103328-6x21o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/LOUISIANA (PIX):Louisiana's Democratic governor fights for re-election in Republican-leaning state</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
