<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'I will be working with authorities to take legal action'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/06/22/justin-bieber-accused-of-rape-by-two-women-on-social-media-denies-and-refutes-i-will-be-working-with-twitter-and-authorities-to-take-legal-action</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two young women — going only by first names Danielle and Kadi– over the weekend accused Justin Bieber of rape. They say the assaults took place respectively in 2014 and 2015. In each ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT SHREDS... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/lincoln-project-mocks-trumps-size-in-new-ad-the-rally-theyre-talking-about-rally-size-probably/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest Lincoln Project ad is full of double entendres about size, mocking the president for low turnout at his rally in Tulsa on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN MANAGER FACING CHOP?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/21/politics/jared-kushner-ivanka-trump-brad-parscale/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump and Jared Kushner are "pissed" at campaign manager Brad Parscale over his predictions of a much larger crowd than the one that turned out at the Tulsa rally Saturday night, according to a Trump campaign source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber denies sex assault allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1018107/justin-bieber-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-receipts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUSTIN Bieber has broken his silence to deny an allegation of sexual assault made against him. The singer, 26, took to Twitter to post a lengthy thread, vehemently refuting claims by an anonymous w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Dems' confidence comes with fear... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-and-Democrats-confidence-comes-with-fear-15355742.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's campaign and his Democratic Party are feeling an emotion they have not sensed in quite some time, and one that prompts more than a little fear: confidence.  Poll after poll has placed the presumptive Democratic nominee ahead of President Donald Trump, with comfortable national leads that in some cases have swollen to double digits. He is ahead by narrower but consistent margins in battleground states, and Biden himself has grown increasingly bullish on the idea that Democrats will win back the Senate majority, a possibility not even dreamed of until recently. Once an anemic fundraiser, he is now routinely drawing multimillion-dollar hauls.  Trump is presiding over a Depression-style economy, a global pandemic and boiling social unrest. His administration has lost several high-profile Supreme Court cases, his former National Security adviser's new book has painted a damning portrait, and he is now in perhaps the weakest position of his presidency with less than five months before the general election. The images of a half-empty arena for Trump's much-hyped rally in Tulsa, Okla., on Saturday underscored the perception of a diminished incumbent, one who has long seen crowd size as a barometer of success.  But for Democrats, the very idea that they are doing well provokes an underlying skittishness. They worry about voting during the coronavirus crisis, amid restrictions that could make it harder to cast ballots. Some fear a coming misinformation campaign and say the party risks underestimating Trump's ability to turn the country against their nominee.  They also worry their party still does not fully understand what led voters to Trump in the first place, and they are terrified that overconfidence, like some of them had four years ago, will lead to complacency.  "It feels like 2016 all over," said Andrew...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane flies Confederate flag over NASCAR race...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/racing/nascar/story/_/id/29344050/nascar-sees-confederate-flags-fly-talladega-superspeedway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR sees Confederate flags fly outside and above the track as the top circuit hits Talladega Superspeedway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How virus tore through Latin America's largest market...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-coronavirus-tore-through-Latin-America-s-15355707.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - Martín Mateo had a cold. Or so he thought: sore throat, body aches, runny nose. "He felt bad but kept working," said his son, Carlos. The 50-year-old father had labored for decades as a tomatero - a tomato man - at Latin America's biggest food market.  Coronavirus? He didn't believe in it.  Then Mateo started gasping for breath. Within days, he was dead.  By then, scores of his fellow tomateros also were infected. Workers hoisted yellow signs outside the market reading "High Contagion Zone." At least 10 tomato men died from mid-April to mid-May. They included Mateo's cousin Antonio, a bookkeeper at a neighboring stall named Guillermo, and a bald man everyone called El Peluche - loosely, "Fuzzy."  The tomato aisle at Mexico City's famed Central de Abasto market offers a glimpse into why the virus has hit the country so hard. It scythed its way through the sprawling complex, picking off workers made vulnerable by poverty-related problems: chronic illnesses, distrust of government, a need to keep earning money.  While there is no official data, vendors can name dozens of people in the vegetable aisles alone who lost their lives - green-bean sellers, chili vendors, potato men - in one of the most brutal outbreaks in the city.  "Here we didn't believe" the coronavirus was a threat, said 57-year-old Anastasio Ramón Alonso, a longtime tomato vendor. "But when people began to die and die and die, we lost our incredulity."  Officials have reported more than 20,000 coronavirus deaths in Mexico, undoubtedly an undercount. The virus appears to have entered the country with the upper class - people returning from business trips in Italy and skiing holidays in Colorado. But it spread quickly to low-income workers, who have been hit particularly hard.  As in the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arena less than third full at campaign kickoff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/503781-tulsa-fire-department-says-trump-rally-attendance-was-about-6200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer than 6,200 people attended President Trump's campaign rally at the BOK Center in Tulsa, Oklahoma, on Saturday night, well below the arena's capacity of roughly 19,000, according to the Tulsa Fire Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star Dimitrov ill after playing in event... </title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/dimitrov-tests-positive-coronavirus-playing-djokovic-event-183427844--ten.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grigor Dimitrov said on Sunday he has tested positive for coronavirus after pulling out of an exhibition tournament which also featured world number one Novak Djokovic. &amp;quot;I want to reach out and let my fans and friends know that I tested positive back in Monaco for Covid-19,&amp;quot; world number 19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no flights, Argentine sails across Atlantic to see parents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-flights-argentine-sails-across-atlantic-see-parents-215309502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar del Plata (Argentina) (AFP) - "Mission accomplished!" That joyful declaration came from Juan Manuel Ballestero, an Argentine sailor who, unable to fly home from Portugal due to the pandemic, crossed the ocean alone in his modest sailboat to see his aging parents. After testing negative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER:  Secret pact between Trump and Zuckerberg?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/whats-facebooks-deal-with-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Nov. 20, NBC News broke the news that Mark Zuckerberg, Donald Trump and a Facebook board member, Peter Thiel,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights vulnerabilities heading into election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49b32796b5a9ab1884624d3173cf6283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump's return to the campaign trail was designed to show strength and enthusiasm heading into the critical final months before an election that will decide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims he told officials to slow coronavirus testing to keep case numbers low..</title>
      <link>http://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-says-he-told-officials-to-slow-coronavirus-15355554.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid surging coronavirus infections nationwide, President Donald Trump said at his campaign rally in Tulsa Saturday night that he told officials to administer fewer coronavirus tests to keep case numbers down.  The comments drew a chorus of criticism from congressional Democrats, who said it validated fears that the president was more focused on saving face amid the pandemic than on protecting public health. A White House official told The Washington Post that Trump was joking, a common defense from Trump's aides when he says something controversial.  Eight states on Saturday reported their highest single-day case counts since the pandemic began, and daily new infections nationwide exceeded 30,000 on both Friday and Saturday. The country has not seen daily totals that high in more than seven weeks.  One of the country's leading public health experts said Sunday that he was worried that Trump's rally in Tulsa could become a "super-spreader" event resulting in many people being infected with the coronavirus.  "We have seen in the past few months around the world that indoor gatherings have been the source of most super-spreading events," Tom Inglesby, director of the Center for Health Security at Johns Hopkins University, told Fox News, responding to a question about possible contagion at the rally. "There's an opportunity for much more spread in a short period of time, so I am worried about that."  Attendance was reported to be significantly lower than expected, but Inglesby said the rally was still "concerning in terms of public health risks."  He noted that attendees were packed close together, shouting and shaking hands, and that many were not wearing masks. "All of those things will increase the risk of spread," he said.  Host Chris Wallace asked whether there was "some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debacle in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Analysis-What-empty-seats-in-Tulsa-tell-us-about-15355871.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. - The omens started early Saturday morning, before the gates to the "Great American Comeback" rally were opened. I got downtown later than I'd wanted to, making a detour to buy a poncho, after weather forecasts suggested a chance of rain. Shortly after 9 a.m., I started looking for parking, and two Tulsans who were charging $30 for a space politely said I might want to drive around before paying.  "I thought we'd be full by now," one of the sellers said, "based on the news."  One minute later, I found free street parking and began walking to the BOK Center. Eight hours later, President Donald Trump's campaign was dramatically downscaling its first rally since March, striking a stage at an overflow section as a few dozen supporters mingled in a space designed for thousands. The rain never came. Neither did the expected audience.  Saturday's rally in Tulsa was, on the campaign's own terms, a debacle - a meticulously organized and well-protected event that left thousands of seats unfilled in an arena once sold out by Nickelback. The president himself had predicted a "record-setting crowd," tweeting as the number of online ticket requests surged to Coachella proportions - 300,000, 600,000, 1 million.  "We've never had an empty seat, and we certainly won't in Oklahoma," Trump had said.  That hubris overshadowed what might have been landmark event, the first campaign rally of any kind since March and the start of the coronavirus pandemic. The audience was still larger than any Joe Biden had drawn before securing the Democratic nomination. And the hours of programming clarified how Trump would run against Biden - a message that partly relied on massive rallies.  "Would anybody sleep on the ground overnight waiting to see Joe Biden?" asked Lara Trump, a presidential daughter-in-law and key campaign surrogate, as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Tightens Controls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/australia-fears-second-wave-as-state-tightens-virus-controls/ar-BB15NSUA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elgort says relationship 'brief, legal and entirely consensual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-8443923/Ansel-Elgort-denies-claims-sexually-assaulted-17-year-old-girl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ansel Elgort denied sexually assaulting a 17-year-old girl in 2014 in a message shared Saturday on Instagram. He said the two had a bad breakup and the relationship was 'legal and consensual.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theodore Roosevelt Statue to Be Removed From Museum of Natural History...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/roosevelt-statue-to-be-removed-from-natural-history-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of former President Theodore Roosevelt that has stood in front of the American Museum of Natural History in Manhattan for 80 years will be removed amid ongoing protests for racial justice, officials said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on Roberts ahead of Supreme Court's abortion ruling... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/503645-all-eyes-on-roberts-ahead-of-supreme-courts-abortion-ruling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts is under the microscope as the Supreme Court prepares to issue its first major ruling on abortion rights in the Trump era, which will give the clearest indication yet of the court’s willingness to revisit protections tha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' Star Accused of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/06/21/ansel-elgort-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-through-instagram-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I cannot claim to understand Gabby’s feelings but her description of events is simply not what happened,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Largest News Website Sees Its Independence in Danger...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/hungarys-main-online-news-says-195524743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary’s leading online news site said Sunday that its editorial staff and independence are at risk because of a reorganization attempt that could compromise its journalistic integrity. Index.hu moved its “ independence barometer,” set up in 2018 after an ownership change, to “in danger” from “independent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FURIOUS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/trump-furious-underwhelming-crowd-tulsa-rally-n1231674</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This was a major failure," one outside adviser said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin hints he could seek FIFTH term as president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-hints-he-could-seek-a-fifth-term-as-president-in-2024/ar-BB15N5vg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to Week of Warning Signs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-tulsa-rally-adds-to-week-of-warning-signs-for-campaign/ar-BB15MD9J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeaching Attorney General 'a waste of time,' top judiciary Dem says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/impeaching-barr-e2-80-98a-waste-of-time-e2-80-99-judiciary-democrat-says/ar-BB15NhL8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parscale threatens to block reporters from future rallies... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-campaign-chief-goes-after-media-coverage-of-low-rally-turnout-suggests-they-may-revoke-credentials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's re-election campaign manager, Brad Parscale, threatened to block reporters from the president's future rallies following coverage on the lower turnout they saw in Tulsa on Sat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There Will Be Recriminations'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/axios-jonathan-swan-there-will-be-recriminations-for-half-empty-trump-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axios White House reporter Jonathan Swan said "there will be recriminations" for the dramatically underwhelming rally President Donald Trump held in Tulsa, Oklahoma Saturday night. Earlier i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany struggles to enforce isolation rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621171158-qic2t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-MEAT (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Germany struggles to impose local coronavirus infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans regret lack of emergency savings during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/americans-regret-lack-of-emergency-savings-during-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adults in the United States are feeling economic pressure due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans some US chicken, shuts Pepsi plant to fight virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beijing-reports-22-virus-cases-millions-tested-055718774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China banned imports from a top US poultry producer and ordered a Beijing Pepsi factory to close Sunday as authorites clamped down on food production and distribution amid a new coronavirus cluster in the capital. Health officials also reported 22 new virus cases in Beijing, where they have tested more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd wave of virus cases? Experts say we're still in 1st...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f401d034122b820a89773432cbf51152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's all this talk about a “second wave” of U.S. coronavirus cases?  In The Wall Street Journal last week, Vice President Mike Pence wrote in a piece headlined “There Isn’t a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirated editions appear online...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d58c06b5dc22674bba6d43d4589421bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — John Bolton's memoir officially comes out Tuesday after surviving a security review and a legal challenge from the Justice Department. But over the weekend, it was available in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian DL Hughley tests positive after fainting onstage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cab1aa39b785468afb0eb19a42bdc3ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Comedian D.L. Hughley announced he tested positive for COVID-19 after collapsing onstage during a performance in Nashville, Tennessee.  The stand-up comedian,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New concerns in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/894beaff53b7e7a30b7de989d960a198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — Will Boyd was at the funeral Saturday morning for a relative who had died after contracting the new coronavirus when he got the call with the news. His brother had also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain declares deadly stabbing spree 'terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/18844d7216c6a25b4e85779806f31a56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;READING, England (AP) — A stabbing rampage that killed three people as they sat in a British park on a summer evening is being considered a terrorist attack, police said Sunday. A 25-year-old man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Former pope Benedict to return to Vatican on Monday...</title>
      <link>http://www.naharnet.com/stories/en/272724</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naharnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former pope Benedict XVI will return to the Vatican on Monday from Germany, where he is visiting his sick brother, the Regensburg bishopric said.  "Return trip is planned for Monday," said the bishopric in the Bavarian city on its website,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 workers in forced quarantine at L.A. hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/150-cannery-workers-are-in-forced-quarantine-at-l-a-hotel-without-pay-suit-claims/ar-BB15Lahe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA LESS MEGA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/trump-s-tulsa-rally-fizzles-as-seats-go-empty/ar-BB15LsJW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Kung Flu' Remark Stirs Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/donald-trump-tulsa-rally-social-media-stunned-president-coronvirus-kung-flu-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's first rally since the start of the coronavirus pandemic in the U.S. was a rundown [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' solar eclipse thrills skywatchers on longest day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ring-fire-solar-eclipse-thrills-skywatchers-longest-day-104709979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers along a narrow band from west Africa to the Arabian Peninsula, India and the Far East witnessed a dramatic "ring of fire" solar eclipse Sunday. Without the coronavirus pandemic, they would have organised a trip to Lake Magadi in southern Kenya where the skies are generally clearer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros conspiracy theories surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f01f3c405985f4e3477e4e4ac27986e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say he hires protesters and rents buses to transport them. Some say he has people stash piles of bricks to be hurled into glass storefronts or at police.  George Soros, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature hits 100 F degrees in Arctic Russian town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/temperature-hits-100-degrees-arctic-russian-town-71370623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Siberian town with the world’s widest temperature range has recorded a new high amid a heat wave that is contributing to severe forest fires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists unearth Galilee Christian town sacked by Persians in 7th century...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/archaeologists-unearth-galilee-christian-town-sacked-by-persians-in-7th-century/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remains of affluent, rural community discovered at Pi Mazuva in 2007 include crosses, pagan-inspired mosaic; new publication illuminates the Christians who lived there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK teens, K-Pop fans take credit...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/TikTok-Teens-and-K-Pop-Stans-Say-They-Sunk-Trump-15355108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign promised huge crowds at his rally in Tulsa, Oklahoma, on Saturday, but it failed to deliver. Hundreds of teenage TikTok users and K-pop fans say they're at least partially responsible.  Brad Parscale, the chairman of Trump's re-election campaign, posted on Twitter on Monday that the campaign had fielded more than 1 million ticket requests, but reporters at the event noted the attendance was lower than expected. The campaign also canceled planned events outside the rally for an overflow crowd that did not materialize.  Tim Murtaugh, the Trump campaign's spokesman, said protesters stopped supporters from entering the rally, held at the BOK Center, which has a 19,000-seat capacity. Reporters present said there were few protests.  TikTok users and fans of Korean pop music groups claimed to have registered potentially hundreds of thousands of tickets for Trump's rally as a prank. After @TeamTrump tweeted asking supporters to register for free tickets using their phones June 11, K-pop fan accounts began sharing the information with followers, encouraging them to register for the rally - and then not show.  The trend quickly spread on TikTok, where videos with millions of views instructed viewers to do the same, as CNN reported Tuesday. "Oh no. I signed up for a Trump rally, and I can't go," one woman joked, along with a fake cough, in a TikTok posted June 15.  Thousands of other users posted similar tweets and videos to TikTok that racked up millions of views. Representatives for TikTok did not immediately respond to requests for comment.  "It spread mostly through Alt TikTok - we kept it on the quiet side where people do pranks and a lot of activism," said YouTuber Elijah Daniel, 26, who participated in the campaign....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Attacks Rise As Extremists Target Protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/06/21/880963592/vehicle-attacks-rise-as-extremists-target-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty people are facing prosecution amid reports of more than 50 vehicle-ramming incidents at protests since late May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden parents fear losing kids if don't send to school...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/coronavirus-sweden-compels-parents-send-kids-to-school-2020-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents say schools or local government have said they may contact social services if the children continue to stay home from school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany riot: Gangs smash shops, attack police...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53126464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A night of mayhem leaves shops smashed up and looted in the industrial south German city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbing rampage in UK park terror attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11916773/reading-attack-terror-cops-confirm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPS have confirmed the Reading bloodbath which left three men dead and three others injured was a terror attack. The 25-year-old Libyan knifeman suspect is still in custody, as police declared the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Warns of Possible Second Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-warns-of-possible-second-coronavirus-lockdown/ar-BB15My6D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was secretive US 'ninja' missile used again in Syria?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/was-the-us-secretive-ninja-missile-used-again-in-syria-saturday-632232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media posts sought to link the strike to a series of other US attacks on al-Qaeda affiliates in northern Syria in which US drones have used such a weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' solar eclipse thrills skywatchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2020/06/21/world/science-health-world/ring-of-fire-solar-eclipse-africa-asia/#.Xu9FdmhKjb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers along a narrow band from west Africa to the Arabian Peninsula, India and the Far East witnessed Sunday a dramatic "ring of fire" solar eclipse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 dead;  25-year-old Libyan knifeman detained...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/uk-stabbing-attack-that-left-3-dead-being-treated-as-terror-incident-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stabbing rampage in a British park that left three people dead is now being treated as a terrorist attack, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic rebounds 90% as commuters avoid public transit...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/traffic-increased-to-pre-pandemic-levels-inrix-report-2020-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have warned that as cities reopen, traffic and congestion could continue to increase past pre-coronavirus levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Kurt Cobain guitar sells for record $6 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/kurt-cobains-mtv-unplugged-guitar-sells-for-staggering-recordsetting-amount-at-auction-002108604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 1959 Martin D-18E acoustic is now the most expensive guitar ever sold, beating the previous record of $3.975 million for a Black Stratocaster owned by Pink Floyd's David Gilmour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake shakes Oklahoma after rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jun/21/earthquake-shakes-oklahoma-after-donald-trump-rall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook northern Oklahoma on Saturday and was felt in parts of Tulsa as protesters filled the city’s downtown streets after President Donald Trump’s campaign rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports 30,000 daily cases, highest number since May 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/20/us-reports-his-number-of-daily-coronavirus-cases-since-may-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S reported more than 30,000 new coronavirus cases on Friday, the highest number of daily infections recorded since May 1, according to data compiled by the Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper films brother beating white MACY'S employee; Says he heard n-word...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/man-who-filmed-macys-beatdown-of-white-man-says-attack-was-instinct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flint police launched an investigation after the video was posted on social media and said they are looking for Quay and his brother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood poised for big-screen gamble as theaters reopen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-poised-big-screen-gamble-theaters-reopen-074415398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than three months of coronavirus-mandated limbo, Hollywood is headed back to the big screen -- and hoping that Russell Crowe's road rage thriller "Unhinged" will jump-start the recovery. Christopher Nolan's much-hyped "Tenet" will follow soon after. While top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 11 wounded in Minneapolis shooting, police say... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/21/us/minneapolis-shooting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man was killed and 11 others were injured in an overnight shooting in Minneapolis, police said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
