<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>First unionized presidential campaign in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/campaigns/bernie-2020-becomes-first-unionized-presidential-campaign-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders ratified a collective bargaining agreement for his presidential campaign last week, the first presidential campaign in history to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignore International Grand Committee on 'Fake News' Request...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mark-zuckerberg-faces-subpoena-in-canada-over-fake-news-on-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO reportedly didn't respond to requests to appear before an international committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark, Sheryl face Canadian Parliament subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebooks-mark-zuckerberg-sheryl-sandberg-face-subpoena-from-canadian-parliament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook brass have ignored repeated requests to appear before a committee of officials from 10 nations, according to a Canadian Member of Parliament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liz Cheney accuses Dems of helping Putin undermine democracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/gop-rep-liz-cheney-accuses-democrats-of-helping-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WY) lashed out at congressional Democrats Wednesday, accusing them of "undermining our democracy and helping Vladimir Putin."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World-famous chef interrogated at LAX over duffel full of piranhas...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/food/la-fo-virgilio-martinez-central-piranhas-lax-peru-20190508-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgilio Martinez of Central in Peru successfully brought 40 frozen piranhas through LAX to cook two dinners as part of Food Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare event to bring secretive BLUE ORIGIN out of shadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/08/tech/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-rocket-company/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos may be ready to bring Blue Origin, his secretive space company, out of the shadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk v Bezos: Military rocket rivalry may reshape national security...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1603659/elon-musk-and-jeff-bezos-wrangle-over-us-military-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force has been terrible at buying rockets. The current contract battle could shape American national security— and the future of private space companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University sprinter impaled by javelin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dawgnation.com/track/details-emerge-after-uga-sprinter-accidentally-pierced-by-javelin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dawgnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS -- Whenever someone hears the words "pierced" and "javelin," they're left to expect the worst. But a UGA track and field athlete who recently suffered that fate apparently is going to be OK. Elija Godwin, a freshmen sprinter for the Bulldogs' men's team, was seriously injured when he fell into a javelin during</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy DONKEYS Calm Students Ahead Of Finals...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/these-animals-work-miracles-therapy-donkeys-calm-college-students-ahead-final-exams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add therapy donkeys to the list of options for college students who want to lower stress levels ahead of final exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetically engineered virus prolongs life...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/05/08/phage-therapy-how-genetically-engineered-viruses-may-have-prolonged-teens-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While phage experts were excited by the work, clinicians wonder to what extent it can be scaled up to combat the global crisis of antibiotic resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUBS investigating fan's alleged racist hand gesture...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sports/cubs/ct-spt-cubs-doug-glanville-racist-gesture-wrigley-field-20190508-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cubs are investigating an on-air incident involving a racist gesture behind NBC Sports Chicago reporter Doug Glanville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Clone Phone Number In Elaborate YELP Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/elaborate-scheme-yelp-imposters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local police said this is an elaborate scheme they’ve never dealt with before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Producer accused of sex misconduct was fired because he's a man...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/08/news-producer-accused-of-sex-misconduct-was-fired-because-hes-a-man-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former employee at a Connecticut TV station is suing the ABC affiliate’s parent company, claiming he was singled out because he’s a man after three female colleagues accused him of sexual miscond…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA to revise sex ed guidance for teachers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6b4018eaebb49bf8ddc63aee0074182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California is close to overhauling its guidance for teaching sex education in public schools, offering teachers a framework for talking to kindergartners about gender...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore passes 'fake news' law despite fierce criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190508-singapore-passes-fake-news-law-despite-fierce-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore passes 'fake news' law despite fierce criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  NFL Network slashed; $20M cuts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/08/nfl-network-shows-slashed-tensions-rise-after-20m-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL Network is being forced to cut $20 million out of its projected budget and, in the process, already has eliminated at least five shows, including one that featured Deion Sanders, The Post h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: High Schooler Who Sued Over Chickenpox Vaccine -- Gets Chickenpox!</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/student-who-sued-over-chickenpox-policy-comes-down-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high school senior who went to court after he was barred from playing basketball because he wasn’t vaccinated against chickenpox has come down with the illness, his lawyer said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY lawmakers jump into fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/116f602be4e34de2b73a35fe7ac02cb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York's Democrat-controlled Senate approved a bill easily Wednesday that would allow three congressional committees to get access to President Donald Trump's state tax...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Drama: Campaign Reset, Advisers Clashing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/08/us/politics/kamala-harris-2020-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months since 20,000 people gathered to kick off her candidacy, Ms. Harris has found herself in a vise, squeezed by factions in her party and her own campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Pans Mayor Pete: 'Boring,' Low Energy...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/nbcs-craig-melvin-calls-mayor-pete-kind-of-boring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melvin said on Wednesday that he doesn't predict South Bend mayor Pete Buttigieg's candidacy will go very far, calling him "kind of boring."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team claims unfamiliar position: Front-runner...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1a7612014544fe99a97fe57d2f04896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump spent his first campaign as an underdog, written off by the political establishment and down on his own chances on Election Night. But as he and his team...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: 850 open investigations into domestic terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/70168e7cf4d5481c8a38589bbfb40483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI has more than 850 open investigations into domestic terrorism across the country, and the threat continues to grow, top counterterrorism officials said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Miami Man Accused Of Threatening To 'Explode Jewish Community'...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/miami-man-accused-of-threatening-to-explode-the-jewish-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Miami man was arrested after Miami Beach police said he threatened to "explode the Jewish community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans goes through grisly castration to 'become a nullo'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9019798/nullo-removes-penis-testicles-knife-washington-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN IT worker has revealed how he hacked off his own penis and testicles with an ultra-sharp knife in a gruesome bid to become a genitalia-free “nullo.” Trent Gates, 23, from Washington DC, cut off …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China backtracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-backtracking-exclusiv/exclusive-china-backtracked-on-almost-all-aspects-of-u-s-trade-deal-sources-idUSKCN1SE0WJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diplomatic cable from Beijing arrived in Washington late on Friday night, wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders shores up superdels...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442617-sanders-shores-up-dem-superdelegate-support</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a year after Donald Trump beat Hillary Clinton, a group of about 20 Democratic National Committee (DNC) members met on the sidelines of the committee’s meeting in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says rocket drill was in self-defense...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190508131901-o61wq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-North Korea says recent rocket drill was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE WARNS:  Iran sending terrorists to Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/nicolas-maduro-providing-a-safe-haven-for-iranian-terrorists-in-the-west-mike-pence-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan strongman Nicolás Maduro is partnering with Iran to establish a beachhead for terrorist groups in the Western Hemisphere, Vice President Mike Pence warned Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions rescued from world's worst zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9025288/lions-rescue-dirty-animals-zoo-safari/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAUMATISED lions have finally escaped their filthy and cramped conditions at the world’s worst zoo. Horrifying photographs of animals living in cramped concrete cages sparked a major rescue operat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Schultz on Pause?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/howard-schultz-has-largely-stopped-his-2020-presidential-prep-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back surgery has sidelined the former Starbucks CEO. But even his social-media presence is virtually gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE OVER MUELLER</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/justice-department-set-ask-executive-privilege-mueller-report-n1003146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department told lawmakers Tuesday ahead of the panel's session that it would recommend that President Donald Trump assert executive privilege to the material the attorney general has declined to provide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>700 ROCKETS, 4 DEAD ISRAELIS: IS THE IRON DOME GETTING WORSE?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/700-rockets-4-dead-Israelis-Is-the-Iron-Dome-getting-worse-589115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of unintercepted rockets and Israeli fatalities sparked inquiry about the effectiveness of Iron Dome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS HOLD BARR IN CONTEMPT</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7006385/House-Judiciary-Committee-votes-hold-Bill-Barr-CONTEMPT-Congress.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump claimed executive privilege over the full, unredacted version of Robert Mueller's report as House Democrats voted to find Attorney General Bill Barr in contempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  JAIL WOULD BE OVERCROWDED</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-pelosi-if-we-were-arresting-all-people-admin-we-would-have-o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We would have overcrowded jail situation, and I’m not for that’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universities nationwide remove historical artwork deemed offensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/trending-universities-nationwide-remove-historical-artwork-deemed-offensive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Censorship on university campuses targets historic figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dems woo rural voters, some say why bother...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/As-Democrats-woo-rural-voters-some-say-why-bother-13828044.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa - J.D. Scholten has gotten phone calls from former Rep. Beto O'Rourke. He's campaigned with Sen. Cory Booker. He held a town hall with entrepreneur Andrew Yang and toured an ethanol plant with Sen. Amy Klobuchar.  The presidential candidates are eager to meet with Scholten, hoping he holds the key to a secret that increasingly bedevils Democrats: how to win rural voters, who seem to be firmly in President Trump's camp. Scholten, a former minor-league baseball star, challenged GOP Rep. Steve King in Iowa last year, driving around in a beat-up motor home. He lost, but just barely, in a heavily conservative rural area.  Scholten tells Democrats the party is too focused on upscale urban voters. "We're becoming the Whole Foods party, when we need to figure out how to win in Dollar General districts like mine," Scholten said. "You don't have to win, but you should be able to compete."  That difficult message comes as Democrats face an increasingly clear crossroads: Do they spend time and resources pursuing rural voters, who are often socially and culturally at odds with the party's increasingly liberal direction? Or do they double down on cities and suburbs, hoping to drive up support among the multiethnic, younger, more highly educated voters that many see as the party's future?  For Democrats still traumatized by Trump's victory, it's a vexing question. Democratic nominee Hillary Clinton struggled on both counts: She suffered from lackluster turnout in the cities but also lost rural voters to Trump by a 3-to-1 margin.  Democrats like former Iowa governor Tom Vilsack say the party can't simply cede small-town voters again. "If we are losing rural counties as we have in the past . . . I don't give a damn how much you run up the vote in the inner cities and in the suburbs, we'll be right back where we were in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Training Brigade Prepares for New Worldwide Deployments...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/121cb682fedc43aea980b63cb4770f15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Just months after the Army's new training brigade returned from Afghanistan, its teams are preparing for a different type of deployment that will scatter them around the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-water cure? Weekend with the 'Ice Man'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/08/wim-hof-cold-water-immersion-cure-ice-man-outdoor-swimming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wim Hof claims cold-water immersion can help fight modern diseases. As outdoor swimming becomes ever more popular in the UK, photojournalist Jonny Weeks joined him for a weekend to experience it firsthand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole lotta rock: LED ZEPPELIN doc announced...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/may/08/first-official-led-zeppelin-documentary-bernard-macmahon-director-american-epic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernard MacMahon, director of roots music series American Epic, will helm film exploring band’s explosive early years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET ON EDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/08/trump-says-chinas-vice-premier-is-coming-to-the-us-to-make-a-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump said Chinese negotiators "just informed" the White House they are "coming to the U.S. to make a deal" on trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC-area radio station told to register as Russian agent...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/dc-area-radio-station-told-register-russian-agent-62897558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The radio station broadcasts Sputnik International 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida man arrested, refused to remove obscene sticker from vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.wptv.com/news/state/florida-man-arrested-after-refusing-to-remove-obscene-sticker-from-window</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sheriff's office says a deputy pulled Webb over in Lake City because of a sticker that crudely described his sexual appetites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Royal Baby Makes First Public Appearence...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9026078/meghan-markle-prince-harry-royal-baby-sussex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry have today beamed as they introduced their “amazing” baby boy to the world – but teased the world by not revealing his name. The new parents appeare…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Person Mired In Boredom 131 Days A Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-fun-americans-mired-boredom-131-days-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling bored all too often lately? It seems that many of us might need to get out a bit more and inject some fun into their lives. A survey of 2,000 Americans finds that for the average adult, more than a third of their year is spent mired in boredom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Stern Reveals Cancer Scare, Trump Regrets and Details of New Book...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/howard-stern-reveals-cancer-scare-trump-regrets-details-a-dishy-new-book-1208773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a health crisis that had him "scared  s—less," the $90 million-a-year radio legend opens up about retirement, the one time he lied to his listeners and his metamorphosis from shock jock to insightful interviewer: "I'd feel really f—ing s—ty if I hadn't evolved."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania school drops 'God bless America' after pledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/pennsylvania-school-drops-god-bless-america-after-pledge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania school principal will no longer say "God bless America" after leading students in the Pledge of Allegiance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waters' moment in power: Confronting Trump, inspiring Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12ddaca673d24c05b508932ebd5761b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — She's been called "Kerosene Maxine" and gaveled off the House floor for accusing Republican men of badgering women. She dismissed President Donald Trump and his allies as thugs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER drivers protest around world ahead of IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/08/uber-drivers-strike-over-low-wages-benefits-ahead-of-ipo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers are also expected to stage protests against Uber and Lyft in at least eight cities around the U.S., including New York, Chicago and San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly One in Two Americans Takes Prescription Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2019/05/08/nearly-one-in-two-americans-takes-prescription-drugs-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly One in Two Americans Takes Prescription Drugs: Survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax the Rich and More: 2020 Dems Plan New Levies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-08/tax-the-rich-and-more-a-guide-to-potential-democratic-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure builds for FTC to punish Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/442618-pressure-builds-for-ftc-to-punish-zuckerberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure is growing for federal regulators to hold Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg personally accountable for his company’s string of privacy scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC faces new debate minefield...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442622-dnc-faces-new-debate-minefield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC) is in a tough spot with just 50 days to go before the first presidential primary debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Make Money? Work for Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/want-make-money-work-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Photo by Mark Wilson/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1% of Guatemala, Honduras entered USA since September...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/shock-over-1-of-guatemala-honduras-entered-us-since-september</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a shocking demonstration of the latest surge of illegal immigrants border officials are struggling with, over 1% of the populations of Guatemala and Honduras have entered the United States since September, according to the Homeland Security Department chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO SEX, PLEASE: DIGITAL LIFE TO BLAME FOR LACK OF LOVEMAKING?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/07/britain-sex-decline-study-married-cohabiting-couples-digital-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research finds drop in sexual activity steepest for married and cohabiting couples</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Death sells water to tech bros too cool for alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegazette.com/subject/news/nation-and-world/liquid-death-sells-water-to-tech-bros-who-are-too-cool-for-alcohol-20190507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 12-pack of Liquid Death 16.9-ounce tallboys is $21.99 on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  SALT LAKE TRIBUNE seeks to become nonprofit 'community asset'... </title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/05/08/salt-lake-tribune-seeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of heavy financial losses, The Salt Lake Tribune is pursuing federal approval to become a nonprofit operation sustained by donations large and small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  FOXNEWS, CNN DEAD HEAT; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLE NEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Robots to Work Construction...</title>
      <link>https://www.roboticsbusinessreview.com/construction/more-than-7000-robots-will-work-in-construction-by-2025-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roboticsbusinessreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worldwide market for construction robotics to reach $226M over six years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen says helped Falwell handle racy photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-falwell-exclusive/exclusive-trump-fixer-cohen-says-he-helped-falwell-handle-racy-photos-idUSKCN1SD2JG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months before evangelical leader Jerry Falwell Jr.’s game-changing presidential ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly mosques receiving threats after video shows children reciting violent poems, songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/muslim-american-society-video-children-philadelphia-20190507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philadelphia branch of the Council on American-Islamic Relations issued an advisory to all Islamic institutions to increase security precautions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET'S MAKE A DEAL:  Trade war cloud over 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trade-war-a-cloud-over-Trump-s-2020-prospects-13827237.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's aggressive trade policies are running headlong into his campaign for reelection.  As Trump prepares to run on the economy, his threat to increase tariffs on imports from China has sent the stock market diving and served to undercut a stretch of positive economic news. U.S. farmers and exporters, already bearing the brunt of China's retaliatory tariffs, now face the prospect of an escalated trade war in which key states that Trump needs to win reelection will be in the crosshairs.  The trade war has also exposed a rift inside the White House and among the president's allies - with some officials pushing for a quick resolution to calm the markets ahead of 2020, and others warning the president that a weak deal with China could leave him politically vulnerable.  "My warning has been, we don't want the 2020 election year to become greatly intensified friction with China over trade issues. We want a deal that works," said Michael Pillsbury, a China expert at the Hudson Institute who has advised the Trump administration on trade. "One way to unite all 21 Democratic primary candidates is if the president gets a quick but flawed deal that inevitably leads to friction when China is caught cheating next year."  However, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin and National Economic Council Director Larry Kudlow are among a group of Trump aides who have encouraged the president to quickly reach a deal with China and avoid political blowback from a full-scale trade war in 2020, according to people familiar with the internal debate.  White House officials said Trump is prepared to take a hard line with China going into 2020 in part because he intends to keep his 2016 campaign promise to fix what he views as bad trade deals. Trump believes strongly in the power of tariffs to force China and other countries to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheila Nevins Sets Next Act: Launching MTV Documentary Films...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/sheila-nevins-sets-next-act-launching-mtv-documentary-films-1207990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former HBO exec, who departed the premium cable network in 2018 after a 38-year run, will develop new projects for third-party outlets and the Viacom-owned cabler via the MTV Studios division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET ON EDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/07/trade-war-fears-are-crushing-stocks-and-sell-off-could-keep-going-if-there-is-no-deal-by-friday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An all-out trade war between the U.S. and China could bite into global growth, squeeze profit margins and drive down stock prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD Officers Catch MRSA After Contact With Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/lapd-mrsa-infection-reseda-west-valley-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Gordon of the L.A. Police Protective League confirmed to CBSLA that it was a homeless transient who came into contact with officers at the station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Computer System Crippled By Ransomware Virus; Residents Not Able To Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/baltimore-city-government-computer-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore City Hall government servers have been infected by a ransomware virus that government officials said is spreading throughout their network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT GETS TRUMP TAX DOCS</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/decade-in-the-red-trump-tax-figures-show-more-than-1-billion-in-business-losses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time his master-of-the-universe memoir “Trump: The Art of the Deal” hit bookstores in 1987, Donald Trump was already in deep financial distress, losing tens of millions of dollars on troubled business deals, according to previously unrevealed figures from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  After Round of Buyouts, CNN Staffers Brace for Layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/round-buyouts-cnn-staffers-are-worried-whats-next-1208356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody is bracing for a reorganization," a senior producer at the network said. "There are all kinds of rumors about impending layoffs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS Internal 'Chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-news-chief-susan-zirinsky-swapping-star-anchors-we-had-shake-things-up-1208317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the network's key shows suffer ratings declines, division president Susan  Zirinsky bets on Gayle King and switches Jeff Glor for Norah O'Donnell and a move to the nation's capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo warns of 'imminent' threat on surprise trip to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190508-usa-pompeo-warns-imminent-iran-threat-surprise-trip-iraq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq has promised to guarantee the safety of US interests from Iran, US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said Tuesday as he paid a surprise trip to Baghdad where he accused Tehran of planning "imminent" attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of killing infant son after losing video game...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2019/05/05/louisville-police-dad-hit-baby-head-after-losing-video-game/1112386001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Trice, 26, is accused of striking his 1-month-old son in the head after losing a video game Friday evening. He's now charged with murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mexico's President threatens critical journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/05/07/mexican-president-to-media-you-know-what-will-happen-for-bad-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the largest and most respected international press freedom organizations called out a series of statements made by Mexico’s President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG LOSSES</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-taxes/trump-tax-returns-from-1985-to-1994-show-1-billion-in-losses-ny-times-idUSKCN1SD2R4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's businesses lost a total of more than $1 billi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Catalan leader running for office via SKYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Fugitive-Catalan-leader-wanted-for-rebellion-is-13825574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - Carles Puigdemont once tried to lead Catalonia to independence from Spain. Now his dominion is a house in the suburbs of Brussels.  He fled charges of rebellion after his fall 2017 attempt to split his prosperous province from the rest of the country. And he is adapting to an odd new life where he can travel just about anywhere he wants - except the rolling hills of his native land.  Puigdemont on Monday scored a rare victory against the Spanish state, winning the right to run for European Parliament on May 26 after an election board initially barred the way. The case rose all the way to Spain's Supreme Court.  As long as he seeks to avoid arrest by Spanish police, it will have to be a campaign by Skype and Facetime. He will dial in to rallies in Catalonia from the pink brick building in Waterloo that he and his supporters have dubbed "the House of the Republic."  Meanwhile, some of his rivals and former compatriots will be running from behind bars in Spain, where they are on trial for rebellion, disobedience and misuse of public funds.  Puigdemont defends his self-imposed exile as strategic.  "We decided to live here in order to continue fighting," Puigdemont said in an interview. "If all of us were in jail, the narrative, the version of the Catalan crisis could be very different."  He said it was just a coincidence that his new home and headquarters is located in Waterloo, the site of Napoleon's final defeat. (He cheerfully notes that Napoleon's defeat was the Duke of Wellington's triumph.)  The Waterloo house "is a part of Catalonia," Puigdemont said, looking more tired than he did when he stirred crowds in Barcelona and across his region during the ill-fated independence attempt.  The walls are covered with Catalan art. The shelves are filled with books in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Privilege?  White House instructs McGahn not to comply with congressional subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/white-house-instruct-counsel-comply-congressional-subpoena/story?id=62873987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jerry Nadler sounding off after former White House counsel Donald McGahn was told not to comply with House Democrats' subpoena for Mueller probe documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT GETS TRUMP TAX DOCS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/5-takeaways-from-10-years-of-trump-tax-figures/ar-AAB2BDR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy Hospital Ship Deployed to Aid Refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/05/07/navy-hospital-ship-comfort-deploy-aid-venezuelan-refugees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy hospital ship Comfort will deploy next month to the Caribbean and Central and South America to provide assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Burglar enters home, pets pup, washes dishes...</title>
      <link>https://klewtv.com/news/offbeat/deputies-say-ohio-burglary-suspect-pet-victims-dog-washed-dishes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;klewtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vinton County Sheriff's Office said a woman is facing a burglary charge after she entered a home, pet the victim's dog and washed the dishes. Cheyenne Ewing is charged with burglary, according to the sheriff's office. Deputies said they received a call about a burglary about 9 a. m. Monday in Hamden. The victim said the suspect entered the home and sat on the couch to pet the family dog. The victim said the suspect then washed the dishes and left the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Censors Musical Short -- About Chinese Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/culture-desk/cbs-censors-the-good-fight-for-a-musical-short-about-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The segment is clear about one of the motives for American self-censorship: China is too big of a market for media corporations to ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive backlash against Seattle woman raped by homeless man...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/seattle-elites-homeless-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle elites show little sympathy for a woman raped by a homeless man.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
