<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Naked Florida woman trashes restaurant before being 'Tasered in breasts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3037915/naked-woman-trashes-restaurant-tasered-cops-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NAKED woman destroyed a restaurant in Florida during a rampage before she was Tasered “in her breasts” by police, footage shows. Tina Kindred, 53, was acting “out of control” as staff…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven sharks circle beachgoers on rubber raft in Pensacola...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3033156/hammerhead-sharks-swarm-pensacola-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment when a group of hammerhead sharks swarmed shallow water alongside beachgoers. Jacqueline Lesso was on a boat while three other women floated on a raft when they all spot…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oops!... She Did It Again:  Britney's bizarre posts ramp up ahead of conservatorship hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3036583/britney-spears-shocks-fans-calls-herself-motherfing-snake-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears shocked fans as the star called herself a “motherf***ing snake” in a bizarre rant. The 39-year-old wore a snakeskin bodysuit in the new Instagram post, which was shared o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sets world record by giving birth to -- 10 babies!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/woman-sets-world-record-giving-24274044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother in South Africa has smashed the record the number of babies born from a single pregnancy as she gave birth to seven boys and three girls - and they were all conceived naturally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS:  Russia's space chief threatens to leave ISS program unless U.S. lifts sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/russia-threatens-to-leave-international-space-station-program.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ISS is the largest hub for scientific research and collaboration in orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu meets fate on Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-government-confidence-vote-bennett-lapid-e8e69d30-866a-4cfa-ba86-608727164a66.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's security chief is warning of Jan. 6-style violence if Netanyahu is ousted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Sent Her iPhone to APPLE. Repair Techs Uploaded Her Nudes to FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbkey/she-sent-her-iphone-to-apple-repair-techs-uploaded-her-nudes-to-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple paid a woman millions to prevent a lawsuit, but it could have avoided all of this if she’d just been able to repair her own phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES asking employees to volunteer to help with summer rush...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/557297-american-airlines-employees-asking-to-volunteer-to-handle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines is asking its employees to volunteer at Dallas Fort Worth International Airport to help handle the travel surge occurring this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Record 70% Support Same-Sex Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/350486/record-high-support-same-sex-marriage.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. support for legal same-sex marriage continues to grow, now at 70% -- a new high in Gallup's trend dating to 1996.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WEB OUTAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-7c607c931faba19584975da74c8fa633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Dozens of websites briefly went offline around the globe Tuesday, including CNN, The New York Times and Britain's government home page, after an outage at the cloud service Fastly, illustrating how vital a small number of behind-the-scenes companies have become to running the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As grocery prices rise, alternative meat takes bigger bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-grocery-prices-rise-alt-meat-takes-a-bigger-bite-of-big-meat-e2-80-99s-burger/ar-AAKPkhx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plant-based proteins surge in grocery sales during the pandemic, with their prices falling rapidly as companies grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have trouble sleeping? You're at higher risk of dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-06/nu-hts060421.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first-known study to examine the effect of the combination of insomnia and diabetes on mortality risk, participants who had both diabetes and frequent sleep disturbances were 87% more likely to die in following 9 years than those who did not have diabetes or frequent sleep difficulties. The study asked one simple question, which the study authors said clinicians and patients should be asking themselves to help address underlying causes of sleep disturbances sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superrich Bought Up Idaho Town. Now Regular Folks May Live in Tents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/superrich-bought-idaho-town-regular-085413034.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photo Courtesy Brad WomackAffordable housing in Ketchum—the Idaho resort community adjacent to billionaire and celebrity playground Sun Valley—has been a problem for decades.But the situation is becoming so dire in the wake of COVID-19 that city officials are considering an unusual range of quick fixes—including building tent cities and RV parks for the common folk in the ultra-rich mountain town, where the average median home listing price is hovering abo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapped in face!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210608115832-97p4v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-POLITICS/MACRON (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-France's Macron slapped in face during walkabout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man admits on FACEBOOK Live to killing partner, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-0f9fe058acc911c1c517a83c1d6ea222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIVERVIEW, Fla. (AP) — A man who announced on social media that he had killed his boyfriend and called on deputies to shoot him as well finally set his condo on fire and turned a gun on himself, a Florida sheriff said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women filmed twerking on top of cop car in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9662689/Three-women-filmed-twerking-police-car-Chicago-similar-incidents-Seattle-St-Louis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police is investigating a viral video showing women dancing and twerking on top of a CPD cruiser.. This cell phone video has gone viral on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUGATTI reveals most powerful car on planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/cars/article-9661077/Ten-things-need-know-Bugattis-new-3-3m-Chiron-Super-Sport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The limited-edition road car is based on the £2.5million 'standard' Chiron but offers increased performance, improved aerodynamics and a svelte, missile-like body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/disclosetv/status/1402248572217794571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble in LA County: Too Many Peacocks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/08/trouble-in-los-angeles-county-too-many-peacocks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;County officials in Los Angeles have a request: Please don’t feed the peacocks. In that slice of Southern California, peafowl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapped in face by man in crowd...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/two-arrested-french-president-macron-124910679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were arrested after French President Emmanuel Macron was slapped by a man during a walkabout session with a crowd in the Drome region in southeastern France, BFM TV and RMC radio reported on Tuesday. BFM TV and RMC published a video clip, circulating on Twitter, which shows a man in a green T-Shirt, with glasses and a face mask shout out "Down with Macronia" ("A Bas La Macronie") and then deliver a slap to Macron's face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As DeSantis takes aim at cruise industry, Republicans step up attacks on longtime allies in corporate America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-desantis-takes-aim-at-cruise-industry-republicans-step-up-attacks-on-longtime-allies-in-corporate-america/ar-AAKOXVE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise ship companies announce varying vaccine rules as they face stiff political pressure in the South.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uyghurs deported from Muslim countries; Concerns about China's growing reach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/08/middleeast/uyghur-arab-muslim-china-disappearances-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After reports of Uyghur disappearances in some major Arab countries, such as the United Arab Emirates, Saudi Arabia and Egypt, some of China's ethnic Muslims fear they are no longer safe in parts of the Islamic world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE new 'private relay' feature will not be available in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607224521-1toz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE-PRIVACY/ (URGENT):Apple's new 'private relay' feature will not be available in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed city of Arabs and Jews remains on edge after violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-violence-voting-rights-09c80818b76620ec0b4d801a478df2f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOD, Israel (AP) — Israeli security forces guard the streets of Lod, weeks after rioters torched patrol cars, synagogues and homes. Attackers who killed an Arab and a Jewish resident are still at large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wandering elephants becoming international stars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-wandering-elephants-becoming-international-stars-05a39c9aac67013d4e7187285f55ea3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Already famous at home, China’s wandering elephants are now becoming international stars. Major global media are chronicling the herd's more than yearlong, 500-kilometer (300-mile) trek from their home in a wildlife reserve in mountainous southwest Yunnan province to the outskirts of the provincial capital of Kunming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOGUL AND THE MONSTER: INSIDE EPSTEIN'S DECADES-LONG RELATIONSHIP WITH BIGGEST CLIENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/inside-jeffrey-epsteins-decades-long-relationship-with-his-biggest-client</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the many mysteries that still surround the life and crimes of the notorious financier, the source of his wealth, and thus his power, might be the greatest. His long-standing business ties with his most prominent client, billionaire retail magnate Leslie Wexner, hold the key.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Olympic Official Dead as Tokyo 2020 Curse Strikes Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/yasushi-moriya-dies-after-jumping-in-front-of-train-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local reports say the man, who is believed to have worked in Japan Olympic Committee’s accounting department, took his own life Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report highlights severe intelligence failures on Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/557253-new-report-highlights-severe-intelligence-failures-on-jan-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate investigators have outlined a spectacular series of intelligence and communication failures leading up to the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Paid $0?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-paid-0-in-federal-income-tax-in-2018-report-1847051810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk, the second richest person in the world, paid precisely $0 in federal income tax in 2018, according to an explosive new report from ProPublica. And Musk isn’t the only one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder plots thwarted...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-57394831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds are arrested worldwide after using the ANOM app, where their messages were monitored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline chiefs urge end to UK-US travel restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airline-bosses-call-uk-us-lift-trans-atlantic-travel-restrictions-2021-06-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heads of all passenger airlines flying between Britain and the United States called on Monday for both countries to lift trans-Atlantic travel restrictions put in place to fight the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY:  Canada prepares to ease quarantine rules for vaccinated travelers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210608014958-mwxv0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CANADA-QUARANTINE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Canada prepares to ease quarantine rules for vaccinated travelers - Bloomberg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC watching memes for 'disruptions of market, manipulative trading'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-amc-entertainment-stock-surges-20-sec-says-its-watching-memes-for-disruptions-of-the-market-manipulative-trading-or-other-misconduct-11623088027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission warns that it is closely monitoring moves in the market, amid the surge in values of meme stocks AMC...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third wave sweeps across Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/07/third-wave-sweeps-across-africa-as-covid-vaccine-imports-dry-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO says continent urgently needs more jabs as eight countries report rise of 30% in cases in a week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  France fines GOOGLE for abusing online dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/07/france-fines-google-for-abusing-online-advertising-dominance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giant will pay £189m after settlement found it unfairly favoured its own tools for buying and selling ads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British tourists rush back from Portugal to escape quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/tourists-returning-portugal-hours-spare-24269750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists who only just escaped having to quarantine upon their return from Portugal said the UK's decision four days ago to put the southern European country on the amber list is "disgraceful"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald eagle kills 54 lambs on Idaho farm!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bald-eagle-kills-54-lambs-on-idaho-farm-owner-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Idaho farmer kept finding his sheep dead with puncture wounds and thought someone may have been shooting them. But then he caught the real culprit in the act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Black Middle School Students Ordered To Pick Cotton...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/06/06/washington-middle-school-students-told-to-pick-cotton-clean.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Spokane, Wash., mother is calling for the removal of a school official after the racially offensive assignment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  USATODAY Slammed Over 'Bogus Advertisement'  For NETFLIX On Front Page...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/streaming/news/sweet-tooth-newspaper-ad-stunt-sparks-divisive-reaction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA Today came under fire on social media this weekend for an advertisement that, at first glance, [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International police reveal 'most sophisticated' organized crime sting!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/raids-worldwide-police-reveal-vast-234028107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International law enforcement agencies on Tuesday revealed a vast three-year global operation to infiltrate an encryption platform popular among criminal groups, resulting in hundreds of arrests worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL BRACES FOR ANOTHER ROUND...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-braces-third-wave-covid-014042141.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already reeling from one of the highest death tolls in the pandemic, Brazil is bracing for the threat of a third wave of Covid-19, fueled by vaccination delays and a lack of containment measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden agenda under threat --- from within his party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-agenda-under-threat-within-214124473.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's policies always faced high hurdles with Republicans, but one Democratic senator balking at the US president's voting rights bill has signalled that the bulk of the ambitious White House agenda is under threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONAIRE RISKING HIS OWN LIFE FOR GLORY!</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/jeff-bezos-join-winner-seat-blue-origin-space-flight-2021-06-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's billionaire founder Jeff Bezos said on Monday he and his brother Mark will fly on the first crewed space flight from his rocket company Blue Origin next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON about to share your internet connection with neighbors!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/amazon-is-about-to-share-your-internet-connection-with-neighbors-here-s-how-to-turn-it-off/ar-AAKMK3y?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have no control over what sort of data flows over Amazon’s new Sidewalk wireless network, which has been lying dormant in Echo smart speakers and Ring cameras... until now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS:  I'M GOING!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/tech/jeff-bezos-space-blue-origin-new-shepard-flight-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds recover crypto paid to pipeline hackers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/colonial-pipeline-ransomware-recovered/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US investigators have recovered millions in cryptocurrency they say was paid in ransom to hackers whose attack prompted the shutdown of the key East Coast pipeline last month, the Justice Department announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Guatemala, Kamala tells would-be migrants to USA, 'You will be turned back'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/her-foreign-debut-vice-president-135142965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris speaks after meeting on migration with Guatemalan president on her first foreign trip as vice president. She is in Mexico on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS READY FOR HISTORIC ROCKET RIDE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-9ac5c4668d9ff8d209889ca089572571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Outdoing his fellow billionaires in daredevilry, Jeff Bezos will blast into space next month when his Blue Origin company makes its first flight with a crew. The 57-year-old Amazon founder and richest person in the world by Forbes' estimate will become the first person to ride his own rocket to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden DOJ Will Keep Defending Trump in Jean Carroll Rape Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-doj-will-keep-defending-trump-on-rape-defamation-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump used the Justice Department to defend him in a defamation case that accuses him of rape, and the Biden administration will continue defending him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MINISTER OF CHAOS:  Boris Johnson knows exactly what he's doing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/07/boris-johnson-minister-of-chaos/619010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson knows exactly what he’s doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gates's Epic Divorce Saga Enters Next Phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/bill-and-melinda-gates-divorce-saga-next-phase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blowup of a billionaire duo’s 27-year marriage was always going to be rife with drama. Now come the private investigators, rumors of affairs, and former employees chafing at NDAs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDIO:  Phone call reveals how Giuliani pressured Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/rudy-giuliani-ukraine-call-investigate-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-before-heard audio, obtained exclusively by CNN, shows how former President Donald Trump's longtime adviser Rudy Giuliani relentlessly pressured and coaxed the Ukrainian government in 2019 to investigate baseless conspiracies about then-candidate Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX turned down Gaetz for a job...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607194243-43225</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/GAETZ (PIX):Newsmax turned down embattled Republican Matt Gaetz for a job -spokesperson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy chief cites risk of cyberattacks crippling power grid...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/energy-chief-cites-risk-cyberattacks-crippling-power-grid-78117554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm is urging more public-private cooperation on cyber defenses, and she says U.S. adversaries already are capable of using cyber intrusions to shut down the power grid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How am I losing to a mental retard?'</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/trumps-deranged-theory-might-have-helped-him-lose-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president was obsessed with the idea that Democrats would strip the primary win from Joe Biden and nominate Hillary Clinton or Michelle Obama instead, reporter Michael Bender writes in an upcoming book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Gets First Pizza Vending Machine. Will Romans Bite?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/07/rome-gets-its-first-pizza-vending-machine-will-romans-bite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME — Romans eat pizza all the time. They have pizza a taglio, cut with scissors to the desired size</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full volume: White House briefing room back to crammed again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-voting-rights-government-and-politics-08fc7329fe679b5c52bf47f49338d353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House briefing room on Monday might have been a fire marshal's nightmare. For the first time in 449 days, reporters could cram into every seat for the daily briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want To Have Sex With A Celeb? Sign An NDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/hallielieberman/celebrity-gossip-sex-scandal-ndas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I thought [the NDA] was really creepy. If he's asking for that, like how much more weird could it get?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Mom and Hornet's Nest...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/amy-chua-jed-rubenfeld-yale-law.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two decades, Amy Chua and Jed Rubenfeld were Yale Law power brokers. A new generation wants to see them exiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality TV news could be casualty of streaming wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/op-ed-quality-tv-news-could-be-a-casualty-of-the-streaming-wars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Rogers, the first president of NBC Cable, lays out the quandary for the TV news business in light of cord-cutting and increased competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK warns of inflation 'time bomb'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/deutsche-bank-warns-of-global-time-bomb-coming-due-to-rising-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation may look like it will go away but is more likely to persist and lead to a crisis in the years ahead, according to Deutsche Bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone refuels fighter jet in midair for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/boeing-drone-refuels-us-navy-fighter-jet-midair-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy F/A-18 Super Hornet and an unmanned aircraft were connected by a hose as the drone transferred jet fuel to the aircraft in the skies over the Midwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to Be Covered by Global Tax Deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-international/amazon-set-to-be-covered-by-global-tax-deal-despite-thin-margins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global policy makers are crafting their international tax plan to make sure Amazon.com Inc. is included, even though the U.S. company’s profit margin is below the 10% proposed threshold that would give other countries rights to collect revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big win for Merkel's party confounds pundits, pollsters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/the-strategic-vote-in-saxony-anhalt-big-win-for-merkel-cdu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor’s CDU romped home in state of Saxony-Anhalt despite polls suggesting close race with far right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Turning Water-Scarcity Crisis into Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/06/china-is-turning-its-water-scarcity-crisis-into-a-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antagonizing neighbors, imposing top-down solutions, and not actually solving the underlying problem — as China in other areas, so with water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise line reverses course on requiring jabs for passengers...</title>
      <link>https://local12.com/news/coronavirus/one-cruise-line-has-already-reversed-course-on-requiring-vaccinations-for-passengers-royal-caribbean-ron-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;local12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (CNN/CNN Newsource/WKRC) - The cruise industry is getting ready to set sail once again but a political storm brewing on land &amp;ndash; one between Florida Governor Ron DeSantis and the Centers for Disease Control &amp;ndash; suggests it will be anything but smooth sailing. Right now, most cruise lines are advertising new summer sailings with vaccination requirements. But Royal Caribbean abruptly changed course on Friday. Only its ships departing from Seattle and the Bahamas on or before Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian neo-Nazis plotted to bomb NATO base...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/italian-neo-nazis-were-plotting-to-bomb-nato-base-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carabinieri raided the homes of 12 alleged members of an extremist group on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Steps up Efforts to Sow Discord Inside USA...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6071615/iran-disinformation-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian state actors are intensifying their disinformation campaign on social media to spread discord and anti-Semitic tropes inside the U.S., two U.S. intelligence officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed in park hours before announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-stabbed-in-central-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed on the east side of Central Park late Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY MASK WARS MAY NEVER END...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-the-mask-culture-wars-may-never-end-163722944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks have been divisive from the start, and even though the pandemic appears to be nearing its end in much of the United States, mask-related divisions remain as wide as ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT REOPENING SHOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/new-york-city-pplans-a-central-park-mega-concert-to-celebrate-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lineup hasn't been announced for the Aug. 21 event, but producer Clive Davis, who has worked with numerous big names, says he's aiming for eight "iconic" stars for the event, which will be televised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned Parenthood loses lawsuit over Texas 'Sanctuary City for the Unborn'...</title>
      <link>https://thetexan.news/planned-parenthood-lawsuit-against-lubbock-abortion-ban-dismissed-by-u-s-district-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thetexan.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Plaintiffs admit that this Court cannot force the city to revoke or amend its ordinance," Judge Hendrix wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious video...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/07/suspicious-floyd-mayweather-logan-paul-video-emerges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exhibition boxing match between Logan Paul and Floyd Mayweather on Sunday night was a farce for many reasons – but a video clip from the fight suggests it may have gone as far as to be fixed. W…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
