<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA developing most powerful laser weapon to blast missiles from sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4007773/us-laser-weapon-missiles-chinas-nuke-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US is developing its most powerful laser weapon yet capable of blasting missiles and drones out of the sky following China’s “round the world” nuke test. Boeing and General At…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Alone Boosts Risk Of Heart Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-alone-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older women eating alone had lower intakes of energy, carbohydrates, dietary fiber, sodium, and potassium in comparison to those eating with others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson accusers detail alleged abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2021-11-05/marilyn-manson-esme-bianco-sexual-abuse-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court records reviewed by The Times and nearly two dozen interviews portray Manson as a transgressive artist who mistreated and isolated women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria bans unjabbed from cafes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211105-austria-bans-those-unvaccinated-against-covid-19-from-caf%C3%A9s-amid-surge-in-new-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria said on Friday it is barring those not fully vaccinated against Covid-19 from cafes, restaurants and hairdressers as infections approach the record set a year ago and the government struggles…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camels escape circus, wander Madrid streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59186294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight camels and a llama were found, with managers blaming their escape on animal rights activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New coronavirus, likely from dogs, infects people...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2021/11/05/1052961177/new-coronavirus-likely-from-dogs-infects-people-in-malaysia-and-haiti</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could turn out to be the 8th coronavirus known to spread humans. Some scientists think doctors and researchers should start actively looking for this virus in patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX REBELLION</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-ripped-for-bonkers-anti-vax-interview-citing-joe-rogan-and-mlk-touting-ivermectin-and-suggesting-the-vaccines-cause-sterility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodgers is just the latest athlete railing against the vaccines, and he was roundly criticized for using his platform this irresponsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi strategy at risk of collapsing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/05/politics/house-votes-infrastructure-build-back-better/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's plan to pass a $1.9 trillion economic package and a $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill, two pillars of President Biden's agenda, is at risk of collapsing as leaders struggle to unify the progressive and moderate wings of the party, a dynamic that has consumed Democrats for the past several months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Axes Estevez From 'MIGHTY DUCKS' Over Vax Status...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/emilio-estevez-leaving-the-mighty-ducks-game-changers-season-2-gordon-bombay-covid-vaccine-mandate-1234868978/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Mighty Ducks franchise will continue without Gordon Bombay. Emilio Estevez, who reprised his role from the 1992 movie and its 1994 and 1996 sequels in Season 1 of The Mighty Ducks: G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR denounces 'Let's go, Brandon' conservative rally cry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-sports-business-united-states-f9bb6c6cb77a78f1302f4f08640cc973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AVONDALE, Ariz. (AP) — NASCAR denounced its association with the “Let's go, Brandon” political cry being used across the country as an insult directed at President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Multiple' bomb threats at YALE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/05/yale-university-bomb-threats-forces-student-evacuations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police evacuated students at Yale University after several bomb threats were called in around campus Friday, police said. Eight buildings were evacuated out of an abundance of caution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Sex-Crime Charge May Be 'Defective,' DA Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/05/cuomo-sex-crime-charge-may-be-defective-d-a-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sex-crime case against former Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo was thrown into doubt on Friday after the Albany County district</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin's Underage Son Tried to Vote in VA Election, Officials Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/glenn-youngkins-underage-son-tried-to-vote-in-virginia-governors-election-officials-say/2870695/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 17-year-old son of Virginia Governor-elect Glenn Youngkin twice tried to cast a ballot on Election Day even though he is not yet eligible to vote, election officials confirm to News4. He was unsuccessful in his attempt to vote. News4 is not naming Youngkin’s son because he is a minor and has not been charged with a crime. Fairfax County…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Woke Meet Their Match -- Parents...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/the-woke-meet-their-match-parents-d7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenn Youngkin's mix of populist policy and moderate style is a breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulted With Joe Rogan For Medical Advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/aaron-rodgers-said-he-consulted-with-joe-rogan-for-medical-advice/ar-AAQn2xv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Packers quarterback Aaron Rodgers made headlines earlier this week when he tested positive for COVID-19. On Friday afternoon, he appeared on “The Pat McAfee Show” to share his side to the story. Rodgers revealed that he’s unvaccinated because he’s allergic to an ingredient in the mRNA vaccines. “I have an allergy to an ingredient that […] The post Aaron Rodgers Said He Consulted With Joe Rogan For Medical Advice appeared first on The Spun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Draft Women Advancing in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/policy/2021/11/plan-draft-women-uniting-unlikely-political-allies/186667/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-war activists and conservative hawks both want women to stay out of the Selective Service System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOY BORN WITH TAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9997843/The-boy-born-TAIL-Brazilian-baby-gets-12cm-long-appendage-chopped-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian baby born with a rare 12cm-long tail, ending in a 4cm ball, has had it surgically removed. The tail is a rare example of true human tail being left from one the baby grew one inside the womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Bill Gives Special Tax Handout to Media Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/dem-bill-gives-special-tax-handout-media-companies-1500-local-journalists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAKE ACTION: Reject Democrats Reckless Tax-and-Spend Bill &amp;#13;&amp;#13;The reconciliation bill working its way through the U.S. House calls on the American taxpayer to subsidize Democrats' media allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan to pay $300K to only staffer fired over Flint water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-environment-michigan-flint-d52c97713e59647ccce70f754ef3a114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The state of Michigan said Friday it agreed pay $300,000 to settle wrongful discharge claims by the only employee who was fired as a result of lead-contaminated water in Flint. The deal with Liane Shekter Smith, who was head of the state’s drinking water division, came weeks after an arbitrator said she was wrongly fired in 2016 by officials who were likely looking for a “public scapegoat” in one of the worst environmental disasters in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARCLAYS subpoenaed over connections to Jeffrey Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/barclays-subpoenaed-over-jeffrey-epstein-connections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of the subpoenas came days after Barclays announced its CEO, Jes Staley, would quit following an investigation into his relationship with Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Religious Exemptions Granted in Air Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/zero-religious-exemptions-granted-covid-vaccines-air-force-deadline-passes/186601/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 5,000 religious exemptions are still pending approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT:  Schools will start requiring vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/05/1051902361/covid-vaccine-schools-history-comic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first vaccine required for school was for smallpox, over 200 years ago. And for decades, all states have required that kids be vaccinated against contagious diseases like polio to attend school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Hollywood is shunning sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/culture/article/20211029-why-hollywood-is-shunning-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While society becomes more sexually open, there are fewer sex scenes in mainstream cinema than ever. Has film really entered a newly Puritan age, asks Christina Newland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers Addresses Vax Fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/11/05/aaron-rodgers-vaccination-status-woke-mob-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers has broken his silence on his vaccination status. He hit back at his critics during an interview with Pat McAfee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 armed men storm beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4006786/cancun-resort-shooting-four-americans-hurt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR Americans were hurt in an attack at a hotel in Cancun that left two dead on Thursday evening. The carnage sent tourists scrambling for cover after 15 drug gang gunmen rocked up in ski masks an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA convenes ANOTHER grand jury in Trump Org case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/manhattan-da-convenes-new-grand-jury-in-trump-org-case-to-weigh-potential-charges/ar-AAQklta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grand jury, which will meet for six months, could consider how Trump’s company valued its assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  TIKTOK influencer Runs Lesbian BDSM Cult, Accusers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/daddys-girls-lesbian-black-bdsm-tiktok-cult-1252122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Vandusen loved big, beautiful Black women, and she gained a following who would call themselves Daddy’s Girls. Then, some former adherents say, she told them to hurt themselves to prov…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone can choose their own avatar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/what-will-the-world-look-like-when-everyone-can-choose-their-own-avatar-in-the-metaverse/ar-AAQlWVv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For all the skepticism Mark Zuckerberg's discussion of the metaverse last week, many Internet visionaries see it as a potential grand result whose benefits and drawbacks should not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Johnson Opens Up About Health 30 Years After HIV Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/magic-johnson-30-years-hiv-diagnosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been 30 years since basketball legend Magic Johnson stunned the world when he announced he had HIV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet MIAMI HERALD's Newest Writer: A Robot!</title>
      <link>https://www.miaminewtimes.com/news/miami-herald-robot-writes-real-estate-stories-13219683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miaminewtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Miami Herald writer has been pumping out bylines like a machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>82.5% of deer tested in Iowa positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/iowa-study-82-5-of-deer-tested-positive-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When researchers in Iowa first began testing deer for COVID-19 in April of 2020, they didn’t find any signs of the virus for months. That changed in the fall when the first positives popped up in September and October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules jurors in trial for Arbery's killing can see license plate with Confederate emblem...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/judge-rules-jurors-in-trial-for-ahmaud-arbery-e2-80-99s-killing-can-see-license-plate-with-confederate-emblem/ar-AAQmxAj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opening arguments began Friday after nearly three weeks of jury selection in a case that went 74 days without charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crypto Coachella' Takes Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/05/the-metaverse-takes-manhattan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The masters of the metaverse — thousands of CryptoPunks and Bored Apes, artists and hackers, starry-eyed idealists and profit-hungry speculators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 In 6 Have Never Traveled Outside Own State...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/traveling-children-adults-culture-empathy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent survey, more than half (55%) believe expanding their horizons when they were young is what motivated them to travel as an adult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Russian Spy's Son Dead After 'Fall' From Embassy in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/another-russian-diplomat-dead-fall-122209363.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fabrizio Bensch via ReutersEither Russians are incredibly clumsy or they should stay away from open upper-floor windows.Another Russian—this time a diplomat in Berlin—was found in a heap on the sidewalk below the Russian embassy last month, dead after an apparent fall, Der Spiegel reports.The 35-year-old man, named by Bellingcat as the son of the deputy director of FSB’s Second Service and the head of the FSB’s Directorate for Protection of Constitutional Order, Gen. Alexey Zhalo, was reportedly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleeing gangs, multiple crises, Haitian migrants turning to Puerto Rico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/fleeing-gangs-multiple-crises-haitian-migrants-are-increasingly-turning-to-puerto-rico/ar-AAQjpq5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The precarious 300-mile voyage on the high seas left from an unusual spot, Haiti’s northern coast. For three days, the 11 men and six women, gripped by fear, huddled together aboard the tiny wooden sloop. With no idea of their final destination, they looked for signs of life but only saw sea and sky, losing hope with every sunset. “They tell you in two hours you’re going to arrive, in three ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FDA Commissioner Proclaims New PFIZER Drug 'End of Pandemic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dr-scott-gottlieb-proclaims-new-pfizer-covid-drug-marks-the-end-of-the-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could the Covid-19 pandemic be coming to an end? In the eyes of one prominent expert, the answer is yes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AEW is WWE's first real fight in decades. It may change face of pro wrestling...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/AEW-is-WWE-s-first-real-fight-in-decades-It-may-16594906.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUEENS, N.Y. -- On a Wednesday night in New York City, wrestler Bryan Danielson has a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIEGEL: Diplomat found dead outside Berlin embassy was Russian secret agent...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/diplomat-found-dead-outside-berlin-embassy-was-russian-secret-agent-der-spiegel-2021-11-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German security services believe that a man found dead in a street outside the Russian embassy in Berlin last month was an undercover agent of Russia's FSB intelligence service, Der Spiegel reported on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUT 100,450,000 NOT WORKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/100450000-more-100-million-not-labor-force-14th-straight-month-no-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the 14th straight month that this "not in the labor force" number has remained above 100,000,000. And labor force participation remained struck at 61.6 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS CLIMB TO NEW RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/04/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move for stocks came as job gains for the month of October came in at 531,000, better than expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEAN UP YOUR MESS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-science-united-nations-scotland-pollution-1cfed640e2eb057a0f4c427a55d2e478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLASGOW, Scotland (AP) — The generation of young people who will inherit a warmer future is telling the generation that caused carbon pollution to clean up its mess — from both inside and outside United Nations climate talks .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma jail officers played 'Baby Shark' on repeat as 'torture tactic,' suit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/oklahoma-jail-officers-played-e2-80-98baby-shark-e2-80-99-on-repeat-as-a-e2-80-98torture-tactic-e2-80-99-federal-lawsuit-says/ar-AAQm4yW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detainees were forced to listen to "Baby Shark" on repeat for hours as they stood in an empty room, handcuffed to the wall, a new federal lawsuit claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas man 'envisioned future' with' stripper. Then, he killed her, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-texas-man-e2-80-98envisioned-a-future-e2-80-99-with-a-stripper-then-he-killed-her-police-say/ar-AAQm2Cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abigail Saldaña posted a video on her Instagram before her murder in which she claimed to have found a tracking device on her car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO HOAX: KROGER says press release announcing acceptance of bitcoin FAKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kroger-says-press-release-announcing-acceptance-bitcoin-cash-is-fake-2021-11-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for Kroger Co said on Friday a press release saying the grocer would accept "bitcoin cash" this holiday season is fraudulent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Drug Decriminalization May Spread, Despite Unclear Results...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/11/03/oregons-drug-decriminalization-may-spread-despite-unclear-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some critics argue Oregon’s law will decrease access to treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job creation roars back in October as payrolls rise by 531,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/jobs-report-november-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase by 450,000 in October, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems scramble for path forward after election setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/580182-democrats-scramble-for-path-forward-after-election-setbacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic lawmakers are scrambling for a path forward after Tuesday’s disappointing election results in Virginia, New Jersey and New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Virginia, Republicans amplify debate over race and education...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-elections-education-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-fc8501fa2b0ef655933f4cce27bf4c9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Republicans plan to forcefully oppose race and diversity curricula — tapping into a surge of parental frustration about public schools — as a core piece of their strategy in the 2022 midterm elections, a coordinated effort to supercharge a message that mobilized right-leaning voters in Virginia this week and which Democrats dismiss as race-baiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's big bill on brink of House votes, but fights remain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-immigration-joe-biden-business-health-da0c5847fe7f3a846ca076c214bb0c79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats in the House appear on the verge of advancing President Joe Biden’s $1.85 trillion-and-growing domestic policy package  alongside a companion $1 trillion infrastructure bill in what would be a dramatic political accomplishment — if they can push it to passage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHMIDT: FACEBOOK WENT TOO FAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/facebook-knew-what-it-was-doing-former-google-ceo-eric-schmidt-says-2599898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's conduct revealed in leaked documents is "pretty concerning," said former Google Chief Executive Officer Eric Schmidt, who called for companies in the tech industry to show more restraint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene linked to doubling risk of death found...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211105112321-qenut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GENE-STUDY (URGENT):Gene linked to doubling risk of COVID-19 death found by UK scientists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm Season Latest Supply Chain Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/latest-threat-supply-chain-nightmares-100000521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Storm season is coming to the shores of Southern California, and that could make global supply-chain bottlenecks even worse.Most Read from BloombergChina’s Climate Goals Hinge on a $440 Billion Nuclear BuildoutResults on Key Ballot Initiatives, From Policing to the EnvironmentSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’‘Airbnb Queen’ Says She’s Caught Up in Platform’s New York FeudClose to 160 vess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towns Offering $200 An Hour To Plow Snow...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/04/snow-plow-driver-shortage-hourly-rates-massachusetts-worcester-lowell-watertown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a shortage of plow drivers in some towns across Massachusetts, and some places are now offering to pay big bucks this winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Largest Grocery Retailer to Accept Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/kroger-to-accept-bitcoin-cash-this-holiday-season-301417472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prnewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/PRNewswire/ -- The Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR) America's largest grocery retailer, announced today that it will begin accepting Bitcoin Cash. Starting December 1,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vows no mercy for Taiwan independence 'diehards'...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/china/china-vows-no-mercy-for-taiwan-independence-diehards/articleshow/87538093.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China News: BEIJING: China vowed Friday to punish "diehard" Taiwan politicians, saying it would ban several from visiting the mainland, as tensions between Beijin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke-Powered Shower? Russia Tests Climate Innovation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/05/a-nuclear-powered-shower-russia-tests-a-climate-innovation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEVEK, Russia — The water was hot, steamy and plentiful, and Pavel Rozhkov let it flow over his body, enjoying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS holiday cups once flash point in 'war on Christmas.' Now meme...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Starbucks-holiday-cups-were-once-a-flash-point-in-16593849.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Starbucks holiday cups have been released, and there's not a Christmas tree or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese journalist jailed over reporting 'close to death'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10168173/Chinese-journalist-jailed-Covid-reports-close-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zhang Zhan, 38, a former lawyer, travelled to Wuhan in February 2020 to report on the chaos at the pandemic's epicentre, questing questioning authorities' handling of the outbreak in her videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Drone plot against electrical grid...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/nation-world/watch-intelligence-bulletin-reveals-plot-against-pennsylvania-electrical-grid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new warning has been issued regarding a potential attack on the electrical grid in the northeast United States. A newly-released intelligence bulletin, obtained by ABC News, reveals a plot involving the use of a drone to disrupt an electrical grid in Pennsylvania in July 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of intel officers refusing vax risk dismissal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-national-security-intelligence-agencies-chris-stewart-bfff7fc2f8ee0635dd4ae3411c9047eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Thousands of intelligence officers could soon face dismissal for failing to comply with the U.S. government’s vaccine mandate, leading some Republican lawmakers to raise concerns about removing employees from agencies critical to national security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst who aided Trump-Russia dossier charged with lying...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel John Durham’s indictment of Igor Danchenko illustrates that he has his sights set on the Clinton campaign.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
