<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Burglar Breaks Into Home, Steals Dog, Christmas Presents...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Burglar-Breaks-Into-Home-Steals-Dog-Christmas-Presents-502860251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A burglar broke into a home through a bedroom window in Dallas Friday and stole jewelry, Christmas presents and the homeowner's dog, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sportswear traced to factory in China's internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/99016849cddb4b99a048b863b52c28cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOTAN, China (AP) — Barbed wire and hundreds of cameras ring a massive compound of more than 30 dormitories, schools, warehouses and workshops in China's far west. Dozens of armed officers and a growling Doberman stand guard outside. Behind locked gates, men and women are sewing sportswear that can end up on U.S. college campuses and sports teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOONVES DOESN'T GET A PENNY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7858ff2dc8044b139c99a20aed18c502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CBS announced Monday that former CEO Les Moonves will not receive his $120 million severance package after the board of directors concluded he violated company policy and was uncooperative with an investigation into sexual misconduct allegations. The decision, which came after a five-month outside investigation, capped the downfall of one of television's most influential figures, the biggest entertainment powerbroker to see his career derailed amid the #MeToo movement against sexual misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreigners Dump Treasuries, Liquidate Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-17/foreigners-dump-us-treasuries-they-liquidate-record-amount-us-stocks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Thousands Of Vegas Homes Get ZERO Offers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-16/residents-should-not-panic-thousands-las-vegas-homes-get-zero-offers-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Generates Humans That Look 100% Real...</title>
      <link>https://www.tomsguide.com/us/nvidia-ai-faces-generative-adversarial-network,news-28869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tomsguide.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Nvidia AI technology defies belief by creating 100% realistic synthetic humans, cats, and even cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media 'turning generation into liars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/12/18/social-media-turning-generation-children-liars-leading-headmistress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media is turning a generation of children into liars, a leading headmistress has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited farm animals coming. Will public eat?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Gene-edited-farm-animals-are-coming-Will-the-13472924.php  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. - Three cows clomped, single-file, through a chute to line up for sonograms - ultrasound "preg checks" - to reveal if they were expecting calves next summer. "Right now. This is exciting, right this minute," animal geneticist Alison Van Eenennaam said as she waited for a tiny blob of a fetus to materialize on a laptop screen on a recent afternoon at the Beef Barn, part of the University of California at Davis's sprawling agricultural facilities for teaching and research. The cows had been implanted a month and a half earlier with embryos genetically edited to grow and look like males, regardless of their biological gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Do more with less:' Mexico president defends budget cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-budget/do-more-with-less-mexico-president-defends-budget-cuts-idUSKBN1OG26C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador on Monday defended deep cuts to se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Events that marked 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181217-events-marked-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Events that marked 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market on pace for worst December since Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/worst-start-to-december-for-the-stock-market-since-great-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two benchmark U.S. stock indexes are careening toward a historically bad December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal court says ban on nunchucks unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://13wham.com/news/state/federal-court-says-ny-ban-on-nunchucks-unconstitutional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;13wham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) -- A federal court says New York's ban on nunchucks, the martial arts weapon made famous by Bruce Lee but prohibited in the state for decades, is unconstitutional under the Second Amendment. Judge Pamela Chen issued her ruling Friday in federal court in Brooklyn. The plaintiff, James Maloney, started his legal quest after being charged with possession of nunchucks in his home in 2000. Maloney wants to teach a form of martial art using nunchucks that he created to his sons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Under Fire For Allowing 'Anti-Semitic' Book Touting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ny-times-alice-walker-anti-semitic-book-under-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The book is an unhinged anti-Semitic conspiracy tract written by one of Britain’s most notorious anti-Semites," Yair Rosenberg says in Tablet Magazine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge barrier sent to corral plastic in ocean -- isn't trapping any...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/716ebcce87a2415c9047156ac84e2c79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A floating device sent to corral a swirling island of trash between California and Hawaii has not swept up any plastic waste — but the young innovator behind the project said Monday that a fix was in the works. Boyan Slat, 24, who launched the Pacific Ocean cleanup project, said the speed of the solar-powered barrier isn't allowing it to hold on to the plastic it catches. "Sometimes the system actually moves slightly slower than the plastic, which of course you don't want because then you have a chance of losing the plastic again," Slat said in an interview with The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIKOFF: Sensational Dossier Claims 'Likely False'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/17/michael-isikoff-steele-dossier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sensational allegations will never be proven and are likely false'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29-year-old announces 'self-care' break before congress even begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-alexandria-cortez-self-care-break-20181217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bronx-bred democratic socialist announced Monday she’s taking some time off to take care of herself before she officially starts her new job — and she’s taking her supporters along for the ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro says civil militia grows to 1.6 million, mission to stop 'invaders'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-militia/maduro-says-venezuelas-civil-militia-grows-to-1-6-million-members-idUSKBN1OH01P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro said on Monday the country's civil mili...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAACP pushes #LogOutFACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/17/naacp-logoutfacebook-senate-report-facebook-2016-election-interference-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia tried to suppress African-American turnout in the 2016 election, the report says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller releases [redacted] Flynn FBI memo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/17/politics/mueller-memo-michael-flynn-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller has released a January 2017 FBI memo detailing the interview by agent Peter Strzok and another FBI agent with President Donald Trump's then-national security adviser, Michael Flynn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware pulls instructions from code hidden in TWITTER memes...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/17/malware-commands-code-twitter-hidden-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security researchers said they’ve found a new kind of malware that takes its instructions from code hidden in memes posted to Twitter. The malware itself is relatively underwhelming: like most primitive remote access trojans (RATs), the malware quietly infects a vulnerable computer, takes scr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey Dodges Questions About Leaking Classified Info...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/katiepavlich/2018/12/17/comey-asked-if-he-leaked-classified-info-in-his-memos-wont-say-that-he-didnt-n2537637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commuters dumbfounded as bus passenger strips, pole dances...</title>
      <link>https://www.perthnow.com.au/news/australia/sydney-bus-stripper-puts-on-show-for-bemused-passengers-ng-b881053446z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.perthnow.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocked bus passengers in Sydney watched on as a woman stripped naked and performed a pole dance during a trip to Bondi Junction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second straight 2% plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd739b64af9e4e6fa1653842d7f38f98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Another day of big losses knocked U.S. stocks to their lowest levels in more than a year Monday. Selling was widespread. Investors dumped high-growth technology and retail companies as well as steadier, high-dividend companies. Hospitals and health insurers slumped after a federal judge in Texas ruled that the 2010 Affordable Care Act is unconstitutional. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 507 points after a 496-point drop Friday, and all the major stock indexes fell at least 2 percent. Oil closed below $50 a barrel for the first time since October 2017. Bonds rose and their yields fell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex toys on INSTA to sow discord...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1498265/instagram-was-a-massively-important-tool-for-russian-operatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin-sponsored influencers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Develop Way to SHRINK Objects to Nanoscale...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/news/mit-researchers-can-shrink-objects-to-nanoscale-1766243/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT researchers invented a method of shrinking objects to the nanoscale. The team can generate structures one-thousandth the volume of the original using a variety of materials, including metals, quantum dots, and DNA. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CASH COMP FOR LES</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/les-mooves-no-severance-cbc-sexual-assault-harassment-allegations-shari-redstone-1202521696/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once powerful CEO of CBS Les Moonves will not be getting a single dime of the $120 million in severance he expected after stepping down under allegations of misconduct this fall, the company’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI crafts 'perfect' Xmas jingles: 'Peaches Twinkleleaves', 'Cocoa Jollyfluff'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6504887/Listen-perfect-Christmas-song-created-AI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Made by AI trained a neural network by inputting one hundred Christmas tunes in the form of Musical Instrument Digital Interface (MIDI) files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers find 'Farout': Most-distant object in Solar System...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/42755-farout-farthest-solar-system-object-discovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have identified a new solar system body, designated 2018 VG18 and nicknamed Farout, that is the farthest solar system object ever observed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannibal, wife, mistress jailed for serving neighbors human-flesh pastries...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/brazilian-cannibal-wife-and-mistress-who-killed-women-stuffed-flesh-into-pastries-sentenced-to-71-years-in-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian man, dubbed the “Sweeney Todd” cannibal, his wife and mistress were sentenced to 71 years in prison after they killed women and mixed their flesh into pastries that they ate and handed out to neighbors, reports said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams tops Beto, Ocasio-Cortez to be most GOOGLED politician...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/421699-googles-most-searched-politician-of-2018-is-stacey-abrams</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Georgia gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams was the top trending politician in searches in 2018, Google announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin calendar sales surpassing those of celebs in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/national/putin-calendar-sales-surpassing-those-of-japanese-stars-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current leader in 2019 calendar sales at a popular chain store in Japan is not a fresh-faced young idol, nor is it a sexy heart-throb actor. Rather, Vladimir Putin, the 66-year-old president of Russia, takes the cake in that category. That’s right, the very same exercise buff that also has claim to a fragrance in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 states to pursue Catholic priest abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/12/17/josh-shapiro-more-horrors-coming-catholic-clergy-abuse-scandal/2329159002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pennsylvania authorities have joined with their counterparts across the U.S., helping craftÂ search warrant applications and grand jury subpoenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER:  Most treacherous market in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/cramer-says-not-a-safe-stock-market-most-treacherous-market-in-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think that there's a lot of people who say, 'I got to get out. I got to get out, because everyone else is getting out,'" says the "Mad Money" host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  AIRBNB Hebrew statement contradicts anti-Israel policy released in English...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/airbnb-suspends-ban-on-west-bank-settlement-homes-expresses-unequivocal-rejection-of-bds-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airbnb announced Monday it would not implement a recently announced policy to exclude homes in Israeli settlements from its listings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran tech columnist quits FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/12/17/veteran-tech-columnist-walt-mossberg-quits-facebook/2336828002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social network has come under fire all year for security breaches and data collection on users. Mossberg says he's "no longer comfortable" with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to intro tax on large internet, tech firms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181217-france-tax-large-internet-tech-gafa-company-usa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France will introduce its own tax on large internet and technology companies from January 1, Finance Minister Bruno Le Maire said Monday amid difficulties in finalising a new EU-wide levy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -500</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/us-stock-futures-fall-slightly-in-early-trading-after-fridays-big-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks sank Monday as investors grew worried that the Fed's plan to raise rates could be too much for the economy and stocks to handle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest diamond in North America found: 187.7 carats...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46562131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 552-carat yellow gemstone was found in a Canadian mine and is more than two inches long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals slash an inflatable black Santa...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article223200495.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vandals slashed an inflatable black Santa Claus in a Bethany, Oregon, family’s yard, but neighbors say they’ll put up their own black Santas in solidarity with the family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking at funeral, priest criticizes teen who killed himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/maison-hullibarger-funeral-priest-don-lacuesta-criticizes-teen-who-killed-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The archdiocese released a statement saying it's sorry that an "unbearable situation was made even more difficult"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumner Redstone declared incapacitated...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-sumner-redstone-incapacitated-20181217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media mogul Sumner Redstone is incapacitated and needs a guardian ad litem to protect his interests in a current legal case, a judge determined Monday during a hearing in a long-running court dispute about the health of the controlling shareholder of CBS and Viacom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blast smashes windows, wrecks offices at Greece TV station...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-greece-blast-skai/blast-smashes-windows-wrecks-offices-at-greeces-skai-tv-in-attack-on-democracy-idUSKBN1OG0CD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful blast smashed windows and wrecked offices at Greece's SKAI TV in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If Feds Went After WASH POST as They're Going After NATIONAL ENQUIRER?</title>
      <link>https://www.nysun.com/national/what-if-g-men-went-after-washington-post-as-they/90499/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nysun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine that a federal prosecutor had gone after The Washington Post Company back in the 1990s on the theory that the reluctance of its magazine, Newsweek, to publish an article about a sex scandal involving Bill Clinton constituted an illegal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops find 3 kids home alone after girl calls 911 for 'help watching YOUTUBE'...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/home-alone-youtube-859231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 17--An Iowa woman who left her three small children home alone late Thursday night was arrested on endangerment charges after one of the children called 911 to report that “her mom and dad le</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First private Israeli lunar mission to launch...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af0168ec78cc4144b8c1bd23327ef75a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEHUD, Israel (AP) — An Israeli nonprofit on Monday said it has pushed back the launch of what it hopes will be the first private spacecraft to land on the moon until February. Officials from SpaceIL and its project partner, the state-owned Israel Aerospace Industries, announced that the landing craft, dubbed "Beresheet," or Genesis, will ship in February to Florida. Propelled by a SpaceX Falcon rocket launch, the robotic lander will then commence its months-long voyage to the moon. It had been slated to launch this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNAL CONFRONTATION...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/12/17/google-china-censored-search-engine-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google reassigned several groups of engineers away from a planned censored search engine after a rift over its use of real internet queries in China for testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VICE' WORST MOVE OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vice-the-dick-cheney-biopic-might-be-the-worst-movie-of-the-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Adam McKay’s political satire, starring an unrecognizable Christian Bale, is getting major awards buzz. But is it any good? Marlow Stern and Kevin Fallon break it down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VICE' BEST MOVIE OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/vice-review-1166477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Bale and Amy Adams play Dick and Lynne Cheney in Adam McKay's sprawling dark comedy about George W. Bush's vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tenn. Republican Senator won't seek 2020 reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/politics/2018/12/17/sen-lamar-alexander-tennessee/2276521002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee Sen. Lamar Alexander, first elected in 2002, also served two terms as governor and as Secretary of Education under Pres. George H.W. Bush</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BAMBI' as punishment? Poacher's sentence includes mandated viewings...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-leader.com/story/news/crime/2018/12/13/multi-year-poaching-probe-nabs-four-sw-missouri-family-members/2305173002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-leader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge orders one poacher to repeatedly watch "Bambi"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn associates charged over lobbying for Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/two-associates-michael-flynn-charged-trying-influence-u-s-politicians-n948816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scheme involved a secret effort to build support among American politicians to remove exiled cleric Fethullah Gulen from the U.S., prosecutors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US conducts airstrikes against Somalia extremists, 62 dead...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/us-conducts-6-airstrikes-against-somalia-extremists-62-100748263.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six U.S. airstrikes that killed more than 60 people in a coastal Somali town were pre-emptive strikes to prevent a major extremist attack, according to a Somali intelligence officer. The U.S. military said Monday it carried out four strikes on Dec. 15 in which 34 people were killed and two more on Dec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kUbskFr2yp4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KiwiBot lights on fire on UC Berkeley campus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS NEED A SANTA!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-stocks-need-a-santa-claus-rally-to-avoid-a-losing-year-11545022860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors hoping to avoid the first annual decline for major U.S. stock indexes since 2015 are dreaming of a Santa Claus rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Targets Unprofitable Items, With Sharper Focus on Bottom Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/amazon-targets-unprofitable-items-with-a-sharper-focus-on-the-bottom-line-11544965201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com has trained people to buy everything online. Now it is having second thoughts about some of those sales because they don’t make money—and is pushing big brands to change how they use its site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot to begin patrolling Los Angeles mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/national/robot-to-begin-patrolling-los-angeles-mall/1662988353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robot was first introduced to the public over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 17 (KNOWN) INVESTIGATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mueller-investigation-trump-russia-complete-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation in to Russian interference and Donald Trump has sprung so many offshoots, it's hard to keep track. Here's a comprehensive list. It's long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Pentagon officers take on Spec ops' misdeeds: abuse, criminality and falling discipline...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/16/special-ops-command-study-misconduct-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are among America’s most elite military fighters, but a string of recent high-profile scandals and abuse allegations — including drug-smuggling, detainee abuse and murder — has put the U.S. special operations forces under unprecedented scrutiny, prompting a commandwide soul-searching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT CALLS COHEN RAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-borrowed-rat-nickname-for-michael-cohen-from-matt-drudge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has long given his adversaries original nicknames to mock and diminish them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 50 most expensive zip codes in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/12/17/these-are-the-most-expensive-zip-codes-in-2018/38693069/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco has the greatest concentration of the most expensive zip codes, with four. New York City and Los Angeles are behind it with three each.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crucified...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7998990/playboy-model-marisa-papen-arrested-nudes-crucified-vatican/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONTROVERSIAL Playboy model Marisa Papen has been arrested after doing a nude photoshoot of her being crucified on a cross at the Vatican. This is the second time the Belgian model has been arreste…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces boycott as public discontent grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/17/amazon-boycott-customers-holiday-shopping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of customers are fed up with the company, from its working conditions at warehouses to anti-tax lobbying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young farmers the new starving artists?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/17/young-farmers-millennials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small but growing movement of millennials are seeking out a more agrarian life but the reality of life on the land is not always as simple as they hoped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chickens freezing to death, boiled alive: Failings in slaughterhouses exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/17/chickens-freezing-to-death-and-boiled-alive-failings-in-us-slaughterhouses-exposed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation finds hundreds of shocking welfare incidents, fuelling concerns about standards in a post-Brexit trade deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists developing AI to combat 'hate speech'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/berkeley-scientists-developing-artificial-intelligence-tool-to-combat-hate-speech-on-social-media/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Ten students of diverse backgrounds' helped developed the algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's highest paid QBs will be watching cheapest in playoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-NFL-s-highest-paid-quarterbacks-will-be-13471405.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last summer, near the conclusion of training camp, a reporter asked Chicago Bears General Manager Ryan Pace about his team's window of contention. How cognizant was Pace of not only building for the future with a second-year quarterback, but also attempting to win immediately, before Mitchell Trubisky's bargain rookie deal grew more expensive? "That is something we internally talk about," Pace replied. "There's no question, the obvious advantages to that, versus going out and signing. In a perfect world, any franchise would want to hit on a young, drafted quarterback, as opposed to maybe hitting on it in free agency, where the financial part is different.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New strike week before Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon-workers-on-strike-in-germany-a-week-before-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Workers at two Amazon distribution centers in Germany have gone on strike as part of a push for improved work conditions, leading to fears that Christmas orders may not arrive in time. The German news agency dpa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China and Russia band together on controversial heating experiments to modify the atmosphere...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2178214/china-and-russia-band-together-controversial-heating-experiments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The countries are testing a technology for possible military application, say Chinese scientists involved in the projectMilitaries have been in a race to control the ionosphere, which allows radio signals to bounce long distances for communication, for decades</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts Fed for 'even considering' rate hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-trump-fed/trump-again-blasts-fed-for-even-considering-rate-hike-idUSL1N1YM0EW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump early on Monday again criticized the Federal Reserve for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burnout, stress lead more companies to try four-day work week...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-world-work-fourdayweek/burnout-stress-lead-more-companies-to-try-a-four-day-work-week-idUSKBN1OG0GY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work four days a week, but get paid for five?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURNS HIMSELF IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-healer-abuse/brazil-faith-healer-accused-of-sexual-abuse-turns-himself-in-idUSKBN1OF0SL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian faith healer who was accused of sexual abuse by more than 300 women ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands march in Brussels against UN immigration demands...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-belgium-protests-migration/thousands-march-in-brussels-against-u-n-migration-pact-idUSKBN1OF0LM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people marched in Brussels on Sunday against a U.N. pact aimed at f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Seeks Dismissal Of Sex Assault Case In Possible #MeToo Setback...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/12/17/676803400/weinstein-seeks-dismissal-of-sexual-assault-case-in-possible-metoo-setback </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Harvey Weinstein was arrested, it was a landmark moment for the movement known as #MeToo. But the criminal case against the former movie mogul has not been the slam dunk many people expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHUMER:  NOT GOING TO GET IT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/schumer-trump-s-temper-tantrum-over-wall-funding-leading-shutdown-n948521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate minority leader said Sunday that it's up to the president to come to the table to prevent a partial shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Deep Will Dems Dig?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/democrats-take-cautious-view-subpoena-powers-they-ready-investigations-n948531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As they prepare to take over the House majority, top Democrats warn that the powerful tool is not a magic wand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAYBOY model poses naked at Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/playboy-model-poses-naked-vatican-13744712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - CONTAINS NUDITY. Marisa Papen has previously been imprisoned after posing nude at the Karnak Temple Complex near Luxor, Egypt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guardsman Kills Wife, Son, Self at Florida Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article223177860.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Presnar, a U.S . Coast Guard serviceman based in Miami Beach, killed his wife and child before killing himself, officials confirmed. His second child was transported to a nearby hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push to restore state and local tax deductions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article223103970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats from California and other high-tax states will push to restore the state and local tax deduction when the party takes control of the House in 2019. Republicans’ 2017 tax overhaul capped those deductions at $10,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst December start since 1980...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-poised-to-edge-lower-in-the-wake-of-worst-start-to-december-since-1980-2018-12-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock benchmarks trade lower after the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell into correction territory and the three main benchmarks on Friday marked their worst start to December trading since 1980.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedtime stories for adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/meet-the-woman-who-tells-bedtime-stories-to-adults-to-put-them-to-sleep-2018-12-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calm app’s ‘Sleep Stories’ are written by the ‘JK Rowling of slow literature’ Phoebe Smith, who highlights soothing, sensory adventures in places like Provence and Nepal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC proposal would let police take guns from people accused of domestic abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/D-C-proposal-would-let-police-take-guns-from-13470614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The D.C. Council on Tuesday could pass new laws restricting the ability of gun owners to modify weapons and require police to seize guns while enforcing protective orders in domestic disputes. The latter provision - known as a "red flag law" - is gaining popularity, with variants implemented in more than a dozen states, including Maryland. The D.C. version would mandate that authorities take firearms out of the hands of suspected abusers more quickly than is permitted under existing laws. Other proposed laws, if passed, would the ban rapid-fire attachments known as bump stocks and increase penalties for extended magazines, accessories that allow guns to fire faster and hold more bullets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese to take over Israeli port... </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/US-Navy-may-stop-docking-in-Haifa-after-Chinese-take-over-port-574414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns prompt â€˜reviewâ€™ of Shanghai agreement within Israelâ€™s inner security cabinet, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Legal Setback Points to Tougher Times Ahead for Media Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/cnn-legal-setback-points-tougher-times-media-companies-1169938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a defamation case, the Eleventh Circuit rejects how CNN and other media companies demanded the special-dismissal provision of Georgia's anti-SLAPP statute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Surfer catches 'biggest wave EVER ridden' at 100ft tall...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748617/surfer-world-record-biggest-wave-100ft-tom-butler-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study predicts end of humanity: Mankind will FAIL to mate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748133/mouse-utopia-experiment-human-extinction-science-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering laser beam zaps 'impossible to treat' brain tumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6499739/Pioneering-precision-laser-beam-zaps-impossible-treat-brain-tumours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The procedure involves a fine narrow tube being inserted into the tumour before a laser is beamed down it, gradually heating up to about 70C, breaking down and killing the cancerous cells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to compensate those who fled Nazis as children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/germany-to-compensate-those-who-fled-nazis-as-children.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany has agreed to one-time payments for survivors, primarily Jews, who were evacuated from Nazi Germany as children, many of whom never saw their parents again, the organization that negotiates compensation with the German government said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ron Paul warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/14/ron-paul-market-meltdown-could-spark-depression-like-conditions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former presidential candidate Ron Paul believes a 50 percent or more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON-KILLING LOSS?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/sports/patriots/2018/12/16/reality-patriots-are-simply-not-great-team/SwL9tWoq054XGW8G5gqh3H/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This loss to the Steelers could be season-killing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans Turn More Pessimistic on Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/americans-turn-more-pessimistic-on-economy-trump-approval-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Americans also say Trump has been untruthful about the investigation into Russiaâ€™s interference in 2016 elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameroon imprisoning journalists accused of 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cameroon-imprisoning-journalists-fake-news-f7f76a2a-a0b3-40a1-9344-b76ed1020bfe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Largely because of their reporting on the country’s de-facto civil war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron govt hopes protests running out of steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/macron-govt-hopes-yellow-vest-protests-running-out-steam-doc-1bn1sj4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC's wettest year on record!</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2018/12/its-official-2018-is-dcs-wettest-year-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Reagan Airport reporting 61.34 inches of rain for the year on Saturday morning, 2018 will go down as D.C.’s wettest calendar year on record — and the rain is still falling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Frequent sex leads to greater enjoyment of life for men, but not women...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2018/12/frequent-sex-associated-with-greater-enjoyment-of-life-for-men-but-not-women-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frequent sexual activity leads to greater enjoyment of life for men. For women, frequent kissing and feeling emotionally close to their partner was associated with higher enjoyment of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn associate charged over lobbying for Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/421670-michael-flynn-associate-charged-over-illegal-lobbying-forturkey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Associates of onetime national security adviser Michael Flynn are being charged with illegally lobbying for the extradition of Fethullah Gülen, a U.S.-based Turkish cleric who has been a frequent public target of Turkish President Recep Tayyi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 3D-printed heads let hackers, cops unlock your phone...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/16/3d-printed-heads-unlock-cops-hackers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a lot you can make with a 3D printer: from prosthetics, corneas, and firearms — even an Olympic-standard luge. You can even 3D print a life-size replica of a human head — and not just for Hollywood. Forbes reporter Thomas Brewster commissioned a 3D printed model of his own head to tes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian 'healer' losing celeb following amid sex abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/12/16/brazilian-healer-losing-celeb-following-amid-sex-abuse-claims/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oprah stamp of approval turned Faria’s small town into an international mecca for the crippled and diseased seeking his “psychic surgeries.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major funds scrambling to prevent  wipeout...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/16/major-hedge-funds-are-scrambling-to-prevent-financial-wipeout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stars of the biggest hedge funds are losing their shirts as analysts fear a major financial wipeout is imminent. From Ken Griffin’s Citadel, to Israel Englander’s Millennium Management, one big…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New figures show fewer Mormons in Utah's biggest county...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/figures-show-fewer-mormons-utahs-biggest-county-201624311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Fewer than half the residents of Salt Lake County belong to the Mormon church, according to new figures that illustrate how Utah's largest county is becoming more religiously diverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers request air conditioning, told 'ROBOTS CAN'T WORK IN COLD'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/hundreds-march-on-amazon-fulfillment-center-in-minnesot-1831113246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAKOPEE, Minn. — If local headlines are to be believed, not much happens in Shakopee. But on Friday evening, this placid town of 40,000 on the outskirts of Minnesota’s Twin Cities became the epicenter of the fight for humane working conditions at one of the world’s most valuable companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY BLAMES SELF</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/16/tom-brady-costly-interception-patriots-steelers-nfl-week-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second straight week, Tom Brady made a very un-Tom-Brady-like play that cost the Patriots points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLDEST DECEMBER</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/16/patriots-steelers-recap-week-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England's struggles on the road continued in Pittsburgh on Sunday, costing them a chance to clinch a playoff spot for the second straight week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parties Dig In On Border Wall Funding...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2b76716fbb2b440b8693e96e46af02b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pushing the government to the brink of a partial shutdown, the White House is insisting that Congress provide $5 billion to build a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border despite lawmaker resistance from both parties. Without a resolution, parts of the federal government will shut down at midnight Friday. President Donald Trump kept up the pressure on Democrats on Monday, tweeting: "Time for us to save billions of dollars a year and have, at the same time, far greater safety and control!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman crushed by own SUV while trying to pay toll...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/woman-who-was-pinned-by-suv-at-indiana-toll-booth-dies-four-days-later/4904557/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan woman died Wednesday after being rescued from her own vehicle crushing her last week at a tollbooth in northwest Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parrot uses ALEXA to order packages while owners gone...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/parrot-used-amazon-alexa-to-order-items-while-his-owner-was-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parrot has fallen in love with his owner’s Amazon Alexa — but keeps using it to order shopping.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
