<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Powerhouse in Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/28/obituaries/harry-reid-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Reid, a Democrat from Nevada, displayed his pugilistic instincts as he steered an economic stimulus package and the Affordable Care Act to passage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'BOXER'S INSTINCTS'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/senschumer/status/1475997288497565699</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARRY REID DEAD AT 82... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegassun.com/news/2021/dec/28/nevada-political-giant-former-us-sen-harry-reid-di/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegassun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska hits record-high temperature for December...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/alaska-hits-record-high-temperature-for-december/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exceptional slew of records has tumbled in the wake of extreme warmth, with highs up to 45 degrees above average. Kodiak soared to 67 degrees on Sunday, while other towns are experiencing anomalous rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARRY REID DEAD AT 82... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/428846-harry-reid-political-pugilist-and-longtime-senate-majority-leader-dies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harry Reid, one of the Senate’s longest serving majority leaders and a Democrat who played a central role in enacting President Obama’s biggest legislative accomplishments, died Tuesday at 82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge extends Maxwell deliberation hours, citing 'astronomical' virus spike...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211228152906-32tf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Judge extends Maxwell deliberation hours, citing 'astronomical' COVID-19 spike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC CHAOS, CONFUSION</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/587506-cdc-lowers-estimate-of-omicron-prevalence-in-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) on Tuesday significantly revised downward the estimate of the percentage of new COVID-19 infections in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Legend John Madden Dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32953839/nfl-hall-fame-coach-broadcasting-icon-john-madden-dies-85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hall of Fame coach and broadcasting icon John Madden died unexpectedly Tuesday morning, the NFL announced. He was 85</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis vanishes during omicron surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-miami-florida-ea2f4f557acb1262621529ee1a9ad3eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — The mayor of one of Florida's largest counties on Tuesday blasted Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis, saying he has been missing in action during the latest wave of COVID-19, as some counties brought back mask mandates for government workers and other municipalities opened up new testing sites in response to overwhelming demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Says NYT Can Retain 'VERITAS' Memos. For Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/28/business/media/new-york-times-project-veritas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York appeals court said the paper did not need to immediately give up or destroy documents related to the conservative group. The paper is still prevented from publishing certain documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Star Was Up for 'VIEW' Gig Until She Refused to Get Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-lisa-marie-boothe-was-up-for-the-view-gig-until-she-refused-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Marie Boothe interviewed to replace Meghan McCain as the talk show’s in-house conservative. But conversations ended when she publicly refused to get any vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax kickboxing champ dies from complications...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4344694/anti-vax-kickboxing-champ-frederic-sinistra-dead-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-VAXXER kickboxing champion Frederic Sinistra has died from Covid complications after he discharged himself from the hospital. The 41-year-old, known as The Undertaker, died at his home in Cine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scots prepare NYE invasion of England -- to escape lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4354791/scots-cross-borders-new-years-eve-sturgeon-clampdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUB landlords in England are gearing up for an invasion of Scottish and Welsh drinkers on New Year’s Eve as anger grows at the nations’ different Covid curbs. Up to 100,000 could cross borders afte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA,</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-atlanta-d829657f6843e7e2559e7bfc86827376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Georgia broke the state's record for the number of test-confirmed COVID-19 cases on Tuesday, with an extremely rapid rise in cases passing the peaks previously set in January. The state recorded 13,670 positive tests in its report released Tuesday, a combination of molecular PCR tests and rapid antigen tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOORDASH requiring engineers to deliver food -- and they're furious...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/tech/article/DoorDash-requires-engineers-to-deliver-food-16732012.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I didn't sign up for this.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citizen Militias Moving Toward More Violent Extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/citizen-militias-in-the-u-s-are-moving-toward-more-violent-extremism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scientificamerican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some members, a longing for &amp;ldquo;simpler&amp;rdquo; times is giving rise to deadly activities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid tests may not be detecting new variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/28/fda-antigen-tests-reduced-sensitivity-omicron-526217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new warning is based on preliminary studies by the National Institutes of Health’s Rapid Acceleration of Diagnostics initiative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positivity rate surges to 20%!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-york-s-daily-covid-positivity-rate-surges-to-almost-20/ar-AASdD2I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food recalls drop off during pandemic, but no one knows why...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/12/28/1064951518/food-recalls-pandemic-covid-usda-fda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the pandemic hit last year, restaurants closed and grocery stores struggled to keep their shelves stocked. A shift also occurred in the national food safety system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He wanted to be soldier. When he failed, he stalked recruiter...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/12/28/he-wanted-to-be-a-soldier-when-he-failed-he-stalked-his-recruiter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At one point, Danley posted a message on Facebook directed to the recruiter stating, "im coming to get you."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This F*cking Girl Reporter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/this-fcking-girl-reporter-dr-oz-and-his-wife-freaked-out-over-reporting-from-ny-mags-olivia-nuzzi-who-overheard-everything-when-they-failed-to-hang-up-the-phone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York reporter Olivia Nuzzi published her account of the major-league meltdown Dr. Mehmet Oz had about her, which she listened to over the phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo to face no charges in Westchester despite 'credible' allegations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/587521-cuomo-to-face-no-charges-in-westchester-despite-credible-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westchester County District Attorney Mimi Rocah announced on Tuesday that she would not pursue criminal charges against former New York Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France reports record 180,000 infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/health/20211228-who-warns-of-omicron-overload-as-france-reports-record-high-of-nearly-180-000-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WHO warned Tuesday that the Omicron coronavirus variant could lead to overwhelmed healthcare systems even though early studies suggest it sparks milder disease, as countries reintroduced tough re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warships stay in Mediterranean amid Ukraine, Russia fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-russia-ukraine-navy-2e29e6cbbe8a32adaf633dc2d849e94c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin has ordered a U.S. Navy aircraft carrier strike group to stay in the Mediterranean Sea region rather than move on to the Middle East, amid worries about the buildup of thousands of Russian troops near the Ukraine border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish man punched, given black eye in Brooklyn for wearing IDF shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/article-689994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children's hospitals filling up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/27/health/covid-kids-hospitals/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A five-fold increase in pediatric admissions in New York City this month. Close to double the numbers admitted in Washington, DC. And nationwide, on average, pediatric hospitalizations are up 35% in just the past week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS driver kidnapped at gunpoint, packages stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-ups-driver-kidnapped-at-gunpoint-packages-stolen/X2IGYTDJDRDD3PJROCCMFFRRPQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UPS driver who did not make his deliveries was discovered tied up and locked inside his tractor-trailer Tuesday morning in northwest Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after posing as special-needs to have women change his diaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbs42.com/regional/louisiana-news/louisiana-man-who-hired-babysitters-to-change-his-diaper-and-treat-him-like-a-child-charged-with-human-trafficking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs42.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana man was arrested and charged with human trafficking after police say he allegedly posed as a young man with special needs, and then hired babysitters to change his diaper and treat him …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethical non-monogamy: Rise of multi-partner relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20210326-ethical-non-monogamy-the-rise-of-multi-partner-relationships</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multi-partner relationships are on the rise, and finding their way into the mainstream. Could this new exposure change the way we look at sex and families?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Burnout Leading to Retail Pharmacy Technician Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/national-international/im-so-burned-out-pharmacy-staffs-struggling-to-keep-up-with-ever-rising-demands/2765456/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working in a pharmacy was always fast-paced, one technician says, but in recent years the workload and stress has increased to unsustainable levels, while staffing and pay failed to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals a rising force inside Argentine prisons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-prisons-argentina-185245bd2714f184cc66e95d76406ea3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROSARIO, Argentina (AP) — The loud noise from the opening of an iron door marks Jorge Anguilante’s exit from the Pinero prison every Saturday. He heads home for 24 hours to minister at a small evangelical church he started in a garage in Argentina’s most violent city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe blows past 50-year December snowfall record...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/2021/12/27/tahoe-breaks-50-year-december-snowfall-record-sierra-winter-storm-ski-resorts-snow-storm-snowpack/9029766002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, December snow totals at the UC Berkeley Central Sierra Snow Lab at Donner Pass reached 193.7 inches, toppling a 1970 record of 179 inches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC sharply drops estimate of Omicron prevalence in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/28/cdc-drops-omicron-prevalence-estimate-526210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency said the disparity was due to the rate with which the highly transmissible Omicron spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Political Life of Dr. Oz...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/dr-oz-senate-pennsylvania.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His campaign to be the next Republican senator from Pennsylvania is facing one major problem: Republicans in Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Jackman tests positive -- Broadway's biggest star...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/12/28/broadway-more-trouble-in-river-city-as-hugh-jackman-tests-positive-the-music-man-cancel-again-til-january-2nd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking mugshots: Online era means they live forever so states limiting release...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/politics/2021/12/rethinking-mugshots-online-era-means-they-live-forever-so-states-are-moving-to-limit-release.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many news outlets have stopped publishing mugshots, but some states like Oregon are beginning to grapple with a more fundamental issue: Why do police release those mugshots — and should they be allowed to? Mugshots are not presumptively public record after Jan. 1 in Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 50 Manhattan residents infected in last week... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/1-in-50-manhattan-residents-infected-with-covid-in-the-last-week/3470148/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread out of control in New York City, transmission rates are soaring, with 2% of all Manhattan residents infected in the last week and nearing that level in the other boroughs. About 2,012 of every 100,000 Manhattan residents tested positive in the last seven days, according to the latest transmission data posted…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGE AT 30,000 FT:  Woman slaps, spits at  80-year-old passenger...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wwjnewsradio/news/national/ex-baywatch-actress-playboy-model-slaps-80-year-old-on-delta-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;’Delta Karen’s’ identity was revealed as Patricia Cornwell, an actress and former NFL Cheerleader and Playmate. She screamed at and slapped a fellow passenger on an recent Delta Airlines flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escobar personal photographer confronts drug lord's complicated legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Pablo-Escobar-s-personal-photographer-confronts-16733523.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDELLÍN, Colombia - When the Jeep pulled up to the gates of the estate, Edgar Jiménez...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron may cut delta infections, study shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/omicron-may-reduce-delta-infections-south-african-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infection with the omicron coronavirus variant can also strengthen immunity against the earlier delta strain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senator Who Could Rescue Joe's Agenda</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/biden-agenda-in-2022-could-depend-more-on-romney-than-on-manchin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senator Who Could Rescue Biden’s Agenda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa terrorism case raises questions of surveillance, searches, mental illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/tampa-terrorism-case-raises-questions-of-surveillance-searches-mental-illness/article_c06a4779-29c0-5fcc-a061-a33db9fbdb33.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. — A year ago, federal prosecutors accused a Tampa man of plotting a mass shooting in support of the Islamic State terrorist group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet people bringing us answers on big bang, and their 13,000-pound helper...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/meet-the-people-bringing-us-answers-on-the-big-bang-and-their-13-000-pound/article_06420d81-ca24-568f-b76b-0143e59850aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — For some people, it’s a memoir or a work of fiction; others, their first company or app. For Scott Willoughby, it’s a more than 13,000-pound telescope that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laws shield hospitals from families who believe loved ones contracted virus as patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/laws-shield-hospitals-from-families-who-believe-loved-ones-contracted-covid-as-patients/article_d0d94edf-6034-5730-8849-8dbfd52b4018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Amanda Wilson lost her son, Braden, 15, to COVID-19 in early 2021, she tried to honor his memory. She put up a lending library box in his name. She</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX runs out of monoclonal antibody treatment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/587466-texas-runs-out-of-monoclonal-antibody-treatment-effective-against</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas has run out of its supply of monoclonal antibodies, and infusion centers in the state will be unable to offer the treatment until more shipments are sent out in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia orders top rights group shut, capping year of crackdowns...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211228121901-dl7iw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/RIGHTS-MEMORIAL (UPDATE 2, TV):UPDATE 2-'Total repression': Russia orders top rights group shut, capping year of crackdowns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child hospitalizations up 400% in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/587456-child-covid-19-hospitalizations-up-nearly-400-percent-in-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pediatric COVID-19 hospitalizations in New York City rose by roughly 400 percent in December as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread throughout the state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Peanut Butter Secret:  Lavish Tax Dodge for Ultrawealthy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/28/the-peanut-butter-secret-a-lavish-tax-dodge-for-the-ultrawealthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the story of the incredible cloning tax break. In 2004, David Baszucki, fresh off a stint as a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nursing home staff shortages worsening problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Nursing-home-staff-shortages-are-worsening-16733486.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the 390-bed Terrace View nursing home on the east side of Buffalo, 22 beds are shut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals 'overrun' again...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211227-no-panic-but-covid-to-overrun-some-us-hospitals-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Monday said some US hospitals could be "overrun" by Covid cases, but the country is generally well prepared to meet the latest surge and Americans need not panic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli leader criticized Jewish 'settler violence.' Now he has 24/7 protection after extremist threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-israeli-leader-criticized-jewish-settler-violence-now-he-has-24-7-protection-after-extremist-threats/ar-AASclMP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mach 5 Missiles Spur New Arms Race as USA Seeks to Match China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/mach-5-missiles-spur-new-arms-race-as-us-seeks-to-match-china/ar-AAScLVy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK moderator sues company, alleging trauma from reviewing videos of rape, killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/TikTok-content-moderator-sues-company-alleging-16733414.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A content moderator who reviewed videos for TikTok is suing the social media company,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grapples with covid failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/28/politics/joe-biden-covid-19-testing-failure/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and his team repeatedly promised more Covid-19 testing, including at-home kits that deliver rapid results, but they are now admitting a virus that is more adaptable than the politicians who fight it has outpaced them again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is There Enough Space in Outer Space for China and Musk?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akv35e/is-there-enough-space-in-outer-space-for-both-china-and-elon-musk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial tech billionaire is under growing scrutiny in China as his satellites almost collided with the country's space station twice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy Florida Man Murdered During Luxury Hotel Orgy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jose-rosado-wealthy-florida-man-murdered-during-luxury-hotel-orgy-in-madrid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of a 42-year-old American was found in Madrid’s Westin Hotel last October with no signs of physical abuse. Cops eventually worked out what happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's Doomsday Prophet Has Dire Warning About Where We're Headed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/12/28/inflation-interest-rates-thomas-hoenig-federal-reserve-526177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Hoenig knew what quantitative easing and record-low interest rates would bring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Mississippi city that became country's most murderous during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/28/us/jackson-mississippi-pandemic-homicides-gun-violence/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around Thanksgiving, crisis-plagued Jackson saw a series of shootings that pushed this year's homicide total past 130, setting a grim annual record for a city that over the last two years has quietly become one of the country's deadliest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy want to own less of everything bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/28/millionaires-want-to-own-a-little-less-of-everything-bubble-next-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millionaire investors surveyed by CNBC say that there isn't a single asset class where they are planning to increase portfolio exposure in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient DNA In Tomb Reveals World's Oldest Family Tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ancient-dna-oldest-family-tree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mapping DNA from the bones and teeth of these individuals reveals 27 of the 35 bodies were close biological relatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Biden Approval Falls Below Harris First Time in Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-approval-rating-falls-below-kamala-harris-for-first-time-in-office-per-latest-gallup-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden's approval rating is below that of his VP Kamala Harris for the first time they took office, according to a recent poll released by Gallup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Strange Light Cosmic Explosion?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/china-says-the-gn-z11-flash-was-a-record-breaking-gamma-ray-burst-but-other-astronomers-say-its-orbital-junk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers can’t agree whether the “GN-z11-flash” was a gamma-ray burst from the universe’s infancy, or just reflected light off junk in Earth’s orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC, MD, VA records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-maryland-and-virginia-emerge-from-christmas-weekend-with-record-coronavirus-case-numbers/ar-AASbNF7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Infections Highest Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/world-hits-record-daily-covid-cases-as-omicron-mars-christmas/ar-AAScvqj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year Basic Income Programs Went Mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-year-basic-income-programs-went-mainstream/ar-AAScGRp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four dead, three injured in Denver 'killing spree'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/four-dead-three-injured-denver-area-killing-spree-rcna10150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Denver have launched a "large-scale" investigation into what authorities have described as a "killing spree" on Monday that left four people dead and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Supreme Court lurching right, state courts offer libs hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-with-the-supreme-court-lurching-right-state-courts-offer-liberals-hope/ar-AASaLg5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to jail drivers in brutal 'zero Covid' lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-jail-drivers-brutal-zero-25799631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing and stricter rules have been imposed on the Xi'an region of China, despite there being only 162 new cases of the Delta variant of Coronavirus - No Omicron cases have been reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists warn too many shots might harm body's ability to fight virus...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/23/israel-considers-4th-vaccine-dose-but-some-experts-say-its-premature/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Israel’s Health Ministry was weighing on Thursday whether to approve a fourth Covid-19 vaccine dose for some people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children as young as five exposed to stabbing massacres on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4349455/kids-youtube-platform-massacres/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILDREN as young as five are being exposed to stabbing massacres and dangerous stunts on the YouTube Kids platform.   After concerns from readers, The Sun tested their app posing as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tells jury deliberating Ghislaine fate to prepare to stay late until verdict reached...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-jury-ghislaine-maxwell-sdny-no-verdict-third-day-20211228-hludubpjvbglfm4ibeex45h4pa-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over objections from Maxwell’s defense team, Manhattan Federal Court Judge Alison Nathan told the panelists to prepare to stay an extra hour each day starting Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing remastered color video of LA from 1930s shows city full of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10348569/Amazing-remastered-color-video-LA-1930s-shows-city-life-old-traffic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly colorized footage of bustling LA in the 1930's resembles a Hollywood set. Although traffic is made up of now-classic cars and haberdashed pedestrians, the gridlock is reminiscent of today's LA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,500-year-old mummy of Egyptian king 'digitally unwrapped' for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/28/world/egyptian-mummy-unwrap-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CT scanning has revealed tantalizing details about the life and death of the pharaoh Amenhotep I for the first time since his mummified remains were discovered in 1881.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Buys Maui Estate for $78 Million...</title>
      <link>https://marketrealist.com/p/bezos-hawaii-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;marketrealist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos’s Hawaii house is his latest big-ticket property. The Amazon founder bought the estate in June 2021, reportedly shelling out around $78 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>817,000 COVID DEATHS ON HIS WATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.google.com/search?q=us+covid+deaths&amp;rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS838US838&amp;oq=us+covid+deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC, MD, VA emerge from Christmas with record numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-maryland-and-virginia-emerge-from-christmas-weekend-with-record-coronavirus-case-numbers/ar-AASbNF7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>817,000 COVID DEATHS ON HIS WATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.google.com/search?q=us+covid+deaths&amp;rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS838US838&amp;oq=us+covid+deaths&amp;aqs=chrome..69i57j69i60.3076j0j4&amp;sourceid=chrome&amp;ie=UTF-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia covid numbers surge as Omicron outbreak strains domestic politics...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211228012839-frkua</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (PIX):Australia COVID numbers surge as Omicron outbreak strains domestic politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC investigating 70 cruise ships hit by cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211227170451-66k33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CDC-CRUISESHIP (URGENT):U.S. CDC investigating nearly 70 cruise ships hit by COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asks judge to define 'enticement'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211227161117-fuxet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Jury in Ghislaine Maxwell sex abuse case asks judge to define 'enticement'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
