<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Justin Bieber Files $20M Defamation Suit Over Sexual Assault Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/justin-bieber-files-20m-defamation-suit-sexual-assault-tweets-1300641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is abundantly clear that these two individuals are trying to capitalize on the climate of fear permeating the entertainment industry," writes attorney Martin Singer in the complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes DC statehood bill...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/congress/2020/06/intense-house-debate-precedes-vote-on-bill-to-make-d-c-51st-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. House on Friday approved legislation to make D.C. the 51st state in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio says 'very substantial' cuts coming to NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/26/de-blasio-says-very-substantial-cuts-coming-to-nypd-budget/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio said Friday that cuts to the NYPD’s $6 billion budget would be “very, very substantial” amid calls to slash $1 billion from the department’s coffers. “We’re working with the Ci…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi lawmakers voting to change state flag...</title>
      <link>https://mississippitoday.org/2020/06/26/lawmakers-plan-to-begin-voting-saturday-to-change-mississippi-state-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mississippitoday.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topless woman heroically saves family from drowning in rip current...</title>
      <link>https://www.cornwalllive.com/news/cornwall-news/topless-hero-jessica-saves-family-4258881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cornwalllive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Not all heroes wear capes, some of them don’t even wear bikini tops’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  Still needs more testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/26/coronavirus-contact-tracing-is-not-going-well-fauci-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci said he personally is an advocate of "flooding the system with testing, so you really get a good handle about what is going on in the community."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why your organs might reach 100 even if you don't...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200625-the-woman-with-a-100-year-old-liver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research suggests some parts of the body age faster than others to the point that they even outlive their owners. Could understanding this better help us to live longer?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ:  Reverted To His Worst Form...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/wall-street-journal-editorial-board-buries-trump-in-devastating-op-ed-hes-reverted-to-his-worst-form/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The editorial board began by joking that Trump will soon to rename "Sleepy Joe" to "President Elect" because Trump is heading for a "historic repudiation that would take the R</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans increasingly cautious as cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.ipsos.com/en-us/news-polls/abc-coronavirus-poll-wave-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ipsos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New ABC News/Ipsos poll data finds most Americans are wearing face masks when leaving the home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Looks to Contain Advertising Boycott Over Hate Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/facebook-looks-to-contain-advertising-boycott-over-hate-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc. is working to persuade its top advertisers not to pause spending on the social network, as it tries to keep a boycott from a handful of marketers from turning into a widespread revolt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 NBA players test positive in single day...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/sports/16-nba-players-test-positive-as-restart-nears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA and the National Basketball Players Association say 16 players tested positive for coronavirus in the first wave of mandatory tests done in preparation for the restart of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One hundred days of solitude...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/504474-one-hundred-days-of-solitude</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we get back to normal, we remember the first shelter-in-place order from California on March 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLINS:  Macho bullshit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/504606-trump-world-boils-over-as-campaign-hits-skids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s allies are urging him to change his tone and key figures in the campaign’s orbit are pointing fingers over who is to blame for the president’s spiraling poll numbers with just over four months to go until Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls him 'child' who won't stop 'whining'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1041158/joe-biden-rips-donald-trump-child-whining/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden slammed Donald Trump’s coronavirus response and likened him to a “whining child” in an outrageous attack. Biden issued a scathing critique of the President during his sp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RE-LOCKS IN TEXAS</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2020/06/26/texas-bars-restaurants-coronavirus-greg-abbott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moves, announced Friday morning, represent Abbott's most dramatic action yet in response a surge in cases after he allowed businesses to reopen in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW PEAK FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/coronavirus/os-ne-florida-coronavirus-friday-june-26-20200626-cmqby4cnujhuznw2k4ui3cy4pa-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Department of Health reported 8,942 new coronavirus cases, shattering the previous high day for positive COVID-19 infections made just two days earlier. The state death toll also climbed by 33 to 3,366. The state is also halting all on-site alcohol consumption at bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARBOROUGH: Tanking on Purpose?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/scarborough-suggests-trump-is-tanking-on-purpose-looks-like-a-deliberate-attempt-to-drive-his-campaign-into-the-ground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Scarborough believes that President Donald Trump could be taking a dive in the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Crashing and burning...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/921970/trump-crashing-burning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's re-election campaign is shaping up to be a historic disaster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City police chief blames Cartel for assassination attempt...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626143847-rl10g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Mexico City police chief shot in assassination attempt, blames drug cartel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Married 53 Years Die Less Than Hour Apart...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/06/25/fort-worth-couple-married-53-years-dies-coronavirus-hour-apart-holding-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“My parents are just normal people, but now the whole world knows their story,” said their son Tim Tarpley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says he would use federal power to require masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e4871debaa7151780768bb301152caa9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANCASTER, Pa. (AP) — A presidential campaign that has largely been frozen for several months because of the coronavirus is looking a bit more like those from other years. President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 is wily virus. Can humans outsmart it?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/covid-19-is-a-wily-virus-can-humans-outsmart-it/article_b61b2ed7-a2c3-5f7a-b6a9-501d9e4f9c1e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To prevent a dangerous new virus from having its way with humankind, you might take a page from the Chinese warrior king Sun Tzu, and think like the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packed Bars Serve Up New Rounds Of Contagion...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/packed-bars-serve-up-new-rounds-of-covid-contagion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials are pointing to reopened bars as a cause of local spikes in coronavirus cases. Bars are tailor-made for the spread of the virus, with a cacophony of conversations that require raise…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES HIT NEW HIGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bc6644329af546be3b06763da8abd29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed new coronavirus cases per day in the U.S. hit an all-time high of 40,000 Friday — eclipsing the mark set during one of the deadliest stretches in late April — in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Disconnect Between Prices And Profits In Stock Market History?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/biggest-disconnect-between-prices-and-profits-stock-market-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Leaving and not coming back': African Americans head overseas...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2020/06/26/blaxit-black-americans-leave-us-escape-racism-build-lives-abroad/3234129001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling cornered and powerless in the face of persistent racial and economic struggles in the USA, some Black Americans decide to settle abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Shadow Campaign for VP...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/06/kamala-harris-shadow-campaign-vice-president/613225/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from California seems like the obvious choice to be Joe Biden’s running mate. So why is she keeping mum about her thinking?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamers Muzzling Controversial Documentaries?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/are-streamers-muzzling-controversial-docs-1299790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half a dozen hot-button docs have been pulled from platforms or dropped by digital distributors in the past year, angering filmmakers and viewers: "People do not like to be told they cannot see a film."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Male #MeToo Stigma and Fear of Coming Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/hollywoods-male-metoo-stigma-fear-coming-forward-1299702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two years into the movement, male victims grapple with consequences after speaking out, from mockery to job offers drying up: "I've never been so vulnerable in my life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporations grapple with slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/corporations-slavery-reparations-d2bca054-cf0a-4fa7-af6e-10490a49e308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reparations debate has moved from the political realm to the corporate one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm young Black man who used to oppose Black Lives Matter'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200625151308-mzg0y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The #BlackLivesMatter movement opened my eyes to the extent of anti-Black racism in the United States today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Venezuelans take extraordinary steps to beat water shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a883de87f3cd5a5da370080cd3200012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela’s economic collapse has left most homes without reliable running water, so Caracas resident Iraima Moscoso saw water pooling inside an abandoned construction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama ICU beds 82% full...</title>
      <link>https://abc3340.com/news/local/82-of-alabamas-icu-beds-full-as-covid-19-cases-soar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc3340.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the last 24 hours, the state of Alabama&amp;rsquo;s seen a record increase in COVID-19 cases with more than 1,100 cases added in a single day. UAB&amp;rsquo;s Dr. Jeanne Marazzo attributes the surge to the relaxation in people&amp;rsquo;s efforts to social distance and wear masks. &amp;ldquo;We are giving the virus more of an opportunity to jump from one person to another,&amp;rdquo; she said. 82 percent of Alabama&amp;rsquo;s ICU beds are now full, according to Dr. Don Williamson with Alabama&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't be a sheep': Sheriffs rebel against masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Don-t-be-a-sheep-Sheriffs-rebel-against-new-15368271.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after Gov. Jay Inslee, D, ordered Washington state residents to cover their faces in public, a Republican sheriff in a rural swath of the state's southwest suggested they should be doing no such thing.  "Here's what I say," Lewis County Sheriff Robert Snaza told the crowd outside a church Tuesday, carrying a megaphone and sporting his green and beige uniform but no face mask. "Don't be a sheep."  Few of the people cheering on Snaza covered their faces either, according to video of the scene taken by the Daily Chronicle of Centralia, Wash. Indeed, the words on a billboard above the crowd seemed to capture their feeling about the pandemic: "Oh, no! A virus. Quick - burn the bill of rights."  With coronavirus infections rapidly spreading across the American South and West and more states making masks a requirement, dozens of sheriffs like Snaza are staging a rebellion against state governments. An adherence to their interpretation of Constitution, they say, comes before any kind of public health advice.  Since April, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has said people should cover their faces in public to stop the spread of the coronavirus, which has killed more than 122,000 people in the United States to date. But Snaza said he did not believe masks were effective, arguing they should be optional instead.  "My frustration is we continue to listen to the governor's requests without asking questions, without saying: 'Well wait a minute, there's the other side to this,' " Snaza told Oregon Public Broadcasting.  He is not alone. In Nevada and North Carolina on Thursday, multiple sheriffs said their Democratic governors' mask requirements were "unconstitutional and unenforceable." After five California counties ignored a similar directive, Gov. Gavin Newsom, D, threatened to withhold state funds. Another...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: India, China massing troops in border showdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-china-deployed-large-numbers-border-showdown-foreign-183951578.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India acknowledged for the first time Thursday that it has matched China in massing troops at their contested Himalayan border region after a deadly clash this month. The neighbours have blamed each other for a June 15 battle in the Ladakh region in which 20 Indian soldiers were killed while China suffered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major gunfight breaks out in upscale Mexico City neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626113001-dyamy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/:Major gunfight breaks out in upscale Mexico City neighborhood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car crashes deadlier as drivers speed during lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626112931-nf9qa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TRAFFIC-CASUALTIES (INSIGHT):INSIGHT-Car crashes deadlier as drivers speed during lockdowns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal raves take off across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626102955-g1xtf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LOCKDOWN-PARTIES (TV):As lockdown eases, illegal raves take off across Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Warns of Re-Lock...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/06/25/newsom-warns-of-another-shutdown-due-to-growing-coronavirus-cases-leaving-local-businesses-in-jeopardy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as businesses across the state are beginning to reopen, Gov. Gavin Newsom is warning of another shutdown if current coronavirus numbers don't improve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis council puts plan to abolish police in motion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/198e18397e404ef9411f2efcdf7754c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The Minneapolis City Council votes Friday on a proposal to change the city charter to allow elimination of the city's police department, a radical move supported by a majority...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New taxes coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Governments-eye-new-taxes-on-cigarettes-homes-15368171.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cash-starved cities and states across the country are starting to weigh whether to raise taxes on homes, cigarettes, local businesses and global tech giants, hoping to rake in new revenue that might help them close the massive budget shortfalls created by the coronavirus pandemic.  The increases that have been proposed - and in some cases adopted - reflect the growing desperation on the part of government leaders nationwide. Many have found that recent spending cuts, furloughs and layoffs haven't been enough to shore up their sagging finances, forcing them to consider more politically noxious and economically risky moves in the middle of an economic crisis.  "No politician wants to lead with raising taxes," said Mark Mazur, the director of the Urban-Brookings Tax Policy Center. "When they get there, it's because they've run out of other options."  Philadelphia increased fees on parking and raised wage taxes on workers who reside outside the city. Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot, D, said this month she couldn't rule out a property tax increase to cover her city's $700 million budget shortfall. From New York to Seattle, other states and municipalities have considered a wide array of prospective rate hikes in response major drops in once-reliable sources of income - and months of failed attempts to get Congress to authorize more federal aid.  Nashville leaders even took the eye-popping step in June to increase property taxes by about 34 percent, a move meant to help pay down rising public education costs - and one that quickly sparked a public outcry.  The city's rates long had been historically low, according to Bob Mendes, an at-large member of the Nashville Metro Council who helped craft the budget blueprint. An increase helped pave the way for the city to close an anticipated $216 million financial hole in the 2021 fiscal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PASSION OF CHRIST' Screenwriter Teases Mind-Blowing Sequel...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/entertainment/films/1300833/Passion-of-the-Christ-2-Resurrection-screenwriter-Randall-Wallace-Mel-Gibson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PASSION OF THE CHRIST 2 screenwriter Randall Wallace has shared another update on Mel Gibson's biblical sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No amount of money' can undo damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8456819/Trump-family-say-no-money-undo-damage-Mary-Trumps-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their application for a temporary restraining order, the Trumps said that they would suffer 'irreparable harm' if Mary's book is released next month as planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL GATES: USA 'not even close' to doing enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/25/us/bill-gates-coronavirus-town-hall-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gates says the current coronavirus picture, both globally and in the US, is "more bleak" than he would have expected and warns that making people take the vaccine may prove more of a hurdle than developing and distributing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial-Recognition Backlash Brews After Fury Over Police Conduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/facial-recognition-backlash-brews-after-fury-over-police-conduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial-Recognition Backlash Brews After Fury Over Police Conduct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House set for historic vote on DC statehood...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/504632-house-set-for-historic-vote-on-dc-statehood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is poised to pass legislation Friday that would make Washington, D.C. the 51st state, the first time such a bill has ever been approved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Doomsday Bunkers Become New Normal?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/26/could-doomsday-bunkers-become-the-new-normal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first tenant for one of Frank Woodworth’s underground bunkers wasn’t a human, it was a seed. “A couple of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE: NO CHANCE OF RE-ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/11th-hour/watch/james-carville-there-is-no-chance-trump-will-be-re-elected-86029381572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran Democratic strategist James Carville says he believes it's more likely that Trump decides to drop out of the 2020 race than Trump wins re-election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music reckons with racial stereotypes and its future...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c34fd394a0275f0726cb5bb231f70833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — When country singer Rissi Palmer was working on her debut album, she wanted a song like Gretchen Wilson’s “Redneck Woman,” a song that would introduce her and tell her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Arizona lost control of the epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/How-Arizona-lost-control-of-the-epidemic-15367484.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX - A drive-up testing site equipped for several hundred people in West Phoenix was swarmed on Saturday by about 1,000 people, leaving some baking in their cars for hours.  A nearby testing station has already reached capacity for this weekend, appointments vanishing within minutes. Hospitals are filling up. Restaurants are again shutting down, more than a month after Arizona reopened its economy under the mantra "Return Stronger."  Arizona has emerged as an epicenter of the early summer's coronavirus crisis as the outbreak has metastasized, flaring across new parts of the country and, notably, infecting more young people.  Maricopa County, which includes Phoenix, is recording as many as 2,000 cases a day, "eclipsing the New York City boroughs even on their worst days," warned a Wednesday brief by disease trackers at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, which observed, "Arizona has lost control of the epidemic."  But physicians, public health experts, advocates and local officials say the crisis was predictable in Arizona, where local ordinances requiring masks were verboten until Gov. Doug Ducey, a Republican, reversed course last week. State leaders did not take the necessary precautions or model safe behavior, these observers maintain, even in the face of compelling evidence and repeated pleas from authoritative voices.  "We have failed on so many levels," said Dana Marie Kennedy, the Arizona director of AARP, who said her organization has yet to receive a response to four letters outlining concerns to the governor. She is working on a fifth.  Neither the governor's office nor the state health department responded to requests for comment.  At critical junctures, blunders by top officials undermined faith in the data purportedly driving decision-making, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO NOVEMBER ELECTION RESULTS FOR WEEKS?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/06/25/wait-weeks-to-tally-novembers-votes-one-ex-official-says-that-could-be-generous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Counting mail-in ballots in New York and Kentucky could take until next week, and delays could be longer in November with higher turnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT IGNORES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ignores-virus-spike-as-us-cases-surge-toward-records/ar-BB15YpgG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Sagging Popularity Drags Down Republican Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/poll-shows-trump-dragging-down-gop-senate-candidates/ar-BB15X7H9?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  BIDEN LEADS IN TEXAS!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/fox-news-poll-shows-biden-leading-in-2016-trump-states-of-georgia-florida-north-carolina-and-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News poll shows Biden leading in 2016 Trump states of Georgia, Florida, North Carolina and TEXAS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA mayor urges residents to stay home... </title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/la-mayor-urges-residents-to-stay-home-as-coronavirus-cases-spike/article_eec6bc87-1949-517e-a86e-d5e34d419621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Amid record-setting spikes in newly confirmed coronavirus infections, Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti urged Angelenos to continue staying home as much as possible — even as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN THE FAMILY:  Trumps LOSE attempt to gag Mary Trump from publishing tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/judge-tosses-trump-family-attempt-to-block-mary-trumps-tell-all?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Queens County Surrogate Court Judge cited “several improprieties” in Robert Trump’s attempt to block niece Mary’s tell-all, slated to be published this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady AGAIN defies virus rules to work out with teammates...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1039711/tom-brady-defies-coronavirus-rules-team-workout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM Brady again defied coronavirus safety advice to practice with his Tampa Bay Buccaneers teammates, despite the fact that two players recently tested positive for the virus. After getting flack f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden Now Leads in ALL Key Battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/showing-strength-with-white-voters-biden-builds-lead-in-battleground-states/ar-BB15WSW0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER 1.5 MILLION JOBLESS CLAIMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jobless claims totaled 1.48 million last week as unemployment related to the coronavirus pandemic remained stubbornly high. Economists surveyed by Dow Jones had been expecting 1.35 million claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noose and concern for Wallace 'was real': NASCAR president...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/noose-concern-wallace-real-nascar-president-194246795--nascar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR president Steve Phelps said Thursday that the noose found in the garage of Bubba Wallace &amp;quot;was real&amp;quot; and while the series&amp;#39; only black driver wasn&amp;#39;t targeted in a hate crime, officials&amp;#39; concern for him was warranted. Phelps held a conference call with reporters on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe COVID-19 can damage the brain...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200625214519-dg2oh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAIN (PIX):Severe COVID-19 can damage the brain, preliminary study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVERNORS BACKTRACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/778da4a2da7e5d9d12e6105c012b8cf9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The coronavirus crisis deepened in Arizona on Thursday, and the governor of Texas began to backtrack after making one of the most aggressive pushes in the nation to reopen, as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task force tracking big spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-says-coronavirus-going-away-his-own-task-force-disagrees-n1232061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New internal data obtained by NBC News show the White House is closely tracking big virus spikes around the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODEL: Phoenix could see 28,000 new infections a DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8459417/Data-shows-23-counties-seeing-uncontrollable-COVID-growth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A color-coded data map, compiled by spatial analytics company Esri, shows how the US is faring in terms of infections by tracking the number of new COVID-19 cases on a county level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Lines Form At DOLPHINS Stadium Test Site...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/06/25/coronavirus-testing-hard-rock-stadium-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Florida's number of coronavirus continues to surge, there has been an increase in the number of people wanting to be tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress test finds some banks could be stressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/fed-puts-restrictions-on-bank-dividends-after-test-finds-some-banks-could-be-stressed-in-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move signals that the unprecedented nature of the coronavirus pandemic, and the difficulty in forecasting what the future holds for banks, is making the Fed cautious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA TOO</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-06-25/florida-s-desantis-doesn-t-plan-to-move-to-next-phase-of-opening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to offer more 'context' on virus posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-seeks-offer-more-context-virus-posts-193736510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said Thursday it was looking to add notifications about the source of coronavirus-related posts and will warn users when they share stories that are more than 90 days old. Facebook Vice President John Hegeman said in a blog post the social media giant would be seeking to direct people to "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy investigating LSD ring...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/navy-warns-of-increase-in-personnel-taking-lsd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy disclosed on Thursday that it has seen an increase in its personnel purchasing, using, and distributing the hallucinogenic drug LSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan prosecutor pick ducks questions about Barr's job offer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/25/jay-clayton-sdny-bill-barr-339888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Clayton — the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission — made the remarks in a congressional hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbyist Jack Abramoff Charged in Crypto-Currency Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/amp/news/articles/2020-06-25/lobbyist-abramoff-charged-in-crypto-currency-case-u-s-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORAD intercepts 2 Russian aircraft near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://wpta21.com/2020/06/25/norad-intercepts-2-russian-aircraft-that-came-near-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpta21.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNEAU, Alaska (AP) — Military officials say two Russian aircraft were intercepted after they came within 50 miles of Unimak Island along Alaska’s Aleutian chain. The commander of the North American Aerospace Defense Command says Wednesday’s incident marked the fifth time this month that such an intercept has taken place. NORAD says the Russian aircraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precinct commander quits in protest...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/25/bronx-nypd-precinct-commander-is-quitting-in-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Brea, a Bronx NYPD precinct commander, is quitting in protest of how the department is handling police reform, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
