<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Claims roiling insurance industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ransomware-claims-are-roiling-an-entire-segment-of-the-insurance-industry/ar-AAL8Qpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyber insurance carriers are raising premiums and limiting coverage in the face of severe ransomware attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's 'Dr. Fauci' Damps Olympic Mood With Call to Ban Fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/japan-s-dr-fauci-damps-olympic-mood-with-call-to-ban-fans/ar-AAL7IeB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Shigeru Omi may invite comparisons to Anthony Fauci, Japan’s top Covid-19 adviser has shown little of his American counterpart’s flair for challenging politicians. That is, until he started suggesting banning spectators from the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No apology: Tavis Smiley makes comeback bid after PBS firing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tavis-smiley-business-lifestyle-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-c6d75e1491e93c96a7f0e64afcbb78c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Three years after workplace misconduct allegations cost veteran TV and radio talk-show host Tavis Smiley his job and a national forum, he’s ending his silence. Smiley, who continues to deny the claims of unwanted sexual behavior that led PBS to drop his long-running show, is attempting to rebound with the purchase of a Los Angeles radio station that will offer a Black and progressive perspective on the city and nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China disease expert says COVID origins probe should shift to USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210617012947-lpli3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONOVIRUS/US-CHINA:China disease expert says COVID-19 origins probe should shift to U.S.- Global Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustbusting Kicks Into Higher Gear...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/17/trustbusting-kicks-into-higher-gear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking up The Department of Justice yesterday filed its first antitrust action since President Biden took office, to block the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editors of Hong Kong paper arrested under security law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hong-kong-arrests-business-97e0fbed611073be258763dcf80c4b7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Hong Kong police used a sweeping national security law Thursday to arrest five editors and executives of a pro-democracy newspaper on charges of colluding with foreign powers — the first time the legislation has been used against the press in yet another sign of an intensifying crackdown by Chinese authorities in the city long known for its freedoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo snubbed COCA-COLA. Company's market value fell $4 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cristiano-ronaldo-coca-cola-market-value/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the end of Ronaldo's press conference, Coca-Cola's shares had already started falling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race for Global Tax Revolution Faces Hurdles in Final Stretch...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-tax-report/race-for-a-global-tax-revolution-faces-hurdles-in-final-stretch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s richest nations have set the stage for a revolution in corporate taxation, but they still have their work cut out to actually achieve that overhaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rattles Rate-Hike Saber as Price Pressures Surprise...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-officials-rattle-rate-hike-233000891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.Federal Reserve officials have said for months that price increases are temporary. On Wednesday, they weren’t so sure.“Is there a risk that inflation will be higher than we think? Yes,” Chair Jerome Powell told a press conference. He spoke after financial markets were taken by surprise when policy makers signaled they expect to make not one, but two, hikes to interest rates in 2023 from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Residence in Orbit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/17/as-astronauts-dock-china-takes-up-long-term-residence-in-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Chinese astronauts docked with the country’s still-under-construction space station on Thursday, beginning what their government expects will be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden drew line on Putin. Now it's Russian's move...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/biden-drew-line-putin-now-it-s-russian-s-move-n1271093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Biden turned the page from the Trump years. It's up to Putin to decide whether to abide by international norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abbott launches TX border wall project with $250 million 'down payment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/abbott-texas-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott on Wednesday formally announced that Texas will build its own border wall, as he accused the Biden administration of abandoning its responsibility to protect the southern U.S. border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline, bank sites go down in another major internet failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/17/tech/airlines-website-outage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines, United Airlines, banks and trading platforms suffered brief website outages after a key piece of internet infrastructure failed, sparking the second major interruption of the past 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed moves up timeline for rate hikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/16/fed-holds-rates-steady-but-raises-inflation-expectations-sharply-and-makes-no-mention-of-taper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the central bank gave no indication as to when it will begin cutting back on its aggressive bond-buying program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Delays, Cancels Hundreds of Flights a 3rd Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/southwest-airlines-delays-and-cancels-hundreds-of-flights-a-third-day/ar-AAL75qC?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Southwest Airlines flights were delayed or canceled again on Wednesday as the company sought to resolve disruptions from earlier in the week amid a pickup in summer travel. The headaches for Southwest, which is widely credited for pioneering the low-fare airline business model, began on Monday night, when a problem with a weather data supplier prevented the airline from safely flying planes. The issue was resolved within hours, but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Million Households Face Foreclosure, Eviction In Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/harvard-university-national-housing-report-2021-foreclosure-mortgage-moratorium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One homeowner in Alabama is five months behind on her mortgage and hopes she can strike a deal with her lender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Infertility Cure Closer To Reality After Genetic Discovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/infertility-cure-genetic-discovery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is shedding light on a key mutation which damages a man's ability to reproduce and the protein which can stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TAX LEAKS:  Manhattan DA candidate's drop before election...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/leading-manhattan-da-candidate-has-repeatedly-paid-virtually-no-federal-income-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tali Farhadian Weinstein, who donated $8 million to her own campaign, and her hedge fund manager husband paid nothing (or almost nothing) to the IRS four times in six years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: NJ Tops List Of Best States To Live In...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/06/16/new-jersey-best-states-live-in-wallethub/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wondering which states are the best to live in?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bin Laden niece protests summit with 'Trump Won' flag...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/558796-osama-bin-ladens-niece-protests-biden-putin-summit-with-trump-won</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The niece of Osama bin Laden on Wednesday protested the Biden-Putin summit with a “Trump Won” flag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds drops lawsuit, grand jury probe over Bolton book...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-lawsuits-entertainment-government-and-politics-0bc0171d2dc3392623ab18278a1a94ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department has abandoned its lawsuit against John Bolton, former President Donald Trump's onetime national security adviser, over his book that officials argued disclosed classified information, Bolton's representatives said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Breaking of Stephen Colbert...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/the-breaking-of-stephen-colbert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The demands of nightly doses of craven partisanship for year upon year have ruined him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No. 1 military recruit concern before heading to basic training? No. 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/06/16/no-1-recruit-concern-before-heading-to-basic-training-no-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bathrooms in basic training leave new recruits shaking in their boots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases of dangerous variant 'rapidly increasing' in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/16/health/us-coronavirus-wednesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As states lift more coronavirus restrictions, experts are worried people who aren't fully vaccinated could contribute to further spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC inmate elected to public office...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/16/joel-caston-dc-jail-inmate-elected-public-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate at the D.C. Jail has been elected to a seat on the Ward 7 Advisory Neighborhood Commission that had been vacant for a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Ransomware Gang Busted...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvz7x3/police-bust-major-ransomware-gang-cl0p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Ukraine announced it arrested members of the ransomware gang that called itself Cl0p, seizing computers and cash in a major international operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional candidate accuses rivals of murder plot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/15/florida-congressional-candidate-accuses-rivals-of-murder-plot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anna Paulina Luna obtained a temporary restraining order Friday against fellow Republican William Braddock — who she claimed was plotting to murder her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Force fires its first shots of drug war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-space-force-has-fired-its-first-shots-of-the-drug-war/ar-AAL6WrT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Space Force wildlife manager doing a sea turtle nesting survey found an estimated $1.2 million worth of cocaine that washed up on a Florida beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA Officer Speaks Out About Mysterious Illness 'Havana Syndrome'...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/ross-investigates/former-cia-officer-speaks-out-about-mysterious-illness-havana-syndrome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among those closely watching the outcome of the summit between President Joe Biden and Russian President Vladimir Putin is former CIA officer Marc Polymeropoulos, who believes the Russians attacked him with a secret weapon that uses high-energy waves to affect the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK launches passport TODAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/3094579/vaccine-passports-euro-2020-wimbledon-holidays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITS can download vaccine passports from today as part of plans to unlock capacity crowds at major sporting events – and eventually foreign holidays. A new “NHS Covid Pass” has n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside PFIZER race to produce world's biggest supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/inside-pfizer-s-race-to-produce-the-world-s-biggest-supply-of-covid-vaccine/ar-AAL6nYb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer had evidence the mRNA vaccine could stop the novel coronavirus. But it would do little good unless the company could quickly take new nanoparticle technology from lab to mass production, a feat never before accomplished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Prince Andrew why Scotland Yard failed to investigate Epstein, Maxwell?</title>
      <link>https://www.channel4.com/news/revealed-epstein-and-maxwell-implicated-in-multiple-uk-abuse-claims-over-a-decade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channel4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  People Are NOT Living Longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/aging-cheat-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers believe today's life expectancy has less to do with people growing older and more to do with fewer people dying earlier in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden Spending Plans Remain Popular; Job rating takes dip...</title>
      <link>https://www.monmouth.edu/polling-institute/reports/MonmouthPoll_US_061621/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.monmouth.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But presidential job rating takes a dip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California and Texas urge power conservation during historic heatwave...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210616152609-rkr1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/HEATWAVE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-As temperatures soar, California and Texas urge power conservation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobweb blankets cover Australian countryside after 'spider apocalypse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/3085332/spider-apocalypse-australia-countryside-cobwebs-biblical-mouse-plague/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLANKETS of cobwebs are covering the Australian countryside in what has been dubbed a “spider apocalypse” as the country battles a biblical mouse plague. Thick blankets of spider webs h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad's superplane has gold-plated toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-vladimir-putins-390m-plane-24332540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian president met his US counterpart for a summit in Geneva to discuss relations between the two powers - and both arrived in style</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Scientists Implant Uterus In Male Rat, Make It Give Birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/shock-study-scientists-implant-uterus-in-male-rat-make-it-give-birth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese researchers hail horrific science experiment as huge advancement in biotechnology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOWING GROWTH HITS THE STREAMERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/disney-netflix-slower-streaming-growth-1234968548/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A funny thing happened in the first half of 2021: The insatiable appetite of consumers for streaming video content began to slow down. “We had those 10 years where we were growing smooth as silk, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencers being paid to pump crypto on socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/15/kim-kardashian-west-charli-damelio-jake-paul-posting-paid-crypto-ads.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian West posted an ethereummax ad on her Instagram Story on Sunday to her 228 million followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Politics of race will destroy nation...</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/identity-crisis-politics-race-wreck-america-charles-murray/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of millions of these people live in towns that have no black residents or just a few and issues of race haven’t impinged on their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN</title>
      <link>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/lifting-the-mask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edwardsnowden.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edward Snowden on privacy, on liberty, on Substack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROM RUSSIA WITH SHOVE:  Summit chaos as press push each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3077651/joe-biden-news-vladimir-putin-meeting-geneva-trump-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden’s high-stakes meeting with Vladimir Putin erupted in chaos today as US journalists were apparently manhandled by Russian officials. The president and Putin exchanged a frosty handsh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash bag of pot flung off roof scatters on sidewalk, leading to frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/trash-bag-of-pot-flung-off-nyc-roof-scatters-on-sidewalk-leading-to-frenzy/3109344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A garbage bag allegedly full of pot that was flung off a Brooklyn rooftop in an apparent sale gone bad scattered onto the sidewalk, sending pedestrians scrambling to pick up marijuana earlier this month, police say. The fracas started when a 29-year-old man allegedly brought the garbage bag to a rooftop on Eighth Avenue late the night of June 1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas clears sprawling vagrant camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/city-clears-out-sprawling-homeless-encampment-in-northeast-dallas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sprawling homeless encampment was covered by a canopy of trees and located behind houses along Tres Logos Lane in northeast Dallas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires ravaging Montana...</title>
      <link>https://nbcmontana.com/news/local/infrared-maps-show-robertson-draw-fire-now-20000-acres-in-size</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nbcmontana.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overnight infrared maps show the Robertson Draw Fire burning near Red Lodge exploded to 20,436 acres. The fire was estimated to be 2,000 acres in size Tuesday, and the overnight flight was the first infrared mapping on the fire. The log&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the Robertson Draw Fire says they noted intense heat &amp;ldquo;throughout much of the perimeter, particular the western part and along the edges and in areas where the fuel type supports larger vegetation. &amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen Teams Up with KILLERS for 'DUSTLAND'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/16/bruce-springsteen-teams-up-with-the-killers-for-new-dustland-single-before-broadway-show-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen, as he promised last week, has teamed up with The Killers for a new single. “Dustland” may be the first of many different singles that Bruce is featured on this year i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow orders mandatory vaccinations after spike in cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/moscow-orders-mandatory-vaccinations-after-spike-in-covid-cases/article_b95feb60-0a7b-5a7d-92c8-da117310a274.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow ordered service-sector and municipal workers to get vaccinated amid a spike in COVID-19 infections, as the Kremlin denied any reversal in Russian President Vladimir Putin’s opposition to compulsory inoculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden goes head to head with Putin as tensions rise between USA, Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-prepares-long-tense-meeting-putin-n1270950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden said he plans to raise the issues of cyberattacks, human rights abuses, Ukraine and election interference with the Russian leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom sees his political fortunes rise as California reopens...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/newsom-sees-his-political-fortunes-rise-as-california-reopens/article_dad1bc00-511d-589b-8d9b-0f4ee7642907.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — As Californians streamed into Universal Studios behind him, an unmasked and unusually jovial Gov. Gavin Newsom declared Tuesday that the state was reopened and finally ready to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fingerprint, whisper networks, INSTAGRAM: How strippers banded together as cops tracked serial rapist...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/a-fingerprint-whisper-networks-and-instagram-how-philly-strippers-banded-together-as-cops-tracked-a/article_46dbc7be-9e9d-5597-ae50-fc5e119b4b23.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — After the first rape last month, women in Philadelphia’s sex-work and strip-club industries were on edge for days, sharing physical descriptions of the attacker on Instagram and whispering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summit chaos as press push each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9692605/Biden-Putin-summit-begins-chaos-press-push-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's and Vladimir Putin's summit began in chaos on Wednesday as journalists pushed to get inside to document the historic event with many of them being left outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Barkley says warned about on-air jokes: 'Can't even have fun nowadays'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/558689-charles-barkley-says-hes-been-warned-about-on-air-jokes-you-cant-even-have-fun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basketball legend Charles Barkley says he’s been warned about the jokes he has made on-air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-summits-health-coronavirus-pandemic-8126c24c511c258f4fc7e4f424bb8e70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — GENEVA — Peace activists unfurled a huge banner in Lake Geneva on Wednesday calling on the Russian and U.S. presidents to slash their nuclear arsenals. Campaigners in a sailboat spread the banner, reading “Peace and Security Through Disarmament,” in the water so that it could be seen from the sky soon before Russian President Vladimir Putin landed at the Geneva airport for a summit with U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snipers 'were ready to shoot' Greenpeace Euro 2020 parachutist...</title>
      <link>https://worldsoccertalk.com/2021/06/16/snipers-were-ready-to-shoot-greenpeace-euro-2020-parachutist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;worldsoccertalk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first website about watching soccer on TV and online. TV schedules, OTT news + interviews with soccer broadcasters. Founded 2005.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Breyer, retire!' Political storm forms around Justice...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/breyer-retire-political-storm-forms-020015121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure on US Chief Justice Stephen Breyer to retire is growing: progressive Democrats are anxiously eyeing his seat, Republicans have laid down the gauntlet, and issues from abortion to voting rights could all be at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Fed Planning Escape Route?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/16/is-the-fed-planning-an-escape-route/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connect the dots Economists and investors will scour the Fed’s policy statement and economic projections later today, looking for small</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China set to send first crew to new space station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-technology-business-science-15643befa1056aa5b8181ca83b98248c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JIUQUAN, China (AP) — The three members of the first crew to be sent to China's space station say they're eager to get to work making their home for the next three months habitable, setting up testing and experiments and preparing for a series of spacewalks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: Woman Beat Girlfriend Over Sleep Talk...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/talking-in-sleep-275930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 15--A Florida Woman pummeled her girlfriend after hearing the victim “talking in her sleep about an ex,” according to an arrest report. Responding late Sunday evening to a 911 call from a neighb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin summit begins with awkward photo-op...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9692273/Russian-President-Vladimir-Putin-lands-Geneva-showdown-summit-Joe-Biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;resident Joe Biden and Russian President Vladimir Putin have begun their summit at a villa on Lake Geneva after a highly-choreographed entrance that culminated in both men shaking hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide gulf, slim hopes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210616113115-sn8u5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/SUMMIT (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Wide gulf, slim hopes as Putin and Biden begin summit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL CARIBBEAN Postpones First Trips After Outbreak Among Crew...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/06/16/royal-caribbean-postpones-sailings-odyssey-of-the-seas-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean has postponed the first four trips of its new cruise ship after eight crew members tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parachuting protester crash lands European soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/greenpeace-bundesliga-europe-euro-2020-soccer-1bbd9b217acbbd976c725dce60befbcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUNICH (AP) — Greenpeace has apologized and Munich police are investigating after a protester parachuted into the stadium and injured two people before Germany’s game against France at the European Championship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 30 pelicans mutilated on SoCal coast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ca-state-wire-california-lifestyle-15630de4494f1656e2cbffe1b41c28fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — More than 30 brown pelicans have been viciously attacked and mutilated along a coastal stretch of Southern California, a wildlife care organization said Monday. At least 22 of the rescued pelicans had their wings broken so severely that bones came through the skin, according to the nonprofit Wetlands and Wildlife Care Center.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
