<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Adults who rely on socials  less informed...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/30/study-u-s-adults-who-mostly-rely-on-social-media-for-news-are-less-informed-exposed-to-more-conspiracies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from Pew Research makes an attempt to better understand U.S. adults who get their news largely from social media platforms, and compare their understanding of current events and political knowledge to those who use other sources, like TV, radio and news publications. The top-level find…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama half-brother rips 'cold and ruthless' ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/01/barack-obamas-half-brother-rips-cold-and-ruthless-ex-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “cold and ruthless” President Obama abandoned his Kenyan family in their greatest hours of need, according to a new tell-all by estranged half brother Malik Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico congressman positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801170608-50tlx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CONGRESS-GRIJALVA:New Mexico congressman tests positive for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George W. Bush Center hacked; Ransom paid in exchange for destruction of stolen donor data...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/aug/1/george-w-bush-center-hacked-ransom-paid-in-exchang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The George W. Bush Presidential Center was the victim recently of a hack attack that resulted in an undisclosed sum being paid to the perpetrator, the organization announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Misconduct, Racism Plunge Into Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2020/aug/01/ellen-degeneres-show-sexual-misconduct-racism-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Host DeGeneres pledges changes amid allegations of sexual misconduct and racism behind the scenes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen In Free Fall as Celeb Pile On Begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/08/01/ellen-degeneres-in-free-fall-as-celebrity-pile-on-begins-back-to-the-future-star-lea-thompson-says-negative-treatment-stories-are-true</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The title of this episode is “Everybody Hates Ellen.” “Back to the Future” star Lea Thompson backed actor Brad Garrett on Twitter in his sentiments expressed about Ellen DeG…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEAKENING...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-hurricane-isaias-saturday-update-20200801-juxrplkohrenhopqftwgcr4uqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Isaias weakened after passing over Andros Island in the Bahamas but it is still on course to arrive off the coast of Florida Saturday night, according to the National Hurricane Center’s 1 p.m. update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tammy Duckworth Is Nothing and Everything Like Joe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/01/tammy-duckworth-is-nothing-and-everything-like-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Tammy Duckworth, like the man she might serve as vice president, prizes loyalty in her ranks and occasional mischief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA: HURRICANE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d51505af1d8991f01538e0013eef7ad9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — Hurricane Isaias snapped trees and knocked out power as it blew through the Bahamas on Saturday and headed toward the Florida coast, where officials said they were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Rife With Sex Misconduct, Employees Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/krystieyandoli/ex-ellen-show-employees-sexual-misconduct-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-employees said one executive producer “had a reputation for being handsy with women,” and that another solicited oral sex at a work party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bari Weiss rips cancel culture as 'social murder'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/510115-bari-weiss-rip-cancel-culture-as-social-murder-on-bill-maher-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Times columnist Bari Weiss likened cancel culture to "social murder" on HBO's "Real Time with Bill Maher" on Friday night, arguing it isn't about criticism but "punishment."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Braun Defends amid Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/music/scooter-braun-defends-ellen-degeneres/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Thank you for all you do and keep your head held high," Scooter Braun wrote in a supportive message to Ellen DeGeneres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin protest over virus restrictions draws thousands...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/berlin-protest-over-virus-restrictions-draws-thousands-140750641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Loudly chanting their opposition to face masks and vaccines, thousands of people gathered in Berlin on Saturday to protest against coronavirus restrictions. Despite Germany's comparatively low toll, authorities are concerned at a rise in infections over recent weeks and politicians took to social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soars Back in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/01/after-plummeting-the-virus-soars-back-in-the-midwest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — First, the Pacific Northwest and the Northeast were hit hardest as the coronavirus tore through the nation. Then</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In coastal Maine, the perfect pace for self-quarantining...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/In-coastal-Maine-the-perfect-pace-for-15449055.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been an annual ritual for longer than I care to admit: summer weeks on the rocky coast of Maine. Much of the appeal, as with any tradition, is its changeless character. The precise times for high and low tides change each day, but in a predictable fashion. Although my children have grown from toddlers to adults - as old as I was when I first took them to Maine - the magical tide pools in which they used to splash are everlasting. The world might be going to hell, but summertime in Maine remains forever constant - "true north," both literally and metaphorically.  Until this summer.  Anticipation morphed into apprehension starting in March, when the local government of a Penobscot Bay island near my coastal cabin voted to ban all visitors, even seasonal residents who owned property there. The North Haven Select Board's order stated that "people who do not reside on the island full time may not travel to the island due to the significant increase in risk associated with the transmission of covid-19."  Although that order was soon rescinded, the governor declared that all out-of-state visitors would be required to self-quarantine for 14 days. Mainers' cordial, symbiotic relationship with so-called "summer people" now took on a wary, fearful tone. With my car's Virginia license plates, I might as well be Typhoid Mary.  Even getting to Maine would now prove daunting. Typically, I would take two days to drive from my year-round home in Virginia (often longer if caught in traffic turmoil around New York City or Boston). Spending the night somewhere new and different en route was part of the ritual, especially when the kids were young. So it was that we enjoyed leisurely and memorable hours at places like the historic Mohonk Mountain House in the Hudson River Valley and the Red Lion Inn in the Berkshires.  As with flying or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Holy land' under attack in another sign of Biblical apocalypse, preacher claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/holy-land-under-attack-another-22436146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian evangelist Paul Begley believes the world is coming to an end and that the escalating border conflict in Israel is an apocalyptic battle "between God and Lucifer"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgence Dims Crisis Recovery Hopes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/summertime-sadness-resurgent-virus-dims-crisis-recovery-hopes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summertime Sadness: Resurgent Virus Dims Crisis Recovery Hopes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans buying up personal bunkers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/01/why-so-many-americans-are-buying-up-personal-bunkers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Soulsby, 69, and his wife, Mary, were one of the first to buy a bunker at Vivos xPoint — the self-proclaimed “largest survival community on Earth” — near the South Dakota town of Edgemont. In 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman With Cane Attacked After Asking Customer To Put Mask On In STAPLES...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/31/woman-assaulted-at-n-j-staples-after-asking-customer-to-put-on-face-covering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say it started when a woman who uses a cane asked another customer to put on a face covering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro's erratic behavior making his military backers nervous...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/bolsonaro-s-erratic-behavior-is-making-his-military-backers-nervous/story-M672ojEcMf5rchNTHh6AzH.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over a third of Bolsonaro’s cabinet hails from the military, which now plays a greater role in government than at any other time since Brazil’s brutal dictatorship ended in the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT plan for preserving union: Drive Trump out by driving him nuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-Lincoln-Project-s-plan-for-preserving-the-15451080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your house is on fire. Do you care who the firemen are?  That is a central question of the 2020 election. Donald Trump has managed to do one thing no other president has done: Bring Republicans and Democrats, conservatives and progressives, boomers and millennials together in unprecedented numbers to try to defeat him in November. For Americans who believe the president is a raging threat to democracy, purity tests are out. Results are in.  Which explains the spectacular rise of the Lincoln Project, a group of Republican Never Trumpers who have moved rent free into the president's head. Their viral videos and tweets mocking his leadership, his intelligence and his patriotism - aimed both at Republican voters who are waveringand Trump himself - have attracted millions of dollars, via donors from both parties. More than 10,000 people showed up for a virtual town hall last month. Lifelong Democrats are organizing fundraisers for the project.  The "Mourning in America" ad attacks Trump's mismanagement of the coronavirus outbreak. "#TrumpIsNotWell" questions his mental and physical fitness. "Bounty" asks why Trump won't confront Vladimir Putin about U.S. intelligence reports that Russia offered bounties for the killing of American soldiers in Afghanistan.  The ads are slick, scathing and more shocking than anything Joe Biden's official campaign has produced. The newest release, "Wake Up," is a dark comic satire about a coma victim hearing about Trump's last three years. "Republicans, we need to wake up. This guy was in a coma. What's your excuse?"  "Donald Trump is so completely at odds with every institution in America and so completely at odds with anything that the Republican Party allegedly stood for: the rule of law, constitutional fealty, institutions, norms, traditions, all of those things are out the window," says...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Ellen telling execs she's had enough, ready to quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8581717/Ellen-DeGeneres-telling-executives-shes-ready-call-quits.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com can reveal that the host is telling executives at Telepictures and Warner Bros that she has had enough and wants to walk away from the show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trump says he will ban TIKTOK through executive action...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/31/trump-says-he-will-ban-tiktok-through-executive-action-as-soon-as-saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Friday told reporters he will act as soon as Saturday to ban Chinese-owned video app TikTok from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Ply With Alternatives to Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/democrats-ply-biden-with-alternatives-to-harris-for-running-mate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Ply Biden With Alternatives to Harris for Running Mate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coin Shortages Causing Liquidity Crisis at Laundromats...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/coin-shortage-u-s-laundromats-are-running-out-of-quarters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coin Shortages Are Causing a Liquidity Crisis at Laundromats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors ask for Depardieu rape case to be reopened...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prosecutors-ask-depardieu-rape-case-reopened-102455010.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris prosecutors said Saturday they had asked for an investigation into rape allegations against French actor Gerard Depardieu to be reopened after an earlier probe was dropped last year. An actress in her 20s accuses Depardieu of assaulting and raping her in his Paris home in August 2018. After she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia preparing mass vaccination for October...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801080054-o9lpq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-VACCINE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia preparing mass vaccination against coronavirus for October</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hear What Was Once Impossible? Musk's Mysterious Brain Chip...</title>
      <link>https://www.techtimes.com/articles/251499/20200801/elon-musks-mysterious-neuralink-chip-could-apparently-make-you-hear-things-that-were-impossible-to-hear-before.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What sounds exactly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data isn't just being collected from phone. It's being used to score you...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/Data-isn-t-just-being-collected-from-your-phone-15449776.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating in the shadows of the online marketplace, specialized tech companies you've likely never heard of are tapping vast troves of our personal data to generate secret "surveillance scores" - digital mug shots of millions of Americans - that supposedly predict our future behavior. The firms sell their scoring services to major businesses across the U.S. economy.  People with low scores can suffer harsh consequences.  CoreLogic and TransUnion say that scores they peddle to landlords can predict whether a potential tenant will pay the rent on time, be able to "absorb rent increases," or break a lease. Large employers use HireVue, a firm that generates an "employability" score about candidates by analyzing "tens of thousands of factors," including a person's facial expressions and voice intonations. Other employers use Cornerstone's score, which considers where a job prospect lives and which web browser they use to judge how successful they will be at a job.  Brand-name retailers purchase "risk scores" from Retail Equation to help make judgments about whether consumers commit fraud when they return goods for refunds. Players in the gig economy use outside firms such as Sift to score consumers' "overall trustworthiness." Wireless customers predicted to be less profitable are sometimes forced to endure longer customer service hold times.  Auto insurers raise premiums based on scores calculated using information from smartphone apps that track driving styles. Large analytics firms monitor whether we are likely to take our medication based on our propensity to refill our prescriptions; pharmaceutical companies, health-care providers and insurance companies can use those scores to, among other things, "match the right patient investment level to the right patients."  Surveillance scoring is the product of two trends. First...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASHES BAHAMAS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hurricane-isaias-strengthens-slightly-bears-084643752.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isaias was carrying top sustained winds of 85 mph (140 kph) and was located about 80 miles (125 km) south-southeast of the Bahamas capital Nassau at 5 a.m. (0900 GMT) heading northwest, the National Hurricane Center said. Its center was approaching Andros Island in the Bahamas and was due to pass over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Berlin against virus restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef70c1af702b89c23e71fcd843e63293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Thousands of protesters against German coronavirus restrictions converged Saturday in Berlin for a demonstration proclaiming “the end of the pandemic” has arrived just as authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Stone thinks he would be 'vilified' if he tried to make his films today amid 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-8579055/Oliver-Stone-thinks-villified-tried-make-films-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Oliver Stone revealed in a recent interview that he thinks he would be 'vilified' if his were released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25,000 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801004545-71yqc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-JULY (UPDATE 1, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-U.S. records over 25,000 coronavirus deaths in July</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for fourth straight day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801002615-f2jqo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-California, Florida report record increases in COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico eclipses Britain with third highest death toll...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801001214-yr80u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LATAM (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Mexico eclipses Britain with third highest coronavirus death toll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmLUULS9ja8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Acted Like the Virus Had Gone. Now It's Spread Everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/japan-acted-like-the-virus-had-gone-now-it-e2-80-99s-spread-everywhere/ar-BB17qNQd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland Security' had access to messages from Portland protesters, document shows... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/DHS-had-access-to-messages-from-Portland-15450458.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Department of Homeland Security official told a Senate committee earlier this month that the department had not collected, exploited or analyzed information from the electronic devices or accounts of protesters in Portland, Ore.  But an internal DHS document obtained by The Washington Post shows the department did have access to protesters' electronic messages and that their conversations were written up in an "intelligence report" that was disseminated to federal law enforcement agencies, including the FBI, as well as state and local governments.  In a letter sent Friday, Democratic members of the Senate Intelligence Committee asked Brian Murphy, acting DHS undersecretary for intelligence and analysis, about statements he made to committee staff on July 23 regarding the department's intelligence activities in Portland.  "You stated that I &amp; A [the intelligence and analysis office] had neither collected nor exploited or analyzed information obtained from the devices or accounts of protesters or detainees. Please confirm," the senators wrote.  A DHS Open Source Intelligence Report dated six days before Murphy's briefing to the committee shows that the I &amp; A office analyzed messages that protesters exchanged on the Telegram messaging app. They discussed which routes to take during marches and how to avoid the police.  The report describes the messages as "likely Portland-based encrypted messaging app users discuss TTPs [tactics, techniques and procedures] to evade law enforcement when being pursued." It also states that the information came from "a Telegram chat room," which it described as "an instant messaging service."  It's not clear how DHS obtained the messages and whether an informant or undercover officer had access to the Telegram group. Some officials familiar with the report, who spoke on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered Bolsonaro says nothing to fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/recovered-virus-bolsonaro-says-nothing-fear-001111535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off a bout of COVID-19, President Jair Bolsonaro said Friday nearly everyone will probably end up catching the new coronavirus, urging Brazilians to "face up to it" and saying there was nothing to fear. "I'm in the high-risk group," the 65-year-old president told journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Jumbo Jets Are Heading for the Boneyard...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-jumbo-jets-heading-boneyard-000002240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The queens of the skies have fallen on hard times.As Covid-19 has frozen the international travel on which they once thrived, double-decker, four-engine planes like the Airbus SE A380 and Boeing Co. 747 are more likely to be found in storage than soaring through the skies.Carriers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNHAM:  MY COVID HELL...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/lena-dunham-talks-covid-19-on-instagram-1203001407/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add Lena Dunham to the growing list of celebrities who have contracted COVID-19. The Girls creator and star shared on Instagram that she contracted the virus in mid-March. Her “Covid Story,” as she…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. outlook revised to negative from stable by FITCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/united-states-outlook-revised-to-negative-from-stable-by-fitch/ar-BB17qy05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden likely to name his running mate in second week of August... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-likely-to-name-his-running-mate-in-second-15450249.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden will most likely announce his running mate in the second week of August, again breaking a self-imposed deadline for unveiling the choice, according to two people familiar with his plans.  Biden, the presumptive Democratic presidential nominee, initially said he'd select his running mate by Aug. 1. Then on Tuesday, he told reporters that he intended to make up his mind by the end of the first week of August, which would be Aug. 8.  "I'm going to have a choice in the first week in August," he said, "and I promise I'll let you know when I do."  But Friday, two people familiar with Biden's vice-presidential search process said the announcement is not likely to come next week.  There are political reasons for Biden to unveil the pick relatively shortly before the Aug. 17 kickoff of the Democratic National Convention, since that timing could add some excitement to the gathering while minimizing the opportunity for Republican attacks. Some Biden allies have been urging him to make the announcement around Aug. 10.  The former vice president has said he will pick a woman to be his running mate. He's also said that he's vetting four Black women for the role, and those close to the campaign say the list includes Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif.; former national security adviser Susan Rice; Rep. Karen Bass, D-Calif.; and Rep. Val Demings, D-Fla. Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill., confirmed Thursday that she's been vetted.  Others believed to be in contention are Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., who has become an informal economic policy adviser to Biden in recent months, and Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer.  Making the announcement just a few days before the convention would allow Biden to build buzz for the party's quadrennial meeting, with less time for the Trump campaign to define...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball Tells Players Union Season Is On Brink... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/31/mlb-facing-shutdown-if-coronavirus-spread-cant-be-contained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commissioner Rob Manfred reached out Friday to union executive director Tony Clark to urge that a redoubling of efforts to adhere to COVID-19 safety and health protocols is necessary or shutting do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight still missing after US Marine amphibious vehicle sinks... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eight-still-missing-us-marine-amphibious-vehicle-sinks-232242800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight military personnel remained missing at sea Friday nearly a full day after a US Marine amphibious assault vehicle sank in deep water off the California coast during training exercises. Officials at Camp Pendleton in southern California said that one of eight Marines rescued in the mishap off the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz Goes To War With CBS Over Connections...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-alan-dershowitz-good-fight-lawsuit-viacomcbs-1203001249/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite having the Oscar-winning Reversal of Fortune made from his book of the same name, it seems Alan Dershowitz this week had the difference between fact and fiction painstakingly explained to h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden likely to name his running mate in second week of August... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/biden-likely-to-name-his-running-mate-in-second-week-of-august/2020/07/31/38dd92c2-d366-11ea-9038-af089b63ac21_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden first said he would reveal his pick by Aug. 1, then by Aug. 8. Now the announcement is likely to come later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Murdoch Resigns From NEWSCORP Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/james-murdoch-resigns-from-news-corp-board-over-editorial-disagreements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mr. Murdoch informed the Company that his resignation was due to disagreements over certain editorial content,” a statement said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY WORST MONTH FOR COVID HOSPITALIZATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1289327679666188288?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many People Hospitalized? Who Knows?</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/how-many-people-in-the-us-are-hospitalized-with-covid-19-who-knows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration told hospitals to stop reporting data to the CDC, and report it to HHS instead. Vice President Mike Pence said the information would continue to be released publicly. It hasn’t worked out as promised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi duels with White House as unemployment aid set to expire...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/31/white-house-democrats-unemployment-benefits-389540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negotiators remain at an impasse over a massive coronavirus relief package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burns, bloody wounds, broken bones: Injuries mount at Portland protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2020/07/burns-bloody-wounds-broken-bones-injuries-mount-at-portland-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks of restive demonstrations in Portland are leaving an indelible mark on protesters as the nightly cries against police violence and racism have often ended with an aggressive show of force by local and federal officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia patients to be sent to giant convention center...</title>
      <link>https://www.onlineathens.com/news/20200731/rsquosurge-bedsrsquo-virus-patients-to-be-sent-to-giant-georgia-convention-center</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — One of the nation's largest convention centers will reopen on Monday with "surge beds" to treat COVID-19 patients as critical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Murdoch Resigns From NEWSCORP Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/james-murdoch-resigns-news-corp-board-citing-disagreements-editorial-content-1305446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mogul sent a letter of resignation on Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future FITBIT? 'Drawn-On-Skin' Electronics...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/future-fitbit-drawn-on-skin-electronics-may-be-breakthrough-for-health-tech-industry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have developed a way to attach electronics to patients' skin. The innovative health technology is simply drawn on skin using a pen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax concerns worrying medical professionals...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/07/31/covid-19-vaccine-amazingly-close-why-am-i-so-worried/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The work to develop a Covid-19 vaccine has been impressive. But we don't need just any vaccine: we deserve one that's been proven to be safe and effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASS BUZZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/31/politics/joe-biden-running-mate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden heads into the weekend weighing the biggest decision of his presidential campaign so far, and people close to the process tell CNN that the former vice president is believed to have now begun to narrow his personal shortlist of potential running mates to a handful of women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbying intensifies among VP candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/nation-world/ct-nw-nyt-joe-biden-vp-choice-20200731-f54rxsdqxna4dkldadrfordymm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has entered the final stage of his deliberations about choosing a running mate as he prepares to talk one-on-one with the finalists next week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
