<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Families crossing skyrockets to record...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/10/29/1-1-million-migrants-crossed-into-u-s-in-fy2019-nearly-half-million-families/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apprehension of migrants who crossed the border into the U.S. reached 1.1 million during Fiscal Year 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXTREME WARNING: DEVIL WINDS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/getty-fire-e2-80-98extreme-e2-80-99-warning-issued-ahead-of-hurricane-force-winds/ar-AAJyr5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tick bite led to former senator's death. Here's what is known about virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-tick-bite-led-to-former-senators-death-heres-what-is-known-about-the-virus/ar-AAJwkbJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel tariffs were supposed to save industry. They made things worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trumps-steel-tariffs-were-supposed-to-save-the-industry-they-made-things-worse/ar-AAJy5Ro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump assumes Obama's mantle as the 'king of debt'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/467825-trump-assumes-obamas-mantle-as-the-king-of-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US national debt at $22 trillion has reached 100 percent of our GDP for the first time in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy upholds sentencing of Navy SEAL for posing with corpse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0af0e8bedab43d892d60bcc7d7fec72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The U.S. chief of naval operations on Tuesday denied a request for clemency and upheld a military jury's sentence that will reduce the rank of a decorated Navy SEAL convicted of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVIE OF THE YEAR:  Scorsese, De Niro and Pacino on time and 'IRISHMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b4ff3ea3207e41a3bef34393223f3a83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — They come into the room not like the moveable Mount Rushmore that they are but like three old friends, energized by being in each other's company. They are chatting about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration official says US-Mexico border crisis not over...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b923da1cb2254ad59846a033dd670be7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A top U.S. Border Patrol official has a warning: The crisis at the U.S.-Mexico border is not over. Even though crossings have been down over the past few months and news of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRUSTRATION RISES WITH ANOTHER ROUND OF BLACKOUTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91e853cb78654387becd90e1bf6bb486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN RAFAEL, Calif. (AP) — With no electricity for the fourth straight day Tuesday, chef and caterer Jane Sykes realized she would have to throw out $1,000 worth of food, including trays of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit ballot: UK lawmakers back December 12 election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ff4178638ac407c8dfe5597f81b6c36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britons will be heading out to vote in the dark days of December after the House of Commons on Tuesday backed an early national vote that could break the country's political impasse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House fires back...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7627521/Democrats-publish-resolution-stage-impeachment-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House blasted the Democrats' resolution that outlines the next steps in the impeachment inquiry as 'an illegitimate sham' that lacks 'any due process' for Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Spacey's sex battery case dropped because anonymous accuser died...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7627513/Los-Angeles-prosecutors-reject-Kevin-Spacey-sex-battery-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles County District Attorney's office said on Tuesday they were rejecting a sexual battery case against Kevin Spacey because the accuser has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian feminist's transgender talk stirs uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50214341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests are planned for the talk by the feminist with controversial trans views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says top replacement also killed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-baghdadis-top-replacement-killed-143811863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Just confirmed that Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi's number one replacement has been terminated by American troops. Most likely would have taken the top spot - Now he is also Dead!" Trump tweeted. Trump did not identify the person or give more detail on how he was killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Economy Might Not Sway 2020 Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/why-the-economy-might-not-sway-2020-voters/ar-AAJvIPK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New procedures unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-unveil-procedures-for-trumps-impeachment-inquiry-rebutting-gop-attacks/ar-AAJy7it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON! UK set for third election in four years to try to break Brexit gridlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/29/brexit-uk-lawmakers-agree-to-hold-december-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British people will vote in the month of December for the first time since 1923.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How millennials are changing funerals
...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191028-the-high-tech-start-ups-taking-on-frances-funeral-providers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As societies age, death will be a growth business. Now young French entrepreneurs are introducing new services to the traditionally conservative industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans defend key witness from attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/29/republicans-defend-impeachment-witness-vindman-061057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT: House resolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/read-full-text-house-resolution-trump-impeachment-process-n1073481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee will continue to take the lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dems alarmed: 'Extremely disturbing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/extremely-disturbing-top-dems-alarmed-over-vindman-s-testimony-trump-n1073371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman, the top Ukraine expert on the National Security Council, was set to testify he was on the July phone call between Trump and Ukraine’s leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY surrenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/sony-surrenders-in-the-streaming-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony to Shut Down PlayStation Vue Live Streaming Service</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanese prime minister quits amid anti-govt protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d17c97c531e4c5eb60215c5bd733858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Lebanon's prime minister resigned Tuesday, bowing to one of the central demands of anti-government demonstrators shortly after baton-wielding Hezbollah supporters rampaged through...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON spends big to remake Seattle's liberal City Council...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/434dc49c048545e682e260b5ad564961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Brian Sweeney has a long list of complaints about Amazon, from the way it treats warehouse workers to the low taxes it pays and its effort to win concessions from cities to bring in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reno's reinvention sparks fight over strip clubs
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2019/10/29/the-city-podcast-season-2-reno-strip-clubs-tesla/2452350001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Reno, a city known for vice, tries to woo big tech to town, a fight erupts over its future. It's the central battle of The City podcast, Season 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA sales tumble 39%...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-results-idUSKBN1X81NM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc's third-quarter revenue tumbled 39% in the United States, its fir...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle Class Addicted to New Kind of Credit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-29/america-s-middle-class-is-getting-hooked-on-debt-with-100-rates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families confront Boeing CEO with photos of 737 MAX crash victims...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/29/families-confront-boeing-ceo-dennis-muilenburg-on-capitol-hill-with-photos-of-737-max-crash-victims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen relatives of Boeing 737 MAX crash victims confronted the airline’s chief executive on Capitol Hill on Tuesday — with one demanding he look them in the eye and apologize. The…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT: House Dems impeachment resolution...</title>
      <link>https://docs.house.gov/billsthisweek/20191028/BILLS-116-HRes660.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;docs.house.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middleman helped Saudi give to Obama inaugural...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/inauguration/2019/10/ap-exclusive-middleman-helped-saudi-give-to-obama-inaugural/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case of Imaad Zuberi raises questions about the degree to which political committees vet donors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Alabama's near-total abortion ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-judge-blocks-alabamas-near-total-abortion-ban-172815261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Tuesday blocked a strict abortion ban in Alabama that would punish doctors with up to 99 years in prison for performing the procedure. The ban was set to go into effect November 15 but US District Judge Myron Thompson granted an injunction pending resolution of a lawsuit that argues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA to allow athletes to cash in on fame...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/325f23d5acc649b48c047b75a79e0e0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The Latest on the NCAA task force's report on the feasibility of allowing athletes to profit from their names and images (all times local): 1:30 p.m. The NCAA Board of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE resumes human listening to Siri audio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/078755dbec364b71a7b34abf63fb6284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is resuming the use of humans to review Siri commands and dictation with the latest iPhone software update. In August, Apple suspended the practice and apologized for the way it used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson investigation underway...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-29/getty-fire-arson-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials have not determined the Getty fire was intentionally set but have determined it did not originate in nearby homeless camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Layoffs at NBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nbc-news-digital-layoffs-3b007407-4f88-41e4-bfb3-eb7df0e5b148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News Digital is expanding its staff by 20% over the next year, while sunsetting a studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 67.3 million speak foreign language at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/record-67-3-million-speak-foreign-language-at-home-over-50-in-90-big-cities-59-in-la</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 67.3 million U.S. residents speak a foreign language at home, the latest sign of the growing influence of immigrants on American culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Funds 29 Journalism Projects That Swing Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/corinne-weaver/2019/10/29/google-funds-29-us-journalism-projects-decidedly-swing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same day Facebook launched its “News” tab, Google quietly poured money into news projects around the world. But many of these projects are aimed in one political direction. The new project, the Google News Initiative North American Innovation Challenge, announced 34 news projects to be funded on Oct. 25. Twenty-nine of these projects were located in the states, while the other four were in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Censoring Conservatives; Company Blames 'Moderation Mistakes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/features/is-facebook-censoring-conservatives-or-is-moderating-just-too-hard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company says it makes moderation errors. Others, particularly conservatives, see censorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturings Now Smallest Share of Economy in 72 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/manufacturing-is-now-smallest-share-of-u-s-economy-in-72-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manufacturing Is Now Smallest Share of U.S. Economy in 72 Years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor slams Trump visit to city: 'Insulting, ignorant buffoonery'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/467861-chicago-mayor-slams-trump-visit-to-city-insulting-ignorant-buffoonery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot (D) on Monday slammed President Trump's visit to the city as "insulting, ignorant buffoonery."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin Open to Looser Rules to Ease Cash Crunch...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mnuchin-open-looser-rules-backed-144300593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin is open to loosening financial crisis-era regulations that have stiffened liquidity rules for big banks to relieve possible cash crunches in short-term funding markets.Mnuchin said in an interview Tuesday that he had spoken to Jamie Dimon, chief executive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 14 Highest Peaks in 6 Months: Nepali Smashes Climbing Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/29/ex-soldier-climbs-worlds-14-highest-peaks-smashing-record-by-eight-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Gurkha Nirmal Purja completed feat in six months and six days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Berners-Lee warns power for good 'under threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theboltonnews.co.uk/news/national/18000579.tim-berners-lee-warns-internets-power-good-under-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theboltonnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inventor of the World Wide Web has spoken out as the technology behind what would become the internet marks its 50th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexy witch. Sexy nurse. Sexy Mr. Rogers? Inside Halloween costume industrial complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Sexy-witch-Sexy-nurse-Sexy-Mr-Rogers-Inside-14570780.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX - Four weeks before Halloween, Dominique Fiacco tried on the costume that its creators hope to turn into one of the holiday's hottest and stepped in front of the camera in a small photography studio.  The tanned, dark-haired model was the first to wear "Miss Impeachment": A clingy peach halter gown with a high slit, a low neckline and a pageant-girl sash across her torso. Also, a princess crown, clear plastic heels (sold separately) and, on a string around her neck, a finishing-touch accessory to take the costume over the top.  "Blow that whistle!" said designer Pilar Quintana-Williams as the camera flashed.  Of course there is a sexy impeachment costume. Yandy, a lingerie and costume company where Quintana-Williams is the vice president of merchandising, can hook you up with pretty much any kind of sexy costume you want - sexy witch, sexy nurse, sexy pirate, sexy Buzz Lightyear, sexy Supreme Court justice, sexy clown from "It," sexy pizza, sexy Minion. In recent years, the company has specialized in costumes with highly topical themes taken from politics and pop culture, so when House Speaker Nancy Pelosi initiated an impeachment inquiry against President Donald Trump, it took Yandy barely a week to turn around its Miss Impeachment outfit.  "Can you do a little bit of a surprised face? Like, I just won my pageant!" Quintana-Williams asked Fiacco.  "Like, I'm going to Disney World!" said photographer Brittany Gentile.  "Or jail!" added Quintana-Williams.  A perfect segue to Fiacco's next costume: Sexy college admissions scandal. It consisted of an orange prison uniform, but with leggings and a crop top. "INMATE" was stenciled across the chest, under the crossed-out text reading "Mom of the Year."  "Handcuffs or no handcuffs?" asked Quintana-Williams. "They're plain,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Lana Del Rey isn't trying to fool you...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Lana-Del-Rey-isn-t-trying-to-fool-you-14570718.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA BARBARA, Calif. - Here's a wild idea: What if Lana Del Rey is exactly who she says she is?  Her music keeps making us think otherwise. It's still too elegant, too plush, too slippery to be real. Maybe that's why, in concert, she likes to talk about a song after she sings it, as if to confirm that it wasn't just a puff of Chanel No. 5 in our collective imagination.  At the Hollywood Bowl this month, she performed "Wicked Game" with Chris Isaak. "We can't be in the middle of Hollywood and not hear the sexiest song of all time," Del Rey explained as Isaak exited the stage. She wasn't thanking her guest so much as expressing her gratitude to sexiness as a sound.  Has everyone heard "Norman F---ing Rockwell!" by now? It's the greatest Lana Del Rey album, dizzying and precise, unknowable and lucid, unprecedented while still feeling like more of the same, genius all the way. She's still blowing thought bubbles from the privacy of her mind into the slipstream of the American Dream, but this time around, she's pared down the studio production and cranked up the paradox. The more beautiful her music becomes, the stranger it feels. It's a triumph.  For years, the easiest way to reconcile the strangeness of Lana Del Rey was to tell ourselves that we were listening to a persona. Here was a remote pop star dream-journaling from a perspective too fabulous to belong to an actual human being.  Del Rey has rejected that idea from the jump. When NPR published a deep, diligent, largely flattering review of her new album last month, Del Rey took issue with its mention of personae and blasted back on social media: "Never had a persona. Never needed one. Never will." Gawkers are still gawking at that retort, but why not take her at her word? Back in 2011, at the dawn of her fame, she told Pitchfork, "I'm not trying to create an image or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACE SCANS TO WATCH PORN?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7621645/Australias-Home-Affairs-wants-people-scan-FACES-watching-porn-online.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's Department of Home Affairs has recommended checking ages by matching a person's photo with a document already lodged with them, such as a driver's licence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In manufacturing Midwest, signs of trouble amid good times...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/In-manufacturing-Midwest-signs-of-trouble-amid-14570918.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANITOWOC, Wis. - Sachin Shivaram, the chief executive of Wisconsin Aluminum Foundry, started to worry this summer when orders for his brake housings and conveyor belt motors first grew scarce. Within weeks, what began as mild concern snowballed into a business drought that has seen bookings plunge by 40%.  In August, Shivaram, 38, reluctantly laid off two dozen workers, hoping to recall them when the outlook improved. It hasn't.  "Things are not good. We didn't anticipate this level of deterioration," he said. "Orders are down across the board."  The sudden slump at this 110-year-old company illustrates the economic erosion that is challenging President Donald Trump's signature promise to restore a lost era of American manufacturing greatness. Even as the $21 trillion U.S. economy continues growing, and unemployment hovers at a half-century low, factory activity has contracted for two consecutive months, according to the closely watched Institute for Supply Management index.  Many consumer-goods makers are still humming. But manufacturers that serve global markets are being buffeted by trade wars and profound uncertainty over the future.  Already, plants in several Midwestern states that will be crucial to the president's reelection campaign are shedding workers. Manufacturing employment is down by almost 9,000 in Pennsylvania over the past year and 6,800 in Wisconsin. Michigan, Indiana and Minnesota also have lost factory jobs, though in Ohio assembly lines continue to add them.  The president's tariffs on China, Canada, Mexico and the European Union - and those trading partners' retaliation against the United States - are sapping manufacturers' strength, economists said. Through August, Wisconsin companies' exports to China of $822 million were 25% less than in the same...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global leaders, tycoons flock to Saudi 'Davos in desert'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/global-leaders-tycoons-attend-saudi-davos-desert-030536631--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia drew top finance moguls and political leaders to its Davos-style investment summit Tuesday, in stark contrast to last year when outrage over critic Jamal Khashoggi's murder sparked a mass boycott. Organisers say 300 speakers from over 30 countries, including American officials and heads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Legislates More Sleep For Better Health...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/california-law-earlier-school-start-times-more-sleep-better-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other states may follow California’s new law requiring later start times for middle and high school students. The new law highlights the importance of better sleep, which will once again be on peop…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Dealt Record Cold, Second Snow Storm In Days...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/10/29/second-snowstorm-denver-record-cold-weather-hits-sooner-than-expected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snow has returned to the Front Range on Tuesday and will continue through the evening commute. Meanwhile temperatures remain in the deep freeze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am a patriot, and it is my sacred duty to defend OUR country'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c45cb728edf84d96adf9a88e98979c51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An Army officer at the National Security Council who twice raised concerns over the Trump administration's push to have Ukraine investigate Democrats and Joe Biden, arrived in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer confidence falls for third consecutive month...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e38fbf8578948ce88c3af790acecd15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. consumer confidence fell for a third consecutive month in October as optimism about job prospects and business conditions down the road grew weaker. The Conference...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman fractured mother's skull during crucifix attack...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/texas-crucifix-attack-521094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 28--A Texas woman yesterday repeatedly struck her mother over the head with a crucifix during a domestic altercation that left the victim with a fractured skull, police report. According to c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhol trans, drag portraits to go on show...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2019/oct/28/andy-warhol-trans-portraits-tate-modern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exhibition will feature one of artist’s biggest ‘but probably least known’ series of works</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE SELLS 'JESUS' SWEATSHIRT FOR $250...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/kanye-west-sells-jesus-is-king-sweatshirt-for-250-sweatpants-140/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is $250 too high a price? No worries, you can get this other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supersonic car readies to crack 800 MPH in land speed record attempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1197017/bloodhound-british-supersonic-car-800mph-land-speed-world-record-attempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Bloodhound supersonic car has completed its second test drive across South Africa's Hakskeen dry lake ahead of its eventual attempt to smash the land speed record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Egypt mystery: How seven sinister deaths gave rise to Tut curse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/ancient-egypt-mystery-how-seven-20707986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new exhibition is bringing the biggest-ever collection of Tut's treasures to the UK. Dare you take the risk?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS FEAR 2020 WIPEOUT</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-party-2020-election-wipeout-house-senate-trump-3ca4a371-cdfb-4213-9ff0-2cf058aa7537.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is happening before public impeachment proceedings have officially begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movement grows to shut down extreme haunted house...</title>
      <link>https://fox17.com/news/local/torture-chamber-under-disguise-petition-wants-extreme-tennessee-haunted-house-to-close</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox17.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands have signed an online petition to shut down an extreme haunted house in Tennessee that they call a "torture chamber under disguise. " It's not the first time people have called for its closure, but "Shut Down McKamey Manor" has nearly nearly 30,000 signatures on Change. Org. Frankie Towery, who started the petition, calls McKamey Manor a "kidnapping and torture house. "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Have Ample Free Time -- Waste On Screens...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-excuses-americans-have-ample-free-time-to-exercise-but-choose-screen-time-instead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new study conducted by the RAND Corporation, the average American actually has about five hours of free time each and every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau victory prompts 'Wexit' talk in Canada's West...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/29/justin-trudeau-victory-canada-wexit-060634</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/wildfires-map/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A map of wildfires currently burning in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLEINROCK: I helped invent. How did it go so wrong?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/opinion/story/2019-10-29/internet-50th-anniversary-ucla-kleinrock</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When my scientist colleagues and I invented the internet 50 years ago, we did not anticipate that its dark side would emerge with such ferocity — or that we would feel an urgent need to fix it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pride of lions butchered to make 'black magic witch doctor potions'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/pride-lions-butchered-make-black-20748540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animals fed poisoned meat before evil poachers chopped their jaws and paws off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Woman Throws Scalding Water At Barista After Told Not To Use Bathroom For Over 10 Mins...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/10/28/arrest-scalding-cup-water-barista-modesto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested a transient woman over the weekend for allegedly throwing a cup of scalding water at a Starbucks Barista, causing first and second degree burns to his face and neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Poor evidence cannabis improves mental health...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poor-evidence-cannabis-improves-mental-health-study-223208216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with psychiatric disorders may want to pass on the joint -- at least until further research is done, a new Australian study suggests. The paper, published Monday in The Lancet Psychiatry, looked at 83 previous studies conducted over almost four decades on medical cannabinoids, including products</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and Cuba rebuild ties that frayed after Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d2e58fa79c2f406c9c126c4cd46f4ef8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — Over the last year Russia has sent Cuba 1,000 minibuses, 50 locomotives, tens of thousands of tourists and a promise to upgrade the island's power grid with a multi-million dollar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do you save endangered gorillas? With lots of human help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71df4e97bcba43769bcaaa7c125e2cec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINIGI, Rwanda (AP) — Deep in the rainforest of Volcanoes National Park, a 23-year-old female gorilla named Kurudi feeds on a stand of wild celery. She bends the green stalks and, with long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of kids watching online videos soars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d2694d32a7d44bf9619172d26c674da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of young Americans watching online videos every day has more than doubled, according to survey findings released Tuesday. They're glued to them for nearly an hour a day, twice as long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration at utility rising as blackouts endure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12e72ec86f92484296137cb45cb7e475</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA ROSA, Calif. (AP) — Millions of Californians prepared to be in the dark — some for five days, or longer — as the nation's largest utility said it was switching off power again Tuesday to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Screening Evacuated After Audience Member Shouts 'Allahu Akbar!'</title>
      <link>http://hollywoodreporter.com/news/paris-joker-screening-evacuated-allahu-akbar-shout-report-1250685 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No weapons or explosives were found and no one was said to have been injured, while the suspect was taken into custody and sent for psychiatric evaluation, according to a report in Le Parisien.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret X-37B spaceplane lands after 780 days in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mysterious-space-plane-lands-after-record-780-days-in-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unmanned orbiter breaks its own record for time spent in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON poised to escalate Pentagon 'war cloud' fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/467827-amazon-poised-to-escalate-pentagon-war-cloud-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight over the Pentagon’s $10 billion “war cloud” contract is entering a new phase after the Department of Defense (DOD) awarded the lucrative contract to Microsoft over rival Amazon in a shocking move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see hopes rise in Senate with impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/467828-democrats-see-hopes-rise-in-senate-with-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment is raising the likelihood that the Senate will be a real battleground next year, and that Democrats could regain the majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK set for third election in four years to try to break Brexit gridlock...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-set-third-election-four-years-try-break-113912078.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain looked set Tuesday for a pre-Christmas election after the main opposition Labour party backed Prime Minister Boris Johnson's push for an early vote to try to overcome the lengthening political deadlock caused by Brexit. Conservative leader Johnson -- overseeing a minority government -- is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden in Danger of Humiliating Loss in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-danger-humiliating-loss-iowa-080000058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden risks a humiliating third or fourth-place finish in Iowa early next year, according to nearly a dozen senior Democrats in the state who attribute it to what they see as a poorly organized operation that has failed to engage with voters and party leaders.With fewer than 100 days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Hooked on Debt With 100% Rates...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-middle-class-getting-hooked-100001049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.The payday-loan business was in decline. Regulators were circling, storefronts were vanishing and investors were abandoning the industry’s biggest companies en masse.And</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger winds whip California fires...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191029093503-ig38p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of residents have already fled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKE CHOKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-28/air-quality-getty-fire-california-smoke</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke from the Getty and Kincade fires are polluting the air in California's two biggest cities, closing schools and adding to disruptions caused by blazes and power outages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narcissists 'happier than most people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/education-50184281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They might be shameless attention-seekers but narcissists are also likely to be happier people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspirin 'better than antidepressants'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/anti-inflammatory-drugs-ibuprofen-aspirin-233000216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-inflammatory drugs like ibuprofen and aspirin can battle major depression effectively and could be a safer alternative than antidepressants, a major new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 years after internet conception, dark side stirs fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/50-years-internet-conception-dark-side-stirs-fear-093822748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 29, 1969, professor Leonard Kleinrock and a team at the University of California at Los Angeles got a computer to "talk" to a machine in what is now known as Silicon Valley. As UCLA marks the anniversary, Kleinrock is opening a new lab devoted to all things related to the internet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden of Eden in Africa: Humanity's first home traced to Botswana...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/garden-of-eden-in-africa-humanitys-first-home-traced-to-botswana-study-11847991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study provides a window into the first 100,000 years of the history of modern humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7623693/AP-PHOTOS-Wildfires-batter-northern-southern-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildfire on Los Angeles' wealthy west side destroyed several homes and forced thousands to flee early Monday, while a blaze in Northern doubled in size.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfires continue in LA, burn in wine country...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Southern-California-Wildfires-205975171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate rejects Rand Paul effort to cut spending...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/floor-action/senate/467817-senate-rejects-paul-effort-to-cut-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Monday rejected an effort by Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLUTEN FREE:  Winter-Wheat Acres Set to Drop to Lowest in 110 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-winter-wheat-acres-set-214215235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- America’s bread basket looks like it’s going gluten free: Dogged by lower prices and tepid demand, U.S. wheat farmers are poised to plant the fewest acres of winter varieties in 110 years.That’s according to a Bloomberg survey. Analysts are predicting another year of declines for acreage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities flee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/463dbdf2973a4fe9a4578f3b416b55fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A wildfire swept through the star-studded hills of Los Angeles on Monday, destroying several large homes and forcing LeBron James and thousands of others to flee. Meanwhile, a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
