<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Autopsy done...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/investigations/after-autopsy-cause-jeffrey-epstein-s-death-awaits-further-information-n1041216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The financier was found unresponsive Saturday in his jail cell in Manhattan, where he was being held on federal sex trafficking charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein kept detailed diaries which could haunt powerful friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9702330/jeffrey-epstein-diaries-prince-andrew-donald-trump-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein kept “meticulously detailed” diaries of his friendships which could come back to haunt his powerful pals, reports claim. The billionaire paedo, who died from an apparent suicide on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choose your own reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/11/opinion/jeffrey-epstein-suicide-conspiracies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With each news cycle, the false-information system grows more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens to Epstein's money and homes now? Can feds seize everything?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/what-happens-to-jeffrey-epstein-s-money-and-homes-now/article_d7931aa7-ff5c-54ec-9d39-a8e0a882d40f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Jeffrey Epstein’s apparent suicide is a significant obstacle for federal prosecutors, who spent months painstakingly building a case against the multimillionaire who was charged in July with in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Republicans in Congress bolting for exits?</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/elections-2020/2019/08/09/many-texas-republicans-congress-bolting-exits-mean-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Four rapid-fire retirement announcements by Texas Republicans in Congress have prompted fresh soul-searching for a political party...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DONE IT?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-death-apparent-suicide-inspires-conspiracy-theories-2019-08-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online theorists Saturday quickly offered unsubstantiated speculation — including some retweeted by President Trump — that Epstein's death wasn't a suicide, or it was faked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO VIDEO </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/11/theres-no-video-of-jeffrey-epsteins-apparent-suicide-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no surveillance video of the incident during which Jeffrey Epstein apparently hanged himself in a federal lockup in Lower Manhattan, law-enforcement officials told The Post on Sunday.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican challenger Weld warns party of Trump's 'racist tirades'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republican-challenger-weld-warns-party-trumps-racist-tirades-193550990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He wants to help the working poor, enact climate protections and unify Americans, but 2020 Republican presidential candidate Bill Weld saved his sharpest talk Sunday for Donald Trump, branding his rival a racist who could destroy their party. Weld, a former two-term governor of Massachusetts, is perhaps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren wows in Iowa... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d34646b9511f4d119f7e1af4057d766e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — The chant — "2 cents, 2 cents, 2 cents" — started in the back of a massive crowd that packed sidewalks at the Iowa State Fair. Elizabeth Warren, basking in the spontaneous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  5 children killed in day care center fire in PA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c940d4b2544facaf60ea18dc03e0da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ERIE, Pa. (AP) — An early morning fire in Pennsylvania at a residential building housing a day care center killed five children and sent the owner to the hospital, authorities said. The fire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEADS MUST ROLL'...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/investigation-underway-after-death-of-jeffrey-epstein-in-nyc-jail/5457853/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Attorney General William Barr said the suicide death of accused sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein raises "serious questions that must be answered." The FBI is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci fires back at President: He will turn 'on everyone' and then 'entire country'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/11/donald-trump-and-former-aide-anthony-scaramucci-engage-twitter-war/1980716001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scaramucci calls Trump's trips to mass shooting sites a 'catastrophe;' Trump says Scaramucci doesn't know anything about him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed remains target as economy falls short of Trump's goals...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-fed-trump/fed-remains-a-target-as-economy-falls-short-of-trumps-ambitious-goals-idUSKCN1V10BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has become a jarring and frequent contradiction. President Donald Trump blame...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals rally round Prince Andrew...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7346077/Prince-Andrew-joined-fellow-royals-church-Balmoral-day-Jeffrey-Epsteins-suicide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew joined the Queen and his daughter Beatrice today at church in Balmoral, after his former friend Jeffrey Epstein was found hanged in his jail cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BLUNDERS PILE UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-gaffes-parkland-trump-467d4127-0107-4ca7-adf9-40e1937ca8c6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden called himself a "gaffe machine" eight months ago, and his slips have long been part of his persona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US gold medallists at Pan American Games face sanctions over anti-Trump podium protests...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/us-gold-medallists-pan-american-games-face-sanctions-173542304--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two US gold medal winners could face sanctions after staging dramatic podium protests against US President Donald Trump at the Pan American Games in Lima. Gwen Berry stunned the crowd when she raised a clenched right fist on the podium and bowed her head as the US national anthem closed her gold medal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fencer Kneels...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-olympic-fencer-kneels-national-145909463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may face disciplinary action from the U.S. Olympic Committee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's Salvini Tells Richard Gere to Take Stranded Migrants to Hollywood on his Jet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-star-gere-speaks-support-113740190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood star Richard Gere on Saturday urged the Italian government to stop "demonising people" and instead help migrants who have been stranded on a Spanish charity boat in the Mediterranean for more than a week. Gere, who visited the Open Arms ship in a show of support on Friday, joined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes at Temple Mount between Muslim protesters, Israel Police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed7127e96f18434599bb0b58b04dc84f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Muslim worshippers and Israeli police clashed Sunday at a major Jerusalem holy site during prayers marking the Islamic holiday of Eid al-Adha. Palestinian medics said at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEADS MUST ROLL'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b609668da05c4ac5bbc9aa50c9e6b6d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Investigators have long been digging into allegations of sexual abuse and conspiracy against Jeffrey Epstein . The financier's apparent suicide brings another mystery to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tells GOOGLE not to advertise "illegal" events after election protests...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190811132824-4jt3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/PROTESTS-GOOGLE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia tells Google not to advertise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia floating nuke plant alarms Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/11/akademik-lomonosov-russia-floating-nuclear-power-p/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russia-designed floating nuclear power plant has begun its journey through the Arctic Ocean, causing concerns in Alaska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  'HIS LIFE IS DEFINITELY IN JEOPARDY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9605078/jeffrey-epsteins-life-in-jeopardy-pals-dont-want-secrets-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s life may be in danger as his powerful pals do not want him to reveal their secrets, his victims’ lawyer has claimed. Spencer Kuvin, who represents three of the billion…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: BIGGEST BOMBSHELLS IN EPSTEIN DOCS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-biggest-bombshells-in-newly-unsealed-jeffrey-epstein-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 2,000 pages were released Friday about the notorious sex offender and his girlfriend, who is accused of procuring young girls for his abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSPIRACIES ERUPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/conspiracy-theories-erupt-after-jeffrey-epsteins-death </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtags were out in force Saturday morning, and President Trump had joined in to retweet the theories by the evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Italy's 'Orgy Island' with dark history of lavish sex parties and murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-italys-orgy-island-dark-18876174</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zannone, which sits off the west coast of Italy between Naples and Rome, was owned by an aristocrat and his actress wife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDS 'DID NOT CHECK CELL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7345589/Epsteins-guards-didnt-follow-procedure-check-cell-30-minutes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former financier, 66, was found hanging in his prison cell shortly before 7am, and was rushed to nearby New York Presbyterian-Lower Manhattan hospital where he was pronounced dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ClintonBodyCount vs. #TrumpBodyCount...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-retweets-conspiracy-post-tying-Clintons-to-14295776.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEWATER, N.J. - President Donald Trump used his Twitter account Saturday to spread an evidence-free conspiracy theory about the death of Jeffrey Epstein, a wealthy and politically connected financier who had been facing multiple charges of sex trafficking involving underage girls.  Trump's own Justice Department announced that Epstein, who was being held in a federal corrections facility, died by "apparent suicide."  But Trump appeared to disregard the statements from within his administration, instead retweeting a message from conservative actor and comedian Terrence Williams, who suggested that Epstein's death might be tied to former president Bill Clinton. Williams also questioned how Epstein could have died by suicide if he had been on suicide watch.  The claim is completely unsubstantiated, and federal officials say Epstein was not on suicide watch at the time of his death. He had been placed on suicide watch last month but then taken off within a week, according to a person familiar with the matter.  White House officials did not immediately return a request for a comment on why Trump was spreading the conspiracy theory. A Justice Department spokeswoman declined to comment on the president's retweet.  A Clinton spokesman responded on Twitter: "Ridiculous, and of course not true - and Donald Trump knows it. Has he triggered the 25th Amendment yet?"  On Saturday, Sen. Marco Rubio, R-Fla., warned against embracing conspiracy theories.  While scrutiny of Epstein's apparent suicide is "warranted," Rubio said, he added: "the immediate rush to spread conspiracy theories about someone on the 'other side' of partisan divide having him killed illustrates why our society is so vulnerable to foreign disinformation &amp; influence efforts."  Still, Trump's retweet will surely...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN FOUND DEAD IN CELL</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/10/heads-must-roll-outrage-at-how-high-security-jail-could-let-jeffrey-epstein-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Every single person in the Justice Department — from your Main Justice headquarters staff all the way to the night-shift jailer — knew that this man was a suicide risk, and that his dark secrets c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Inmate: 'No Way' He Killed Himself...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/10/former-mcc-inmate-theres-no-way-jeffrey-epstein-killed-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former inmate of the Metropolitan Correction Center in lower Manhattan, where Jeffery Epstein was found unresponsive Saturday, and declared dead at a hospital of an apparent suicide, has claimed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSAL Scraps 'HUNT' Release Following Gun Violence Uproar...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/the-hunt-release-pulled-mass-shootings-donald-trump-hollywood-1202665785/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal will not be releasing Blumhouse’s The Hunt on September 27 as planned. Deadline hears that a collective decision was made by Universal leadership, led by Donna Langley, with The Hun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth MacFarlane quietly becomes major Hollywood political donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-08-10/seth-macfarlane-has-quietly-become-one-of-hollywoods-biggest-political-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Family Guy" and "American Dad!" creator has given $4.6 million to Democrats, making him one of largest political donors of his generation in Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety simmers as mass shootings loom any time, anywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/08/11/mass-shooting-anxiety-stress-america-gun-violence/1938509001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It could happen to anybody anywhereÂ you go now," says Lee Dorchak Sr., a Warren man who was shot in the leg in a 2017 Las Vegas massacre that killed 58.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit rewind: SONY Walkman triggers nostalgia on 40th birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190811-hit-rewind-sony-walkman-triggers-nostalgia-40th-birthday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hit rewind: Sony Walkman triggers nostalgia on 40th birthday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking moment TESLA erupts in flames, explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7346215/Tesla-car-erupts-flames-autopilot-failure-saw-driver-plough-truck-Moscow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexey Tretiyakov, 41, was driving with his children on the Moscow ring road when his Tesla Mark 3 ploughed into the back of a parked tow truck and exploded into flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside most intact Colorado ghost town...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/life/style/colorado-guide/this-colorado-ghost-town-is-one-of-the-most-intact-in-the-state/73-aee08db9-773a-4f31-a71c-b74583b24b56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animas Forks started like many other ghost towns: with mining. It was once buried under so much snow that residents had to dig tunnels from building to building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California city denies Straight Pride rally permit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/11/modesto-california-denies-straight-pride-rally-per/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Straight Pride Coalition says it supports heterosexuality, Christianity and white contributions to Western civilization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern cave man offers 'Neanderthal' survival courses...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190811-modern-cave-man-offers-neanderthal-survival-courses-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern cave man offers 'Neanderthal' survival courses in Italy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang goes after 'fat' slob Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7345213/Andrew-Yang-calls-Donald-Trump-fat-slob-challenges-push-contest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang tore into Donald Trump, calling him fat and a slob who cheats at golf, challenged him to a push-up contest and said America would love to see the president pass out trying to run a mile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea-to-Sky gondola cable deliberately cut: 'Crime scene'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/sea-to-sky-gondola-in-squamish-closed-after-cable-snaps-1.5242787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RCMP says they believe someone deliberately cut the cables of the Sea-To-Sky gondola in Squamish, B.C., which crashed into the ground overnight Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versace apologizes after T-shirt triggers fierce criticism in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-versace-idUSKCN1V10BK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian luxury label Versace and its artistic director Donatella Versace apologi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Air: Shackled deportees, air freshener and cheers. USA's one-way trip out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ice-air-shackled-deportees-air-freshener-and-cheers-americas-one-way-trip-out/ar-AAFD1KW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police, protesters clash in downtown Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190811104316-2fmfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/WANCHAI (URGENT):Police and protesters clash in downtown Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes at Temple Mount between Muslim protesters, Israel Police...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/clashes-break-out-on-temple-mount-between-muslim-protesters-israel-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police use tear gas, riot control weapons on flashpoint holy site after worshipers make 'nationalistic calls' and riot; 4 cops, 61 protesters injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most overworked cities in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/10/us/us-overworked-cities-list-trnd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you live in one of these cities, it might be time to take a vacation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankruptcy filings rising...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/11/bankruptcy-filings-rising-across-the-country-and-it-could-get-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bankruptcies are back — flashing warnings that more Americans are knee-deep in debt in big cities like New York. While total bankruptcy petitions nationwide by consumers and businesses are still we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 players ejected after big brawl at WNBA game...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/sports/wnba/mercury/2019/08/10/dallas-wings-edge-mercury-game-dunk-near-brawl/1738616001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brittney Griner, Kristine Anigwe, four others ejected in Phoenix Mercury loss to Dallas Wings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE CONFUSION...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/456987-biden-mistakenly-says-he-was-vp-during-2018-parkland-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden said Saturday that he was vice president during a mass shooting last year in Parkland, Fla., even though it occurred more than a year after he had left office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taunts Bill Maher... </title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-labels-bill-maher-wacko-comedian-who-tells-so-many-lies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He is right about one thing, though," Donald Trump said of Bill Maher. "I will win again in 2020. Otherwise, he pays 95% in taxes!"</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
