<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHARON STONE: Cancel culture stupidest thing I have ever seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/mar/26/sharon-stone-cancel-culture-is-the-stupidest-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharon Stone gave an impassioned rant against cancel culture Thursday, saying people need to “grow up” and learn from each other instead of rushing to judgment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6,000 apprehended on border in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/6-000-apprehended-at-southern-border-2019-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people being taken into custody per day on the southern border has surpassed the number that Border Patrol agents saw at the height of the 2019 crisis during the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something Huge and Invisible Making Nearby Stars Vanish...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epdy8j/something-huge-and-invisible-is-making-nearby-stars-vanish-scientists-propose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars that have gone missing from the Hyades cluster may have been torn away by a dark matter monster with the mass of 10 million Suns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectacular fireball lit Pacific Northwest sky. SPACEX rocket was to blame...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/26/22351956/oregon-washington-meteor-shower-explanation-spacex-falcon-9-rocket-debris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most likely the remains of a Falcon 9 rocket</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Godzilla' monkey sent to FAT CAMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14466529/obese-monkey-godzilla-fat-camp-twice-size-junk-food-bangkok/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MORBIDLY obese monkey who ballooned to twice his normal size gorging on junk food has been rescued and sent to a fat camp. Godzilla, a three-year-old macaque, swelled to 20kg (44lb) after being t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ASTRAZENECA vax became political football and PR disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/mar/26/how-the-astrazeneca-vaccine-became-a-political-football-and-a-pr-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly accused of data manipulation by the US, AstraZeneca has faced unprecedented scrutiny over the past six months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Kinzinger: All We Do Is Call Other Side Douchebags...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rep-adam-kinzinger-says-all-we-do-is-call-the-other-side-douchebags</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once there was Ronald Reagan and Tip O’Neill. Who will bridge the political divide today? Rep. Adam Kinzinger comes on the latest episode of The New Abnormal to hash it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of Silent Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/03/psychology-of-silent-treatment-abuse/618411/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social ostracism has been a common punishment for millennia. But freezing someone out harms both the victim and the perpetrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS BURIALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2586018/brazils-300000-covid-deaths-genocide-chilling-pics-bodies-graves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL’s soaring Covid death toll has been slammed as “genocide” as chilling pictures show scores of gravediggers working through the night to bury thousands of victims. The numbe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans have dumped on the poor pigeon for too long. It's time to admire this fascinating bird...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/pacific-nw-magazine/we-humans-have-dumped-on-the-poor-pigeon-for-too-long-its-high-time-to-admire-this-fascinating-fast-quirky-bird/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We pick on pigeons, but we shouldn't. The unfairly treated, fast-flying birds are beneficial to other birds and, sometimes, to us. And they're here to stay. Pigeons have become accustomed to living among humans, and the food they provide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23 travelers in USA monitored for Ebola...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article250234060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last confirmed cases in the U.S. came in 2014-16, when 11 people were treated for the deadly virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Drones Swarmed Destroyers. No One Knows Where Came From...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/a35926949/mystery-drones-swarmed-navy-destroyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy can't explain the bizarre encounters that took place across four nights in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley giants line up behind Newsom in recall fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/03/26/silicon-valley-giants-join-fight-against-california-recall-1369697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the message of support for Newsom doesn't mention funding to fight the recall, Silicon Valley insiders say that's likely the next step for many of the deep-pocketed tech executives who have written big checks in elections before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Green Energy' -- Might Be Ruining the Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/26/biomass-carbon-climate-politics-477620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biomass industry is warming up the South's economy, but many experts worry it's doing the same to the climate. Will the Biden Administration embrace it, or cut it loose?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA says Biden's lost it. Republican senators disagree...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/26/biden-health-republican-senators-477813</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven GOP senators who’ve met with Biden lately described him as cogent and well-versed on the issues they discussed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Has Charged 500 With COVID-Related Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/03/26/981598848/doj-has-charged-nearly-500-with-covid-related-fraud-in-the-past-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after the first major coronavirus relief package passed, the Justice Department has charged defendants over exploiting loan and unemployment programs as well as with fraud targeting consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle to control America's 'most destructive' species: Feral pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/article/battle-to-control-america-most-destructive-invasive-species-feral-pigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These “ecological zombies” will eat almost anything and can live almost anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Releasing Container Ship From Suez Canal Could Capsize It...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/releasing-container-ship-from-suez-canal-could-capsize-it/ar-BB1f0aBC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the global shipping industry bleeds $400 million each hour the massive Ever Given container ship stays stuck in the sand of the Suez Canal, an elite team of salvors on the ground in Egypt is facing an entirely different problem: How do you make a top-heavy ship stuck in shifting sands weigh less without capsizing it? “They’ll need a full survey of the seabed and canal bottom to see what the extent of grounding is,” Nick Sloane, the salvage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach charged spring breaker with inciting riot. His crime was playing music...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/miami-beach-charged-spring-break-visitor-with-inciting-a-riot-his-crime-was-playing-music/ar-BB1f0rLM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 26—On the second evening Miami Beach imposed its 8 p.m. curfew as part of a crackdown on spring breakers, an elite police unit crashed one pulsating street party packed with 400 or more people. Police reports describe an out-of-control scene after curfew in a residential area of South Beach — some people jumping on cars, others shattering glass, vandalizing property, trespassing, blocking ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran to give $1,000 a month to artists in basic income program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/san-francisco-to-give-dollar1000-a-month-to-artists-in-basic-income-program/ar-BB1f07r1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The guaranteed income pilot program will distribute funds for six months to 130 eligible artists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Warren clashes with AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/elizabeth-warren-clashed-with-amazon-over-unionization-and-said-shed-break-up-big-tech-so-that-it-cant-heckle-senators-with-snotty-tweets/ar-BB1eZtyQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren called Amazon out for exploiting tax "loopholes," opposing unionization, and "heckling" senators on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Revealing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/revealing-amazon-criticizes-warren-for-calling-for-breaking-them-up-over-snotty-tweets/ar-BB1f0pxH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail giant Amazon said Friday that Democratic Sen. Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts was trying to break up the company in order to suppress criticism from the corporation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS:  Masks and Hand Sanitizer Are Tax Write-offs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/taxes/masks-and-hand-sanitizer-are-tax-write-offs-the-irs-says/ar-BB1f05jT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Face masks, hand sanitizer and disinfectant wipes can qualify as medical expenses for tax deductions or can be paid for with money from tax-advantaged health accounts, the Internal Revenue Service announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CDC Director Says He Believes Escaped' From Wuhan Lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-former-cdc-director-says-he-believes-coronavirus-escaped-from-wuhan-lab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CDC Director Robert Redfield said he believes the coronavirus escaped from a Wuhan lab, a stunning assessment that echoes claims made by other members of the Trump administration, including Secretary of State Mike Pompeo. In an interview with CNN’s Sanjay Gupta, Redfield made clear he was expressing his opinion that the coronavirus, which erupted […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorologist learns home hit --  while on-air...</title>
      <link>https://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/national/article250228905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ledger-enquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five people were killed in Alabama on Thursday as severe storms spawned tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon criminal probe in NY heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Bannon-criminal-probe-in-N-Y-includes-embedded-16054913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - The New York attorney general's office has partnered with Manhattan's district...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piracy fears mount as ships take long way around Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-massive-ship-remains-stuck-in-the-Suez-Canal-16054898.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO - Brand-new Kia automobiles, cases of Heineken beer, live animals and billions of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USATODAY editor fired for saying Boulder shooting 'white man'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/usa-today-editor-hemal-jhaveri-boulder-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A USA Today editor announced Friday that she was terminated over a tweet she posted in reaction to Monday's deadly shooting in Boulder, Colorado that erroneously blamed a "White man" for the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant says it won't serve people who stink of marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/smell-like-weed-this-detroit-restaurant-says-to-stay-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upscale Detroit restaurant has a message for guests: Dress up and don't come in smelling like marijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite image reveals extent of traffic jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9405423/Suez-Canal-Satellite-image-reveals-extent-traffic-jam-stuck-ship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An image captured above the Gulf of Suez, leading into Egypt's Suez Canal, shows at least 50 large ships at anchor waiting to pass through the narrow waterway where cargo ship Ever Given is stuck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need to remove 706,000 cubic feet of sand...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/25/middleeast/suez-canal-ship-sand-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescue teams working to dislodge the giant container ship blocking the Suez Canal have failed in another bid to free the boat, according to the vessel's technical manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg pushes car mileage tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/26/buttigieg-says-white-house-is-weighing-mileage-levy-to-fund-infrastructure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg, the Transportation secretary, said a mileage tax could be on the table in infrastructure talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City newspaper sends warning with blank front...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Kansas-City-newspaper-sends-a-warning-with-a-16055276.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editors of Kansas City's Northeast News opted for an unusual choice for the front page of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA Editor Temporarily Banned for Criticizing Use of 'Tree' as Pronoun...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2021/03/26/wikipedia-editor-temporarily-banned-for-criticizing-use-of-tree-as-pronoun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wikipedia page for actor Keiynan Lonsdale became part of a fight over “preferred pronouns” due to a Twitter thread noting Lonsdale once suggested “tree” as a pronoun for himself. Despite doubts about Lonsdale’s sincerity, editors repeatedly changed the male pronouns on his article to “tree” this week until an editor sought a compromise by removing pronouns entirely. One editor who criticized the move and denigrated the idea of “tree” as a pronoun was banned for a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid 'showed the excesses of business travel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2021-03-26/will-business-travel-return-to-normal-after-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic proved how much work could be accomplished with a screen and an internet connection, much to the detriment of airline profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LULA: Biggest genocide in Brazil history...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/brazil-virus-deaths-biggest-genocide-in-our-history-lula-01616751604 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China flies at least 20 war planes in Taiwan airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-incursion-war-planes-taiwan-airspace-3d5994f1-71d1-41f7-a4c8-f825d6043262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the largest incursion reported by Taiwan to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Outbreak Rips Across Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2021-03-26-severe-weather-outbreak-impacts-alabama-mississippi-tennessee-georgia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homes and lives were ruined as deadly tornadoes and severe weather trekked across the South Thursday and into Friday morning. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strain to supply chains...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/suez-canal-blockage-adds-strain-083544394.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stuck container vessel in the Suez Canal, which has blocked the flow of goods through the narrow channel, will add strain to global supply chains already stretched by rebounding economic activity and tight shipping container supplies, analysts said on Friday. The 400-metres long Ever Given container vessel has been stuck in the canal since Tuesday, suspending traffic of containers transporting goods, parts and equipment through the shortest sea link between Europe and Asia. The blockage comes as shipments have already been disrupted by the coronavirus pandemic and a surge in demand for goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo testing story stirs controversy for CNN anchor...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/545063-cuomo-testing-story-stirs-controversy-for-cnn-anchor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN should investigate anchor Chris Cuomo and he should publicly talk about allegations he received prioritized COVID-19 testing — ordered by his brother, New York Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half billion vaccines given...</title>
      <link>https://sg.style.yahoo.com/half-billion-vaccine-jabs-given-124120477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 500 million doses of vaccines have been given around the world as of Friday, according to an AFP tally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*** This Place!' SOUTHWEST Pilot Tirade Against 'Liberal' Bay Area On Hot Mic...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/26/southwest-pilot-expletive-filled-tirade-liberal-bay-area-san-jose-hot-mic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines pilot departing Mineta San Jose International Airport has been caught on an open mic delivering an expletive-filled rant against the liberal Bay Area population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon accidentally funnels millions to Iran-backed death squads...</title>
      <link>https://prospect.org/world/how-pentagon-accidentally-funnels-millions-to-iraqi-militias/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;prospect.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked documents reveal that the defense contractor Sallyport enriched companies connected to Iranian-backed death squads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals stranded on 20 livestock ships...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/26/animals-stranded-on-20-livestock-ships-caught-in-suez-canal-jam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 20 ships stuck in the Suez Canal jam are hauling livestock — sparking fears about the animals’ safety on the fourth consecutive day of blocked maritime traffic, according to a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France steps up travel controls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-steps-travel-controls-virus-145916197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government warned Friday of increased police checks to enforce travel restrictions in place in Paris and several other regions as coronavirus cases continue to soar around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders joins union drive as clashes with AMAZON intensify...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-joins-union-drive-155219531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Bernie Sanders joined the drive Friday to unionize Amazon workers in Alabama as clashes intensified between lawmakers and the e-commerce giant ahead of a deadline for a vote that could lead to the first union on US soil at the massive tech company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things Just Keep Getting Worse for Hedge Funds as Long Bets Sour...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/things-just-keep-getting-worse-161340912.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In a year when mutual-fund stock pickers are shining, their hedge-fund counterparts are bleeding.After being burned during January’s retail-driven short squeeze in stocks such as GameStop Corp., now hedge funds are feeling the pain on the long side as well. A basket of the 50 most-popular stocks has fallen this month, while a group of the 50 most-crowded shorts gained, dealing a double blow to performance, client data compiled by Morgan Stanley’s prime brokerage unit show.As a result, the long-short spread, a measure of the industry’s above-market returns, or alpha, has worsened after a brief recovery in February. Down almost 11% since the end of December, hedge funds’ alpha is heading for the worst year since at least 2015.While Morgan Stanley didn’t identify any specific stocks, the latest hedge-fund filings shed some light on what positions may have added insult to injury. Churchill Capital Corp., a special purpose acquisition company, and internet stocks like Twitter Inc. and Zillow Group Inc. were among their favorites at the start of this year, according to Goldman Sachs Group Inc. These stocks are down more than 20% this month as rising yields sparked a sudden selloff in speculative names and richly valued technology shares.“The market keeps shifting every few days or every week,” said Jeffrey Kleintop, chief global investment strategist for Charles Schwab &amp; Co. “In many cases, hedge funds tend to be -- not all of them -- but they’re often momentum traders,” he added. “As soon as something starts to get momentum, it suddenly reverses and they get caught on the wrong side.”The weak showing contrasts with mutual funds that just had one of their best starts to a year in a decade. Large-cap active funds beat their benchmarks by an average of 2 percentage points in the first two months of 2021, according to Bank of America.Read more: With Tech Oligarchy Shaken, Active Funds Are Having a Great TimeThat comparison isn’t strictly apples to apples, though. Hedge funds are evaluated on their most concentrated bets, while mutual funds are judged by the performance of all their holdings. Still, that doesn’t change the fact that professional speculators are doing poorly, at least going by client data at Morgan Stanley.It’s a rare blunder for an industry that’s historically been good at picking stocks. Their alpha from crowded longs and shorts stayed positive in most of the previous six years, averaging more than 5%, Morgan Stanley’s data show.“Unlike the pain seen back in January which came almost entirely from the short side, longs are now the ones weighing most heavily” on returns, Morgan Stanley wrote in the note. “Performance has been challenging over the past few weeks, with most strategies capturing little upside in the first half of March, and now capturing much of the recent downside.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival Puerto Rico Bills Dim Dem Hopes of 51st State...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rival-puerto-rico-bills-dim-140633962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Two competing bills trying to end Puerto Rico’s status as one of the world’s oldest territories threaten to undermine each other -- damping hopes that the island might become the 51st U.S. state and a decisive power in Washington.On one side are those who want to make Puerto Rico a peer of New York, California and Wyoming. A rival measure would explore all status options for the island, including independence, statehood, a compact between sovereign states “or any other option other than the current territorial arrangement.”The efforts come as some Democrats, who long to address the structural imbalance of the Senate and Electoral College, see statehood for Puerto Rico and the District of Columbia as a way to solidify control of Congress for years to come. Puerto Rico leans Democratic, and if it were a state it would be eligible for two Senate seats and five House seats.While both bills have Democratic support, they echo the century-old debate on the island about the benefits of statehood versus more autonomy, said Pedro Reina-Perez, a political analyst and columnist. And the net effect is that “they cancel each other out.”“They’re going to fail not because there are two of them, but because each one is an independent effort,” he said. “When you go at it alone, the other side will always have veto power over what you do. It’s like mutually assured destruction.”Staggering ForwardThe struggle comes as the Caribbean island of 3.2 million people -- more than that of 20 U.S. states -- is still recovering from hurricanes, earthquakes and the global pandemic. It’s also crawling out of a historic bankruptcy aimed at reducing nearly $18 billion of debt, and reckoning with the turmoil created by the 2019 ousting of Governor Ricardo Rossello. The member of the New Progressive Party and registered Democrat was driven from office amid disclosures that he and aides cruelly mocked consituents.The island has been a U.S. possession since 1898 when William McKinley’s administration seized the colony at the end of the Spanish-American War. Since then, La Isla del Encanto has progressively won greater autonomy, but is still at a disadvantage when it comes to federal funding, programs and representation.Although Puerto Ricans have been U.S. citizens since 1917, residents don’t have the right to vote for president and don’t have a say in Congress.A change in the island’s territorial status could have dramatic financial consequences. Although both sides say their bills won’t affect continuing bankruptcy negotiations, a move toward autonomy might threaten the commonwealth’s heavy reliance on federal funding for everything from education to health to social security. And embracing statehood might undercut Puerto Rico’s niche as a tax haven for wealthy mainlanders.This month, Florida Democratic Representative Darren Soto -- with the support of the island’s Republican non-voting member of Congress, Jenniffer Gonzalez and Democratic Governor Pedro Pierluisi -- introduced the “Puerto Rico Statehood Admission Act.” That bill would trigger a binding island-wide referendum on statehood. If that option won, the Biden administration could potentially be sewing a new star on the flag before the end of his first term.Days later, Representative Nydia Velazquez, a Puerto Rican-born New York Democrat, introduced the “Puerto Rico Self-Determination Act.”That law creates a body elected by island residents that would attempt to settle the status issue by studying all the options. Whatever the “status convention” decided would have to be be ratified by a plebiscite.Self-DeterminationOn Monday, Velazquez told supporters that her proposal is the only one that offers a true choice.“Puerto Ricans are sick and tired of being played by politicians in D.C. and San Juan,” she said in a statement. “The collective political future of a people is not some trivial partisan matter and needs to be addressed in a serious and constructive way.”One of her co-sponsors, New York Democrat Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, said a single-choice referendum like the one Pierluisi is pushing is tantamount to the island’s leadership putting its “thumb on the scale” for statehood.Sixth Time a Charm? Puerto Ricans Vote on Statehood Once AgainThere have been several attempts to untangle the Puerto Rico status knot, including three nonbinding referendums since 2012. In November, 53% of voters on the island said they favored statehood. They also narrowly elected a Pierluisi, an ardent statehood advocate, as governor.Those votes and Gonzalez’s bill were giving statehood momentum, said George Laws Garcia, executive director of the Puerto Rico Statehood Council. Velazquez’s initiative slams on the brakes.“You would have to be naive to think that her bill is not an active effort to oppose statehood,” Laws said, citing Velazquez’s track record of opposing statehood initiatives in Congress.Island EliteGonzalez, who is one of Puerto Rico’s most popular politicians, said Velazquez’s plan to create a deliberative body is antidemocratic.The “legislation looks to delegate Puerto Rico’s future to a select few, instead of allowing the majority to decide for themselves,” Gonzalez said in a statement. “There is nothing more colonial in nature than imposing other’s views over us.”The chief Senate sponsor of the opposing Self-Determination Act, New Jersey Democrat Robert Menendez, said the status-deciding body “ensures that the people of Puerto Rico will have a robust, inclusive, and democratic process to consider the future of their political status.”“When Puerto Rico decides its future, the people on the island deserve to fully understand all their options,” he said in a statement Friday.With the battle lines drawn, each side has enlisted supporters and dozens of community groups. But both bills will likely face headwinds. While Democrats are split on the bills, many Republicans are wary of the political implications of statehood. Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell has spoken repeatedly against Democratic efforts to make Puerto Rico and the District of Columbia states.But Senator Marco Rubio, a Florida Republican, who is up for re-election next year in a state where many Puerto Ricans have resettled, has supported statehood.“Our fellow American citizens in Puerto Rico have democratically expressed their support for becoming a state,” Rubio said in a March 2 statement. “I urge my Senate colleagues to keep an open mind and learn more about statehood before taking a firm position in opposition. I will continue to do my part to one day achieve the 60 votes needed in the Senate for admission.”Reina-Perez, the analyst, said the status issue is so divisive and complicated that until everyone is on the same page, there’s little hope for a lasting resolution.“This is a case of a death foretold,” he said of both bills. “There’s a lot of hype, a lot of posturing, a lot of theater and drama -- only for it to all die in the procedure.”(Updated with quote from Robert Menendez in the 21st graph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES to Unveil Flagship Electric Sedan With TESLA-Beating Battery...</title>
      <link>https://europe.autonews.com/automakers/mercedes-unveil-flagship-electric-sedan-tesla-beating-battery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;europe.autonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy Ends $22M Suit Over Show, Out Of Loyalty To CBS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/judge-judy-lawsuit-cbs-judy-sheindlin-rebel-entertainment-amazon-1234722325/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Judge Judy has brought down the gavel on her own $22 million countersuit against talent agent Richard Lawrence and Rebel Entertainment Partners, and it’s because of CBS. “We declin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57-Year-Old Woman Gives Birth!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/03/25/barbara-higgins-new-hampshire-woman-57-years-old-gives-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her daughter died in 2016, Barbara Higgins began having dreams of another baby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MADAME CLAUDE': Gritty take on Paris sex icon...</title>
      <link>https://au.lifestyle.yahoo.com/madame-claude-gritty-netflix-paris-132756455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.lifestyle.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was a salacious icon of 20th century Paris -- the brothel-keeper to the stars -- and Netflix hopes the basis for another hit in the recent run of French successes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST ON KIDS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-pandemics-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-3c2490cd1bef6221c9b33146fee0fe4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 9-year-old twins didn’t flinch as each received test doses of Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine -- and then a sparkly bandage to cover the spot. “Sparkles make everything better,” declared...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How two friends made art history buying $70M digital work...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sculpture-jeff-koons-art-history-financial-markets-david-hockney-dfb5f80c55d61692b83bf693467c95c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took a few minutes for Vignesh Sundaresan and Anand Venkateswaran to realize that they'd parted with $69.3 million for a digital artwork stored in a JPEG file, coincidentally securing their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE:  DOMINION sues FOXNEWS for $1.6 BILLION over election claims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-media-lawsuits-elections-912eea8e168f95d51dec02da78ac2760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Dominion Voting Systems filed a $1.6 billion defamation lawsuit against Fox News on Friday, arguing the cable news giant, in an effort to boost faltering ratings, falsely claimed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala  to focus on diplomacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-diplomacy-immigration-coronavirus-pandemic-central-america-c89f7b50d980dce085ec5e9f2d17dee2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Vice President Kamala Harris won’t be on the ground at the Southwest border anytime soon as she leads efforts to address a rise in migrants trying to enter the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney gets Profile in Courage Award for impeachment vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-impeachments-mitt-romney-d77c4e352ce6fce8bd12079252edabff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — U.S. Sen. Mitt Romney was named the recipient of the John F. Kennedy Profile in Courage Award on Friday for splitting with his party and becoming the only Republican to vote to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  Ambitious Republicans starting to make moves in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-des-moines-elections-iowa-mike-pompeo-dc85426cae010d9d050767144d523c9e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;URBANDALE, Iowa (AP) — Ambitious Republicans are starting to make moves in Iowa, long a proving ground for future presidents. Their first step is finding out whether activists there have gotten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico complains of mask-less tourists, closes ruin site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-mexico-city-mexico-d8f2570f0e4022566bf7454e22029ce3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Authorities in Mexico’s Yucatan peninsula complained Friday about tourists not wearing face masks, as Mexico braces for a surge of Easter Week visitors. The acting police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ART OF THE POSSIBLE'</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/President-s-policy-approach-is-the-art-of-the-16054266.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden, answering the 29th question in his first presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of life amid concern in second year of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Signs-of-life-amid-signs-of-concern-in-the-second-16052735.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic isn't over, but its psychological grip on the United States has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Exercise? 'Smart' Gear Measures Breathing, Blood Oxygen Levels...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-03-smart-movements.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years there have been exciting breakthroughs in wearable technologies, like smartwatches that can monitor your breathing and blood oxygen levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL STYLE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-biden-contrast-styles-debut-221325943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sporting a red tie, Donald Trump -- combative, goading, sometimes angry and insulting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE'S NO DRAMA PRESS CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-2804de86cb2bd901c14c109efe024e5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden at his first news conference Thursday left the door open to backing fundamental changes in Senate procedure to muscle key parts of his agenda like immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 being monitored for Ebola virus in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.kgw.com/article/news/local/oregon-monitoring-4-people-ebola/283-234f6395-b2f4-4133-9354-4a2f79a1ac26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kgw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four people recently returned from Guinea and Democratic Republic of the Congo. The Oregon Health Authority said there is low risk for people in Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen caught driving 148 mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/queens-18-year-old-issued-43-tickets-after-upstate-police-chase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect hit speeds as high as 148 mph while fleeing from police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT BACK:  Asian American businesses defending themselves against rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Asian-American-businesses-are-defending-16053182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To San Antonio restaurateur Mike Nguyen, the threat was clear. Alongside the racist...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia bans giving water to voters in line under sweeping restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325223236-nzehq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-GEORGIA/VOTING (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Georgia bans giving water to voters in line under sweeping restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL NO PEAK!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325211932-tw1el</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Brazil hits record 100,000 coronavirus cases in a day, piling pressure on Bolsonaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octopus research yields insight into evolution of sleep...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325210100-ulrbq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-OCTOPUS/ (PIX):Octopus research yields insight into the evolution of sleep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% have no money in stock market and over 50% say it's 'rigged'...</title>
      <link>https://grow.acorns.com/what-keeps-people-from-investing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grow.acorns.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"People who aren't investing predominantly say it's because they don't have the money available to invest, or they don't understand stocks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:   LA TIMES Reveals 'Catastrophic' $50 Million Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/la-times-reveals-catastrophic-50-201038446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Times and the San Diego Union-Tribune lost “north of $50 million” in revenue in 2020, company leadership told staffers at an all-hands meeting on Thursday. Chris Argentieri, the president of the two papers’ California Times parent company, described the losses as a “catastrophic drop in revenue for the company north of $50 million on top of a business that was already using cash and not producing cash,” according to a recording of the meeting obtained by TheWrap. The majority of the losses came from print advertising, though digital advertising and print circulation also sustained some losses. “What we saw in 2020, was [an] acceleration of trends that we were well aware of and have been aware of, really, for far more than a decade,” Argentieri said. “We won’t go back, particularly in print advertising, to where we were.” Also Read: Los Angeles Times Discloses $10 Million PPP Loan Screenshot from California Times meeting Like many legacy print news operations, the L.A. Times has been losing millions of dollars in recent years — a departure from many decades of profitable operation. But the losses in the COVID year of 2020 have been much more damaging and lend credence...Read original story LA Times Reveals ‘Catastrophic’ $50 Million Revenue Loss in 2020 (Exclusive) At TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says China Won't Be Most Powerful on His Watch..</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biden-china-idUSKBN2BH2ZE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden on Thursday said he would prevent China from passing the United States to become the most powerful country in the world, vowing to invest heavily to ensure America prevails in the race between the world's two largest economies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Covid Cases Rising Again, Reversing Months of Progress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-covid-cases-are-rising-again-reversing-months-of-progress/ar-BB1eXMcj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid cases in the U.S. are rising again, reversing course after months of decline and threatening another setback in the return to normality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 being monitored for Ebola virus in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/4-people-being-monitored-in-oregon-for-ebola-after-returning-to-us-from-west-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people are being monitored by Oregon public health officials after potentially being exposed to Ebola while on a recent visit to Guinea and the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), according to an Oregon Health Authority news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk-Bond Sales Break Record for Busiest Quarter in History...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-junk-bond-sales-break-202540274.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. high-yield debt sales set a new quarterly record as companies take advantage of low funding costs before potential inflation causes rates to rise further.Carvana Co. launched $600 million of notes Thursday, which pushed issuance over the mark to $139.6 billion for the first quarter. That surpasses the previous high of about $139 billion set in the second quarter of 2020, when businesses rushed to raise liquidity at the start of the Covid-19 pandemic, data compiled by Bloomberg show. MGM China Holdings Ltd., Interior Logic Group -- issuing through Signal Parent Inc. -- and Dycom Industries Inc. set sizes for their deals earlier in the day to help drive volume past the record.Junk-rated companies have tapped the market relentlessly this year, extending 2020’s record pace as yields have stayed relatively low, at least for now. A $1.9 trillion debt-funded stimulus package and inflation expectations have been pushing Treasury yields higher, encouraging corporations to take advantage of borrowing conditions that are still attractive.Risky borrowers, including those such as retailer Neiman Marcus Holding Co. Inc. that only recently emerged from bankruptcy, have tapped the market, while there’s also been a pick-up in leveraged buyout funding after a swath of refinancings this year. Ingram Micro Inc. is in the market with a $2 billion offering to support its acquisition by Platinum Equity, following similar deals from Triton Water Holdings Inc. and Interior Logic Group.“It’s really hard to keep up with the issuance,” said Kevin Loome, portfolio manager of the U.S. high yield fund at T. Rowe Price. “Now the pendulum is shifting a little bit toward more aggressive behaviors.”Companies have been issuing debt at a rampant pace all year with supply setting new high marks in January, February and March. In 2020, annual sales zoomed past the previous record by over $100 billion, ending at nearly $432 billion.With the Federal Reserve and central banks globally keeping rates low, investors have sought out U.S. junk bonds for higher returns, which pushed average yields below 4% for the first time ever in February. Although they’re back up to 4.34% now, mostly thanks to the selloff in Treasuries, that’s still well below the 10-year average of 6.4%.Read more: Junk Bonds With Low Yields? Here’s Why They’re Hot: QuickTakeThat strong demand has allowed jumbo deals to easily clear syndication and pad issuance volume. American Airlines Group Inc. sold $10 billion this month as part of a joint bond-and-loan package in the biggest ever airline debt sale. T-Mobile US Inc. issued $3.8 billion to help finance the purchase of 5G airwaves, an expenditure that’s also propelled a rush of borrowing in the investment-grade market.There have also been at least two dozen inaugural junk-bond issuers to come forward this year, contributing about $13 billion of supply, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Pandemic stock darlings Crocs Inc., the colorful clog maker made cool again thanks to Justin Bieber and Bad Bunny, and cloud-based software company Twilio Inc. seized on their equity valuations to sell their first bonds.As so many companies have pulled forward financing needs, it’s hard to imagine the issuance party going on forever. A slowdown could be coming as the market itself will eventually push back, Loome said.“It’s almost like an indigestion problem, and we’re getting to that point,” he said.U.S.MGM China Holdings, Dycom Industries, Oasis Midstream and Interior Logic Group are also in the high-yield pipeline and slated to sell notes Thursday. Meanwhile four other borrowers are in the market with debt deals that may wrap up before the end of the month.London Stock Exchange Group Plc is tapping the U.S. high-grade bond market to help refinance debt it took on related to its acquisition of Refinitiv Holdings Ltd.Green bonds. Blue bonds. Brown bonds. Environmentally-conscious investors may soon be able to buy a different color of asset every day of the weekFor deal updates, click here for the New Issue MonitorFor more, click here for the Credit Daybook AmericasEuropeThere are at least 14 deals in European primary markets on Thursday, including Advanz Pharma and utilities supplier E.ON, which is issuing an euro-benchmark green bond.A “meaningful acceleration” in the EU’s vaccine program is needed to kick start corporate rating upgrades in Europe, according to Bank of America strategistsFormer British Prime Minister David Cameron is under investigation by the Office of the Register of Consultant Lobbyists for possible unregistered consultant lobbying on behalf of Greensill Capital, according to the Daily TelegraphAsiaFirms in India rush to issue bonds in rupees before the end of the fiscal year on March 31, with at least seven borrowers seeking bids for deals on Thursday.The Philippines is marketing a yen bond, in what would be the sovereign’s first Samurai issuance since August 2019China’s central bank asked lenders to keep loan growth stable and reasonable, with increased support to house leasing, innovative technology and the manufacturing sector(Updates to reflect the record was hit starting in the first paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channels Reagan?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/joe-biden-press-conference-review-donald-trump-reelection-covid-1234721790/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I got elected to solve problems,” Joe Biden said today in response to the first question at his first solo press conference as President. “All I know is I’ve been hired to solve problems, not crea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Time for Putin's most outspoken opponent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-alexei-navalny-health-worse-prison-d3d79f448100dab11271a50d29ebf73a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny has accused prison authorities of failing to provide proper treatment for his back pain and leg problems, saying in a letter posted Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Final vote results show major setback for Israel's Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-parliamentary-elections-benjamin-netanyahu-elections-4cb571e47b2f1d8f7068e4e595777645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and his right-wing allies fell short of winning a parliamentary majority in Israel’s latest election, according to a final vote count released...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers press Big Tech CEOs on speech responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-media-misinformation-social-media-censorship-159ef7e3040dd65234e4e49404bfe00c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The CEOs of tech giants Facebook, Twitter and Google faced a grilling in Congress Thursday as lawmakers tried to draw them into acknowledging their companies' roles in fueling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says migrant surge was WORSE under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2578690/biden-first-press-conference-migrants-guns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden blamed Donald Trump and the weather for the humanitarian crisis on the Mexican border in his first press conference as President. Having avoided the press for 65 days, Biden was grilled a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Income Growth Highest Ever Last Year on Govt Bailouts!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-personal-income-growth-highest-ever-last-year-on-stimulus/ar-BB1eX9yN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans earned an additional $1.1 trillion last year -- the most ever in data dating back to 1930 -- thanks entirely to stimulus checks and other government aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUTGERS to Require Proof of Vaccination to Enroll for Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/lifestyle-buzz/rutgers-to-require-covid-19-vaccination-for-students-this-fall/ar-BB1eXp2g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rutgers University has announced that all students planning to attend in-person classes in the fall semester must be fully vaccinated, with limited exceptions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
