<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>11 shot in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/nopd-at-least-11-people-shot-along-canal-street/30064186#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOPD: At least 11 people shot along Canal Street</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEREMY: Terrorists should 'not necessarily' serve full sentences...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-security-corbyn-idUSKBN1Y50VO?taid=5de3b3b8ee0d2300017c7a3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted terrorists should "not necessarily" serve their full prison ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed robbers hold up drivers, steal 60 packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/armed-robbers-hold-amazon-drivers-steal-packages-cops-say/IIBhfMGAFkQCEbcyZYlRzL/#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 60 online shoppers will receive their orders later than expected after a group of robbers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocky road ahead for Merkel after ally loses shock vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rocky-road-ahead-merkel-ally-loses-shock-vote-110602823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel faces a rocky political road ahead as she battles to hang on until 2021 as German chancellor, after her junior coalition partner SPD elected a left-leaning leadership duo. Rank and file Social Democrats late Saturday delivered a humiliating blow to Finance Minister Olaf Scholz's run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy rally cut short by police tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/584dfb8a30804634bb422ba715fd4a82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Thousands took to Hong Kong’s streets Sunday in a new wave of pro-democracy protests, but police fired tear gas after some demonstrators hurled bricks and smokes bombs, breaking a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack now political football as Johnson, Corbyn spar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/01194743767948599f8007b4da663255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain’s political leaders sparred Sunday over who is responsible for the early release of a convicted extremist who launched a stabbing attack in central London that left two dead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONDAY:  Schiff to circulate Ukraine report...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/30/intelligence-committee-draft-ukraine-report-074518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a crucial step in the House's fast-moving impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 shot in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/10-people-shot-new-orleans-police-say-n1093721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An individual was detained near the scene on the city's Canal Street, police added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China introduces mandatory face scans for phone users...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-introduces-mandatory-face-scans-phone-users-091042257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will require telecom operators to collect face scans when registering new phone users at offline outlets starting Sunday, according to the country's information technology authority, as Beijing continues to tighten cyberspace controls. In September, China's industry and information technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 killed in South Dakota plane crash... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.keloland.com/news/local-news/9-dead-in-brule-county-sd-plane-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.keloland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;12 people were on board the plane. The three survivors were taken to Sioux Falls and are in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Unusual Tornadoes Confirmed in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/weather/news/2019-11-30-tornadoes-confirmed-arizona-phoenix-late-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three tornadoes were confirmed in Arizona as a powerful low pressure system moved through the West after Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus on early release of convict in London stabbings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10459154/london-bridge-terrorist-ex-convict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was banned from entering London but had a one day exemption to attend an ex-convict event, it has emerged. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was released from prison i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS WAS WARNED OVER RISKS OF FREEING TERRORISTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/boris-johnson-warned-london-bridge-attack-usman-khan-stabbing-terrorist-a9227681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate debt nears record $10 trillion; Poses new risks..</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Corporate-debt-nears-a-record-10-trillion-and-14870792.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little more than a decade after consumers binged on inexpensive mortgages that helped bring on a global financial crisis, a new debt surge - this time by major corporations - threatens to unleash fresh turmoil.  A decade of historically low interest rates has allowed companies to sell record amounts of bonds to investors, sending total U.S. corporate debt to nearly $10 trillion, or a record 47% of the overall economy.  In recent weeks, the Federal Reserve, the International Monetary Fund and major institutional investors such as BlackRock and American Funds all have sounded the alarm about the mounting corporate obligations.  The danger isn't immediate. But some regulators and investors say the borrowing has gone on too long and could send financial markets plunging when the next recession hits, dealing the real economy a blow at a time when it already would be wobbling.  Some of America's best-known companies, including AT&amp;T, Ford Motor and CVS Health, have splurged on borrowed cash. This year, the weakest firms have accounted for most of the growth and are increasingly using debt for "financial risk-taking," such as investor payouts and Wall Street dealmaking, rather than new plants and equipment, according to the IMF.  Amid the avalanche of debt, the sharp growth in lower-quality corporate bonds, just one notch above junk, represents a special concern. Investors hold nearly $4 trillion in these bonds, including $2.5 trillion from U.S. companies, according to the credit rating agency Standard &amp; Poor's.  Since Oct. 1, familiar names like Hasbro, Nordstrom, Marriott and Hyundai all have tapped investors for cash by selling near-junk bonds that S&amp;P labels "BBB."  This low-quality corporate debt bulge, by itself, is unlikely to cause a recession, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick speaks at Native American 'Un-Thanksgiving Day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7742499/Colin-Kaepernick-speaks-Thanksgiving-Day-criticizes-government.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former 49ers star was at the Indigenous People Sunrise Ceremony Thursday, main. He later tweeted the US government 'has stolen over 1.5 billion acres of land', inset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY:  I was hired by Weinstein to dig dirt on his accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7742171/Spy-admits-befriending-Harvey-Weinsteins-alleged-rape-victim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stella Penn Pechanac befriended Scream actress Rose McGowan after claiming that she worked for a London asset management firm which wanted to invite her to speak at a gala dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER JACK:  I'M LEAVING USA FOR 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/29/tech/jack-dorsey-africa-future/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg 'might be better off skipping debates'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/30/michael-bloomberg-might-be-better-off-skipping-democratic-debates-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may be the 14th richest person on Earth, but one thing Michael Bloomberg can’t buy is a spot in the 2020 Democratic debates. Current Democratic National Committee rules require candidates …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION JOLTED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130174142-fwiqb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-SECURITY/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-UK PM Johnson pressured on jail terms after London Bridge attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU investigating GOOGLE data collection...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129180550-7qhd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regulators are quizzing companies about the details of any agreements to share data with the tech firm, according to a document seen by Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California famous for earthquakes and wildfires -- but don't forget about its volcanoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-is-famous-for-earthquakes-and-wildfires-but-don-t/article_ce2dbb40-e8dd-5571-90a2-0e281b0bdc02.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margaret Mangan didn’t sleep well in the weeks following the Ridgecrest, Calif., earthquakes. The July shaking triggered a swarm of smaller tremors in the nearby Coso Volcanic Field, a cluster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN IOWA BLITZ</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b70788340dee4d82ab6078637ee0e002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COUNCIL BLUFFS, Iowa (AP) — Joe Biden launched an eight-day bus tour of Iowa on Saturday projecting confidence, ignoring his many Democratic presidential competitors and pledging that he will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL NEWS SITES...</title>
      <link>http://www.mentaldaily.com/article/2019/11/worlds-most-powerful-news-outlets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mentaldaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the transition into the digital age, there's been a substantive rise in online-based news outlets and blogs. In this excerpt, we compiled a list of the ten most powerful news outlets on the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family fury after finding out killer on day release tackled terrorist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10457317/familys-fury-killer-hero-london-bridge-james-ford/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE family of one of the London Bridge have-a-go-heroes are furious that the killer was allowed out of prison without their knowledge – and that he’s being hailed a hero. James Ford, 42…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast braces for foot of snow during first days of December...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/northeastern-us-braces-for-foot-of-snow-during-first-days-of-december/637449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein, Blackmail and Lucrative 'Hot List'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/30/jeffrey-epstein-blackmail-and-a-lucrative-hot-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon after the sex criminal Jeffrey Epstein died in August, a mysterious man met with two prominent lawyers. Towering, barrel-chested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane season ending, but Dorian left 'massive, massive crisis' in Bahamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article237664359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico rise in violence starts sticking to 'Teflon president' after year in office...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/mexico-s-rise-in-violence-starts-sticking-to-teflon-president/article_63f21506-6e0f-5ee8-83a2-da65962b4c3a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — At 7 a.m. each weekday morning, as the sun is still rising over this sprawling mountain capital, Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador steps in front of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS STRIKES AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/london-bridge-terror-attack-isis-20998291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Islamic State has claimed responsibility for Usman Khan’s knife-wielding attack on London Bridge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As members of Congress head for exits, loosely regulated gravy train beckons...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-excongress-lobbying-20191129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON The road from Capitol Hill to K Street is designed to have a speed bump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Yesterday's Cocaine: Death Toll Rising From Tainted Drug...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/not-yesterdays-cocaine-death-toll-rising-from-tainted-drug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the U.S. continues to focus mainly on the opioid crisis, cocaine is quietly making a comeback and has become one of the biggest overdose killers of African Americans when tainted with fentany…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein, Blackmail and Lucrative 'Hot List'...</title>
      <link>https://bdnews24.com/world/2019/11/30/jeffrey-epstein-blackmail-and-a-lucrative-hot-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bdnews24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide receiver stabbed in Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d8d4c3f93ef43579201ed01ffddb986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — NFL wide receiver Terrelle Pryor was stabbed in Pittsburgh, but an agent said Saturday that the player is expected to make a full recovery. Police officers were called to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem presidential campaign has produced confusion rather than clarity...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-Democratic-presidential-campaign-has-produced-14872449.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential candidates have been on the campaign trail for nearly a year. Confusion rather than clarity continues to be the story of their contest for the 2020 nomination.  Early in the year, the party's liberal wing seemed to be ascendant, defined by the candidacies of Sens. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and the embrace of a single-payer, Medicare-for-all health-care program. Sanders and Warren were calling for other dramatic changes to the system - economic and political - and their voices stood out. Some other candidates offered echoes of their ideas.  That proved to be a misleading indicator of where the Democratic electorate was on some of the issues, particularly health care, in part because there were fewer moderate voices being heard. Former Vice President Joe Biden didn't join the race until April. South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg wasn't being taken very seriously. Sen. Amy Klobuchar, D-Minn., wasn't breaking through.  The candidate debates provided the setting for the arguments to play out before a larger audience. Warren and Sanders came under attack from moderate Democrats at the first debate in June in Miami, with former Maryland congressman John Delaney the most vocal. But Warren and Sanders more than held their own. It appeared as though the progressive wing was on solid ground.  Subsequent debates, however, have produced a different impression. The progressives have been much more on the defensive and the moderates more assertive. Biden tangled with Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., in the Detroit debate over the issue of health care. Harris subsequently modified her position, moving toward the center. On the issue of Medicare-for-all, the ground has shifted.  During the Atlanta debate in late November, even Sanders seemed to be tempering his overall message....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BOWL PREVIEW? </title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/sports/nfl/san-francisco-49ers/article237804539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right AfD party elects new leader backed by radical wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-politics-afd/german-far-right-afd-party-elects-new-leader-backed-by-radical-wing-idUSKBN1Y40A2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-right Alternative for Germany on Saturday elected a decorator from the e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Kerry Launches Star-Studded Climate Coalition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/30/climate/john-kerry-climate-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Kerry and a group that includes some Republicans, some military members and a lot of Hollywood, are launching a new  coalition to push for public action on climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In bitter British election, influence of wealthy U.S. donors causes stir...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-a-bitter-British-election-influence-of-14872390.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Dec. 12 election is a bitter fight to shape the country's future, with voters not only hoping to chart the next steps of Brexit, but also picking between startlingly different visions of the country from right-wing Prime Minister Boris Johnson and left-wing Labour Party leader Jeremy Corbyn.  However, it isn't just British voters who are influencing Britain's future. A number of wealthy American individuals and organizations appear also to be having a big influence on this fraught British election.  The prominent left-leaning newspaper the Guardian reported Friday that 11 wealthy American donors have given a total of more than $3.7 million to influential right-wing British groups over the past five years.  One conservative American billionaire who was having an outsize influence on right-wing groups across the pond is no longer alive. John Templeton, who died in 2008, was behind a set of foundations that gave $3.3 million to British groups, the newspaper reported.  The news comes as Washington focuses on allegations of foreign influence on U.S. elections and is a reminder that outside the United States, the problem is often seen through the opposite lens: wealthy Americans seeking to influence foreign elections.  The U.S. donations in Britain do not appear to be illegal, and some of the think tanks involved have pushed back against the Guardian's framing. One recipient of Templeton-linked money, the Legatum Institute, told the paper that it had "a strong policy of maintaining intellectual independence" despite foreign financial backing.  In a statement in response to the article, the John Templeton Foundation, one of the organizations linked to the late investor, said that it was "proud to support academic research and civil dialogue in the natural sciences, human sciences, philosophy, classical liberalism, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KID ROCK GOES ON DRUNKEN RANT ABOUT OPRAH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7741989/Kid-Rock-explains-reason-lurid-rant-against-Oprah.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rocker - who was caught on camera making foul-mouthed slurs  last week - took to Twitter on Saturday night after the footage went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete to Visit Black Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/11/30/pete-buttigieg-visit-black-church-pastor-said-president-country-racist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg will visit a black church in North Carolina Sunday, seeking to improve support with the early primary state’s black community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg health scare raises prospect of election year Supreme Court battle...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/472354-ginsburg-health-scare-raises-prospect-of-election-year-supreme-court-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent hospitalization of Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg following a year of health scares has raised the prospect of a Supreme Court vacancy in an election year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Woes Pile Up From Winter Storms as Thanksgiving Ends...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/travel-woes-pile-winter-storms-162409169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Millions of travelers heading back from their Thanksgiving holiday could be caught up in a fast-moving winter storm making its way east from California to the Midwest and beyond.The National Weather Service expects significant travel impacts across wide swaths of the U.S. this weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Clickmas: Black Friday online sales hit record $7.4B...</title>
      <link>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/ap-news/merry-clickmas-black-friday-online-sales-hit-record-74b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;1010wins.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — This year’s Black Friday was the biggest ever for online sales, and Adobe Analytics says carts filled on phones, computers and tablets rang up $7.4 billion in transactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrorist linked to notorious hate preacher...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10456386/london-bridge-terrorist-anjem-choudary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was a student of hate preacher Anjem Choudary before he was caged for plotting to bomb the London Stock Exchange, it has emerged. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex criminal's legal legacy may have years to run...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/30/jeffrey-epstein-prince-andrew-legal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The financier’s associates, such as Prince Andrew and Ghislaine Maxwell, and his victims are unlikely to see closure any time soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sinister Scientist Behind the CIA's Mind-Control Mayhem...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-sinister-scientist-behind-the-cias-mind-control-mayhem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book digs deep into the horrifying career of Sidney Gottlieb, the scientist who ran the CIA's damaging and possibly lethal experiments in drug-induced mind control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Rises Between Mayor Pete, Warren...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/tension-rises-between-pete-buttigieg-and-elizabeth-warren-as-first-contests-draw-near</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing competition between South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) is one of several trends to follow as the primary shifts into a new gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea threatens Japan with 'real ballistic missile'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50613051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea calls Japan's leader an "imbecile" and "political dwarf" in a row over its latest test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiCaprio Responds to Brazil President Claim He Funded Amazon Wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/leonardo-dicaprio-amazon-wildfires-brazil-president-1203420108/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo DiCaprio has refuted bizarre and false claims from Brazil’s right-wing president Jair Bolsonaro that the actor financed the wildfires in the Amazon, playing into a ploy by the the Wo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY WAS HE FREE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edbd48353f9b4766abc7ddb34c0300cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — U.K. counterterrorism police on Saturday searched for clues into how a man imprisoned for terrorism offenses before his release last year managed to stab several people before being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ice preserved tiny puppy in near-perfect condition for 18,000 years. Scientists fascinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ice-preserved-a-tiny-puppy-in-near-perfect-14871919.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have big outstanding questions about the puppy they have named Dogor - "friend" in a language of the Siberian area where the creature spent 18,000 years in permafrost.  They're still trying to figure out if the tiny animal is a dog or wolf. They wonder whether he could be part of the evolutionary bridge that turned a fierce wild animal into man's best friend.  They don't have to speculate about what Dogor looked like, however, because icy conditions have left him remarkably frozen in time. Scientists can touch his fur, lift his padded paws and pull back his lips to bare small, yellowed teeth.  "Fantastic, right?" says Dave Stanton, a research fellow at the Centre for Palaeogenetics in Stockholm who has been scrutinizing the long-lost canine. "We have quite a lot of ancient samples. . . . But this has got be one of the best-preserved."  The puppy was discovered last year by locals in Yakutia, said Sergey Fedorov, who heads the exposition hall at the Mammoth Museum of Russia's North-Eastern Federal University. Dogor left the wilderness as a lump of soil and ice, but scientists could make out the head and paws of what they believed at first to be a young wolf.  Federov told The Washington Post that he carefully cleaned off dirt and debris to reveal near-intact fur - "extremely rare for animals of that time period."  "It's an amazing feeling, to see, touch and feel the history of earth," he said.  The puppy, whose name was announced earlier this week, remains in Russia. But he has caught the attention of researchers in Sweden and England who want to better understand Dogor's life and place in a still-mysterious evolution.  Testing on a rib bone has revealed the animal's age: about two months, said Stanton, a postdoctoral scholar who's been working for over a year on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BOWL PREVIEW? </title>
      <link>https://www.ninersnation.com/2019/11/29/20986214/super-bowl-preview-49ers-ravens-baltimore-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ninersnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2 hottest teams in football face off, round 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces of the heroes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/london-bridge-heroes-who-risked-20994292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usman Khan's rampage left two people dead and three injured before he was dragged to the ground by members of the public outside Fishmongers' Hall. He was then shot by elite police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genealogical databases goldmine for police, but with few rules and little transparency...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/genealogical-databases-are-a-goldmine-for-police-but-with-few/article_a15200f8-30cd-5423-991d-cfb15b8b5209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orlando police detective Michael Fields was sure he had the break he needed right in front of him to close in on a serial rapist: a list of people whose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing impeachment inquiry, Trump strives to look hard at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-impeachment-inquiry-Trump-strives-to-look-14872290.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. - As Democrats in Congress push to impeach him, President Donald Trump has toured a manufacturing plant in Texas, boasted about economic gains and signed numerous bills. He served turkey to U.S. troops in Afghanistan on Thanksgiving and grieved with the families of fallen service members at Dover Air Force Base in Delaware.  And next week, Trump is scheduled to jet to London to meet with European allies and be received at Buckingham Palace by Queen Elizabeth II.  Sure, Trump has been consumed by the impeachment proceedings, popping off daily, if not hourly, about what he dubs a "hoax." But he and his aides also have staged photo opportunities and public events designed to showcase the president on the job - a strategy one year out from the election to convince the American people that he is hard at work for them at the same time that Democrats are trying to remove him from office.  "I'm working my ass off," Trump told a thunderous rally crowd of roughly 20,000 on Tuesday night in Sunrise, Florida. He added: "The failed Washington establishment is trying to stop me because I'm fighting for you and because we're winning. It's very simple."  Trump is taking a page out of the Clinton playbook. Then-President Bill Clinton survived his 1998 impeachment in part because the economy was roaring and because he appeared to many voters to be relentlessly focused on doing the business of the American people. When Clinton left office in 2001, Gallup measured his job approval rating at 66%.  Clinton had a built-in advantage that Trump does not enjoy: popularity. Throughout his second term, Clinton's approval rating hovered in the high 50s and 60s, whereas Trump's has been mired below 50%.  Still, Clinton's experience has been instructive to Trump, who recently met in the Oval Office with former Clinton strategist Mark...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu-hit PATS hope they're past worst...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/flu-hit-pats-hope-theyre-past-worst-193317046--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England coach Bill Belichick is hoping the Patriots will be close to full strength for their trip to Houston on Sunday after illness sidelined eight from mid-week practice. &amp;quot;We&amp;#39;ve had some guys miss,&amp;quot; Belichick told reporters on Friday. Four of the ailing players returned to action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIRAL: Iraqis keep up anti-regime demos despite PM's vow to quit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iraqis-keep-anti-regime-demos-despite-pms-vow-073400257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraqis kept up their anti-government protests in Baghdad and across the south on Saturday, unsatisfied with the prime minister's planned resignation and insisting "all corrupted people" must step down. Prime Minister Adel Abdel Mahdi announced on Friday he was planning to submit his resignation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's far-right AfD elects new leaders as radicals rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-far-afd-elects-leaders-radicals-rise-034202709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's far-right AfD party will elect new leaders on Saturday, with its increasingly influential radical wing seeking to tighten its grip on the group after a series of electoral victories. Underlining the polarising effect the party has on Germany, up to 12,000 protesters are expected to gather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 25: The day it all began...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed77e5d517054816b51d2285ed4efe88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The forecast for July 25 was typical for Washington: sunny, mid-80s. President Donald Trump had good reason to be feeling bright and sunny himself. It was the morning after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bystanders used whale tusk, fire extinguisher to subdue...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/nov/30/narwhal-tusk-and-fire-extinguisher-used-to-tackle-london-bridge-attacker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the public, including a convicted murderer, bring terrorist to the ground</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to blitz Iowa back roads by bus in 800-mile hunt for support...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden/biden-to-blitz-iowa-back-roads-by-bus-in-800-mile-hunt-for-support-idUSKBN1Y40AK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden will crisscross Iowa by bus for eigh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge 'for death of ISIS leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/london-bridge-terrorist-plotted-revenge-20995155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security source revealed Usman Khan was also taking part in a mandatory Government de-radicalisation course after being jailed for terrorism offences. al-Baghdadi was killed during a military raid last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One city's plan to combat: Bulldoze homes, rebuild paradise...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/One-city-s-plan-to-combat-climate-change-14863871.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. - Swinging cranes and clawing excavators have reshaped the landscape here, elevating Charlotte's skyline, expanding its girth and transforming this former cotton-shipment town into the South's financial hub and one of America's fastest-growing cities.  But the Queen City also has been steadily unbuilding itself, bulldozing houses and razing apartment complexes along its creeks, ripping up a mall parking lot to reveal a hidden waterway and then stripping away its concrete banks, all in a bid to prevent the flash flooding that turns communities into deathtraps.  The county has removed 460 structures and replaced them with absorbent grasslands, winning national praise as a prototype for regional flood planning that anticipates the impact of projected development and the growing effects of extreme weather. The innovative strategy was ahead of the curve when it launched in the 1990s, by calculating future flood risk and then purchasing - and demolishing - vulnerable homes, businesses and office buildings.  But the region is facing more-complex challenges as climate change threatens bigger and more-lasting deluges. Six out of North Carolina's seven wettest storms have occurred in the past 20 years. In June, following an 11-inch downpour upstream, the Catawba River burst its banks here in a catastrophe that can't be cured by opening up a few extra acres of flood plain.  "We just can't engineer ourselves out of this problem," said Bill Hunt, a civil engineer at North Carolina State University who predicts that more-drastic steps will become necessary to move entire communities out of danger.  "What Charlotte has done works very well for two- or three-inch rains," Hunt said. "But we don't have tools to fix 11- or 12-inch rains."  The program, operated jointly by the city of Charlotte and Mecklenburg County, has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bows to 'fake news' law with post 'correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50613341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first time the social media giant has added a correction to a post under the new law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Students Fainting From Hunger in Venezuela Schools...</title>
      <link>https://theunionjournal.com/college-students-fainting-from-starvation-in-venezuelas-failing-college-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theunionjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOCA DE UCHIRE, Venezuela — Tons of of kids filed into their college courtyard to listen to a neighborhood Catholic bishop lead prayers for his or her scho</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of Republicans say Trump better president than Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/472460-poll-majority-of-republicans-say-trump-better-president-than-lincoln</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Republicans say President Trump is a better leader than former President Abraham Lincoln, according to this week’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INCIDENT AT FORT BRAGG' MOVIE SET TO TELL 'TRUE STORY' OF SOLDIER'S EXORCISM...</title>
      <link>https://sofrep.com/news/incident-at-fort-bragg-movie-set-to-tell-the-true-story-of-a-soldiers-exorcism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sofrep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Osgood Perkins is slated to direct the new film,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper gives beat to Chile street revolt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rapper-tijoux-gives-beat-chiles-street-revolt-094116817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilean singer Ana Tijoux says she is scared of cameras. Latin America's richest country has been rocked by more than six weeks of protests sparked by a 30 peso (four US cents) rise in metro fares. Tijoux -- who Rolling Stone magazine has hailed as the "best rapper in Spanish" -- is just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack began at rehabilitation event...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/how-the-london-bridge-terror-attack-unfolded-11874155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the London Bridge terror attack began at a prisoner rehabilitation event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEGRAPH CEO heralds digital growth as takeover talk swirls...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/business/telegraph-ceo-heralds-digital-growth-as-takeover-talk-swirls-1.68171705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turning casual online readers into paying subscribers is critical for Hugh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Posts First Month in 70 Years as Net Petroleum Exporter...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-posts-first-month-70-154903996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. solidified its status as an energy producer by posting the first full month as a net exporter of crude and petroleum products since government records began in 1949.The nation exported 89,000 barrels a day more than it imported in September, according to data from the Energy Information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Set, Billions Minted: Will Be Hard to Top 2019 Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/records-set-billions-minted-hard-181030572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In a bull market almost everyone thought was living on borrowed time, the S&amp;P 500 is poised to post one of its best years in two decades. Extraordinary returns like those are complicating the lives of people paid to predict what happens next.Stretches like this are only raising the stakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON EVERYWHERE: How Tech Giant Wove Self Into Life of American City...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/30/prime-mover-how-amazon-wove-itself-into-the-life-of-an-american-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — Another big Prime Air 767 takes off from Baltimore-Washington International Airport — where Amazon’s shipping last year eclipsed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tests hypersonic missile in Arctic...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130114502-1lz1m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ARCTIC/MISSILES:Russia tests hypersonic missile in Arctic - TASS cites sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters burn tires in Iraq in renewed anti-govt rage...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130085156-dqa7o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-PROTESTS/ (PIX):Protesters burn tyres in southern Iraq in renewed anti-government rage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY WAS HE FREE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-attack-usman-khan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was free to kill an innocent man and woman despite the judge who jailed him ruling he should never be let out. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was released from pris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belonged to jihadist group that admired Hitler...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/30/london-bridge-stabber-belonged-to-jihadist-group-that-admired-hitler-plotted-to-bomb-us-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knife-wielding terrorist who was subdued by civilians, then shot dead by police on London Bridge on Friday was a paroled bomb plotter who once hoped to start a jihadist training camp in Kashmir…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
