<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau's wife tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/529199/canada-justin-trudeau-prime-minister-coronavirus-wife-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA’S Prime Minister Justin Trudeau’s wife Sophie tested positive for coronavirus and the couple are self-isolating. She began exhibiting “mild flu-like symptoms” before …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic team grasps for credibility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5878d878b1c1b5c3274c529ed2bc38bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — During the financial crisis a decade ago, President Barack Obama could look around the room and turn to an economist who served as Harvard's president, a former president of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio, Maryland shut schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/education/2020/03/12/coronavirus-school-closings-ohio-maryland-washington-seattle-king-closures/5036252002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools in Ohio will close for three weeks, and schools in Maryland will close for two, in the most sweeping school closures in the country so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lag ignites political uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-Congress-bipartisan-complaints-to-Trump-15126672.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Concerns about the lagging pace of coronavirus testing have exploded into a major political issue, with lawmakers of both parties angrily demanding more tests for Americans as President Donald Trump has insisted problems that have hindered capacity are being addressed.  The issue dominated separate briefings for members of the House and Senate on Thursday, emerged in the presidential race and became a flash point at a House Oversight and Reform Committee hearing, where the country's top public health officials struggled to explain why more Americans could not get tested for a global pandemic.  "The system is not geared toward what we need right now, what you are asking for," Anthony Fauci, an immunologist and the head of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases at the National Institutes of Health, said at the hearing. "That is a failing. Let's admit it."  At the White House on Thursday, Trump responded to a question about the lack of test availability by claiming that "over the next few days, they're going to have four million tests out."  "Frankly, the testing has been going very smooth," he said. "If you go to the right agency, if you go to the right area, you get the test."  So far, in the United States, only about 11,000 people have been tested, according to figures shared with members of Congress on Thursday. According to statistics compiled by the American Enterprise Institute, nationwide capacity to process the test kits being distributed has so far ramped up only to about 20,000 people per day - meaning it could be weeks before any tested patient gets results.  Members of Trump's party sounded alarms Thursday. After a Senate briefing with Fauci and other officials, Sen. James Lankford, R-Okla., acknowledged that Trump's recent statement that anyone who wants to get tested can get...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore mobilizes system of state control...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/national/singapore-mobilizes-system-of-state-control-to-contain-coronavirus/article_869f8af5-b78a-5561-8494-e21db3332bf3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE — In a fearful time of nationwide lockdowns and supermarket-aisle fights over toilet paper, Zhi Peng Lee’s website tracking the coronavirus is oddly reassuring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden speech marks opening salvo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-03-12/biden-speech-marks-opening-salvo-in-general-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's speech on coronavirus dovetails with Democrats' strategy of portraying Trump as a feckless and ineffective leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines call for govt aid...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312234702-pjm14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-AIRLINES (UPDATE 7, PIX):UPDATE 7-Global airlines call for government aid and United warns of cuts to U.S. routes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life upended for Americans... </title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312223849-ae25q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Life upended for Americans as U.S. scrambles to contain coronavirus threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX L.A. Offices In Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/coronavirus-netflix-infection-staffer-lockdown-los-angeles-1202881859/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As nations and the entertainment industry take dramatic precautions over the spreading coronavirus, Netflix may have been hit with by a potential inflection here in Los Angeles. An employee in the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Will virus kill New World Order?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2020/03/will-coronavirus-kill-new-world-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Sen. Bernie Sanders does not like "millionaires and billionaires," he should be pleased. There are far fewer of them today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: SYSTEM 'FAILING'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/it-failing-let-s-admit-it-fauci-says-coronavirus-testing-n1157036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The system is not really geared to what we need right now," Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, said at a House hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED PUMPS ANOTHER TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/fed-to-pump-more-than-500-billion-into-short-term-bank-funding-expand-types-of-security-purchases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve intervened in financial markets for the second day in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City that never sleeps self-isolates...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/12/coronavirus-in-ny-gov-cuomo-bans-gatherings-of-more-than-500-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo has announced statewide bans on gatherings of more than 500 people in the most drastic step yet to combat the coronavirus contagion, as the number of confirmed cases spiked to 328…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC ONLY TESTED 77 THIS WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cdc-tested-only-77-people-this-week-coronavirus-testing-slow-around-the-nation-153646616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus testing in the United States appears to be proceeding with a marked lack of urgency. An examination of state and federal records by Yahoo News finds that American states are, on average, testing fewer than 100 people per day — while the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had tested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches across Rome shut... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/catholic-churches-across-rome-shut-due-virus-213310360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican on Thursday closed all Catholic churches across Rome to stem the spread of a coronavirus pandemic that has killed more than 1,000 people across Italy. The papal vicar for Rome said the churches would reopen when a broader Italian government crackdown on public gatherings expires on April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 MILLION AMERICANS COULD GET INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/150-million-americans-could-coronavirus-us-projection-185632345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between 70 to 150 million people in the United States could eventually be infected with the novel coronavirus, according to a projection shared with Congress, a lawmaker said Thursday. Congresswoman Rashida Tlaib made the remarks during a hearing of the House of Representatives with members of the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORST DAY ON WALL ST SINCE '87</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4dec5de0bcb4d32a1e28ada66e2fc6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The escalating coronavirus emergency sent the stock market Thursday into its worst slide since the Black Monday crash of 1987, extending a sell-off that has now wiped out most of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Chelsea Manning released...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/12/chelsea-manning-release-ordered-federal-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge ordered the release of Chelsea Manning from jail, days after a reported suicide attempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 could be first virtual election...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/03/coronavirus-could-make-2020-first-virtual-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No rallies, handshakes, or live studio audiences show how the pandemic is already changing the way campaigns are run. A moderator is even skipping the next debate over possible exposure. Will virtual conventions be next?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City to Carl Icahn: Tear down Trump Plaza before it kills somebody...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/new-jersey/trump-atlantic-city-plaza-demolished-carl-icahn-20200312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former casino, now owned by billionaire Carl Icahn, is an immediate danger to the safety of people on the Boardwalk, city officials said. They are suing to force Icahn to tear it down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court,</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/487291-supreme-court-will-close-to-public-amid-coronavirus-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court will close to the public indefinitely starting on Thursday afternoon amid concerns over coronavirus, but the building remains open for "official business," a spokeswoman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar marries political consultant, months after affair claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/Ilhan-Omar-announces-new-marriage-months-after-15125718.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) - U.S. Rep. Ilhan Omar of Minnesota has married a political consultant who worked for her, months after the two were accused of having an affair, which she denied.  A marriage license filed in Washington, D.C., shows Omar married political consultant Tim Mynett on Wednesday. Omar announced her new marriage Wednesday night on Instagram, with a photo of her and a bearded man smiling and displaying wedding rings. "Got married! From partners in politics to life partners, so blessed," the post says, without identifying Mynett by name.  Filings with the Federal Election Commission show Omar's campaign paid Tim Mynett or his firm nearly $600,000 since July 2018. Though it may raise eyebrows, family members, including spouses, can be on the campaign payroll as long as the family member provides services at a fair market value.  Larry Jacobs, a politics professor at the University of Minnesota's Humphrey School of Public Affairs, said the work needs to be reasonable and there has to be actual work being done.  Jacobs said constituents may question the way Omar handled the situation.  "Remember the story began with her denying a relationship, and now she's marrying that person," Jacobs said. "I think there are legitimate questions that constituents might ask about whether Congresswoman Omar has been fully truthful in her discussion of this relationship, and the nature of her marriage to a previous husband," whom Omar divorced last fall.  A relationship between Omar and Mynett was publicly alleged in August, when Mynett's then-wife, Beth Mynett, filed for divorce and accused her husband and Omar of having an affair. In response, Tim Mynett filed his own court document denying that he told his wife he was in love with Omar and that he was ending his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Throws Surveillance Bill Into Chaos With Implicit Veto Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-throws-surveillance-bill-into-chaos-with-implicit-veto-threat/ar-BB116Evxc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison Square Garden closed 'for months'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/new-york-city-declares-state-of-emergency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large venues like Barclays Center and Madison Square Garden will likely be closed for months to try to contain the fast-spreading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March Madness canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/coronavirus-ncaa-conference-tournaments-cancellations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organization also canceled "all remaining winter and spring" championships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland,</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/coronavirus/2020/03/coronavirus-update-alexandria-records-1st-first-case-loudoun-co-schools-closed-for-more-than-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s a look at the latest coronavirus developments in the Washington, D.C. region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domestic Travel Could Be Curtailed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/12/world/coronavirus-live-news-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks plunged again despite the Fed offering at least $1.5 trillion worth of short-term loans to banks, with the S&amp;P 500 index tumbling 9.5 percent. A Brazilian official tested positive days after being with the president and Vice President Mike Pence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Fastest Supercomputer Tasked with Finding Cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/03/researchers-oak-ridge-national-lab-tap-supercomputing-help-combat-coronavirus/163708/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The efforts may eventually support scientists on their quest for the cure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Miami public hospital, docs and nurses 'begging'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article241109776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORST DAY SINCE '87...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dow-plunges-10-and-marks-worst-worst-day-since-the-1987-crash-as-coronavirus-crushes-wall-streets-buying-sentiment-2020-03-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks staged a fresh plunge Thursday, pushing the S&amp;amp;P 500 index and Nasdaq Composite into a bear market and officially ending a record-setting,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's high-stakes campaign to smear USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/china-smear-united-states-coronavirus-wuhan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a high-stakes strategy for the Asian nation fighting to keep its superpower status amid a national lockdown and palpable anger over claims of a cover-up made worse by an economic crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio Shutters All Schools For 3 Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/03/12/ohio-shuts-down-all-schools-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio is shutting down all K-12 schools for the next three weeks in an attempt to stop the spread of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America starts shut down...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/12/coronavirus-shutdowns-across-country-127018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Capitol to California, officials are taking aggressive new measures to limit social interactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB,</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28892315/sources-mlb-expected-suspend-spring-training</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball is delaying the start of the 2020 regular season by at least two weeks in response to the coronavirus pandemic, the league announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro being tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8106149/Trump-learn-TOMORROW-Brazilian-leader-shook-hands-Mar-Lago-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will learn Friday whether Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has tested positive for the coronavirus after the two men dined together at Mar-a-Lago on Saturday and shook hands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/12/broadway-shutting-down-all-productions-over-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broadway will shut down four to six weeks beginning tonight, due to the coronavirus outbreak, several sources told The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top adviser to supreme leader infected...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312174950-luqxo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/IRAN-AIDE (URGENT):Top adviser to Iran's supreme leader infected with coronavirus - Tasnim</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus vs Constitution? When liberties meet a pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article241106636.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL suspended...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nhl/story/_/id/28891430/sources-nhl-suspending-play-immediately-due-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NHL has suspended play because of the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB,</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/espn/now?nowId=1-28892331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read more on ESPN</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston doctors: Severe shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2020/03/12/nation/severe-shortage-tests-blunts-coronavirus-response-boston-doctors-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite assurances, Massachusetts is testing fewer people and revealing less information than other states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: SYSTEM 'FAILING'</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-relief-actions-awaited-cases-233032307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The leading U.S. infectious-disease official said the testing system in the country is failing. President Donald Trump’s travel restrictions drew criticism from European Union leaders and triggered a slump in airline stocks.Germany is prepared to abandon its long-standing balanced-budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> UK announces you must self-isolate even with mild cold symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-coronavirus-brits-mild-cough-21682819  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools have been told to cancel all foreign trips, and the elderly or anyone with underlying health conditions are advised to avoid cruise ships. It comes as the government officially moved into the "delay" phase of its response</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vast Iranian  burial pits visible from space...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Iran-s-coronavirus-burial-pits-are-so-vast-15125717.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two days after Iran declared its first cases of the novel coronavirus - in what would become one of the largest outbreaks of the illness outside of China - evidence of unusual activity appeared at a cemetery near where the infections emerged.  At the Behesht-e Masoumeh complex in Qom, about 80 miles south of Tehran, the excavation of a new section of the graveyard began as early as Feb. 21, satellite images show, and then rapidly expanded as the virus spread. By the end of the month, two large trenches - their lengths totaling 100 yards - were visible at the site from space.  According to expert analysis, video testimony and official statements, the graves were dug to accommodate the rising number of virus victims in Qom.  Iran, a nation of about 80 million people, has suffered a particularly deadly surge of coronavirus infections, including among its top leadership. Iran's Health Ministry says that 429 people have died of the virus, which causes the disease known as covid-19, and more than 10,000 have fallen ill. Among the dead are members of parliament, a former diplomat and even a senior adviser to the Supreme Leader. At least two dozen other officials, including a vice president, have been infected.  In Qom, the spiritual center of Iran's ruling Shiite clerics, more than 846 people have contracted the virus, officials say. Iran's government has not released an official death toll for Qom, however, where about 1.2 million people live. But videos, satellite images and other open-source data from the cemetery - a vast complex six miles north of the city center - suggest that the number of people struck down by the virus there is significantly higher than the official figure.  A senior imagery analyst at Maxar Technologies in Colorado said the size of the trenches and the speed with which they were excavated together...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Hanks, Rita Wilson isolated in Australian hospital...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/12/tom-hanks-rita-wilson-isolated-in-australian-hospital-amid-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’ll be “isolated for as long as public health and safety requires.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S NOT A HOAX:  TRUMP SPEECH FAILS TO REASSURE NATION...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tasked-reassuring-us-trump-fumbles-fumes-150003898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump had one job to do in a primetime address on coronavirus: reassure an anxious nation, a panicking stock market and divided world. "The virus will not have a chance against us," Trump claimed, echoing his stump speech lines about "killing terrorists" and forcing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China shuts down Everest... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-shuts-down-everest-over-coronavirus-084008527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has cancelled permits for Mount Everest because of the coronavirus, expedition organisers said Thursday, ahead of the spring climbing season on the world's highest peak. Last year's traffic-clogged spring window saw a record 885 people summit Everest, 644 of them from Nepal and 241 from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau working from home as wife tested...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/canada-pm-working-home-wife-tested-covid-19-170639234--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and his wife announced they were self-isolating Thursday as she undergoes tests for the new coronavirus after returning from a speaking engagement with "mild flu-like symptoms."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington strains for virus response amid public closures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6052e677cfc38b76224eccddb9f36eb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Washington is straining for an ample response to the coronavirus outbreak that is testing the nation's political and health care systems after President Donald Trump restricted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian positive for coronavirus days after posing with Trump and Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/528592/president-trump-coronavirus-brazil-aide-mike-pence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP aide to the president of Brazil has tested positive for coronavirus just days meeting with President Trump at Mar-a-Lago. Fabio Wajngarten, press secretary to president Jair Bolsonaro, tested…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus 'can survive in air'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/03/researchers-oak-ridge-national-lab-tap-supercomputing-help-combat-coronavirus/163708/ '&gt;America's Fastest Supercomputer Tasked with Finding Cure...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients contagious up to 37 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article241124531.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantined couple die of coronavirus two hours apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8104001/Elderly-couple-die-hours-apart-contracting-deadly-coronavirus-northern-Italy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Severa Belotti, 82, and Luigi Carrara, 86, lived in the town of Albino, in the northern Italian city of Bergamo, in Lombardy, and reportedly spent eight days locked at home with a fever of 39 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORWAY SHUTS COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/901770/entire-country-norway-shutting-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you think things have gotten bad in the United States â€” where St. Patrick's Day parades have been canceled, and the NBA is suspended for the rest of the season â€” just wait until you hear about Norway. Starting Thursday, the small Nordic country announced 'measures that will be the most extensive Norway's population has experienced in peacetime,' and which involve practically shutting down the entire country in order to slow the spread of the new coronavirus, Norwegian Minister of Health and Care Services Bent HÃ¸ie told the national broadcaster, NRK. In addition to kindergartens, child care facilities, schools, and universities closing nationwide, and a ban on both professional and amateur sports â€” measures that have been taken only regionally so far in the U.S. â€” the entire country of Norway is also requiring all hairdressers, massage clinics, gyms, and tattoo parlors to close, Life in Norway and Swedish journalist Peter Imanuelsen report based off the announcement on NRK. Cultural events are also banned, with museums, pools, and libraries additionally closing. While grocery stores will remain open, restaurants, bars, pubs, and nightclubs are required to close if they can't guarantee a three-foot distance between patrons. Buffets, naturally, are banned. Additionally, everyone entering Norway from anywhere other than another Nordic country will be required to be home-quarantined, regardless of symptoms â€” one of the most drastic measures taken in Europe so far. Healthcare professionals are no longer allowed to travel abroad, and the country is encouraging its citizens traveling abroad to return home at once. Oslo-based Twitter user Cathrine Wilhelmsen emphasized that 'Norway is shutting down â€¦ this is serious.' The country faces one of the worst outbreaks in Europe, with some 632 positive cases as of Thursday morning. 'It is extremely important that people follow this advice,' Norwegian Prime Minister Erna Solberg said. 'To be able to curb this, we need everyone to come together.' Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKET -25% SINCE PRESIDENT SAID 'BUY'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/12/stocks-fallen-trump-kudlow-buy-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. stock market has lost a quarter of its value since President Donald Trump and Larry Kudlow urged investors to buy because coronavirus was contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Had 'Mild Heart Attack' After Sentenced...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/harvey-weinstein-had-mild-heart-attack-after-being-sentenced-to-23-years-in-prison-fox-news-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He is being watched carefully at Bellevue,” his spokesperson told The Daily Beast on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says coronavirus epidemic peak has passed...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-says-peak-of-coronavirus-epidemic-has-passed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (REUTERS) - China has passed the peak of the coronavirus epidemic, the National Health Commission said on Thursday (March 12).. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: SUSPEND TAX COLLECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2020/03/12/jim-cramer-the-federal-government-should-stop-collecting-taxes-from-businesses-and-individuals-to-fight-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's Jim Cramer calls for radical fiscal policy--no taxes and fearless support for businesses--to support the economy amid the coronavirus pandemic. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SPEECH FAILS TO REASSURE NATION...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/12/trumps-coronavirus-speech-fails-to-unify-or-reassure-a-nation-on-edge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — If President Trump’s goals in his prime-time address to the nation were to reassure Americans and unify the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEDLAM AT AIRPORTS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8103753/American-tourists-desperate-flee-Europe-descend-Barcelona-airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of travelers, confused as to whether they will be let back home, rushed to airports across Europe Wednesday night and in the early hours of Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCESS Cruises cancels all sailings for two months...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/carnivals-princess-cruises-to-pause-global-ship-operations-for-60-days-over-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Carnival, which owns Princess Cruises, have fallen more than 57% since Jan. 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress shutting Capitol, House, Senate office buildings to public...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2020/03/congress-shutting-us-capitol-house-and-senate-office-buildings-to-public-until-april-1-in-reaction-to-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Congress shutting US Capitol, House and Senate office buildings to public until April 1 in reaction to coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL PRESIDENT BOLSONARO BEING MONITORED AND TESTED...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-president-jair-bolsonaro-being-135238577.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Peculiar Life of the Man in the 'BIG LEBOWSKI' House: Wild L.A. Mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/inside-nba-superfan-james-goldsteins-wild-la-party-mansion-1283516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Goldstein, the city's most unapologetic 80-year-old bon  vivant (and Lakers fixture), throws parties with models and Leonardo DiCaprio as he rushes to finish his architectural legacy: "The villains always live in the modern houses."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civility, or civil war?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/486819-civility-or-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may take a new generation to restore common courtesy and decency to American politics once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man knew had virus, flew from JFK to Palm Beach anyway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/12/coronavirus-in-ny-passenger-on-jetblue-flight-from-jfk-tests-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a JetBlue flight from JFK Airport has tested positive for the coronavirus after landing in Palm Beach, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate staffer tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/us-senate-staffer-tests-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer for US Senator Maria Cantwell has tested positive for coronavirus – the first known congressional worker to catch the virus, her office said Wednesday. The unidentified patient, who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It caused mass panic': Rush to get back...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312095943-wmvg5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/EUROPE-AIRPORT (TV, PIX):"It caused a mass panic": travellers in Europe rush to get back to US after Trump order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sit, stay forever: Americans willing to pay top dollar to keep old dogs alive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312092305-1g7b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DOGS/ (TV, PIX):Sit, stay forever: Americans willing to pay top dollar to keep old dogs alive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World walls off as leaders warn pandemic will worsen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a123df57403757910e63ca01fde2f322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Sweeping travel bans accelerated across the globe on Thursday, walling regions apart, keeping people inside their homes and slowing the engines of commerce in an effort to stem the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems smell blood in Texas after sky-high primary turnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/12/democrats-texas-primary-126651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party is targeting another half-dozen House seats in the Lone Star State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A no-savings generation is cashing in its sneaker collections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/a-no-savings-generation-is-cashing-in-its-sneaker-collections/ar-BB10Zo24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUTURES HIT LIMIT DOWN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/11/futures-are-steady-wednesday-night-after-dow-closes-in-bear-market-traders-await-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came after yet another wild session on Wall Street and the demise of the Dow's record-setting bull market run that began in March 2009.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals brace for onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/487151-hospitals-brace-for-coronavirus-onslaught</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are bracing for an onslaught of patients as the coronavirus spreads in the United States, with experts warning that a spike in cases could overwhelm the health care system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macho men more likely to suffer health, social issues in old age...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/macho-men-more-likely-to-suffer-health-social-issues-in-old-age/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toxic masculinity may literally be hazardous to men’s health. While movies may make the macho lifestyle seem alluring, a new study has found that hypermasculine males could suffer from a host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Re-election Chances Suddenly Look Shakier...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/12/trumps-re-election-chances-suddenly-look-shakier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump faces the biggest challenge yet to his prospects of being re-elected, with his advisers’ two major assumptions for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Going To Die, Might as Well Do It At DISNEY WORLD'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/12/if-im-going-to-get-sick-and-die-i-might-as-well-do-it-at-disney-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Vice President Mike Pence was asked, earlier this month, if he would feel comfortable taking his children and grandchildren</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
