<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside Wuhan lab: French engineering, deadly viruses, big mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/inside-wuhan-lab-french-engineering-095320117.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One chilly morning in February 2017, a tall Chinese scientist in his 50s named Yuan Zhiming showed Bernard Cazeneuve, then the French prime minister, around Wuhan's new high-security pathogen lab. Built with French engineering, it was China's first P4 lab, one of several dozen in the world with that highest security designation. Yuan, the director of the lab, had worked more than a decade to make it a reality. Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stories f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victorious Taliban gloat over ruins of CIA's Afghan base...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210907-victorious-taliban-gloat-over-ruins-of-cia-s-afghan-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victorious Taliban gloat over ruins of CIA's Afghan base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL return-to-normal season doesn't look so normal yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/sports_copy_5037_20201105191556/article/fbn-virus-normal-season-16438612.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The league said late last month that it is interested in a vaccine requirement for all...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans increasingly balk at intrusive govt surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-afghanistan-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-government-surveillance-d365f3a818bb9d096e8e3b5713f9f856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As the 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks approaches, Americans increasingly balk at intrusive government surveillance in the name of national security, and only about a third believe that the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq were worth fighting, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotions raw before Paris trial for Islamic State carnage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/soccer-sports-religion-trials-paris-1c0332c13b10c6d5d4744c59376f97d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — For the music lover, it was nearly three hours at gunpoint, wondering if he would become yet another body on the floor of the Bataclan concert hall in Paris. For the grieving mother, the night of carnage robbed her of her son and tarnished her view of the vibrant neighborhood they both loved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People spend 100 DAYS of lives deciding what to watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3614968/time-brits-spend-tv-shows-films-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL SURGE WARNING</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/israel-e2-80-99s-covid-surge-shows-the-world-what-e2-80-99s-coming-next/ar-AAObmmF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former leader on vaccines is now focusing on boosters to protect the vulnerable after cases rose to a record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia set to remove Richmond's Lee statue on Wednesday...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/george-floyd-richmond-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-virginia-6fe850aff69b858d99b34436b9b87d8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A towering statue of Confederate Gen. Robert E. Lee in Richmond, Virginia, will be taken down on Wednesday as a symbol of racial injustice, more than 130 years after it was erected in tribute to the South’s Civil War leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau, facing 'anti-vaxxer mobs' on election trail, is met with flying gravel at campaign stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trudeau-facing-e2-80-98anti-vaxxer-mobs-e2-80-99-on-election-trail-is-met-with-flying-gravel-at-campaign-stop/ar-AAOam3A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian prime minister dismissed the incident, comparing it to when pumpkin seeds were thrown at him in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young pot consumers twice as likely to suffer from heart attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/07/health/cannabis-heart-attack-young-adult-study-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 1.3% of adults under age 45 who used cannabis within a 30-day period later had a heart attack while only .8% of non-cannabis consumers suffered the same fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning of Income Gap, Xi Tells China Tycoons to Share Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/07/warning-of-income-gap-xi-tells-chinas-tycoons-to-share-wealth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four decades ago, Deng Xiaoping declared that China would “let some people get rich first” in its race for growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodels Speak Out Against Sex Harassment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/07/supermodels-speak-out-against-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of fashion month, six women, all former models, flew into Paris from across the world — not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's Green. She's Young. And She Wants to Change Germany...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/07/shes-green-shes-young-and-she-wants-to-change-germany/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOCHUM, Germany — The woman who wants to replace Chancellor Angela Merkel strode onto the stage in sneakers and a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Coup Fears Rise as Thousands of Bolsonaro Supporters Flock to Capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/brazil-coup-fears-rise-thousands-jair-bolsonaro-supporters-flock-capital-1626572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An open letter signed by more than 150 leftwing leaders warned that the rallies could be a prelude to a military coup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tent cities now part of American landscape...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tent-cities-now-part-of-the-landscape-16438916.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just outside Union Station, there's a moment when tourists getting off the Amtrak Capitol...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems stare down nightmare September...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/570825-democrats-stare-down-nightmare-september</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are staring down a nightmare September, a month jam-packed with deadlines and bruising fights over their top priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't cry for me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3612294/michael-k-williams-shared-cryptic-final-instagram-sudden-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian militants escape from high-security Israeli prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/six-palestinians-escape-high-security-israeli-prison-israeli-radio-2021-09-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Palestinian militants broke out of a maximum security Israeli prison on Monday in a Hollywood-style escape that left their jailors peering through a hole in the floor of a cell, and had Palestinians celebrating in the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Global First, El Salvador Adopts Bitcoin as Currency...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/07/in-global-first-el-salvador-adopts-bitcoin-as-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — El Salvador on Tuesday became the first country to adopt Bitcoin as legal tender, allowing the cryptocurrency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Miami Public School Staffers Dead In Just 10 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/15-miami-dade-public-school-021517732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a tremendous loss," said one education official of the death of a 30-year teacher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-year-old girl dies on amusement park ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/local-news/glenwood-caverns-adventure-park-closed-through-tuesday-following-fatal-incident-on-ride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenwood Caverns Adventure Park is closed Monday and Tuesday after a young girl died on a ride called the Haunted Mine Drop on Sunday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MU IN 49 STATES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-mu-covid-variant-now-found-in-49-u-s-states/ar-AAO9Uf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since being discovered in Colombia in January, the Mu variant of COVID-19 has spread to nearly four dozen countries and has made its presence known in Hawaii and Alaska. It has so far been found in 49 states with Nebraska being the only state to not have a Mu variant case detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First responders nationwide resist mandates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-f459b8d187cd915e17588873e07e8bdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;March 11, 2021. It was supposed to be a turning point in the coronavirus pandemic for Erin Tokley, a longtime Philadelphia police officer, Baptist minister and 47-year-old father of three. It was supposed to be the day of his vaccine appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WIRE', 'BOARDWALK EMPIRE' Star...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/movies/movie-news/michael-k-williams-dead-1221006/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrated actor who also appeared in Lovecraft County found dead inside his Brooklyn home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seniors left in dark, hot facilities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-dd7efb4ba9b29389fa5888fd930dec5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Crews in Louisiana have restored power to nearly 70% of greater New Orleans and nearly all of Baton Rouge after Hurricane Ida, but outside those large cities, getting lights back on is a complex challenge that will last almost all of September, utility executives said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALASKA AIR passenger booted 'for being fat in sports bra'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/09/06/woman-kicked-off-alaska-airlines-flight-sports-bra-fat-discrimination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman allegedly kicked off an Alaska Airlines flight for her outfit believes she was discriminated against for being fat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats &amp; Leaks: New Docs Show Just How Crazy GA Recount Fiasco Got...</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/docs-show-internal-discord-during-083410653.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastBack in January 2021, as then-President Donald Trump was calling on Georgia election officials to “find 11,780 votes,” new documents show that the secretary of state’s office in Georgia was in full crisis mode.There were death threats ​​promising to “make the Boston bombings look like child’s play.” Impassioned pleas for Georgia’s top elections official to stand firm in the face of pressure from Trump to break the law. And an alarmed state offici</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham Predicts Military 'Will be Going Back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/lindsey-graham-predicts-the-us-military-will-be-going-back-into-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican senator Lindsey Graham insists the United States "will be going back into Afghanistan" due to the threat of terror.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China flies 19 nuke jets into Taiwan air space for 'WW3 invasion' war games...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3608771/china-flies-nuke-bombers-fighter-jets-taiwan-air-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD War Three fears are mounting after China flew 19 nuke bombers and fighter jets into Taiwan air space for “invasion” war games. The latest Chinese military incursion on Sunday invo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL PLANS 4TH DOSE!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9959811/Israel-planning-administer-FOURTH-Covid-vaccine-adjusted-fight-new-variants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country's national coronavirus czar Salman Zarka said the country needs to prepare for a fourth injection, which could be modified to better protect against new variants of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans for $400-billion new city in American desert unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/telosa-marc-lore-blake-ingels-new-city/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cleanliness of Tokyo, the diversity of New York and the social services of Stockholm: Billionaire Marc Lore has outlined his vision for a 5-million-person "new city in America" and appointed a world-famous architect to design it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Fashion Week back in person -- masked and vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/06/new-york-fashion-week-is-back-in-person-masked-and-vaxxed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashionistas will be strutting all over the Big Apple this week for the first time in 18 months. New York Fashion Week shows will take over Battery Park, the Rainbow Room, the streets of Soho and t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael K. Williams found dead in NYC apartment...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/06/actor-michael-k-williams-found-dead-in-nyc-apartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Wire’’ actor Michael K. Williams was found dead in his Brooklyn apartment Monday afternoon, law-enforcement sources told The Post. Drug paraphernalia was found in the apartment, suggesting a p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment Benefits Expire for Millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/unemployment-benefits-expire-for-millions-without-pushback-from-biden/ar-AAOa2M5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Expanded unemployment benefits that have kept millions of Americans afloat during the pandemic expired on Monday, setting up the abrupt cutoff of assistance to 7.5 million people as the Delta variant rattles the pandemic recovery. The end of the aid came without objection from President Biden or his top economic advisers, who have become caught in a political fight over the benefits and are now banking on other federal help and an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyotes flood U.S. border with Ecuadorians...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/06/coyotes-flood-us-border-with-ecuadorians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuadorians typically pay up to $15,000 per person to human smugglers, also known as “polleros,” or chicken herders, to reach the southern border, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Cradle to Grave, Dems Move to Expand Social Safety Net...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/06/from-cradle-to-grave-democrats-move-to-expand-social-safety-net/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — When congressional committees meet this week to begin formally drafting Democrats’ ambitious social policy plan, they will be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curtain divides male, female students as Afghan universities reopen...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210906165017-umd9e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/WOMEN-CLASSROOM (PIX, TV):A curtain divides male, female students as Afghan universities reopen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ will 'protect' abortion seekers in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/abortion-business-health-texas-738cfb097227037ac0ce33ccb79c2e4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department said Monday that it will not tolerate violence against anyone who is trying to obtain an abortion in Texas as federal officials explore options to challenge a new state law that bans most abortions .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash flood watch for New Orleans as half million still without power...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/flash-flood-watch-orleans-half-million-residents-power/story?id=79856484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Orleans is facing a flash flood watch amid Hurricane Ida recovery efforts in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As El Salvador adopts Bitcoin, young president dismantles democracy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/el-salvador-adopts-bitcoin-young-100039614.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Nayib Bukele faced international condemnation after his supporters moved to fire a third of the nation's judges and clear the way for Bukele to seek a second term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors see growing number of respiratory disease in kids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-6325b093c223b98d5daa15d495e657ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Pediatricians and public health officials say a common respiratory disease that most children can easily deal with is spreading earlier than usual in Wisconsin. The disease, called respiratory syncytial virus, or RSV, is common in kids under age 2 and usually results in mild symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic French New Wave actor Jean-Paul Belmondo dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210906-iconic-french-new-wave-actor-jean-paul-belmondo-dies-aged-88-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Jean-Paul Belmondo, one of postwar French cinema's biggest stars and whose charismatic smile illuminated the screen for half a century, has died aged 88 in his Paris home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back on Trail, Bernie Sanders Campaigns for Legislative Legacy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/05/back-on-the-trail-sanders-campaigns-for-a-legislative-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEDAR RAPIDS, Iowa — With a khaki-clad leg propped up on a bench, hand on his hip, Senator Bernie Sanders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortages of supplies and workers will delay rebuilding...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-1ebb836d454ad09b0da429e0ba10e98a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Sobol, owner of Big Easy Construction in New Orleans, has bad news for homeowners who've been calling about roofs damaged by Hurricane Ida or to get an update on renovations that were scheduled before the storm ripped through the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1073-HP PORSCHE Mission R Previews Electric Future of Racing...</title>
      <link>https://www.caranddriver.com/news/a37484399/porsche-mission-r-electric-future-racing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.caranddriver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The electric Mission R concept is about the size of the 718 Cayman but wider and lower, and it can hold its own with a 911 GT3 Cup car around the track.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic spiritual boon for some, and Rosh Hashanah shows what's changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Pandemic-has-been-a-spiritual-boon-for-some-and-16437608.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barrie Rein Thunemann was a spiritual seeker for decades, looking for a deep Jewish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans 911 Dispatcher On Run From Police After Hanging Up On Callers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/09/04/911-dispatcher-on-run-hanging-up-caller-new-orleans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Precious Stephens is reportedly on the run from the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Week returning to New York with in-person energy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fashion-week-returning-york-person-015250128.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Rapid Move Into Banking Elicits Alarm in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/05/cryptos-rapid-move-into-banking-elicits-alarm-in-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BlockFi, a fast-growing financial start-up whose headquarters in Jersey City are across the Hudson River from Wall Street, aspires to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Confidant Dies Days After Becoming China Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/the-german-ambassador-to-china-jan-hecker-dies/a-59094563</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hecker had been ambassador only for a few days before he died. German Foreign Minister Heiko Maas said there was "no evidence" that the death was linked to Hecker's diplomatic role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasured West trout streams wither amid heat, drought...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-environment-and-nature-droughts-science--fb247eb1eb5f2889afcbe6c3456c675d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SARATOGA, Wyo. (AP) — The North Platte River in southern Wyoming has been so low in places lately that a toddler could easily wade across and thick mats of olive-green algae grow in the lazy current.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
