<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell's tawdry fall from grace -- and new PR push...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Ghislaine-Maxwell-s-tawdry-fall-from-grace-and-16032146.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In times gone by, she luxuriated on a yacht named in her honor by her publishing mogul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How year of restrictions has changed friendships forever...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/03/17/how-the-pandemic-has-changed-our-friendships-possibly-for-the-better-14132264/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are learning to value quality over quantity friendships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Assembly Opens Cuomo Impeachment Inquiry, Hires Law Firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ny-assembly-opens-cuomo-impeachment-inquiry-hires-law-firm/ar-BB1eGhad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Assembly on Wednesday said it hired law firm Davis Polk &amp; Wardwell LLP to carry out an impeachment investigation into Governor Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Customer Angry Over Wrong Wing Order Throws Cash Register Through Window...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/03/16/wingstop-vandalized-wrong-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent reaction to a restaurant order led to chaos at a Wingstop in Antelope over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pizza, guns and God'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/17/atlanta-massage-parlor-shooting-suspect-had-passion-for-guns-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old man suspected of killing eight people – six of them Asian women – at three metro Atlanta massage parlors professed a passion for guns and God, according to a report. Robert Aaron Lo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next 'Jewish Jordan'? Can Ryan Turell become first Orthodox NBA player?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/next-jewish-jordan-ryan-turell-110038000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Van Nuys native Ryan Turell was on a historic NCAA tournament tear when the pandemic shut down his season, but not his dream of becoming the first Orthodox Jew to play in the NBA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientific breakthrough paves way for Alzheimer's test years before symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/health/alzheimers-dementia-university-manchester-study-blood-test-916659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Currently, the disease can only be diagnosed by brain scans after a person has been showing symptoms such as memory loss</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After taking on Wall St bears, REDDITORS pumping money into saving gorillas...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/redditors-reddit-money-donate-adopt-apes-gorillas-gamestop-2021-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street Bets members have spent more than $300,000 adopting gorillas through the Dian Fossey Gorilla Fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The robots indistinguishable from humans...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/03/15/hyper-realistic-skin-for-humanoid-robots-is-being-sculpted-in-russia-14246326/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slip me some skin?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House limits what Border Patrol can share with media about migrant surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/biden-administration-limits-what-border-patrol-can-share-media-about-n1261133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restrictions on what border agents can share with the media were passed down verbally, say officials. Some have released videos of the border surge anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA reviewing hundreds of cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-faa-is-reviewing-hundreds-of-cases-involving-unruly-airline-passengers/ar-BB1eEaMn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FAA said it will extend a "zero-tolerance" policy aimed at curbing unruly behavior on flights during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era beckons for Cuba, without a Castro in power...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210317-new-era-beckons-for-cuba-without-a-castro-in-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New era beckons for Cuba, without a Castro in power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacist propaganda in hit record in 2020, group says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210317083338-jdoux</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WHITE SUPREMACY/ (PIX):White supremacist propaganda in U.S. hit record in 2020, group says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As endangered birds lose their songs, they can't find mates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-asia-pacific-birds-f38f5c97cccc50cba1e884a907db13d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Male songbirds usually learn their tunes from adult mentors. But when aspiring crooners lack proper role models, they hit all the wrong notes — and have less success attracting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious High-Altitude Flight Corridor Opened Between Area 51, Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39787/mysterious-high-altitude-flight-corridor-was-opened-up-between-area-51-and-the-pacific</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The restricted strip of airspace bridged the Nevada Test and Training Range with the Pacific Ocean during a few-hour window last Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market for Musical Gear Amping Up Like Never Before...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/the-market-for-musical-gear-is-amping-up-like-never-before/ar-BB1eFBCy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amateur musicians are powering the demand of both new and secondhand instruments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year into pandemic, Florida booming and DeSantis taking credit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/17/politics/ron-desantis-covid-florida/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year of criticism by health experts, mockery from comedians and blistering critiques from political rivals, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is standing unabashedly tall among the nation's governors on the front lines of the coronavirus fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Ailing Empire: Fortune Slips as Covid, Riot Take Toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2021-donald-trump-net-worth-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revenue is down and debts are coming due.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's rolling disaster is threat to world...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-rolling-coronavirus-disaster-is-a-threat-to-the-world/ar-BB1eFhPN </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Aliens Arrive, What Will They Look Like? Zoologist Has Answers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/16/when-the-aliens-arrive-what-will-they-look-like-a-zoologist-has-answers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ZOOLOGIST’S GUIDE TO THE GALAXY What Animals on Earth Reveal About Aliens — and Ourselves By Arik Kershenbaum Is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slay suspect was 'big into religion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/seven-killed-in-shootings-at-atlanta-spas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four of the victims were Asian women, and a 21-year-old was in custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Asian Americans verbally and physically attacked, shunned during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asian-americans-verbally-physically-attacked-182920825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 68% of the anti-Asian attacks documented during the pandemic were verbal harassment, 21% were shunning and 11% were physical assaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE:  Candace Owens says she's '100% suing' Cardi B...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2524479/candace-owens-blasts-cardi-b-poisoning-minds-grammys/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOWING a bitter back and forth over Twitter, Candace Owens said she’s planning on suing Cardi B after the rapper tweeted a fake tweet from saying Owens’ husband cheated on her with h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russia boosted Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/03/16/us-intelligence-says-russia-boosted-trump-put-down-biden-in-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia did not attempt to physically alter voting process or election results but did launch propaganda efforts against Biden and for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA-Based Dating? NETFLIX Series Isn't So Far Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/netflix-the-one-dna-match-dating-real-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s new relationship drama series The One follows the founder of a fictional company that scientifically matches people with their perfect partner — using DNA. Though the show is based on the book of the same name by John Marrs and is completely fictional, you may be wondering whether DNA matching is possible in real […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS to get big stimulus boost as checks are spent on lattes...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/starbucks-upcoming-gains-from-restaurant-reopenings-and-federal-stimulus-drive-analyst-upgrade-11615908088</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurant restrictions are the biggest hurdle to getting young customers back through the door, according to BTIG data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside The Cuomo Impeachment Fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-the-new-york-democrats-messy-fight-over-whether-to-impeach-andrew-cuomo-213249118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With mounting sexual misconduct accusations and an alleged cover-up of nursing home deaths, New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo is facing an investigation from his fellow Democrats in the state Assembly that could result in his removal from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 killed in 3 shootings at Georgia massage parlor, spas... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/3-dead-shooting-georgia-massage-parlor-suspect-loose-n1261262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were killed in Cherokee County, and in Atlanta, four people were shot at or near two spas. The shootings have not been linked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland', CBP want military support...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/03/16/border-deployments-could-be-extended-past-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security has asked for an extension to the mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admiral: China Used Covid to Expand 'Influence'...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/03/16/southcoms-faller-china-used-pandemic-to-expand-corrosive-insidious-influence-in-central-south-america-u-s-influence-eroding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has used the COVID-19 pandemic to rapidly expand its “corrosive, insidious influence” – from money laundering for transnational gangsters to using its own ships to illegally fish protected waters and benefit from illegal logging and mining – “in our neighborhood,” U.S. Southern Command’s top officer said Tuesday. “I can’t stress enough the full-court press” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of hot spots emerge in Midwest, New York City...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/after-weeks-of-declining-cases-echoes-of-hot-spots-emerge-in-upper-midwest-new-york-city-area/ar-BB1eEs17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan has seen a rise in hospitalizations and positive test results. Minnesota’s numbers are creeping up, as are Maryland’s and New Jersey’s. Many places, including New York City and surrounding counties, are no longer seeing steady declines in cases, despite intensive vaccination efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Serial Stowaway Arrested AGAIN At O'Hare...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/serial-stowaway-marilyn-hartman-interview-cbs-2-investigators-brad-edwards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California heads toward recall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-elections-california-gavin-newsom-recall-elections-d0a0cba5a08af32d115a2d1f79b32661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCKLIN, Calif. (AP) — A plodding, months-long review kicks off Wednesday to confirm what appears inevitable: California Gov. Gavin Newsom will face a recall election that could oust the Democrat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Sharon Osbourne Referred to Julie Chen as 'Wonton', 'Slanty Eyes'...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/exclusive-sharon-osbourne-frequently</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharon Osbourne, co-host of the CBS daytime panel show “The Talk,” would frequently refer to then-co-host Julie Chen, who is Chinese American, as “wonton” and “slanty eyes,” according to multiple sources, including former co-host Leah Remini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAKERS star a 'noted YANKEES fan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nba/2021/03/16/lebron-james-becomes-part-owner-red-sox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James and longtime friend Maverick Carter reportedly entered the venture together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron becomes part owner of RED SOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/31076745/source-lebron-james-becomes-part-owner-boston-red-sox-joins-fenway-sports-group-partner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James has become a partner in the Fenway Sports Group, making the NBA superstar a part owner of the Boston Red Sox, a source has confirmed to ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human tear glands grown in lab actually cry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/human-tear-glands-grown-in-a-lab-actually-cry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers have an ambitious vision for their organoid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah campaign against porn marches on with phone filter plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-utah-coronavirus-pandemic-pornography-laws-d2f3911b7887f2f145918d1718bf2504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Conservative lawmakers in Utah have fired another salvo in their longtime campaign against online porn with a new requirement that all cellphones and tablets sold in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea 'readying first nuke weapons test' since Biden took office...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2524190/north-korea-planning-first-nuke-weapon-test-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea is allegedly preparing to carry out its “first nuclear weapons test” since President Joe Biden took office, United States intelligence has learned. CNN reported on the news …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin pushed Joe misinfo to Don allies and media in '20 election, USA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/16/putin-pushed-biden-misinformation-to-trump-allies-during-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Vladimir Putin authorized intelligence assets to promote misinformation about President Joe Biden through people close to then-President Donald Trump, an intelligence report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Exvangelicals' Living Uniquely American Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akdbee/what-its-like-to-leave-the-evangelical-community-exvangelicals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abandoning the religion you were raised in is a long-standing tradition. But for former evangelicals, leaving the church is a lonely path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Lightning may have sparked life on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210316-lightning-may-have-sparked-life-on-earth-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lightning may have sparked life on Earth, study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: New strain might be able to evade tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210316-france-investigating-new-coronavirus-variant-detected-in-brittany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coronavirus variant has been found in the French region of Brittany, the French health ministry said in a statement late Monday, adding that an initial analysis did not show this new variant to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAIBBI: The Sovietization of the American Press...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/opinion/matt-taibbi-the-sovietization-of-the-american-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Epidemic: Hundreds of burnt, stripped abandoned cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/local/article/oakland-abandoned-car-epidemic-16027155.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swaths of inoperable vehicles are plaguing Black and brown communities. Residents say the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet packs on way to battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/03/16/jet-packs-are-on-their-way-to-a-battlefield-near-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 2021 will be good for something: Jet packs!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars Has Much More Water Than Previously Known...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5947142/water-on-mars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if most of Mars' water never actually drifted into space?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Can't Hear Signals -- Because Earth Too Loud...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM: CA recall appears to have enough signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/03/16/newsom-california-recall-appears-to-have-enough-signatures-1368400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor has quickly signaled that his campaign will paint the recall effort as an outgrowth of pro-Trump extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why having kids doesn't necessarily make you happier, according to research...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/16/does-having-children-make-you-happier-science-of-parenthood-explained.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents are not happier than nonparents, according to research, but there are other benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports About to Look Like '19 Again...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/03/sports-are-about-to-look-like-2019-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Rangers and Wrestlemania are paving the way for crowded stadiums and arenas to become the norm within weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bereaved families call for judge-led public inquiry into UK response...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/mar/16/bereaved-families-call-for-judge-led-public-inquiry-into-uk-covid-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson can decide whether to heed calls for wide-ranging inquiry or keep a tighter focus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch scientists grow human tear glands...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/mar/16/for-crying-out-loud-dutch-scientists-grow-human-tear-glands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creation of mini-organs using stem cells will help research into tear-related disorders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope navigates divided church...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/on-same-sex-unions-pope-francis-must-navigate-a-divided-church/ar-BB1eEbR7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarization of Catholics around the world could explain the course the pope is trying to set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Dems Launch 'Ron Be Gone' to Oust DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.wptv.com/news/political/ron-be-gone-group-led-by-south-florida-democrats-aims-to-oust-desantis-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida Democrats have announced the creation of Ron Be Gone, a new political group aimed at ensuring Gov. Ron DeSantis doesn't win re-election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Elliot Page becomes first trans MAN to star on TIME cover...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/16/elliot-page-undergoes-top-surgery-it-transformed-my-life/?_ga=2.220168217.1444238805.1615859795-160136807.1611102406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He covers Time Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE TO MONITOR SLEEP, BREATHING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-nest-adds-sleep-tracking-130000660.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Google’s Nest unit is expanding into health technology with a feature that tracks sleep patterns, offering a potential new revenue stream but also raising privacy concerns.The company unveiled the second-generation model of its Nest Hub smart display in a blog post Tuesday, and this time it comes with a function called Sleep Sensing that monitors the breathing and movement of a person sleeping next to the screen -- without a camera or needing to wear a device in bed.The system also detects disturbances such as coughing and snoring, along with light and temperature changes using the Nest Hub’s built-in microphones and ambient light and temperature sensors. Over time, it learns the user’s sleep patterns and gives personalized recommendations.Ashton Udall, a senior product manager at Google Nest, said Sleep Sensing will be available as a free preview until next year. That suggests the company may begin charging for the service in the future.Nest was a pioneer in so-called smart home technology through its internet-connected thermostat. Google acquired the company for $3.2 billion in 2014. Since then, Nest struggled with some new product launches, lost its founders and dealt with recurring privacy questions.On Tuesday, the internet giant addressed the privacy implications of Nest’s new sleep-sensing feature. The system relies on a low-energy radar technology called Soli to do the tracking, but it can be disabled.Audio of users’ snores and coughs will be processed on the Nest Hub device rather than being sent to Google’s servers. There’s even a hardware switch that physically disables the microphone. Users can also review and delete their sleep data at any time, and Google stressed that the information isn’t used for personalized ads.Google, Amazon.com Inc. and Apple Inc. have developed smart displays and speakers to expand their platforms further into consumers’ homes and lives.Fresh off its acquisition of Fitbit Inc., which makes wearable health devices, Google is also making a stronger effort to commercialize years of research it’s done on human health. The company said it will look for ways to integrate Nest with Fitbit’s sleep-tracking features in the future.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Threatens to Block TWITTER as Content Dispute Escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-social-media-russia-child-pornography-suicides-726fc480f89a499605623e9a08c19017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian authorities said Tuesday they would block Twitter in a month if it doesn't take steps to remove banned content, a move that escalates the Russian government’s drawn-out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microbes Unknown to Science Discovered on Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/four-bacterial-strains-discovered-on-the-iss-may-help-grow-better-space-plants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The menagerie of bacterial and fungal species living among us is ever growing - and this is no exception in low-gravity environments, such as the International Space Station (ISS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive piece of junk tossed from ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/space-news/massive-piece-of-space-junk-tossed-from-iss-sets-record/916013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weighing in at nearly 3 tons, the object is the largest ever jettisoned from the International Space Station and is expected to float around in space for the next few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes First Major Tax Hike Since 1993...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-eyes-first-major-tax-060001525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden is planning the first major federal tax hike since 1993 to help pay for the long-term economic program designed as a follow-up to his pandemic-relief bill, according to people familiar with the matter.Unlike the $1.9 trillion Covid-19 stimulus act, the next initiative, which is expected to be even bigger, won’t rely just on government debt as a funding source. While it’s been increasingly clear that tax hikes will be a component -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has said at least part of the next bill will have to be paid for, and pointed to higher rates -- key advisers are now making preparations for a package of measures that could include an increase in both the corporate tax rate and the individual rate for high earners.With each tax break and credit having its own lobbying constituency to back it, tinkering with rates is fraught with political risk. That helps explain why the tax hikes in Bill Clinton’s signature 1993 overhaul stand out from the modest modifications done since.For the Biden administration, the planned changes are an opportunity not just to fund key initiatives like infrastructure, climate and expanded help for poorer Americans, but also to address what Democrats argue are inequities in the tax system itself. The plan will test both Biden’s capacity to woo Republicans and Democrats’ ability to remain unified.“His whole outlook has always been that Americans believe tax policy needs to be fair, and he has viewed all of his policy options through that lens,” said Sarah Bianchi, head of U.S. public policy at Evercore ISI and a former economic aide to Biden. “That is why the focus is on addressing the unequal treatment between work and wealth.”While the White House has rejected an outright wealth tax, as proposed by progressive Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren, the administration’s current thinking does target the wealthy.The White House is expected to propose a suite of tax increases, mostly mirroring Biden’s 2020 campaign proposals, according to four people familiar with the discussions.The tax hikes included in any broader infrastructure and jobs package are likely to include repealing portions of President Donald Trump’s 2017 tax law that benefit corporations and wealthy individuals, as well as making other changes to make the tax code more progressive, said the people familiar with the plan.The following are among proposals currently planned or under consideration, according to the people, who asked not to be named as the discussions are private:Raising the corporate tax rate to 28% from 21%Paring back tax preferences for so-called pass-through businesses, such as limited-liability companies or partnershipsRaising the income tax rate on individuals earning more than $400,000Expanding the estate tax’s reachA higher capital-gains tax rate for individuals earning at least $1 million annually. (Biden on the campaign trail proposed applying income-tax rates, which would be higher)White House economist Heather Boushey underlined that Biden doesn’t intend to boost taxes on people earning less than $400,000 a year. But for “folks at the top who’ve been able to benefit from this economy and haven’t been this hard hit, there’s a lot of room there to think about what kinds of revenue we can raise,” she said in a Bloomberg TV interview Monday.An independent analysis of the Biden campaign tax plan done by the Tax Policy Center estimated it would raise $2.1 trillion over a decade, though the administration’s plan is likely to be smaller. Bianchi earlier this month wrote that congressional Democrats might agree to $500 billion.The overall program has yet to be unveiled, with analysts penciling in $2 trillion to $4 trillion. No date has yet been set for an announcement, though the White House said the plan would follow the signing of the Covid-19 relief bill.An outstanding question for Democrats is which parts of the package need to be funded, amid debate over whether infrastructure ultimately pays for itself -- especially given current borrowing costs, which remain historically low. Efforts to make the expanded child tax credit in the pandemic-aid bill permanent -- something with a price tag estimated at more than $1 trillion over a decade -- could be harder to sell if pitched as entirely debt-financed.What Bloomberg’s Economists Say...“The next major legislative initiative, infrastructure investment, could provide the sort of durable economic gains that not only support higher pay, but promote diffusion of those gains across demographic lines and political persuasions.”--Andrew Husby and Eliza Winger, U.S. economistsFor the full report, click hereDemocrats would need at least 10 Republicans to back the bill to move it under regular Senate rules. But GOP members are signaling they are prepared to fight.“We’ll have a big robust discussion about the appropriateness of a big tax increase,” Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell said last month, predicting Democrats would pursue a reconciliation bill that forgoes the GOP and would aim for a corporate tax even higher than 28%.Kevin Brady, the top Republican on the House Ways &amp; Means Committee, said, “There seems to a be a real drive to tax investment of capital gains at marginal income rates,” and called that a “terrible economic mistake.”While about 18% of the George W. Bush administration’s tax cuts were allowed to expire in a 2013 deal, and other legislation has seen some increases in levies, 1993 marks the last comprehensive set of increases, experts say. That bill passed on a two-vote margin in the House and required the vice president to break a tie in the Senate.“I don’t think it is an understatement to say the current partisan environment is more severe than 1993” said Ken Kies, managing director of the Federal Policy Group, a former chief of staff of the congressional Joint Committee on Taxation. “So you can draw your own conclusions” about prospects for a deal this year, he said.Still, there could be some tax initiatives Republicans could get behind. One is a shift from a gasoline tax to a vehicle-miles-traveled fee to help fund highway projects.Read More: By-the-Mile Vehicle Tax to Help Fund Infrastructure Gains SteamAnother is more money for Internal Revenue Service enforcement -- a way to boost revenue without raising rates. Estimates have found that for every additional $1 spent on IRS audits, the agency brings in an additional $3 to $5.Democrats are also looking to revise tax laws that they say don’t do enough to stop U.S. companies from shifting jobs and profits offshore as another way to raise revenue, one aide said. Republicans could potentially support incentives, though it’s unclear whether they’d back penalties.White House officials including deputy director of the National Economic Council, David Kamin -- who wrote a 2019 paper on “Taxing the Rich” -- are in the process of fleshing out the Biden tax plans.As for timing, if passed, tax measures would likely take effect in 2022 -- though some lawmakers and Biden supporters outside the administration have argued for holding off while unemployment remains high due to the pandemic.Lawmakers have their own ideas for tax reforms. Senate Finance Committee Chairman Ron Wyden wants to consolidate energy tax breaks and require investors to pay taxes regularly on their investments including stocks and bonds that have unrealized gains.“A nurse pays taxes with every single paycheck. A billionaire in an affluent suburb on the other hand can defer paying taxes month after month to the point where their paying taxes is pretty much optional,” Wyden told Bloomberg in an interview. “I don’t think that’s right.”Warren has pitched a wealth tax, while House Financial Services Committee Chair Maxine Waters has said she would like to consider a financial-transaction tax.Democratic strategists see the next package as effectively the last chance to reshape the U.S. economy on a grand scale before lawmakers turn to the 2022 mid-term campaign.“Normally, the party in power gets one or two shots to do major legislative packages,” said Chuck Marr, senior director of Federal Tax Policy at the left-leaning Center on Budget and Policy Priorities. “This is the next shot.”(Updates with White House economist comments in first paragraph after bullet-pointed section.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran starts trial of new homegrown vax...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tehran-clinical-trials-iran-coronavirus-pandemic-fde9601ee7d3dabc381dbff67b057d3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's campaign to inoculate its population against the coronavirus and promote itself as an emerging vaccine manufacturer inched on as health authorities announced Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT IT HIM?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2522119/qanon-leader-q-revealed-ex-8chan-administrator-ron-watkins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CONSPIRACY documentary has claimed to have unmasked QAnon’s mysterious leader Q. Makers of the new six-part HBO docu-series Into the Storm have concluded Ron Watkins — the longtime administrator …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus check argument leads to quadruple murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/stimulus-check-argument-led-to-quadruple-murder-family-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man suspected of killing three adults and a child had pulled out a gun and opened fire following a heated argument over dividing a stimulus check, the family says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL TRIP:  Family Kicked Off Flight After 4-Year-Old Won't Wear Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/spirit-airlines-kicks-four-year-old-boy-with-autism-off-flight-for-not-wearing-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline says it's changing its policy to allow for medical exemptions but there were no exemptions when it happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU 'CONVINCED' VAX BENEFIT OUTWEIGHS RISK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eu-regulator-astrazeneca-benefit-outweighs-risk-37c3f8fa9523c58576cbff6d9c13a103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — With coronavirus cases rising in many places, governments faced the grimmest of dilemmas Tuesday: push on with a vaccine that is known to save lives or suspend use of AstraZeneca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With few other options, Texas Dems need Beto to challenge Gov. Abbott in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-few-other-options-texas-democrats-need-beto-orourke-to-challenge-gop-gov-greg-abbott-in-2022/ar-BB1eDlhQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — With few other viable options, Texas Democrats are hoping that next year former Rep. Beto O’Rourke challenges Republican incumbent Greg Abbott for governor. The El Paso Democrat is considering running for governor, saying that Abbott has failed Texas during the pandemic. He later criticized his handling of the February winter storm that left millions of Texans without power and water. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new facility already at 700% capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9367667/Bidens-border-crisis-Inside-new-Texas-migrant-facility-700-capacity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The center - located in the Rio Grande Valley - opened on February 24 and was initially permitted to hold 250 migrants as they were processed by authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Wallen music sales still soaring six weeks after he was 'canceled,' but story bigger than him...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Morgan-Wallen-s-music-sales-are-still-soaring-six-16029374.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six weeks after critics cried that country star Morgan Wallen was being</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southwest border crossings on pace for highest levels in 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/southwest-border-crossings-pace-highest-levels-20-years-biden-admin-n1261192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Emergency Management Agency is setting up a convention center in Dallas to hold up to 3,000 unaccompanied teenage migrants, NBC News confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel priests defy Vatican, vow to bless same-sex couples...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210316124934-4j1yv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Elliot Page becomes first trans man to star on TIME cover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210316123602-zsqf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
