<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Williamson sticking with love...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2019/07/28/democratic-debate-marianne-williamson-keeping-message-love/1847071001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her performance in the first debate drew praise and mockery. Now Marianne Williamson will forgo traditional debate prep, but her message will be the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter cut through back fence to avoid security, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-07-28/gilroy-garlic-festival-shoot-gunman-cut-through-fence-to-avoid-security-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gilroy, California Garlic Festival Shooting: Here is how gunman was able to avoid security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well-known Christian author, purity advocate, renounces faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/faith-values/christian-author-joshua-harris-kissed-dating-goodbye-faith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author Joshua Harris, after announcing the end of his marriage, is now kissing his faith goodbye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motive mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/29/shooting-reported-at-gilroy-garlic-festival-in-san-jose-california.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were searching on Monday for a suspected accomplice of the gunman who killed three people, including a 6-year-old boy, in a mass shooting at a food festival in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities investigating 11 fires overnight in Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-11-fires-in-edmondson-village-20190729-3wlqpyq4fndkvng6ldwnkxou5a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters were called to the Edmondson Village area for a report of a fire around 1:30 a.m., Baltimore fire spokeswoman Blair Adams said. Then, after they arrived they were called for a report of another fire a few blocks away. That process was repeated nine more times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ayyy garlic festival time. Come get wasted on overpriced shit'...</title>
      <link>https://heavy.com/news/2019/07/santino-william-legan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heavy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Gilroy Garlic Festival gunman has been identified as 19-year-old Santino William Legan. Three were killed and 15 injured in the mass shooting Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Stealth Breakthrough?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/metamaterials-has-china-just-made-a-major-stealth-breakthrough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of Chinese scientists have created a new “metamaterial” that could dramatically shrink the radar signature of a jet or missile. But does it really work?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic contact lens allows users to zoom in by blinking...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/robotic-contact-lens-zoom-blinking-signals-a9024176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doesn't Guarantee Fairy Tale Ending...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/once-a-time-hollywood-debut-doesnt-gurantee-a-happy-ending-1227512 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino's ninth film, teaming Leonardo DiCaprio and Brad Pitt, needs to have strong staying power to be considered a success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of metallic object flying over base adds fuel to fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1159078/area-51-raid-facebook-ufo-sightings-2019-alien-ufo-news-area-51-event-maps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UFO has allegedly been seen flying near the top secret Area 51 base in Nevada, adding fuel to the fire at claims the US government is hiding alien technology there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug lord to 'wipe out El Chapo sons and take control of cartel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/794387/el-chapo-news-prison-el-mayo-to-wipe-out-sons-take-control-of-sinaloa-cartel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA aircraft 'scanning San Andreas Fault' sparks fears quake imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/794829/NASA-aircraft-spotted-California-scanning-San-Andreas-Fault-Big-One-fears-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran releases audio of patrol boat warning off Royal Navy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jul/29/iran-releases-audio-of-patrol-boat-warning-off-royal-navy-ship </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recording from seizure of Stena Impero is attempt to show Iran’s capability in Gulf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startling Study Reveals Majority Of Packaged Food Ultra-Processed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/startling-study-reveals-majority-packaged-food-is-ultra-processed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study out of Northwestern University has identified another contributing factor: the overwhelming majority of packaged foods available in the U.S. in 2018 were ultra-processed and unhealthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Dancers controlled by wearable robots at 'forced exoskeleton rave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/dancers-controlled-wearable-robots-creepy-18794451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rave took place at Silicon Valley’s Gray Area Festival last week, and saw dancers take to the stage wearing robotic exoskeletons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second warship arrives in Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/warship-strait-hormuz-britain-tankers-seized-iran-gulf-hms-duncan-a9025176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could worsen next downturn...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/As-it-faces-pressure-from-Trump-and-investors-14192385.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Federal Reserve this week is all but certain to cut interest rates despite unemployment being at historic lows, a highly unusual action that is shaping up to be the biggest gamble of Fed Chair Jerome Powell's brief tenure as leader of the world's most powerful economic institution.  Many economists say the Fed is acting prudently to prolong the economic expansion, which this month became the longest in U.S. history. Yet the support is far from unanimous.  Some economists, Fed officials and people on Main Street say the Fed's action will benefit the stock market more than the real economy. And they argue cutting rates would introduce risks that could worsen the next downturn.  Typically, when the Fed slashes interest rates, borrowing costs drop for mortgages, business loans, auto loans, and credit cards, leading to more homes being sold, more businesses investing, and more economic activity overall.  But loans are already cheap and few industries are asking for lower rates, suggesting that other factors outside the Fed's control - a labor shortage, trade wars, a lack of housing supply - are capping the economy's potential.  "A Fed rate cut will have zero impact on the housing market," said Tendayi Kapfidze, chief economist at Lending Tree. "Mortgage rates are already at three-year lows."  Washington-real estate agent Kara Sheehan agrees. She hears a long list of concerns from prospective home buyers these days - urban homes with a parking spot or garage, a good price, and homes that don't need to be renovated. But she hears little about mortgage rates.  "Buyers are a little more hesitant lately and very price conscious. They are all about property condition," said Sheehan, of Washington Fine Properties.  The Fed's actions this week, and the stage they set for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Giant Spy Drone Just Tailed U.S. Navy Cruiser...</title>
      <link>https://nationalinterest.org/blog/buzz/china%E2%80%99s-giant-spy-drone-just-tailed-us-navy-cruiser-69881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalinterest.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Beijing’s years of investment in drones are finally starting to pay off, if the Soar Eagle’s July 2019 mission tailing Antietam is any indication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touts economy, but not everyone in Michigan feeling it...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/55b8c21a307948e490d27deeb8f06a8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Defector Tells of Spying, Stealing, Mutiny in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/top-defector-tells-spying-stealing-090000438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Days after being named chief of Venezuela’s feared SEBIN intelligence agency last fall, General Manuel Ricardo Cristopher Figuera was called in by President Nicolas Maduro and asked where the enemy was.“I don’t understand the question, sir,” Figuera says he responded.“I want a report every</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priests accused of sex abuse turned to under-the-radar group...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abe2da0da2f648ad89dde483a92d3f19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Definitely weird': Man bites snake...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190729111302-ogr0h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-SNAKE/ (TV):'Definitely weird': man bites snake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Warns Hong Kong Protests Won't Be Tolerated...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-commentary-says-hong-kong-064513002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China said violent protests in Hong Kong wouldn’t be tolerated, its most high-profile response to unrest rocking the city after a chaotic weekend of unrest illustrated the government’s struggles in quelling a leaderless, unpredictable and widespread movement.The Hong Kong and Macau Affairs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposition leader may have been poisoned, says doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jul/29/russian-opposition-leader-alexei-navalny-may-have-been-poisoned-says-doctor </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politician was taken to hospital from jail where he was detained over call for protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DO-OR-DIE IN DETROIT: 2020 Dem race enters new phase...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/455014-the-memo-2020-democratic-race-enters-do-or-die-phase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race for the Democratic presidential nomination enters a new phase this week, with candidates desperate to make an impact in a second round of debates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Was COSMO's Bachelor of the Month...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/when-jeffrey-epstein-was-cosmopolitan-bachelor-of-the-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In July 1980, the predatory financier was featured as the magazine’s “Bachelor of the Month" seeking a "cute Texas girl."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film studios appeasing China the way they did Nazis in '30s...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/07/american-movie-studios-are-wrong-to-appease-chinese-censors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it’s not the first time Hollywood has bowed to authoritarian foreign powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES:  WHY IS PRESIDENT TRUMP COMMITTING SUICIDE?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/why-is-president-trump-committing-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Emergency Message To 45</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Breaks Yearly Box Office Record -- In July!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-disney-hits-record-767b-2019-global-ticket-sales-1227497</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The powerhouse Hollywood studio accomplished the feat with more than five months left to go in the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTER SAYS HE NEEDS SECURITY TO WALK STREETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7294779/Brazilian-president-Jair-Bolsonaro-threatens-journalist-Glenn-Greenwald-jail-reporting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's threats come a few days after members of his party said the American's Brazil-based internet publication was 'aligned with criminal hackers' for reporting hacked phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN DOME REMOVED FROM 'TEMPLE OF SEX'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7294665/Jeffrey-Epstein-doomed-dome-Pedophile-Islands-mysterious-temple-lost-golden-dome.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrest of Jeffrey Epstein on federal sex trafficking charges earlier this month has turned his two properties off the coast of St Thomas into ghost islands - and his temple now has no dome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT PAGE ONE MONDAY:  Federal Inquiry of Trump Friend Focused on Foreign Lobbying... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/federal-inquiry-of-trump-friend-focused-on-foreign-lobbying/ar-AAEZ4bl?PC=EMMX20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP SPOOK EXITS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ad59c9104dc425bba166de4b9723612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Storm Area 51' turnout overwhelms Nevada town...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/28/storm-area-51-turnout-overwhelms-rachel-nevada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1 million people have responded to the internet post calling for people to “Naruto run” at 3 a.m. into the remote U.S. Air Force test area in the Nevada desert that has long been the focus of UFO conspiracy theories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal gold mining at epidemic proportions...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jul/28/amazon-gold-miners-invade-indigenous-village-brazil-leader-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil’s police have been urged to investigate a ‘very tense situation’ in Amapá state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mosquito: A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/27/opinion/sunday/mosquitoes-malaria-zika-history.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are our apex predator, the deadliest hunters of human beings on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Trash TV making people dumber...</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2019/07/junky-tv-is-actually-making-people-dumber-and-more-likely-to-support-populist-politicians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: Alex Stamos and Renee DiResta are launching an "observatory" for internet abuse at Stanford, and misconceptions about disinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS Hires UNIVISION Anchor After Hispanic Group Threatens Boycott... </title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2019/07/22/maria-elena-salinas-joins-cbs-news/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salinas will serve as a contributor across the network's broadcasts and platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside weekly itinerary of world's most frequent flyer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/27/worlds-most-frequent-flyer-has-an-insane-weekly-itinerary/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Stuker loves going the extra mile. Give or take a few million. The world’s most frequent flier just racked up a record-setting 21 million miles flown. That’s nearly 844 times around the equator…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo of Blindfolded American Teen Rocks Rome Cop Killer Case...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/europe/photo-of-blindfolded-teen-rocks-rome-cop-killer-case-1.65496990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Image sparks police probe of their own officers’ actions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can birds help connect North Korea to world?</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/can-birds-help-connect-north-korea-to-the-world-1.65493149</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border means little to millions soaring over it as they travel along migration corridor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> World Economy's Biggest Week of 2019 as Fed Preps Cut...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-economy-biggest-week-2019-020000486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- There will be no chance of a summer break for investors or policy makers in coming days as they brace for what might be the busiest week for the world economy this year.The highlight is Wednesday’s decision by the Federal Reserve with markets and economists virtually united in predicting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY:  IT WASN'T RACIST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76da6dbad40e4209827abacc0b3d3ea7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Lawmaker blasted for saying USA might look like South America...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/037d7ac4daf44e4c9dca6b5e339efbcf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$15,000 fine for sharing memes?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/senate-moves-bill-with-up-to-15000-fines-for-sharing-memes-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bi-partisan bill working its way through Congress could drastically change how copyright claims are processed, and would create a system to impose up to $30,000 in fines on anyone who shares protected material online. In other words, the Congress wants to make it easier to sue people who send a meme or post images …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian police probe tribal leader's killing, village invasion...</title>
      <link>http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/341752.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.ahram.org.eg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
