<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  SITS FOR HOUR-LONG THERAPY SESSION WITH ZANE LOWE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1gtPULpjzuA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zane Lowe sits down with Adele to unpack her fourth studio album, ’30,’ exploring the inspirations behind each track and their impact on her life. Adele expl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICTURES: Longest lunar eclipse in 600 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4100119/photos-of-lunar-eclipse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A STUNNING lunar eclipse occurred this morning and it could be viewed for over three hours in the US. It involved the Earth’s shadow covering about 97 per cent of the full Beaver Moon. Viewer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook moves 3 Senate races toward Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cook-political-report-senate-races-gop-3cd595f8-db50-4a53-b58d-2ba3de23475a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moves reflect the increasingly bullish midterm environment for Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden transfers power to Kamala while gets colonoscopy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4102232/biden-colonoscopy-birthday-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden is set to undergo a colonoscopy today ahead of his 79th birthday and Kamala Harris will become acting president while he is under anesthetic. The president arrived at Walter Reed Hospital…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump writes picture book, son brags: Dad 'wrote all the captions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-book-coffee-table-29bcec81-74d3-4eef-975d-c529002bdf29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It features 300+ official White House photographs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT INTENSIFIES: HOW MANY SHOTS WILL BE REQUIRED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-vaccines-boosters-fauci-america-c0f4e198-9a2f-42c4-ba74-3fa06ce1d811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some experts and officials are pushing for the definition of "fully vaccinated" to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becomes first woman to hold presidential power...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-transfer-power-harris-colonoscopy-physical-3503f6b9-3f98-463a-97d3-d9b3e7480dfb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden will also receive his first annual physical as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside world's first lockdown for unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/11/inside-the-austrian-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We explore the world's first lockdown for the unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado ICU Doctor: More Worried NOW Than BEFORE...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/covid-trajectory-fort-collins-surge-hospitals-icu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the Delta variant has caused a surge of COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations in northern Colorado, medical providers in the packed halls of the ICU are sharing their stories with CBS4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Among Jurors?</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/kyle-rittenhouse-jury-deliberations-irv-miller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors in the Kyle Rittenhouse trial left the Kenosha County courthouse for the third night with no verdict late Thursday – and the deliberations seem to be taking longer than some thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60-foot waves exploded off Pacific Coast during bomb cyclone...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/60-foot-waves-exploded-off-the-pacific-coast-during-octobers-bomb-cyclone/article_123708be-1231-5c90-992d-ac2de04fc646.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The bomb cyclone and atmospheric river that pummeled Northern California in late October produced exceptionally heavy rain and high winds. But it also battered the California coast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roadrunner hitched 3,000-mile ride from Vegas to Maine. Bird experts trying to send back...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/A-roadrunner-hitched-a-nearly-3-000-mile-ride-16634451.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In less than an hour, 73-year-old Karen Silverman did what Wile E. Coyote has not been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why NASA Probe Set to Slam Into Asteroid and Kill Self...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nasas-dart-mission-will-slam-into-an-asteroid-to-teach-us-how-to-save-earth-from-annihilation?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DART is a $325 million suicide mission in space that could teach us how to save the world from annihilation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Death toll could soar by 300,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4101928/study-warns-of-300000-covid-deaths-in-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW study has revealed Europe could face “300,000 deaths and one million people in hospital” as Covid wreaks havoc across the continent this winter. The London School of Hygiene and T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch delay care for cancer, heart patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211119135227-ycl1s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS:Facing new COVID wave, Dutch delay care for cancer, heart patients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Bonnie and Clyde of MAGA World...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/11/19/dustin-stockton-jen-lawrence-trump-profile-522823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a decade, Dustin Stockton and Jennifer Lawrence had surfed the wave of populist-right politics like few other people in America. Then came Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania GOP baffled by Dr. Oz Senate bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/19/pennsylvania-republicans-dr-oz-senate-bid-523023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP insiders are rattled by the unsettled primary field in one of the nation’s most important Senate races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosters authorized for all adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-authorizes-pfizer-moderna-booster-adults-rcna5856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA authorized Pfizer and Moderna booster shots for all adults. A CDC advisory panel will take up the issue on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ire grows as DeSantis popularity with Republicans takes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/19/politics/trump-desantis-relationship/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a matter of months, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has gone from being a shining example in Donald Trump's eyes of a MAGA leader molded in his image to an average politician who forgot his roots as he rose to Republican stardom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci office flooded with attacks over beagle experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Fauci-s-office-flooded-with-attacks-over-beagle-16634352.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Anthony Fauci was swamped by so many angry messages and threats that in late...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown fears rattle investors, spark dash for safe-havens...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/global-markets/europe-lockdown-fears-rattle-investors-spark-dash-for-safe-havens-idUSKBN2I4068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European stocks retreated from record highs, while government bond yields, oil prices and the euro tumbled on Friday as the specter of a fresh COVID-linked lockdown in Germany and other parts of Europe cast a fresh shadow over the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron used to be indestructible. Now, his health is biggest concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/lebron-james-used-to-be-indestructible-now-his-health-is-the-lakers-e2-80-99-biggest-concern/ar-AAQU2lB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurch founder forced girls and young women into sex, telling them it was 'God's will'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/filipino-megachurch-founder-forced-girls-and-young-women-into-sex-telling-them-it-was-e2-80-98god-e2-80-99s-will-e2-80-99-feds-say/ar-AAQTT9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA worker alleges sex harassment rampant in suit. Now other women stepping forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/A-Tesla-factory-worker-alleges-sexual-harassment-16634382.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Jessica Barraza was only months into her job at Tesla's factory when she...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary opposition leader vows to restore western alliances...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-russia-china-elections-48d6759386cb29344f7925b2eca593bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HODMEZOVASARHELY, Hungary (AP) — Hungary's opposition leader wants to restore his country's frayed ties with the West — and also has a message for American fans of right-wing Prime Minister Viktor Orban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists mystified, wary, as Africa avoids COVID disaster...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-united-nations-fcf28a83c9352a67e50aa2172eb01a2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARARE, Zimbabwe (AP) — At a busy market in a poor township outside Harare this week, Nyasha Ndou kept his mask in his pocket, as hundreds of other people, mostly unmasked, jostled to buy and sell fruit and vegetables displayed on wooden tables and plastic sheets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway tightens entry rules, urges dropping handshake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-denmark-norway-2343d26b5e7475b489b8d68be8d4039b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Norwegian officials said Friday the country is introducing stricter controls at border crossings, requiring everyone to register before entering the country, in a bid to tackle the rise in COVID cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacist prison guards work with impunity in FL?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prisons-florida-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-60b96681445509d89e6c0497405497d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June, three Florida prison guards who boasted of being white supremacists beat, pepper sprayed and used a stun gun on an inmate who screamed “I can’t breathe!” at a prison near the Alabama border, according to a fellow inmate who reported it to the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at intimate details AMAZON knows about us...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211119112546-ny6lf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AMAZON.COM/PRIVACY-SIDEBAR (PIX, TV):A look at the intimate details Amazon knows about us</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bars NYT from publishing VERITAS memos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/court-bars-new-york-times-from-publishing-project-veritas-memos-in-move-called-e2-80-98unconstitutional-e2-80-99/ar-AAQSGeu </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saying grace: How moment of thanks, religious or not, adds meaning to meals...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Saying-grace-How-a-moment-of-thanks-religious-16632304.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brett Levanto and his family had never said grace before meals, not regularly, anyway....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Forcing Out Soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/exclusive-army-force-out-soldiers-who-refuse-covid-vaccine/186954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New policy bars unvaccinated soldiers from re-enlistment, promotions as Oklahoma governor says National Guard need not obey Biden's vax mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Diet-related illness increases with availability of red meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/diet-related-illness-increases-with-availability-of-red-meat-study-01637276708 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware Putin amid US-China rivalry, Hillary Clinton warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiaone.com/world/beware-putin-amid-us-china-rivalry-hillary-clinton-warns-bloomberg-forum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiaone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the United States' rivalry with China, Washington and its Western allies must remain wary of Russian President Vladimir Putin and his use of dubious "non-state actors" to sharpen his global projection of power, former US Secretary of State Hillary Clinton has said. Speaking via video link on the final day of the Bloomberg New Economy Forum in Singapore, Clinton...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse in 580 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/beaver-moon-lunar-eclipse-photos-november-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the longest partial lunar eclipse in 580 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zemmour draws comparisons to Trump as he upends French presidential election...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/c3-a9ric-zemmour-draws-comparisons-to-trump-as-he-upends-french-presidential-election/ar-AAQTx8d </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy late night speech punctuates two party's disdain for each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mccarthy-e2-80-99s-late-night-speech-punctuates-week-where-the-two-party-e2-80-99s-disdain-for-each-other-was-on-full-display/ar-AAQT0db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Tells Trump He Needs to Leave Past Behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rupert-murdoch-tells-trump-he-needs-to-leave-the-past-behind/ar-AAQPEyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHIFT: Florida Republicans Overtake Democrats in Registered Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/florida-republicans-overtake-democrats-in-registered-voters/ar-AAQStxc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE NATION, APPLE, Travis Scott sued for $2 billion over 'Astroworld' disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/live-nation-apple-travis-scott-sued-for-242-billion-over-astroworld-disaster/ar-AAQRYrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro winter of discontent: Now Germany locks down unvaccinated!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10218895/French-protest-against-Austrias-new-Covid-apartheid-fearing-rule-spread-Europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large crowds waving flags gathered outside the Austrian Embassy in Paris in protest at Vienna's lockdown for the unvaccinated, with Italy and Greece considering similar restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS: THIRD day of deliberations in Rittenhouse case with no verdict...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kyle-rittenhouse-wisconsin-shootings-kenosha-ac4ff9ba75f00884ce6cd5e5932d5543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — The jury at Kyle Rittenhouse’s murder trial deliberated for a third full day without reaching a verdict Thursday, while the judge banned MSNBC from the courthouse after a freelancer for the network was accused of following the jurors in their bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House moves toward OK of sweeping social, climate bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-joe-biden-business-lifestyle-environment-a518d86dfb69ab2a56ac507746a8d810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A divided House moved toward passage Thursday of Democrats' expansive social and environment bill  as new cost estimates from Congress' top fiscal analyst suggested that moderate lawmakers' spending and deficit worries would be calmed, moving President Joe Biden closer to a badly needed victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure on Fed rising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-economy-prices-inflation-jerome-powell-583029ed34f028d4950fd5b0d896388f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell surely expected to have some breathing room after taking the first step this month to dial back the Fed’s emergency aid for the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The vaccine tore her family apart. Could a death bring them back together?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/the-vaccine-tore-her-family-apart-could-a-death-bring-them-back-together/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Thanksgiving nearing, infections high or rising in many parts of the U.S. and vaccines now widely available to children, family breaches over COVID immunization status are reaching new levels of rancor and intensity. Here's the Haughts' story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Charlottesville trial, jurors learn to decode secret slang of white supremacists...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-Charlottesville-trial-jurors-learn-to-decode-16632986.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. - The jury in a federal courtroom listened as a longtime researcher...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL: BIDEN APPROVAL DROPS TO 36%</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/poll-release?releaseid=3827</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Society Bracing for Ghislaine Maxwell Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-high-society-1258165/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What will be revealed? Who might she name? Jeffrey Epstein’s right-hand woman is going on trial for their alleged crimes — and those who used to know her can’t stop talking about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA wants 55 years to process FOIA request over data...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/wait-what-fda-wants-55-years-process-foia-request-over-vaccine-data-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freedom of Information Act requests are rarely speedy, but when a group of scientists asked the federal government to share the data it relied upon in licensing Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine, the response went beyond typical bureaucratic foot-dragging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi on $550 billion climate spending: 'Religious thing'...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/pelosi-550-billion-climate-spending-me-its-religious-thing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's Build Back Better Act is estimated to cost $4.79 trillion if its policies are made permanent, according to the Committee for a Responsible Budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Jury ends THIRD day of deliberations with no verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-verdict-watch-11-18-21/h_87dc3885421105e20787bd01af3fbdbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in the trial of Kyle Rittenhouse will continue deliberations today. Follow here for live updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeking strength in numbers, U.S.-bound migrants form new caravan...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118214502-s84as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Seeking strength in numbers, U.S.-bound migrants in Mexico form new caravan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Starts Using Drones In New Delivery Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/walmart-starts-using-autonomous-drones-in-new-delivery-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News got an exclusive look at a new on-demand delivery service, which uses autonomous drone technology, outside a Walmart headquarters in Pea Ridge, Arkansas. Errol Barnett reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star accused of obtaining fake card...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/sports/bucs/2021/11/18/bucs-antonio-brown-accused-of-obtaining-fake-vaccine-card/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former live-in chef also says Brown, who missed one game this season after testing positive for COVID, owes him $10,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland city council votes to INCREASE police funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/portland-city-council-votes-to-increase-police-funding-crack-down-on-homeless-camping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$500,000 is allocated to install benches to prevent the homeless from setting up camp near city parks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88% of Americans worried about inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/inflation-has-88percent-of-americans-worried-heres-how-they-will-cut-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worries about rising prices are at the top of most American consumers' minds as we head into the holiday season, a new Country Financial survey shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man banned from all-you-can-eat BBQ for eating too much...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-59331975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A live-streamer has been banned from a buffet restaurant in China after multiple food binges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million Americans May Have Permanently Lost Sense of Smell...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/over-a-million-americans-may-have-permanently-lost-thei-1848082265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study estimates that up to 1.6 million Americans have experienced covid-related smell loss for longer than six months, with little chance of recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem retirements spark worry over holding House majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democratic-retirements-spark-worry-over-holding-house-majority-2548f85b-ab8d-4cb1-b191-3afe2a25dee5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;15 House Democrats and 10 Republicans are not running again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Known Covid Case Was Vendor at Wuhan Market, Scientist Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2298195-analysis-of-earliest-covid-19-cases-points-to-wuhan-market-as-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fresh look at what we know about the first covid-19 cases shows that the earliest known case was in a person who worked at the Huanan Market in Wuhan, which was suspected as the source from the start of the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 'Great Resignation' may not last very long...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/why-the-great-resignation-may-not-last-very-long.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4.4 million people quit their jobs in September, but there’s more to the “Great Resignation” than just worker dissatisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE pushes fully autonomous car forward...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/tech/bloomberg-apple-plans-to-launch-fully-autonomous-car-as-soon-as-2025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple’s electric autonomous car will have no steering wheel or pedals, with a new chip managing the vehicle’s self-driving abilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black pastors rally outside trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-georgia-brunswick-al-sharpton-6daf56b12c4fa58da89d1424d5ba090c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — Hundreds of pastors both rallied and prayed Thursday outside the trial of three white men in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery , gathering in response to a defense lawyer's bid to keep Black ministers out of the courtroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France bans wild circus animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211118-france-bans-wild-circus-animals-and-mink-farms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French parliament voted Thursday to end wild animals being used in live circus shows and outlawed mink farming, in new animal-rights legislation hailed as a step forward by campaigners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wargame Tests Navy's Mettle...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/are-naval-forces-right-path-leaders-run-wargame-check/186924/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis of the classified, Pacific-focused “Global 14” will continue for weeks or months, a Navy official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limit public life for unjabbed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118164736-9c3im</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Germany to limit public life for the unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who raped 4 teens gets no jail time: 'Incarceration isn't appropriate'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/man-who-raped-four-teenagers-gets-no-jail-time-judge-says-incarceration-isnt-appropriate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who fatally shot Arbery says he feared for life in struggle for gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/man-who-fatally-shot-ahmaud-arbery-says-he-feared-for-his-life-in-struggle-for-gun/ar-AAQPfX9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis McMichael testified Wednesday that he feared for his life when Arbery grabbed his gun, setting up a potential battle over the prosecution’s ability to grill him on alleged “racial animus.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Ejects MSNBC...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/live-trials/live-trials-current/kyle-rittenhouse/judge-ejects-msnbc-from-kyle-rittenhouse-courthouse-after-extremely-serious-incident-of-person-following-jury-bus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Bruce Schroeder has ejected cable news organization and website MSNBC from the Kenosha County Courthouse for the remaining duration of the Kyle Rittenhouse homicide trial.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
