<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Russian Spy Plane Flies Over DC, Nuke Bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-27/russian-spy-plane-flies-over-washington-us-military-nuclear-bases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIHADIS 'PLOTTING ATTACKS ON AMERICA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/774414/sri-lanka-news-bombings-blasts-explosions-bomb-attack-colombo-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX PISTOL Johnny Rotten rails against homeless anarchy in LA; 'Needles on beach, poo all over sand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6966735/Sex-Pistols-Johnny-Rotten-complains-homeless-crisis-LA-neighborhood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Rotten says homeless people have moved 'en masse' to his exclusive Los Angeles neighborhood of Venice Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo 10 lunar module finally found? Left orbiting Moon 50 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6965985/Astronomers-believe-spotted-module-moon-want-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1969, the Apollo 10 crew, inset left, ejected lunar module ‘Snoopy’ from the Apollo command module into orbit never to be seen again – or so they thought. It is possible that it has now been spotted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
With more than 500 kills, this vegetable farmer is world's deadliest hitman...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/27/meet-julio-santana-the-worlds-deadliest-hitman-with-500-kills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julio Santana dropped to his left knee and propped his right elbow on his hip, holding firm his hunting rifle until he had the man known as Yellow in his sights. It was Aug. 6, 1971, and Santana wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. general says will have what's needed to stop any dangerous act by Iran...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190427164730-gqg6x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ (URGENT):U.S. general says will have what's needed to stop any dangerous act by Iran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: POPE FUNDS CARAVANS</title>
      <link>https://www.vaticannews.va/en/pope/news/2019-04/pope-francis-central-american-migrants-aid-peters-pence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vaticannews.va&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Central American migrants in Mexico are in need of assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 5 Doctors Suffer From Emotional Distress; 4 In 5 Risk Burnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-40-percent-doctors-suffering-psychological-emotional-distress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing level of stress that doctors and health care practitioners face amid increasing workloads is taking a major toll on their mental health. A new study finds that four in 10 are suffering from psychological or emotional distress and eight in 10 are at serious risk of burnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Kim warns of return to tension, blames USA 'bad faith'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-russia-kcna/north-korean-leader-warns-of-a-return-to-tension-blames-u-s-bad-faith-idUSKCN1S12QH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un told Russian President Vladimir Putin that peace...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Guard monitors US aircraft carrier with drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/irans-guard-monitors-us-aircraft-carrier-with-drone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's semi-official Tasnim news agency is reporting that the country's powerful Revolutionary Guard has successfully managed a surveillance flight over a U.S. aircraft carrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force plans combat exercise, weapons evaluation in Utah...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/30133950e2b44f9ba6017225de5d0707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILL AIR FORCE BASE, Utah (AP) — The U.S. Air Force will conduct a large training exercise and a weapons evaluation in Utah in coming weeks. Hill Air Force Base officials said Saturday that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT apologizes for cartoon depicting anti-Semitic tropes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/440957-ny-times-opinion-apologizes-for-cartoon-depicting-anti-semitic-tropes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times Opinion section on Saturday apologized for a political cartoon that included anti-Semitic tropes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver North Out as NRA President...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d5d90ab1596f478c8f20d4dbe3f73979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — Retired Lt. Col. Oliver North has announced that he will not serve a second term as the president of the National Rifle Association amid inner turmoil in the gun-rights...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' Record $158M+ 1st Day...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/avengers-endgame-opening-weekend-box-office-record-1202602445/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;6TH UPDATE, Saturday 6:19 AM Writethru following Friday 10:14 PM post: And with a snap, Avengers: Endgame is swelling, just as expected.  Industry estimates as of last night for Friday stand at $15…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico: President Amlo's criticism of national newspaper sparks death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/27/mexico-president-campaign-vow-tested-press-battles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrés Manuel López Obrador promised to protect the press, but his barbs have resulted in journalists being harassed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pride vs. Pence: Gay Republicans grapple with Mayor Pete breakout...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/27/buttigieg-pence-gay-republicans-2020-1291201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 37-year-old mayor has climbed the ranks of the 2020 Democratic primary with help from a fundraising surge after launching barbs at the vice president, an icon among many Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame my brain: Killer's bold defense gets court hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/blame-my-brain-killer-s-bold-defense-gets-court-hearing-n998676</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More criminal defendants are turning to brain science to argue that they shouldn't face harsh punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson campaign TWITTER account suspended within hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/tommy-robinson-mep-campaign-twitter-account-suspended-election-8888976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Can't Monitor Autistic Son with GPS Tracker at School, Ruling Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/parents-cant-monitor-autistic-son-with-gps-tracker-at-school-nevada-ruling-says-11556357400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of an autistic child in Nevada who fought to have his school let him wear a GPS tracker with the ability to listen in on his surroundings lost their battle in a case that could resonate in school districts across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Spying Poses Rising Threat to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-spying-poses-rising-threat-to-u-s-11556359201 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese spies are increasingly recruiting U.S. intelligence officers as part of a widening, sustained campaign to shake loose government secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cracks Down on Apps That Fight iPhone Addiction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/27/technology/apple-screen-time-trackers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, with much fanfare, the tech giant unveiled a screen-time tracker of its own. Then it quietly began purging competitors from its store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers Tracking Where You Shop -- and Sleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-27/retailers-are-tracking-where-you-shop-and-where-you-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Playing Defense in Rust Belt as He Opens Re-Election Bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-playing-defense-rust-belt-080000511.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, he’ll hold a campaign rally in Green Bay, an event timed to compete for cable-news eyeballs with the White House press corps’ annual charity dinner. Trump’s interest in the region is already being matched by his top Democratic rivals -- former Vice President Joe Biden and Senator Bernie</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New theory suggests sisterhood ruled ancient Egypt before King Tut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/egyptologist-canada-presents-theory-two-queen-rule-tutankhamun-022746811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tutankhamun, the boy king of ancient Egypt, came to power only after two of his sisters jointly held the throne, according to an Egyptologist at Canada's Universite du Quebec a Montreal (UQAM). Researchers have known for more than half a century that a queen had reigned before Tutankhamun, whose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans at 'crossroads' as newly homeless numbers rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f85bb3d93ecf4022a591ca734ea4f8c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Daylight seeps through holes in the ceiling as 22-year-old Royon Rene Burbank walks across the sagging floor, the dirt below visible through gaps where rotten boards have given...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslims in hiding in Sri Lanka as tensions rise after bombings... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/25/muslims-flee-town-in-sri-lanka-as-tensions-rise-after-bombings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group of about 500 Muslims being sheltered in one city after fleeing Negomobo, as communal tensions rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Julian Assange and the Woeful State of Whistle-Blowers... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/26/opinion/media-constitution-assange-leaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the media’s indispensable helpmates, don’t they deserve constitutional protection too?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm to dump snow on millions this weekend...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2019-04-26-winter-storm-xyler-forecast-midwest-great-lakes-northeast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colder temperatures, even snow, will put spring on pause from the northern Rockies into the Great Lakes to end April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Clock Is Running Out on Big Media Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/why-the-clock-is-running-out-on-big-media-companies-11556290801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live sports remain the sole reason legacy media companies haven’t lost many more customers than they already have, but that could change as tech companies enter the bidding war for sports broadcasting rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOONAN:  How Trump Lost Half of Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-trump-lost-half-of-washington-11556232864</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The old ambassadors were willing to give him a chance. He destabilized the whole town instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAS RECESSION BEEN CANCELLED?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/has-the-recession-been-cancelled-11556311511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strength of the U.S. economy continues to confound the liberal establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford professor claims aliens are already breeding with humans on earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8950579/oxford-university-professor-aliens-breeding-hybrid-humans-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Oxford University professor has claimed aliens are already breeding with humans to create a new hybrid species that will save the planet. Dr Young-hae Chi, an instructor in Korean at Oxford’s Or…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS medics 'removed organs of prisoners and performed Nazi-style experiments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8950274/british-isis-medics-torture-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO British jihadi health workers carried out sickening Nazi-style medical experiments on ISIS prisoners in Syria, witnesses claimed last night. Former NHS doctor Issam Abuanza, 40, left his wife a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARE:  Cell phone thrown at president at gun rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8948653/cell-phone-thrown-at-donald-trump-national-rifle-association-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump was targeted with a mobile phone which had been hurled at him as he addressed a gun supporters’ rally.  The handset was seen being thrown from the crowd who gathered at a Nationa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sleepy' or 'Hyper'?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/26/sleepy-biden-2020-1291181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after he entered the White House race, it appears the former vice president is getting under Trump's skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates tune out voter anxieties over security...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2201684?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Few fights have Democrats more certain that they have the upper hand against President Donald Trump than the one over border security: His plans to build walls, separate immigrant families and punish asylum-seekers have alienated voters since he took office....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome 'under attack' from criminals, says mayor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rome-under-attack-criminals-says-mayor-212743388.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rome's mayor vowed Friday to defend the Italian capital from criminals following a fire at an illegal landfill, the latest blow to an already beleaguered city. "Rome is under attack. Under attack from criminals that continue to act against citizens," Virginia Raggi said in a Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto draws crowd of tens at college campus...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/04/26/beto-orourke-campaign-las-vegas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Texas Rep. and current presidential candidate Beto O'Rourke had a small crowd for a campaign event at the University of Nevada Las Vegas on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP BIG:  3.2%</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e48cd0b437294313b570c490b83c63fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The worries that hung ominously over the U.S. economy early this year appear to have lifted. And that sunnier picture has helped bolster confidence in the stock market — driving...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archdiocese of NY releases names of 120 predator priests, many now deceased...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2d572976fdc4e1fb2aa2e9903cb3a2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — At least 120 priests accused of sexually abusing a child or having child pornography have worked in the Archdiocese of New York, the archdiocese said Friday in releasing a list of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUGHT:  Mother-daughter duo fly drone into Florida prison; Drop off tobacco...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/mom-daughter-drone-duo-headed-to-jail-426190</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 26--A mother-daughter duo who used a $4000 drone to drop a package of contraband behind the walls of a Florida prison will themselves serve time as a result of a felony plea deal struck with p</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico voices concern over crossing delays...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190426214918-f5drw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO-TRADE (URGENT):Mexico voices concern to U.S. government over border delays</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homophobic remarks by Brazil's president may harm tourism industry...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190426213516-ysfvy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-LGBT/POLITICS:Homophobic remarks by Brazil's president may harm tourism industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds board freight train...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190426182531-qdk24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Hundreds of migrants in southern Mexico board 'The Beast' heading north</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Group Leader LaPierre Says Being Extorted, Resign Pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nras-wayne-lapierre-says-he-is-being-extorted-pressured-to-resign-11556314763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Rifle Association leader Wayne LaPierre has told the group’s board he is being extorted and pressured to resign by the organization’s president, Oliver North.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. colleges quarantine 900+ possibly exposed to measles...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b825c8b75ad84a02b4f1d39b77c26123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — More than 900 students and staff members at two Los Angeles universities were quarantined on campus or sent home this week in one of the most sweeping efforts yet by public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man guilty of sharing NZ mosque massacre faces 14 years jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/national/christchurch-shooting/112281653/philip-arps-guilty-of-sharing-livestream-of-christchurch-mosque-massacre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He sent the terror attack video to a friend, asking for it to be modified with a "kill count" as people were shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Juiced ball' claims as MLB hitters blasting record home runs...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/MLB-hitters-are-blasting-homers-at-a-record-rate-13799008.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE - It's not exactly true that the Baltimore Orioles' pitching staff is single-handedly responsible for the staggering spike in home runs across Major League Baseball this season - but when you're standing on the mound or sitting in the dugout at Oriole Park at Camden Yards, watching another long flyball leave the yard, it's natural sometimes for it to feel that way.  "I've never seen home runs given up like we do," Orioles manager Brandon Hyde marveled last week.  That's because no one has ever seen home runs given up like the 2019 Orioles. Before this month, the major league record for homers allowed before the end of April was 50 by the 1996 Detroit Tigers. The Orioles zoomed past that record on April 20 - a day that saw them give up 11 long balls in a doubleheader sweep at the hands of the Minnesota Twins. Entering Friday, with five days left before the calendar turns to May, the Orioles' total sat at 59.  But the Orioles are merely an extreme example of something taking place all across the game. Even in an era of unprecedented, leaguewide home-run power, the first month of the 2019 season stands out. Entering Friday, teams had combined to hit a record 979 homers - an average of 1.32 per team-game. That's 116 more than teams hit in April 2017, a season that would eventually see a record 6,105 homers.  In other words, the 2019 home run rate is 5 percent higher than the highest rate in history (1.26 per team-game in 2017), and up 15 percent from last year, when the leaguewide rate dipped to 1.15.  And what is truly scary is that the early part of the season normally produces the lowest rate of homers. What's going to happen when the weather warms, typically resulting in balls carrying further? At least in Baltimore, nobody seems to have any answers.  "I have no idea," Orioles reliever Mychal Givens said. "But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans selling grass from Kanye Coachella performance for $405...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/04/26/fans-are-selling-grass-from-kanyes-coachella-sunday-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One listing is going for a heart-stopping $405 (plus shipping).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Installed Top Cop to Steer INTERPOL. Then He Disappeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-installed-its-top-cop-to-steer-interpol-then-he-disappeared-11556304500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meng Hongwei’s election as president of the global police agency was expected to help China’s crackdown on corruption, but the official himself was arrested—one side says for bribe-taking, the other for failing to do Beijing’s bidding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Carolina considers firing squad as death penalty workaround...</title>
      <link>https://www.wltx.com/article/news/local/sc-may-use-firing-squad-as-death-penalty-workaround/101-35f7f6df-20f9-4c31-aaab-e29e99c7ff63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wltx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are currently 29 men on South Carolina death row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training boys to be 'alpha' to counter 'masculinity crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-masculinity-pop-idols-backlash-20190426-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a freezing winter day, boys as young as 7 are running shirtless in a Beijing Park, training to be "real men." It's part of a backlash in China against flawlessly made-up Chinese pop stars and an existential fear for nation's "virility."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hijacked listing for Bel-Air megamansion leads to $60M lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/realestate/hot-property/la-fi-hp-zillow-makowsky-lawsuit-20190426-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit that developer Bruce Makowsky filed against real estate company Zillow underscores how image is everything when seeking nine figures for a single estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Helping Govt Conduct Warrantless Searches?</title>
      <link>https://www.cpomagazine.com/data-privacy/epic-alleges-google-may-be-helping-u-s-government-conduct-warrantless-searches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cpomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scanning images in billions of users’ files without warrants, is Google helping the U.S. government to conduct warrantless searches and violating the Fourth Amendment?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia killing millions of feral cats with poisoned sausages...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/26/australia-is-killing-millions-of-feral-cats-with-poisoned-sausages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian officials are killing millions of feral cats by airdropping frozen sausages laced with poison across the Outback. The felines die within 15 minutes of ingesting the toxic treats, which a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Grand Canyon deaths, tourists still drawn to edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/grand-canyon-deaths-after-latest-fatal-fall-tourists-still-drawn-n998791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s really tempting because you see the way to go down and you want to go down there to get a better view,” a park visitor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French architects want Notre Dame reborn as GREENHOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6963757/Notre-Dame-reborn-GREENHOUSE-French-architects-propose-replacing-damaged-roof-glass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French architects have revealed a stunning set of plans to redesign Notre Dame Cathedral's fire-ravaged roof as a greenhouse, complete with a glass roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RECORD HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/26/stock-market-gdp-data-and-corporate-earnings-in-focus-on-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Composite closed at record highs on Friday as better-than-expected economic data offset a mixed batch of corporate earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of female gun ownership...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/female-gun-ownership-and-the-rise-of-fashionable-carrywear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexo Athletica designed a pair of Lulelemon-like leggings with pockets for guns -- and women gun owners took notice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wants to Make America -- Great Again?</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2019/04/joe-biden-2020-launch-maga-trump-us-history.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president needs voters to believe that the country was totally great before Donald Trump ruined it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Makes Snitching Profitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-profitable-prospects-of-snitching-for-the-irs-11556271006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS awarded more than $312 million to whistleblowers last year, including about $100 million to a single tipster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Clients in College Admissions Scandal From China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-biggest-clients-in-the-college-admissions-scandal-were-from-china-11556301872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families from China were among those who allegedly paid the most in the college admissions scandal, a new sign of the reach of the cheating ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executions for 'sorcerers', homosexuals, mentally ill DOUBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8946867/saudi-arabia-executions-sorcerers-homosexuals-double/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE number of sick executions in Saudi Arabia has DOUBLED in recent years  – with people beheaded for bizarre reasons including “sorcery” and for simply being gay. Crown Prince Mohammed bin S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Flexes Fundraising Strength...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440860-joe-biden-announces-63-million-fundraising-haul-in-first-24-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden raised $6.3 million in the 24 hours after launching his 2020 White House bid, his campaign announced Friday, a record fundraising haul in the crowded Democratic presidential field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey from disgraced officer to police chief surprisingly common...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2019/04/24/police-officers-police-chiefs-sheriffs-misconduct-criminal-records-database/2214279002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During NRA speech, Trump revokes another global arms treaty...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/during-nra-speech-trump-revokes-another-global-arms-treaty/ar-BBWjL4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PRICES PLUNGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/26/oil-market-opec-output-rises-us-sanctions-on-iranian-oil-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump says he "called up" OPEC and told the producer group to take measures to cut the price of gasoline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Efforts To Search For, Send Messages To Extraterrestrial Life Advance...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/messages-extraterrestrial-life-advancing-digital-age/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ambitious new effort is underway to make direct contact with intelligent life beyond earth, improving upon 70s-era space missions which included attempts to bring messages from Earth to extraterrestrials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Mulls Sending 300 More Troops To Border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0d2c4a017104b61a244408223aaf6b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon may send about 300 more troops to the U.S.-Mexico border in roles that could put them in contact with migrants and thus mark a break from current practice, officials...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
