<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon looks to microbes to feed troops with air, water, trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-12-15/darpa-cornucopia-air-water-microbe-foods-military-deployments-3978766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chow halls and “warrior restaurants” of the future could serve deployed troops meals made by microorganisms using water, air, electricity and little else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine defense in disarray as one witness refuses to respond to subpoena, another  pleading fifth and a third stuck in the UK... MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10321579/Ghislaine-Maxwells-defense-disarray-plans-witnesses-fall-apart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell's second day of defense got off to a rocky start Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Ghislaine trial nears end, she faces choice that carries enormous risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/17/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-defense-finish-arguments-sex-trafficking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers say they expect the defense case to conclude Friday or Monday, setting stage for closing arguments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The photos she didn't want the jury to see...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/the-photos-that-ghislaine-maxwell-didnt-want-the-jury-to-see/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos displayed during Ghislaine Maxwell’s sex-trafficking trial show her in an apparently happy relationship with Jeffrey Epstein, her notorious former companion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies FOXNEWS Motion to Dismiss DOMINION $1.6 Billion Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-judge-dismisses-fox-news-move-to-dismiss-smartmatic-libel-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge presiding over Dominion's $1.6 billion lawsuit against Fox News has denied the cable network's move to dismiss the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom gives birth to 'TESLA baby' while vehicle drives on autopilot...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mother-gives-birth-to-tesla-baby-while-vehicle-drives-on-autopilot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Pennsylvania baby was born with a lot of drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED Holiday Party Superspreader, Infected Had Boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/buzzfeed-nyc-holiday-party-becomes-a-covid-superspreader-event-several-employees-infected-insider/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several BuzzFeed staffers have been infected with Covid-19 following the company's Holiday party in Manhattan last week, according to a report from Insider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKETTES SHUTDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/christmas-shows-canceled-at-radio-city-music-hall-over-covid-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID cases forced the cancelation of all of Friday's Christmas Spectacular shows at Radio City Music Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France bans UK travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/dec/16/france-tighten-covid-restrictions-travel-omicron-uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government says travel will be limited to ‘essential purposes’ for vaccinated and unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark proposes closing public venues...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/586296-denmark-closing-public-venues-amid-omicron-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's prime minister announced on Friday that the government is proposing new restrictions, including closing the country's concert halls, theaters and cinemas, amid a record-breaking surge in daily COVID-19 cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands USA, NATO stay out of Kremlin's 'sphere of influence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2021/12/17/ukraine-russia-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin’s far-reaching security demands have been repeatedly ruled out by NATO officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Dangerous Is Tulum for Tourists Right Now?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4aw3x3/how-dangerous-is-tulum-for-tourists-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murders in the tourist paradise have surged and tourists are wondering whether partying there is worth the risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seedling by seedling, Joshua trees will rise again in fire-scorched desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/seedling-by-seedling-joshua-trees-will-rise-again-in-fire-scorched-desert/article_37fa4fc8-8406-5c44-9937-faa556364138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Joe Landeros plunged a shovel into the earth, poured water into the hole and carefully inserted a spiky green seedling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Muscles Can Balloon In Size As Strange New Side-Effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/muscles-balloon-in-size-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biopsies of the most powerful muscle in the thigh from 18 COVID patients revealed the muscles in four of them increased "massively" while in the ICU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colonists called him tyrant. But was King George III really so bad?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/American-colonists-called-him-a-tyrant-But-was-16709602.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Last King of America: The Misunderstood Reign of George III</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closures, mandates, new fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/concerns-over-a-winter-wave-of-omicron-prompt-closures-mask-mandates-and-new-covid-fears/ar-AARUzRw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin 'may not last that much longer,' academic warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/17/bitcoin-may-not-last-that-much-longer-academic-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of bitcoin is anyone's guess, but one academic has warned that the world's most popular cryptocurrency could fade out in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW drops more 400 points in volatile trading as market set to post losing week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/16/stock-futures-inch-higher-following-tech-sector-sell-off-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors sold tech stocks again, a day after losses in the sector dragged down the rest of the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destinations That 'Forgot' COVID Making Killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/destinations-forgot-covid-making-killing-095758281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELVIS BARUKCIC/AFP via GettyROME—If you would have asked Dejan Ljevanic, who runs the Jahorina ski resort on Bosnia’s famed winter ski mountain, a year ago if he thought the 2021 ski season would be such a success, he says he would have laughed in your face. But Jahorina and Bosnia’s second mountain Bjelasnica are doing the best business they’ve done since long before the pandemic started.Skiing in Bosnia has always been popular for those who live in the Balkans. It’s considerably cheaper than t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto hackers make killing robbing trading platforms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/bitcoin-crypto-exchange-hacks-little-anyone-can-do-rcna7870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not just lucky investors getting rich from crypto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI predicts who will develop dementia with 92% accuracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10317707/AI-accurately-predict-develop-dementia-two-years-study-suggests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from 15,300 patients in the US was used to train the AI by researchers from the University of Exeter, teaching it who would and wouldn't go on to develop dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Significant amounts of water' found in Mars Grand Canyon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/16/world/exomars-water-mars-grand-canyon-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A European orbiter has detected "significant amounts of water" in Mars' version of the Grand Canyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dog Owners Less Likely To Be Depressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-boosting-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Dog walking during confinements may have alleviated stressors and motivated self-care," researchers add.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police say six men targeted and robbed elderly Asians in Bay Area: 'Victims hunted'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Police-say-six-men-targeted-and-robbed-elderly-16709313.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The smash-and-grab robbery crew knew who they were after: elderly Asian women who, they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Ghislaine trial nears end, she faces choice that carries enormous risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/12/17/nyregion/ghislaine-maxwell-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As testimony in Ms. Maxwell’s sex-trafficking trial nears its end, she faces a choice that legal experts said carries enormous risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope at 85: No more Mr Nice Guy, as reform hits stride...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pope-francis-health-religion-europe-2f733bf842c499eab9f06a48363a68df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis celebrated his 85th birthday on Friday, a milestone made even more remarkable given the coronavirus pandemic, his summertime intestinal surgery and the weight of history: His predecessor retired at this age and the last pope to have lived any longer was Leo XIII over a century ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No evidence' less severe than Delta...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211217134928-cbrot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Viral blizzard' about to hit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/586274-former-biden-covid-19-adviser-viral-blizzard-about-to-hit-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former COVID-19 adviser for President Biden's transition on Thursday warned of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick world of Cuomo ex CNN producer revealed in police report...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/16/sick-new-details-of-cnn-producer-john-griffin-revealed-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired CNN producer John Griffin allegedly led a perverted double life in recent months involving the “adoptive” mother of a 9-year-old girl in Henderson, Nevada, who was part of a sordi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Says $100 Oil Possible as Record Demand Outpaces Supply...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-says-100-oil-possible-052256088.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Oil at $100 a barrel cannot be ruled out in 2023 as supply additions are expected to be too slow to keep up with record demand, according to Goldman Sachs Group Inc.Most Read from BloombergAcross the U.S., School Shooting Threats on TikTok Prompt Closures and More PoliceDemocrats Drop Year-End Push on Biden Economic Plan Amid DiscordSouth Africa Hospitalization Rate Plunges in Omicron WaveChinese Spies Accused of Using Huawei in Secret Australia Telecom HackMelania Trump Is Releas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC EPICENTER -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10318707/NYC-Covid-positivity-rate-DOUBLED-new-cases-increase-26-3-days-wave-strikes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long lines formed at test sites on Thursday, as New York City's Covid test positivity rate doubled in a matter of only three days, from 3.9 percent to 7.8 percent from December 9 to December 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says redefinition of fully vaccinated on table...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/17/covid-fauci-says-a-redefinition-of-fully-vaccinated-is-certainly-on-the-table.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A redefinition of what it means to be fully vaccinated against Covid-19 is "certainly on the table," Dr. Antony Fauci has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychologist testifies accusers fell prey to 'false memories'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/586247-maxwells-lawyers-argue-accusers-fell-prey-to-lapses-in-memory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A psychologist called to testify for the defense at the trial of British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell, who is accused of helping her close confidant Jeffrey Epstein recruit and sexually abuse underage girls, said that Maxwe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida man kicked off flight for using underwear as mask in protest...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/586267-florida-man-kicked-off-united-flight-for-using-underwear-as-mask-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man was kicked off a United flight for using a thong as a mask to protest the airline's mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems face painful reality as priorities stumble...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/586250-democrats-face-painful-reality-as-priorities-stumble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats are stumbling into the end of their first year in the majority, with two of their biggest priorities—President Biden’s spending bill and voting rights—stuck in limbo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud or failure?: Final arguments in THERANOS trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/fraud-or-failure-final-arguments-in-theranos-us-trial-2656059547/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US jurors heard clashing visions Thursday at fallen Silicon Valley star Elizabeth Holmes's trial, with prosecutors calling her a fraudster in closing arguments and the defense claiming she truly believed in her blood testing startup.Holmes potentially faces years in prison if convicted on allegation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans blow off The Don's bid to oust McConnell...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/17/gop-trump-oust-mcconnell-525207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just two Senate candidates — and no senators — have publicly called for replacing the Republican leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In bad sign for Boris, Britain's Conservatives lose parliament seat they held for 200 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-a-bad-sign-for-boris-johnson-britain-e2-80-99s-conservatives-lose-parliament-seat-they-held-for-nearly-200-years/ar-AARUm9E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An uncrowned king: Saudi's Prince Mohammed takes reins...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211217-an-uncrowned-king-saudi-s-prince-mohammed-takes-the-reins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From greeting foreign leaders to heading regional summits, Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman is taking over the reins from his elderly father and becoming Saudi Arabia's uncrowned king.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake gynaecologist snares 400 women in webcam scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanherald.com/international/world-news-politics/fake-italian-gynaecologist-snares-400-women-in-webcam-scam-1061878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian police Friday searched the house of suspected serial sexual predator believed to have posed as a gynaecologist to persuade dozens of women to undergo vaginal exams via weblink. Police in the southern city of Bari seized several smartphones and memory cards from the 40-year old, after wiretapping his calls following complaints from multiple victims. The man is alleged to have called women who had undergone swabs at clinics across the country, to tell them they had been diagnosed with "several vaginal infections," the police said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Turkey, critics say the sultan has no clothes. Erdogan's advisers won't tell him...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-Turkey-critics-say-the-sultan-has-no-clothes-16709196.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Turkey, the lira is falling, and so is the sky. Prices at supermarkets are changing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans feel virus whiplash...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/12/16/americans-feel-virus-whiplash-with-omicron-variant-upending-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boosters appear to provide good protection, and studies suggest omicron symptoms may be milder. But amid soaring cases and increasing closures, many are puzzled on how to assess the risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WAVE WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/lockdown-by-stealth-coming-in-as-people-shun-pubs-and-parties-1356747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People appear to be putting off socialising to save their contacts for Christmas itself, heeding Professor Chris Whitty’s appeal to 'prioritise what matters'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies Try to Run Out Clock on Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/16/facing-subpoenas-trump-allies-try-to-run-out-the-clock-on-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — On Tuesday night, as the House prepared to hold Donald J. Trump’s former chief of staff Mark Meadows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area car owners leaving trunks open to avoid forced entry by thieves...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/trunk-open-car-break-in-why-not-to-leave-your/11344070/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaving your trunk open to deter car break-ins? Some auto owners in the Bay Area are trying it, but police warn this is a very bad idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With too few nurses, it won't take much to overwhelm system...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/12/09/with-too-few-nurses-it-wont-take-much-to-overwhelm-hospitals-this-winter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals nationwide are so short-staffed they’re unable to operate at full capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC FORECAST: 15,600 DEATHS PER WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10314687/CDC-issues-grim-forecast-warning-weekly-COVID-cases-jump-55-1-3-MILLION-Christmas-Day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC projects that the U.S. will record up to 1.3 million new COVID-19 cases during the week of Christmas, a 55 percent increase over current totals. It also predicts a sharp death increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA broadens access to abortion pills as Supreme Court weighs Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/16/politics/medication-abortion-fda-supreme-court/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Food and Drug Administration announced Thursday that it is lifting a requirement that patients seeking medication abortion had to pick up the medication in-person, instead allowing pills to be sent by mail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vast study confirms rare heart risk from MODERNA jabbing...</title>
      <link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/overseas/12/17/21/vast-study-confirms-rare-heart-risk-from-moderna-jab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moderna Covid jab carries a slight risk of usually non-serious heart problems a study of the entire population of Denmark found Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First salt, now SUGAR warnings coming to NYC menus...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/high-sugar-warnings-on-menus-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for high sugar warnings at restaurants in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida couple saw bees coming out of their shower; Massive beehive of 80,000 was in wall!</title>
      <link>https://people.com/pets/thousands-of-bees-found-in-florida-couples-shower-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Removing the insects and the 100 pounds of honey found with them took more than five hours and came at the cost of $800 — which was not covered by insurance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS SEARCH BALDWIN PHONE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/alec-baldwin-shooting-rust-search-warrant-cell-phone-police-halyna-hutchins-1234892657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost two months after the fatal shooting of Rust cinematographer Halyna Hutchins by Alec Baldwin on the New Mexico set of low budget Western, Santa Fe police want to look at the Emmy winner’s iPh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 heart inflammation cases among young dosed kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/eight-heart-inflammation-cases-seen-174452995.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC had previously said that reporting rates of myocarditis for boys aged 16 to 17 could be more than 69 cases per million second doses administered and around 40 cases per million second doses in boys aged 12-15 years old. The CDC did not say whether it believes there is a link between the myocarditis cases and the vaccine, or disclose the rate of myocarditis in the age group without vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNARD GOLDBERG: Who will abandon FOXNEWS next?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/585791-who-will-abandon-fox-news-next</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Wallace was a Fox News star, someone who believed in the network’s one-time motto of “Fair and Balanced” coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL cracks down...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/12/16/nfl-covid-19-protocols-testing-out-masking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is amping up the league&amp;amp;#039;s COVID-19 protocols. Masking is required for everyone, but positive players can test out sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC warns NOT to get J&amp;J over blood clot risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10318751/CDC-panel-unanimously-recommends-Pfizer-Moderna-vaccine-instead-J-J.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans should be given the Pfizer or Moderna mRNA vaccines instead of the Johnson &amp; Johnson shot, U.S. health advisers recommended Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy begins kicking out 5,731 sailors; Army prepares to ax 3,800 soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10317305/Army-says-nearly-98-got-COVID-19-vaccine-deadline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Navy and Army each say 98% of their active-duty members have gotten at least one dose of COVID vaccine, but the last 2% have refused to comply with the order and will be discharged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court 'packing' commission member says adding justices dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10317471/Member-Bidens-Supreme-Court-packing-commission-says-adding-justices-dangerous-democracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of President Biden's Supreme Court commission broke ranks on Thursday to warn that increasing the number of justices would have a dangerous impact on justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ashley Biden Diary Made Its Way to 'VERITAS'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/16/how-ashley-bidens-diary-made-its-way-to-project-veritas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the final two months of the 2020 campaign, President Donald J. Trump, his grip on power slipping because of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse has groping problem -- already...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/12/16/1042516/the-metaverse-has-a-groping-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was sexually harassed on Meta’s VR social media platform. She’s not the first—and won’t be the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC recommends others over J&amp;J due to clots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/16/cdc-panel-prefers-pfizer-moderna-vaccines-over-jj-due-to-rare-blood-clot-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC has confirmed 54 cases of people developing blood clots and showing low blood platelet levels following J&amp;J vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Striking' jab resistance in variant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/16/columbia-university-finds-omicron-vaccine-resistance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study out of Columbia University says the Omicron variant is “markedly resistant” to vaccines and boosters might not do much to help, spelling bad news for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cyber mercenaries' using FACEBOOK to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211216-meta-targets-cyber-mercenaries-using-facebook-to-spy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook parent Meta announced Thursday the shutdown of some 1,500 accounts tied to "cyber mercenary" companies accused of spying on activists, dissidents and journalists worldwide on behalf of payin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parscale Probed...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/brad-parscale-says-jan-6-161701536.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom BrennerThe Jan. 6 Committee now appears to be looking into former Trump campaign manager Brad Parscale, with Parscale telling The Daily Beast late Wednesday night the committee investigating the attack on the Capitol had subpoenaed his phone records from November through January.Parscale said he had received a notice from his phone carrier earlier in the day and “just agreed.”“I had nothing to do with Jan. 6,” said Parscale, who has not played an active role in the campaign since a month bef</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers promise sensational revelations...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4282550/ghislaine-maxwell-sensational-revelations-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell is unlikely to testify in her sex trafficking trial — but her lawyers are promising sensational revelations in their bid to clear her. The British socialite, 59, is said to be “to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil becomes first to fly in and out of active volcano...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/16/ex-chilean-pilot-becomes-first-person-to-fly-in-active-volcano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thrill-seeker jumped out of the chopper at an altitude of almost 2.2 miles and reached speeds of about 180 mph as he flew into and out of the 656-foot-wide crater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE RETIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/12/16/lowenthal-wont-seek-reelection-in-2022-1400288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Long Beach Democrat said in a statement that he would not seek a sixth term in Congress, choosing instead to “pass the baton” and spend time with family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From blood clots to infected neurons, how virus threatens brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/12/16/1064594686/how-covid-threatens-the-brain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus that causes COVID-19 can cause strokes, inflammation, oxygen deprivation and infection in the brain. And each of these may lead to long-term neurological problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>103 Marines booted for refusing vax...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/103-marines-booted-refusing-covid-vaccine-services-begin/story?id=81793800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marines have discharged more than 100 Marines for refusing to take the COVID vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In profane rant, Nevada Rep. blames fellow liberals for competitive race...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/profane-rant-nevada-congresswoman-blames-fellow-democrats-competitive-race-n1286153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Titus suggested that Democrats could lose the three Nevada congressional seats they currently hold in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEX AND CITY STAR' denies rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10317761/Sex-Citys-Chris-Noth-accused-sexual-assault-two-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allegations against the 67-year-old American actor were detailed in a new report from The Hollywood Reporter published on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Beware Prophecies of Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/beware-prophecies-of-civil-war/ar-AARS8eg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge grips NYC:  'Never seen this before'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/16/new-york-city-is-seeing-a-covid-surge-ahead-of-the-holidays-weve-never-seen-this-before.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's test positivity rate doubled in just three days, Dr. Jay Varma, a top health advisor to Mayor Bill de Blasio, tweeted Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone' Has Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/technology/2021/12/omicron-spike-nyc-explained.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron is spiking among a very specific group of people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
