<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the grave: What's next for the horror reboot?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/oct/23/halloween-horror-reboots-upcoming-pet-sematary-it </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Halloween’s record-breaking haul, Hollywood is set to look to the past to bring back horror’s most feared villains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Dem win Kansas gov race?</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Could-a-Democrat-win-the-Kansas-governor-s-race-13332002.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kansas is a state entirely controlled by Republicans now and one that voted for President Donald Trump in 2016 by 20 points. And yet in a couple of weeks, voters there could elect a Democrat to be their governor for the first time in eight years - just in time to have a hand in the upcoming redistricting battle that could shape control of the state for the next decade. That there is such a tight race is more a reflection of Republican control of the state for the past eight years than any major shift in conservative Kansas to the left. Kansas has been struggling for years with massive budget shortfalls. Those have cut deep into budgets for roads, schools and hospitals in a way that's hard for the average Kansan to miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when they arrive?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/trump-administration-has-not-settled-on-a-plan-for-what-to-do-if-the-migrant-caravan-arrives-at-the-us-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has not settled on a plan for what to do if a migrant caravan arrives at the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dogs now have cameras, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9ec0ccc37af3477c9c6f2e0577484f34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILWAUKEE (AP) — Police dogs have always helped their human counterparts through their eyes and nose, and now some of the dogs are getting their own backup — cameras that transmit live video. The devices generally attach to dogs' backs on a vest and transmit video to a handler watching from a screen, possibly on their wrist or around their necks. It's so the officers can better assess what they are up against before they go into a situation. "If we have a really close encounter with armed people it doesn't work out well for anyone," said Shawn Gore, Portland, Oregon, police K-9 officer. "If we can gain distance it gives us lots of options to negotiate and de-escalate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise lost: Tourist spots in danger of being loved to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181024-paradise-lost-tourist-spots-danger-being-loved-death </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince first speech since Khashoggi murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/saudi-crown-prince-make-first-speech-khashoggi-murder-doc-1a943n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger may help...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/americans-anger-may-help-democrats-november-6-vote-101320273.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Chico, 67, a Republican in California, says his annoyance with Democrats morphed into full-blown outrage when he heard they might try to impeach President Donald Trump after the Nov. 6 elections. Eden Stramer, 23, a North Dakota Democrat, says the possibility of abortions becoming illegal again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever auction of AI-created artwork set for Christie's gavel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6310909/First-auction-painting-created-AI-artist-opens-Christies-New-York.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artwork - which is up for auction in New York - is one of a group of portraits of the fictional Belamy family created by a Paris-based trio of 25-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's internment camps: tear gas, Tasers and textbooks...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/717/inside-chinas-internment-camps-tear-gas-tasers-and-textbooks-doc-1a73p63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Class Flying More Luxurious Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/first-class-flying-is-back-and-it-s-more-luxurious-than-ever#gs.MHyve5I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carriers are adding routes and amping up the amenity quotient of their premium cabins.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicides Surge in Hopeless Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/suicides-surge-in-a-hopeless-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicides Surge in a Hopeless Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota at Crossroads of Divided America...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/-ground-zero-for-house-control-puts-trump-s-appeal-to-the-test#gs.uWH4n8w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;`Ground Zero' for House Control Puts Trump's Appeal to the Test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Weighs Teaching Arabic In School...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/france-weighs-teaching-arabic-in-schools-to-keep-lessons-secular-1540373401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Macron’s government is considering giving parents a secular alternative to intertwined Arabic and Islamic instruction in mosques by prodding more public schools to offer Arabic lessons—without religious content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook blistering attack on 'data industrial complex'...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/10/24/apples-tim-cook-makes-blistering-attack-on-the-data-industrial-complex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple’s CEO Tim Cook has joined the chorus of voices warning that data itself is being weaponized again people and societies — arguing that the trade in digital data has exploded into a “data industrial complex”. Cook did not namecheck the adtech elephants in the room: Googl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even 10-Min Walk Good for Brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/24/well/move/exercise-brain-memory-fitness-cognitive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten minutes of mild exercise can immediately alter how certain parts of the brain communicate and coordinate with one another and improve memory function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SCARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/dow-poised-for-triple-digit-losses-at-the-open-after-tuesdays-500-point-recovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures indicated a weak start to the trading day, as investors look ahead to a raft of economic data and third-quarter corporate earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record numbers of West Nile cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/24/record-numbers-of-west-nile-virus-cases-reported-in-parts-of-us </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warming temperatures and flooding driven by climate change is heightening the risk of contracting the disease, experts warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials prepare for potential false claims of election interference...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/412863-officials-prepare-for-potential-false-claims-of-election-interference</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State and federal officials say they are well prepared for the possibility of a cyberattack on American election systems Nov. 6, but experts warn that even a false claim of interference by foreign actors on Election Day could undermine the public’s faith in the voting process.Officials prepare for potential false claims of election interference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese Tells Pope: 'World Marked by Evil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/10/23/watch-martin-scorsese-tells-pope-the-world-is-marked-by-evil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film director Martin Scorsese told pope Francis Tuesday that the world is “marked by evil” and asked how to “strengthen and guide the young.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate slipping away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d97c666cf6fa4a42a7cadc9b9ac742de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — In the closing stretch of the 2018 campaign, the question is no longer the size of the Democratic wave. It's whether there will be a wave at all. Top operatives in both political parties concede that Democrats' narrow path to the Senate majority has essentially disappeared, a casualty of surging Republican enthusiasm across GOP strongholds. At the same time, leading Democrats now fear the battle for the House majority will be decided by just a handful of seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants split over corporate tax to help homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-tech-giants-split-over-corporate-tax-help-015821021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxing San Francisco's wealthiest companies to rein in the city's homelessness problem makes sense to local campaigners -- but the local tech giants aren't all so sure. On November 6, voters in the city that is the home base of Twitter, Uber and Airbnb will decide the fate of "Proposition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'all Trump, all the time' help in midterms?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-time-help-gop-midterms-204647756--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is betting that his ubiquitous role in the midterm elections — all Trump, all the time — will pay off for Republicans trying to hang onto their perilous majorities in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gays, blacks still voting for Brazil's Bolsonaro despite rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gays-blacks-still-voting-brazils-bolsonaro-despite-rhetoric-015504908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right-wing Brazilian presidential candidate Jair Bolsonaro once said he'd rather have a dead son than one who came out of the closet, but that isn't stopping conservative gay voters from backing him in Sunday's decisive election run-off. For these voters, Bolsonaro is tough on crime and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador no longer to intervene with UK for Assange... </title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/exclusive-ecuador-no-longer-intervene-uk-wikileaks-assange-003907346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign Minister José Valencia said in an interview with Reuters that Ecuador's only responsibility was looking after Assange's wellbeing, after the Australian national sued the country over new conditions placed on his asylum in the London embassy. "Ecuador has no responsibility to take</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SCARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/10/23/stocks-drop-after-caterpillar-3-m-issue-disappointing-forecasts/1737169002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks sold off again Tuesday after Caterpillar and 3M issued outlooks that worried investors. Stocks later recovered part of those losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHODUNNIT MYSTERY IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/23/british-metoo-scandal-cannot-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading businessman has been granted an injunction against The Telegraph to prevent this newspaper revealing alleged sexual harassment and racial abuse of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAT:  Candidates clash at Georgia gov debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/stacey-abrams-brian-kemp-debate-tonight/h5hAHuiFtUPlEOR66cK0HN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire alarm was a surprise, but otherwise Tuesday’s debate between Georgia gubernatorial ca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How it became so big and why it continues to grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/How-the-migrant-caravan-became-so-big-and-why-13331175.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUIXTLA, Mexico - Edith Cruz was sitting at home in central Honduras, scanning Facebook on her phone, when she saw the post about the caravan on a community news page. It was Oct. 12. She and her cousin had just opened a small business selling tortillas when they were confronted by a gang, threatened with death if they didn't hand over half of their profits. She looked at the Facebook post: "An avalanche of Hondurans is preparing to leave in a caravan to the United States. Share this!" Within three hours, her bags were packed. The question of how the migrant caravan began has wound its way to the American midterm elections. President Donald Trump and other Republicans have suggested that Democrats paid migrants to begin the journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Could Hold Back Wave? Economy, Confidence, Independence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/what-could-hold-back-a-democratic-wave-economy-confidence-independence/ar-BBOM067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS AT CBSNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/23/60-minutes-correspondents-threaten-to-quit-over-potential-new-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman from “48 Hours” running “60 Minutes”? You must be joking. Snooty correspondents at CBS’ “60 Minutes” are apoplectic over the idea that Susan Zirinsky — the longtime boss of the network’s cr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY TRICKS:  Racist robocalls in campaign for Florida governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article220490950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An out-of-state website is once again making robocalls to Florida voters with a racist message intended to malign Democrat Andrew Gillum, who would be the state’s first black governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal families set record for year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/23/illegal-immigrant-families-set-record-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration by families surged this summer after the collapse of President Trump’s zero-tolerance border policy, reaching record levels and leaving the Trump administration frustrated over the lack of easy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane season most powerful on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/10/23/hurricane-season-most-active-record-atlantic-pacific-combined/1741226002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When all the hurricanes and tropical storms in the Atlantic and Pacific are added together, the 2018 hurricane season is the most active season ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAPCHAT helped 400,000+ register...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/snapchat-helped-over-400000-people-register-to-vote-says-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popular app got even more people to register than Taylor Swift did, says The New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON execs already donating for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/amazon-ceo-jeff-bezos-backs-senator-cory-gardner-for-re-election---in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Sen. Cory Gardner's campaign saw a boost from Amazon executives in the third quarter, including CEO Jeff Bezos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARSCALE: Big Tech Meddling with Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/10/23/exclusive-brad-parscale-big-tech-is-meddling-with-free-speech-and-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest of the Big Tech companies are quickly positioning themselves as the internet’s thought police, threatening to stamp out one of America’s most cherished freedoms — the right to free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN SWELLS TO 14,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/23/mexican-news-outlet-officials-say-14000-honduran-migrants-heading-to-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican El Universal news outlet is reporting that more than 14,000 Hondurans are heading to the United States border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto superhero mural pops up in Austin...</title>
      <link>http://spectrumlocalnews.com/tx/austin/news/2018/10/23/mural-of-beto-as-a-superhero-pops-up-in-east-austin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectrumlocalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist goal to show “out of the darkness comes the light.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors brace for surge of polio-like disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-investigating-more-cases-polio-syndrome-n923041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are bracing for an upsurge in cases this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county adopts rules to preempt sexbot brothels...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/politics/houston/article/Harris-County-adopts-new-rules-to-pre-empt-robot-13329896.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris County Commissioners Court on Tuesday unanimously adopted new rules regulating sexually oriented business to prevent so-called "robot brothels" from opening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Steps Up Attacks on Fed Chairman...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-steps-up-attacks-on-fed-chairman-jerome-powell-1540338090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump escalated his attacks on Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, saying the head of the nation’s central bank threaten U.S. economic growth and appeared to enjoy raising interest rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armies of lawyers mobilize...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/midterms/article220481405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Americans go to the polls for midterm elections, political parties and interest groups are deploying thousands of lawyers nationwide to guard against voting problems or challenge results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Uses Gillum Soundbite for Network Promo...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/23/cnn-andrew-gillum-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facts First?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets -- can tell time...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2018/10/23/Your-pets-know-what-time-it-is-study-shows/9121540315010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests animals have a relatively accurate sense of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll worker error means vote re-do...</title>
      <link>https://www.greensboro.com/ap/north_carolina/poll-worker-s-error-means-vote-re-do-for-legislative/article_5f59cf9c-6798-5490-b742-05e68d176c83.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greensboro.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOLIVIA, N.C. (AP) — Nearly 150 North Carolina voters will be invited to cast their ballots a second time after a poll worker's mistake meant they were given the wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA founder lays off all journalists from new media website...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/10/23/18015174/wikipedia-founder-jimmy-wales-wikitribune-journalist-lay-off-community-focus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiTribune is shifting to a community-focused operation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Brain Trust Sees 2020 Successor: Deval Patrick...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/darrensands/deval-patrick-2020-president-campaign-barack-obama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The perils of the road to the presidency — and a life and business he loves — may ultimately keep Deval Patrick away from the Democratic primary. It’s just that he’s running into an awful lot of reaso</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot survives as plane crashes, burns on CA freeway...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/traffic/small-plane-reportedly-down-on-101-freeway-in-agoura-hills/4543306/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small plane crashed on the westbound 101 in Agoura Hills on Tuesday, and the fiery wreck shut down both sides of the freeway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer falls to death from airplane in failed music video stunt...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/canadian-rapper-dies-after-falling-off-airplane-wing-in-failed-stunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon James McMurray died Saturday filming a project he had been working on for months, a statement said. He trained ‘intensively’ for the stunt, it said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,100 mostly unarmed Guard troops on border...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/10/23/2000-unarmed-guard-troops-on-border-as-trump-vows-to-send-more-to-stop-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Guard could send 2,000 more troops to border, if governors OK the deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple narrowly escape death after beaver topples 65-ft tree onto yacht!</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/germany-beaver-couple-tree-yacht-muritz-elde-a8597841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodent causes thousands of euros in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Speeding escalator at metro goes haywire, piles dozens on floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/rome-subway-escalator-out-of-control-video-2018-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An escalator malfunctioned at a Rome metro station and injured at least 10 people. A video of the event shows people being spit out onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy expert quits GOOGLE-backed 'smart city'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/privacy-expert-resigns-from-alphabet-backed-smart-city-1829934748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A privacy expert tasked with helping a new smart city development protect the data privacy of residents has resigned over concerns that her guidelines would be largely ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City bans clowns on Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/no-clowns-allowed-michigan-city-bans-clowns-on-halloween</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you plan to attend the Boo Bash in the Detroit suburb of Oak Park on Halloween, you can be a ghost, goblin, zombie, vampire or any other character that you wish, but you can't be a clown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON futuristic cashierless convenience store coming to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/amazon-go-cashierless-store-reportedly-opening-in-new-york-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Go stores use "Just Walk Out" technology so shoppers can skip the wait to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM HOT IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/florida-governor-election-2018-andrew-gillum-leads-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto bets big on FACEBOOK ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/facebook-ad-report-puts-o-rourke-as-top-spender-after-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP 6</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/florida/release-detail?ReleaseID=2582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gillum Leads In Tight Florida Governor's Race, Quinnipiac University Poll Finds; Dem Boosted By Independents, Women, Non-White Voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 MILES AWAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/honduran-migrant-caravan-resumes-march-mexico-us-142832691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of mainly Honduran migrants heading to the United States -- a caravan President Donald Trump has called an "assault on our country" -- stopped to rest Tuesday after walking for two days into Mexican territory. "They're exhausted," said migrant rights activist Rodrigo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS AT FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/adenovirus-wanaque-center-for-nursing-and-rehabilitation-new-jersey-outbreak-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strain of adenovirus is affecting "medically fragile children with severely compromised immune systems," health officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ILLEGALS TO VOTE IN SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-allow-noncitizens-vote-school-board-184120600--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco will become the largest city in the United States and one of only a handful nationwide to allow noncitizens, including people in the country illegally, to vote in a local election in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum ahead by 6 points in Florida gov's race...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/10/23/poll-andrew-gillum-leads-ron-desantis-by-6-in-florida-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent governor's race poll shows what every independent general election survey has shown: Andrew Gillum is winning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEOs give employees time off to vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ceos-give-employees-time-off-to-vote-in-hotly-contested-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEOs Give Employees Time Off to Vote in Hotly Contested Midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service cancels controlled burn near Earth's largest tree...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-prescribed-fire-sequoias-20181023-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Park Service plan to set fire to an ancient sequoia grove in the western Sierra Nevada has been canceled for the second time this year, further delaying a delicate forestry operation aimed at triggering new growth near the world’s largest tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  Nuke Weapons in Space Possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pence-leaves-open-the-possibility-of-nuclear-13330288.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Vice President Mike Pence on Tuesday declined to rule out the idea of deploying nuclear weapons in space, saying the current ban on their use is "in the interest of every nation" but the issue should be decided on "the principle that peace comes through strength." "What we need to do is make sure that we provide for the common defense of the people of the United States of America and that's the president's determination here," Pence said in an interview with The Washington Post, when asked if nuclear weapons should be banned from orbit. Pence added, "What we want to do is continue to advance the principle that peace comes through strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper whose lyrics reflected Baltimore's pain fatally shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rapper-whose-lyrics-reflected-baltimores-pain-fatally-shot-151532492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — A rising Baltimore rapper who advocated for nonviolence and whose lyrics often reflected the city's trauma has been shot and killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein, Accusers in Early Talks to Settle Civil Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/harvey-weinstein-accusers-insurers-in-early-talks-to-settle-civil-claims-1540319930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Harvey Weinstein and women who have accused him of sexual misconduct are working with insurance companies and the New York attorney general’s office in an attempt to reach a sweeping settlement of all civil suits pending against the disgraced producer and his former film studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams's Burning of Georgia Flag Surfaces on Eve of Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/abrams-role-in-burning-georgia-flag-is-revealed/17938592/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — At a protest on the steps of the Georgia Capitol in 1992, Stacey Abrams, now the Democratic candidate for governor, joined in the burning of the state flag, which at the time incorporated the Confederate battle flag design and was viewed by many as a lingering symbol of white supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/health/6-kids-dead-12-sick-in-viral-outbreak-at-nj-rehab-center/4542019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state Department of Health on Tuesday confirmed 18 cases of adenovirus at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, Passaic County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stealth bomber makes emergency landing in CO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-stealth-bomber-lands-colorado-emergency-152740438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (AP) — The Air Force says a Missouri-based B2 stealth bomber landed in Colorado Springs after an unspecified emergency, but neither of the pilots was injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Support Claims Rep. Married Her Brother...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/davidsteinberg/official-school-records-support-claims-that-rep-ilhan-omar-d-mn-married-her-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is implicated in multiple felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea says it will arrest citizens who smoke weed in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/23/bong-arm-of-the-law-south-korea-says-it-will-arrest-citizens-who-smoke-weed-in-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seoul reminds 23,000 South Korean students in Canada that domestic law applies to them no matter where they are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100,000 in rare emeralds taken in brazen NC mine heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article220452165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An emerald mine in the foothills of North Carolina was the scene of an old fashioned jewel heist, with thieves making off with more than $100,000 in rare gems and gold jewelry, says the mine owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of control subway escalator injures 10 in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/738264/roma-vs-cska-moscow-russia-football-fans-injured-escalator-rome-video-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue wave? First clues coming in...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article220437025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California election will be in the national spotlight, as it could shape whether Republicans or Democrats control the U.S. House Representatives. Initial mail ballot returns cast doubt on whether a ‘blue wave’ is forming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'flaunt wealth' socials craze: Elites post photos surrounded by luxury goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/23/chinas-rich-post-photos-lying-face-surrounded-luxury-goods-flaunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of people lying face down on the ground surrounded by luxury goods have gone viral on Chinese social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JUDGE JERRY': Springer Working On Daytime Courtroom Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jerry-springer-daytime-courtroom-show-judge-jerry-development-nbcuniversal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Springer has a syndicated courtroom show focused on small-claims cases in the works at NBCUniversal, called "Judge Jerry," of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest amphibious plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/china-ag600-worlds-largest-amphibious-plane-does-first-water-takeoff-test-2018-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AG600, said to be the world's largest amphibious aircraft, is designed for civil aviation and operations like firefighting, but experts believe it could be repurposed for military uses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profanity Used In Ads...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/politics/ct-met-illinois-governors-race-bruce-rauner-ad-profanity-20181022-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Gov. Bruce Rauner is launching a new TV ad on Tuesday that’s provocative for its use of a bleeped-out profanity to describe the future of Illinois if Democratic challenger J.B. Pritzker wins and serves in government alongside House Speaker Michael Madigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School cancels 'ALADDIN' over Arab stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbaltv.com/article/school-cancels-production-of-aladdin-jr-for-complaints-of-stereotyping-arab-culture/24086346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbaltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore County elementary school has stopped plans for a school play because of complaints of negative stereotyping of Arab culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa to recover 'looted' cash after bank collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/south-africa-recover-looted-cash-bank-collapse-161650904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa said Tuesday it would seek to recover millions of dollars stolen from a local bank that subsequently collapsed owing substantial sums to creditors. A central bank report, titled "The Great Bank Heist", into the failure of VBS Mutual bank said $130 million (112 million euros) was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts force Venezuelans to perform surgery in darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article220464510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelans have learned to live by candlelight during electrical blackouts. Commerce and education are paralyzed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook shifts 8 MORE House races toward Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cookpolitical.com/analysis/house/house-overview/ten-rating-changes-democrats-enthusiasm-edge-narrows-and-fundraising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER:  86% DEMS TAKE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2018-midterm-election-forecast/house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2018 House elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bring me the head of the dog'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7559690/how-saudi-crown-prince-aide-ordered-jamal-khashoggis-murder-via-skype-as-journalists-severed-fingers-sent-back-to-royal-as-trophy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE dismembered body of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi has been found near where he is believed to have been tortured and killed, it’s been claimed today. Reports say the butchered remains …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son Glares at MBS During Meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6306539/Saudi-hit-squad-deliberately-disabled-CCTV-consulate-Turkeys-president-Erdogan-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salah bin Jamal Khashoggi was pictured shaking hands with the powerful heir to Saudi Arabia's throne in Riyadh during a meeting also attended by King Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowner Turns Heads With Vicious Trump-Themed Halloween Display...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/10/23/alameda-halloween-display-takes-aim-trump-administration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An East Bay homeowner's elaborate Halloween decorations are drawing a lot of curiosity from neighbors with a clearly anti-Trump political theme that satirizes the current administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Outraged After Drag Queen 'Jessica L'Whor' Speaks At Middle School...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/10/22/adams-county-career-day-drag-queen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A school district has apologized to parents, after hosting a drag queen as part of a career day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT LYIN' TED ANYMORE!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-beautiful-ted-apos-trump-024209079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruz is coming under extreme pressure from his Democratic challenger, Beto O’Rourke, while Trump, troubled by the prospect of a blue wave in November’s midterm elections, is trying to shore up Republican control of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Cat 4 Hurricane Willa closes in on Mexico coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/storms/hurricane/news/2018-10-22-hurricane-willa-pacific-ocean-mexico-landfall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX New $2B Borrowing Sparks Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/netflixs-additional-2-billion-borrowing-raises-wall-street-eyebrows-1154325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer's long-term debt has soared north of $10 billion, though Moody's says ratings and outlook remain stable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC attorney general launches investigation of clergy sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/us/dc-catholic-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Attorney General Karl Racine announced Tuesday that he has launched a civil investigation into whether the Archdiocese of Washington violated the law by covering up the sexual abuse of minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC FOX-TV break-in suspect shot by guard had history of 'irrational' lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2018/10/fox-break-in-suspect-shot-by-guard-said-microchip-was-implanted-in-head/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who was shot by a security guard after kicking his way through two plexiglass doors Fox 5’s D.C. television station Monday has a history of filing “irrational” lawsuits — including one that alleged he had a microchip implanted in his head that controlled his thoughts and actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dec537c487da4dbab9d2212940c8a69a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is battling Democrats for control of Congress. But you might think it's 2016 all over again. As the 2018 midterms shifted to the final two weeks of campaigning, Trump staged a large Monday night rally in Houston, Ted Cruz's hometown, to help the Texas senator and his 2016 presidential rival fend off a tough challenge from Democratic Rep. Beto O'Rourke. During the 2016 primaries, Trump mocked Cruz as "Lyin' Ted," insulted his wife's appearance and suggested Cruz's father played a role in the Kennedy assassination. Cruz assailed Trump as a "sniveling coward" and told Trump to leave his wife alone. But campaigns have a way of letting bygones be bygones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Device Found Near George Soros Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/explosive-device-found-ny-home-billionaire-soros-141259535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI on Tuesday was investigating an explosive device found in the mailbox at the New York home of US billionaire and liberal donor George Soros, a target of right-wing groups, officials confirmed. An employee of the residence in Bedford, north of Manhattan, found the suspicious package in the mailbox</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SPOOKED!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/djia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump Lawyer: There's No 'Witch Hunt,' Mueller 'Is American Hero'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/former-trump-lawyer-ty-cobb-no-witch-hunt-mueller-is-an-american-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It was important to me not to have criticism widely thrown back-and-forth and turn it into a Ken Starr-like process, the way that ended up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Buying of Treasurys Softens...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foreign-buying-of-u-s-treasurys-softens-unsettling-financial-markets-1540303515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overseas investors, traders and central bankers are buying fewer Treasurys, which helped fuel a bond selloff this fall, pushing yields up and shaking stocks. Foreign buyers now hold 41% of outstanding Treasury debt, their lowest share in 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Turns Over Identities of Bloggers on Soccer Team...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/23/sports/benfica-bloggers-google.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymous writers who disclosed proprietary information about the storied club may not be able to remain anonymous for much longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcker thinks 'we're in hell of mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/former-fed-chairman-paul-volcker-thinks-were-in-a-hell-of-a-mess.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Federal Reserve Chairman Paul Volcker, who has reached legend status in the world of central banking, isn't optimistic about current conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TITANIC to set sail...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-titanic-will-sail-from-dubai-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans are continuing to launch a new Titanic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA shares rocket as short seller reverses position...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-shares-rocket-5-as-short-seller-citron-reverses-position-2018-10-23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook shifts 8 toward Dems...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412700-cook-shifts-8-house-races-toward-dems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook Political Report on Tuesday shifted eight House races toward Democrats and two in favor of Republicans with 14 days to go before the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 relatives of GOP Nevada gov candidate pen op-ed opposing him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412694-12-family-members-of-gop-nevada-governor-candidate-pen-op-ed-opposing-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen relatives of a Republican running for governor in Nevada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Ellison falls behind in bid to become Minnesota AG...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/minnesota-poll-doug-wardlow-leads-keith-ellison-in-attorney-general-s-race/498264151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican gained ground since last month's poll; about one in six Minnesota voters still undecided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND migrant caravan heads for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6307043/SECOND-migrant-caravan-1-000-heading-following-first.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second caravan is believed to have started near the site of the first, in Honduras, and has already crossed into Guatemala, spending Monday night near the town of Chiquimula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can rodeo legend win SDakota?</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/803164/democratic-rodeo-legend-become-south-dakotas-next-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the most inspiring governor's race in America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate Arrested For Stealing Rival's Campaign Signs...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/10/22/buena-park-candidate-steals-campaign-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youngsun “Sunny” Park was arrested at about 10 a.m. Friday in a residential neighborhood near Malvern Avenue and Dale Street on reports that a man and a woman were removing campaign signs from people’s lawns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and rise of mega yacht: Billionaires play one-upmanship...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6306281/The-rise-rise-mega-yacht-Billionaire-one-upmanship-high-seas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global yacht management company Hill Robinson says demand for mega yachts has surged over recent years, with the vessels decked out with extreme toys, from submarines to helicopters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Swedes getting microchips inserted into bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6306569/Thousands-Swedes-getting-microchip-IDs-inserted-hands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Swedes have been implanted with a microchip that allows them to replace cash, tickets and access card with a chip the size of a grain of rice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathing through nose boosts memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6306249/Breathing-nose-BOOSTS-memory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts from the Karolinska Institute in Sweden found participants in their test who were exposed to certain odours were better at recalling them if their mouths had been taped over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identical twins born female -- now brothers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6306369/Identical-twins-born-girls-brothers-transitioning-came-transgender.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack and Jace Grafe, 23, originally from Baltimore, Maryland, were born female but are now transitioning together. The brothers are now both in happy relationships with women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The squadron of ex-military men behind Bolsonaro's rise in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-election-generals-insight/the-squadron-of-ex-military-men-behind-bolsonaros-rise-in-brazil-idUSKCN1MX1QX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who will likely be Brazil's next Defense Minister greeted two repor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overuse of antibiotics 'risks return to dark ages of life-threatening surgery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/23/overuse-of-antibiotics-risks-return-to-dark-ages-of-life-threatening-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning comes as report shows 3 million common surgical procedures could be hazardous if infections become resistant to antibiotics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boise, Reno Capitalize on California Real Estate Exodus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/boise-and-reno-capitalize-on-the-california-real-estate-exodus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boise and Reno Capitalize on the California Real Estate Exodus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOKTWITTER staffs splurge on Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/google-facebook-and-twitter-staffs-splurge-on-democrats-ahead-of-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google, Facebook and Twitter employees have donated substantially more to Democrats than Republicans with the 2018 midterms less than three weeks away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 smart glasses appeal to masses?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/norths-focals-smart-glasses-first-look.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A start-up called North, formally Thalmic Labs, is introducing a pair of smart glasses that it thinks will appeal to the masses because the design looks so similar to normal glasses. They're called Focals, and they cost around $1,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto dealers see slowing sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/auto-dealerships-see-sharp-decline-in-sales-in-october.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of auto dealers around the country is seeing a noticeable drop in retail sales and customer traffic, raising the possibility that a long-anticipated slowdown in auto sales has arrived.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
