<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Cheney, unbound, settles into 'bull's-eye of controversy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/18/liz-cheney-gop-interview-489144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with POLITICO, the deposed House GOP leader seemed to view her current place in the political wilderness as her destiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD Investigates Rapper T.I. Over Sex Assault Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/t-i-lapd-investigation-sexual-assault-1234954846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Los Angeles are investigating T.I. after several women came forward to accuse the rapper of sexual assault, The Hollywood Reporter has confirmed. An LAPD spokesman told THR on Monday nigh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer dies after 'unprecedented' shark attack near popular Oz beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/shark-kills-surfer-australia-forster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Despite the best efforts of paramedics and bystanders at the scene, the man could not be resuscitated," officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMBORGHINI hits accelerator on electric future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lamborghini-hits-accelerator-electric-future-112029149.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian sports car maker Lamborghini on Tuesday unveiled Tuesday a 1.5-billion-euro ($1.8 billion) electrification plan for its luxury vehicles, joining a global push away from fossil fuels at the risk of upsetting fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darwin's Arch, Famed Rock Formation in Galápagos, Collapses...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/18/darwins-arch-a-famed-rock-formation-in-the-galapagos-collapses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darwin’s Arch, a famous, photo-friendly rock formation in the remote Galápagos Islands, collapsed on Monday because of natural erosion, Ecuadorean</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians go on strike as Israel, Hamas trade fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hamas-gaza-middle-east-israel-israel-palestinian-conflict-ab0bfc2b25d2a03756fb0c084fca1a3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israeli medics say that a strike from Gaza has wounded 10 people, four of them seriously. Israeli media say the projectile attack Tuesday hit a region in southern Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREATS TO MEMBERS OF CONGRESS DOUBLE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-business-health-shootings-0b15dca112b48c05904a969bb21030c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Colorado Rep. Jason Crow, a former Army Ranger who served three tours in Iraq and Afghanistan, says it took time for him to stop constantly scanning his environment for threats when he returned from war 15 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Restaurant Apocalypse Greatly Exaggerated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/america-e2-80-99s-restaurant-apocalypse-has-been-greatly-exaggerated/ar-BB1gR7TM </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nüwa seeks to become first city on Mars with 1 million residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/how-nuwa-the-first-sustainable-city-on-mars-aims-to-serve-1m-people-someday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aerospace engineer Gisela Detrell, who helped design the Martian city, discusses what a city like Nüwa can offer residents by relying solely on Mars resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strippers back on job but COVID rules hurting pay...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210518085208-vs5tk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strip clubs are starting to re-open, but workers see more woes ahead as distancing rules put private dances off-limits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concern over 'chemsex' grows in Thailand...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210517225311-ixexo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who attend chemsex parties face health risks including overdoses, addiction and HIV infection, campaigners say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOBEL Winner: AI Will Crush Humans; 'Not Even Close'...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/nobel-winner-artificial-intelligence-crush-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence will be beating humans — outworking if not entirely outmoding them — in plenty of functions as the future approaches. Here's why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is BMI Scam?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/18/is-b-m-i-a-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are few single measures in health care that seem to carry as much weight as body mass index, or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects power across Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arctic-europe-russia-business-technology-b67c5b28d917f03f9340d4a7b4642790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAGURSKOYE, Russia (AP) — During the Cold War, Russia's Nagurskoye airbase was little more than a runway, a weather station and a communications outpost in the Franz Josef Land archipelago. It was a remote and desolate home mostly for polar bears, where temperatures plunge in winter to minus-42 Celsius (43 degrees below zero Fahrenheit) and the snow only disappears from August to mid-September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper posed on SWAT truck during Capitol riot and put on album. He's facing federal charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-rapper-posed-on-a-swat-truck-during-the-capitol-riots-and-put-it-on-his-album-he-s-facing-federal-charges/ar-BB1gRk39 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Putin's military base at North Pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9590885/Inside-Putins-huge-military-base-North-Pole-Moscow-tells-West-land.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nagurskoye airbase in the Franz Josef Land archipelago was built in the 1950s as a weather station and communications outpost but is now a huge military base for Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders flexes on Biden, seeking to shape Dem agenda...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/554001-sanders-flexes-on-biden-seeking-to-shape-democratic-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is starting to flex his political muscle and become more outspoken on a number of issues after months of mostly keeping his head down and being a team player.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Money Is Going Vegan...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/18/the-big-money-is-going-vegan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private equity has a place at the table, and so do Oprah and Jay-Z. Food giants like Nestlé are scrambling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk loses world's second-richest ranking...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/topstories/elon-musk-loses-world-s-second-richest-ranking-as-tesla-dips/ar-BB1gPXyr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s Twitter posts keep sending Bitcoin prices tumbling. His own fortune is heading in the same direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian PM stands firm on border closure...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210518001244-1b9hz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA:Australian PM stands firm on border closure due to COVID-19, as industries plea for reopening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. general warns of broader destabilization...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210517193202-z5lb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/USA-MILITARY (URGENT):Top U.S. general warns of broader destabilization risk from Israel-Palestinian hostilities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina Halts Beef Exports for 30 Days to Contain Inflation!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/argentina-halts-beef-exports-30-010200477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Argentina’s government is limiting exports of beef, a staple in the country, in the latest unorthodox move to try to contain runaway inflation that’s approaching 50% annually.President Alberto Fernandez told a key beef export association that they won’t be allowed to sell the product abroad for 30 days, according to a Production Ministry statement released late Monday. In that period, the government will determine a set of emergency measures for the sector.The measure shows that the government is willing to sacrifice much-needed dollars from exports to appease local consumers ahead of a key midterm election later this year. The country’s beef exports in 2020 amounted to roughly $3 billion, but the government may be more focused on the political cost of falling domestic consumption.“The president expressed his concern over the sustained growth in domestic beef prices over the last few months,” according to the statement. Discussion at the meeting also included “possible steps to restrict speculative practices” and fiscal evasion. Some of the measures will be adopted over coming days.Fernandez added that the 30-day period could be shortened if the implementation of the measures leads to “positive results,” the note added.Read more: Argentina Inflation Rose Faster Than Expected Again in AprilArgentine beef exports have been surging for four years and reached a record in the first two months of 2021, according to beef group Ciccra. The suspension resembles similar policy decisions during 2003-2015 under the presidencies of Nestor Kirchner and his successor, Cristina Fernandez de Kirchner, which led cattle numbers to plunge and the country losing market share in the international market.The government last month formalized a registry to ensure domestic supplies of beef at accessible prices as well as monitor shipments and supplies at home.Not all beef cuts may be included in the resolution, which has not yet been published, according to a person with knowledge of the matter. The story was first reported by local newspaper La Nacion.(Updates with government statement in second paragraph)More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Supreme Court to hear abortion case challenging Roe v. Wade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-mississippi-laws-reproductive-rights-us-supreme-court-5d066a9dc0030a4f8297711f341c9f5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court agreed Monday to a showdown over abortion in a case that could dramatically alter nearly 50 years of rulings on abortion rights. With three justices appointed by President Donald Trump part of a 6-3 conservative majority, the court is taking on a case about whether states can ban abortions before a fetus can survive outside the womb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab states split for first time on refusal to condemn...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/may/17/arab-states-split-for-first-time-on-refusal-to-condemn-israel-over-gaza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silence over bombing of occupied territory puts UAE, Bahrain, Morocco and Sudan at odds with their populations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World is home to 50 BILLION birds!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/may/18/world-is-home-to-50bn-birds-breakthrough-citizen-science-research-estimates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;University of NSW study suggests six times as many individual birds as humans but that many species are very rare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police faced equipment shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/05/17/capitol-police-faced-equipment-shortage-during-jan-6-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most officers who fought that day did so without helmets, face shields or gas masks that would have better protected them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maricopa County officials decry 2020 recount as sham, call on Republicans to end process...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/e2-80-98our-democracy-is-imperiled-e2-80-99-maricopa-county-officials-decry-2020-recount-as-a-sham-and-call-on-arizona-republicans-to-end-the-process/ar-BB1gQhCg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP-dominated county board said Monday that the audit commissioned by state Republicans is promoting falsehoods and defaming public servants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  After guilty verdict, convicted man slits his throat in courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article251484633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man killed himself inside a federal courtroom in Fargo after a jury reached a verdict, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House consumed by tension over Capitol riot as vote on investigation nears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-consumed-tension-over-capitol-213900608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than four months out from Jan. 6, hostility surrounding the riot is deeply felt on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Reality Show Coming To FOX...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/fox-teases-tom-brady-unscripted-series-1234758685/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An hour into its upfront presentation, Fox threw a hail mary. The network teased that it was working with Super Bowl champion Tom Brady on an unscripted series. Charlie Collier, CEO of Fox Entertai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLACK Destroying Companies?</title>
      <link>https://taibbi.substack.com/p/is-slack-destroying-american-companies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taibbi.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bounced from Apple over complaints about his book Chaos Monkeys, the author questions the wisdom of conflating your entire "political, moral, and religious being with your professional persona."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCNEIL: How I Learned to Stop Worrying And Love the Lab-Leak Theory...</title>
      <link>https://donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com/how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-the-lab-leak-theory-f4f88446b04d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early spring 2020, I reported an article for The New York Times on which I put the tentative headline: “New Coronavirus Is ‘Clearly Not…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remains struggle in NC -- and prices surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article251469743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prices at the pump are about 20 cents higher than a week ago, AAA says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Baffert Banned from Belmont...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/general/news/bob-baffert-suspended-by-new-york-racing-association-ahead-of-belmont-stakes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baffert's horse, Medina Spirit, failed a drug test after winning the Kentucky Derby</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sirens in North: Rockets fall in Lebanon...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/sirens-in-northern-israel-rockets-fall-in-lebanon-report-668376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six rockets were launched from Lebanon, all of which fell in within Lebanese territory, the IDF reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Cuts Ties With Writer Who Praised Hitler...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/cnn-cuts-ties-writer-praised-hitler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN says it cut ties with a writer who took to social media to praise Adolf Hitler, but his admiration for the Nazi leader who killed more than six million Jews was well-established prior to this weekend's post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campervans boom in Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2021/05/17/colorado-vanlife-campervan-conversion-industry-booming-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado’s campervan companies are booming as the pandemic shifts work locations and home prices climb, fueling the vanlife craze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Atlanta stations still out of gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/no-gas-available-at-nearly-half-of-metro-atlantas-stations/FO6L2WFTIZCAJJTXWOQN6LS22A/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colonial Pipeline is running but transporting fuel to stations with empty tanks will take days. Gas prices remain higher than before the gas pipeline shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censorship, Surveillance and Profits: Hard Bargain for APPLE in China...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/17/censorship-surveillance-and-profits-a-hard-bargain-for-apple-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUIYANG, China — On the outskirts of this city in a poor, mountainous province in southwestern China, men in hard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS: 0 DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/news/health/coronavirus/texas-covid19-deaths/269-58605f39-e029-4a3e-984a-0ef494cf283c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas reported zero "newly reported fatalities" and 388 "new confirmed cases" on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal wildfire challenges firefighters in area that hasn't burned in 75 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/2021-05-Palisades-Fire-Santa-Monica-16182356.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Palisades Fire sparked Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Set to Receive $5.1 Million from Pandemic Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/cuomos-pandemic-book-deal-earns-him-5-1-million-over-3-years-taxes-show/3060071/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“American Crisis: Leadership Lessons from the COVID-19 Pandemic,” a book written during the first few months of the pandemic, will earn Gov. Andrew Cuomo approximately $5.1 million, according to information in the governor’s tax filings released Monday. The New York governor reported earnings of $3.21 million last year for the book, with additional $1 million payments expected over the next…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Set to Receive $5.1 Million from Pandemic Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/17/nyregion/cuomo-tax-returns-pandemic-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York governor reported earning $3.1 million last year from his leadership memoir, with additional payments coming in the next two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burry reveals a $530 million bet against TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/michael-burry-of-the-big-short-reveals-a-530-million-bet-against-tesla.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Burry is long puts against 800,100 shares of Tesla or $534 million by the end of the first quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue States Reject CDC Mask Guidance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/following-the-science-blue-states-reject-the-cdcs-mask-guidance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A slew of Democrat-led locales are maintaining mask mandates despite the CDC’s shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv Strike Threatened in Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/idf-launches-massive-strike-against-gaza-bombs-hamas-chiefs-home-668286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamas rocket barrages on southern Israel continued Sunday with almost 300 projectiles launched at Israel since Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy's lawyer says feds treated him like 'terrorist'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/17/rudy-giulianis-lawyer-says-he-was-treated-like-a-terrorist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for former Mayor Rudy Giuliani blasted federal prosecutors complaining they have treated him like a “terrorist” as they executed two search warrants on his electronic device…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS: P. Bush preps primary against Trump ally...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/05/17/ken-paxton-george-p-bush-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bush has a unique history with Trump as the only prominent member of his famous political family to back the former president. Meanwhile, Paxton has tightly aligned himself with Trump in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penn State To Stop Using 'Freshman,' 'Sophomore,' Other 'Gendered' Terms...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/17/penn-state-approves-to-stop-using-freshman-sophomore-terms-and-others-due-to-male-centric-academic-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Penn State's Faculty Senate has approved a proposition that would remove gendered and binary terms from their course and program descriptions, according to the university's student-operated newspaper The Daily Collegian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns West against Arctic encroachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210517-russia-warns-west-against-arctic-encroachment-ahead-of-talks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia warns West against Arctic encroachment ahead of talks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How processed food changed our species
...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210514-how-humanity-has-changed-the-food-it-eats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Processed food isn’t just a modern invention, created from artificial ingredients. It is as old as humanity itself and may have helped create our species, writes Nicola Temple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Military's Secret Undercover Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/exclusive-inside-militarys-secret-undercover-army-1591881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of soldiers, civilians and contractors operate under false names, on the ground and in cyberspace. A Newsweek investigation of the ever-growing and unregulated world of "signature reduction."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO says pandemic far from over...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/who-says-pandemic-is-far-from-over-despite-high-vaccination-rates-in-some-countries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global pandemic isn't over yet despite high Covid vaccination rates in some countries, the head of the World Health Organization warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP slammed for claim it was unaware of Hamas in office...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/17/ap-slammed-for-claiming-it-was-unaware-of-hamas-presence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press has been blasted for claiming it had no clue Hamas militants maintained a presence at the news agency’s Gaza headquarters that was destroyed in an Israeli airstrike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melinda could be angling to change kids' $10M inheritance...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/17/melinda-gates-may-be-angling-to-change-kids-10m-inheritance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divorce experts say there’s a clue in Melinda Gates’ blockbuster divorce filing that she’s angling to change her three children’s inheritance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Bush Cured Covid Through Faith-Healing-By-Phone...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/meet-rep-cori-bush-and-her-fellow-faith-healers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Cori Bush (D., Mo.) spent years working as a faith healer for a religious group that claims to have resurrected the dead and cured thousands of people suffering from AIDS, cancer, paralysis, and other serious maladies—including Bush’s own severe case of coronavirus last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz associate pleads guilty to six federal crimes, including sex trafficking teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/17/joel-greenberg-matt-gaetz-488993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of his deal with federal prosecutors, Joel Greenberg has also agreed to “cooperate fully" with authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'REAL HOUSEWIFE' under real scrutiny: Hunt for missing millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/the-real-housewife-under-real-scrutiny-erika-girardi-and-the-hunt-for-the-missing-millions/ar-BB1gPbEn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bankruptcy trustees have accused the reality star of concealing assets for her husband and are dispatching investigators to comb through her belongings and accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Nears Deal With House on DEUTSCHE Subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-nears-deal-with-house-on-deutsche-bank-subpoenas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Nears Deal With House on Deutsche Bank Subpoenas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador's millennial president is man with one vision: Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/world/el-salvadors-millennial-president-is-a-man-with-one-vision-power/article_ff557582-fc7f-5263-933d-08c90c49b8c4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador — A few days after he led a coup, the president of El Salvador uploaded a video onto TikTok of him gliding in a military vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami danger lurking off San Diego coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.10news.com/news/local-news/tsunami-danger-lurking-off-san-diego-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report says fault lines like the ones off the coast of California could be more likely to cause tsunamis than previously thought. ABC 10News Reporter Jared Aarons takes a look at what that means for San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redemption of 'Ugly American' Tourist...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-redemption-of-the-e2-80-98ugly-american-e2-80-99-tourist/ar-BB1gOVtm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American tourists are stereotypically thought of as loud, boorish, and tacky. This summer, Europe wants them back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to hear abortion case challenging Roe v. Wade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/supreme-court-to-hear-mississippi-abortion-case-challenging-roe-v-wade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday agreed to hear arguments in a major abortion case from Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese businessman with links to Bannon is driving force for sprawling disinformation network, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/chinese-businessman-with-links-to-steve-bannon-is-driving-force-for-a-sprawling-disinformation-network-researchers-say/ar-BB1gPgfN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese businessman with links to Steve Bannon is the "linchpin" of a sprawling disinformation network that pushes election and covid-19 falsehoods, researchers say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA investigates second case of mystery 'syndrome' near White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/17/politics/us-investigates-second-case-mystery-syndrome-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two White House officials were struck by a mysterious illness late last year -- including one who was passing through a gate onto the property -- newly revealed details that come as investigators are still struggling to determine who or what is behind these strange incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires who favor raising taxes on rich protest in front of Bezos home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/pro-tax-millionaires-launching-protests-in-front-of-jeff-bezos-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mobile billboards will also make appearances in front of Sen. Mitch McConnell's D.C. residence and Sen. Chuck Schumer's office in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>64% of millennials have regrets about buying current home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/64percent-of-millennials-have-regrets-about-buying-their-current-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of millennials say they have at least one regret about purchasing their current home, according to a new poll from Bankrate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of megadonor: Thiel makes play for Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/17/peter-thiel-senate-megadonor-488799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech billionaire Peter Thiel's twin $10 million investments in two Senate candidates made him one of the key early figures in the 2022 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDM acts often hide identity. For Zhu, that's always had two meanings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/edm-acts-often-hide-their-identity-for-asian-american-star-zhu-thats-always-had-two-meanings/ar-BB1gK85s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally back performing in front of a live crowd, dance-music star Zhu reflects on his year in lockdown and the violence against the AAPI community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER WILL STAY</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/att-discovery-cnn-jeff-zucker-5b0d1614-faf2-4a91-8a95-2dc3d8164be3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Absent this tectonic media shift, Zucker was gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR: ISRAEL POUNDS HARDER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gaza-israel-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-9f55fcb62af8224b954632b9e3edc2a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — The Israeli military unleashed a wave of heavy airstrikes on the Gaza Strip early Monday, saying it destroyed 15 kilometers (9 miles) of militant tunnels and the homes of nine Hamas commanders, as international diplomats worked to end the week of fighting that has killed hundreds of people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
