<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER VICTORY FOR JARED: Mexico Praises For New Trade Agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/jared-kushner-scores-another-victory-mexico-praises-trump-son-in-law-for-exceptional-work-on-new-us-mexico-trade-agreement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacrilegious spies:  Tried hacking Orthodox clergy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26815e0d06d348f4b85350e96b78f6a8/Sacrilegious-spies:-Russians-tried-hacking-Orthodox-clergy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Russian hackers indicted by the U.S. special prosecutor last month have spent years trying to steal the private correspondence of some of the world's most senior</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSIONS WITH MEXICO EASE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-trade-nafta/u-s-mexico-reach-nafta-deal-talks-with-canada-to-start-immediately-idUSKCN1LC1E7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and Mexico reached a deal on Monday to change the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) and talks with Canada were expected to begin immediately, U.S. President Donald Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BETO THISCLOSE TO CATCHING CRUZ...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/403786-poll-cruz-leads-orourke-by-one-point-in-texas-senate-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz (R-Texas) leads his Democratic challenger, Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSIONS WITH MEXICO EASE</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/403781-trump-announces-deal-with-mexico-on-nafta-overhaul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday announced the U.S. has reached a deal with Mexico on overhauling the three-nation North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Snow Blankets Montana, Idaho, Wyoming...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/summer-snow-falling-in-northern-rockies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some areas have been placed under a Winter Weather Advisory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASHIN: Stock market betting on Pence should legal issues take dark turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/27/cashin-market-betting-on-pence-should-trump-legal-troubles-take-turn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Intriguingly, the president's legal woes don't seem to have any market effect yet," Art Cashin says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 Americans have less than $5,000 saved for retirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/27/1-in-3-americans-have-less-than-5000-dollars-saved-for-retirement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of Americans say they're concerned about not having enough money for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How President Is Remaking Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/it-is-the-era-of-trump-how-the-president-is-remaking-the-republican-party-1535380861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump upended the GOP when he first ran for office. Since then, he’s dragged the party in his direction, undercutting its traditional policy preferences, with his critics leaving and his favored candidates winning. Some establishment Republicans worry his influence could hurt in the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SEASON:  Tom Brady hangs up during live radio interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2018/08/27/tom-brady-radio-interview-alex-guerrero-questions/1108341002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't ask the Patriots quarterback about longtime personal trainer Alex Guerrero or he will hang up on you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SMASH RECORDS ON NEW NAFTA</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/27/us-stocks-to-open-higher-after-powell-signals-further-rate-hikes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks jumped on Monday as the United States and Mexico drew closer to a deal on NAFTA. Investors also digested reassuring comments from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on the central bank's policy-tightening path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States reconsider confidential deals in workplace harassment...</title>
      <link>http://www.morningjournal.com/general-news/20180825/states-reconsider-confidential-deals-in-workplace-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.morningjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidentiality agreements have come under fire during the #MeToo movement as one way abusive men have been able to hold on to their jobs, and keep harassing more women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD:  Trump is NOT a singular evil...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2018/09/03/glenn-greenwald-the-bane-of-their-resistance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leftist journalist’s bruising crusade against establishment Democrats—and their Russia obsession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man busted with 800 pounds of stolen lemons...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/Man-Busted-Pounds-Stolen-Lemons-491721071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 69-year-old man was arrested in Thermal, California, for possessing hundreds of pounds of lemons allegedly stolen from a nearby farm, a sheriff's sergeant said Saturday. Dionicio Fierros of Los Angeles...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it has full control of Gulf, U.S. Navy does not belong there...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180827115338-hpqo0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-NUCLEAR/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Iran says it has full control of Gulf, U.S. Navy does not belong there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Chairman Andy Lack on the chopping block?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/27/nbc-news-chairman-andy-lack-could-be-on-the-chopping-block/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s facing the boot over his mishandling of a series of #MeToo scandals and the Megyn Kelly debacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flags at White House back at full staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/flags-white-house-back-full-staff-mccains-death-130355395--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flags at the White House, which were lowered over the weekend to mark the death of Sen. John McCain, are back at full-staff. The flags at the U.S. Capitol, meanwhile, remained at half-staff on Monday to honor the Arizona Republican, who died Saturday of brain cancer. President Donald Trump offered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexually frustrated dolphin terrorizes tourists on beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/27/swimming-banned-french-beach-sexually-frustrated-dolphin-named/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seaside village in Brittany has banned swimming on its beach because a dolphin in heat has been scaring tourists and locals by approaching them and trying to rub up against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Kids Take More Meds, Dangerous Drug Mixes Rise...</title>
      <link>https://consumer.healthday.com/general-health-information-16/prescription-drug-news-551/as-u-s-kids-take-more-meds-dangerous-drug-mixes-could-rise-737091.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;consumer.healthday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone worries about drug abuse among children, but a hidden danger for some kids rests in prescription medicines intended to help them, a new study warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Third Of Teens Haven't Read Book In Year; Just 2% Read News...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-third-teens-havent-read-book-past-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bookworm teens have always been few and far between, but now they seem like a dying breed. A new study puts some weight behind this notion by revealing just how American teenagers choose to spend their time (hint: it’s not with a book).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German antitrust watchdog plans action on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-antitrust-facebook/german-antitrust-watchdog-plans-action-on-facebook-this-year-idUSKCN1LC17R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's antitrust watchdog expects to take first steps this year in its probe against Facebook after finding that the social media giant abused its market dominance to gather data on people without their knowledge or consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh becomes largest city without daily print newspaper...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/403746-pittsburgh-becomes-largest-us-city-without-a-daily-print-newspaper</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pittsburgh will hold the distinction of being the largest city in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next iPhones expected to be biggest ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/08/27/next-iphones-apple-expected-largest-ever/1087793002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple will officially introduce new iPhones in September; analysts predict there will be 3 new models, with the sequel to the iPhone X, clocking in at 6.5 inches, substantially larger than the current X, which has a 5.8 inch OLED screen. The new iPhones should be in stores by the last week of Septem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: States with best and worst economies...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2018/08/27/states-best-and-worst-economies/37490453/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall Street reviewed economic growth, poverty, unemployment, job growth, and college attainment rates to compare and rank state economies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur DNA structure recreated by scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/725808/dinosaur-dna-university-kent-jurassic-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents fight back after school drops Pledge of Allegiance for oath to 'global society'...</title>
      <link>http://eagnews.org/parents-fight-back-after-school-drops-pledge-of-allegiance-for-student-authored-oath-to-global-society/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta Neighborhood Charter School Principal Lara Zelski decided students will no longer recite the Pledge of Allegiance during the school’s morning meeting agenda, which she described to parents as “an effort to begin our day as a fully inclusive and connected community.” “Over the past couple of years it has become increasingly obvious that more and more of our community were choosing to not stand and/or recite the pledge,” she wrote, according to the Atlanta Journal Constitution. The statement, posted to the school website, promised parents students could recite the Pledge of Allegiance later in the day, if they felt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soothing music before bed could prevent heart attacks...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6102151/Listening-yoga-music-bed-prevent-deadly-heart-attacks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Sunil Memorial Superspeciality Hospital, Jaipur, India, found that hearing soothing, meditative tunes just before a person nods off increases their heart rate variability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sleeper' case could torpedo Mueller report...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/27/robert-mueller-special-counsel-report-sleeper-case-797373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might even keep the special counsel from sending a report to Congress, shaking Democrats’ hopes that such a document could provide the impetus for impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos believes people shouldn't do jobs software can do...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/jeff-believes-people-shouldn-t-do-jobs-software-can-do-h2tc0f8kt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the east bank of Lake Washington, across the water from Seattle, is Medina, a town of about 3,000 people that has become a home for tech billionaires. Among them are Bill Gates, the founder of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naughty dolphin causes beach ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/unfit-porpoise-naughty-dolphin-causes-french-beach-ban-105309856.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A love-lorn dolphin has prompted a French coastal town to ban bathing on its beaches, fearing people may be hurt by the antics of the over-excited mammal. Roger Lars, mayor of Landevennec, on the western tip of Brittany, issued a ban on voluntarily approaching within 50 metres (yards) of the dolphin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rouhani under attack from all sides...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/irans-rouhani-under-attack-sides-105630397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's President Hassan Rouhani is clinging to power but finds himself under attack from all sides -- conservatives, reformists and the street -- as he prepares for a grilling in parliament on Tuesday. The US withdrawal from the 2015 nuclear deal between Tehran and world powers and Washington'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Without Water: Sweaty, Smelly, and Furious in Caracas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/27/life-without-water-sweaty-smelly-and-furious-in-caracas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life Without Water: Sweaty, Smelly, and Furious in Caracas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest says life in danger for criticizing Duterte...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/08/27/catholic-priest-says-life-in-danger-for-criticizing-duterte.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Roman Catholic priest who was one of the earliest critics of Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte's deadly crackdown on drugs has gone into hiding due to what he says were signs he's being targeted by motorcycle-riding hitmen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China targets rumors, religion in updated party rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-corruption/china-targets-rumors-religion-in-updated-party-rules-idUSKCN1LC0AQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's ruling Communist Party has issued a revised set of regulations governing members' behavior, threatening punishment for spreading political rumors and recommending those who cling to religious beliefs be asked to leave the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind-altering breast milk? New pot study poses that question...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f3eee039def845a58f71030ef8b8826c/Mind-altering-breast-milk?-New-pot-study-poses-that-question</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Marijuana's main mind-altering ingredient was detected in nursing mothers' breast milk in a small study that comes amid evidence that more U.S. women are using pot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says has full control of Gulf; U.S. navy does not belong there...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180827101830-o9zb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-NUCLEAR/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Iran says it has full control of Gulf and U.S. navy does not belong there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee delivery drone predicts when need caffeine...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/4059117/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your cup of Joe could soon be coming to you by drone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHOKE: Burning Man burn out?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/burningman/article/Burning-Man-Art-mutant-vehicles-build-week-dust-13184007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER hurricane?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tropical-storm-miriam-path-track-latest-weather-forecast-hawaii-today-2018-08-27-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forecasters say newly-formed system churning over Pacific is likely to strengthen; Hawaii was just hit with huge rainmaker Lane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Tries to Make O.J. Simpson Confess...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sacha-baron-cohen-tries-to-make-oj-simpson-confess-in-who-is-america-finale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yet the long-awaited Sarah Palin appearance failed to materialize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Tycoons About to Learn How Rich They Really Are...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/08/26/these-crypto-tycoons-are-about-to-learn-how-rich-they-really-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the world’s biggest cryptocurrency tycoons are about to find out how much they’re really worth.The secretive bosses of Bitmain Technologies Ltd., Canaan Inc. and Ebang International Holdings Inc. -- three of the largest makers of cryptocurrency mining gear -- are all facing the prospect of public-market scrutiny for the first time as they pursue stock listings in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers plead for more security after Jacksonville shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/gamers-plead-more-security-after-deadly-jacksonville-shooting-n904016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s time esports events (large and small) double down on security for everyone in general and players specifically," the CEO of an esports team tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Ends 'WHO IS AMERICA' Season Without Airing Palin Footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/who-is-america-sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen-finale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin said she was duped by one of Sacha Baron Cohen's "Who Is America" characters, but her segment wasn't in the season finale</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN court to hear Iran lawsuit against US sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/27/world-court-hears-iran-lawsuit-to-have-us-sanctions-lifted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit filed with the International Court of Justice says the U.S. sanctions violate terms of a little-known 1955 friendship treaty between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians on trial for sharing memes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russians-trial-sharing-memes-networks-ask-law-change-015544008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2015, Eduard Nikitin shared a joke on social media about Russia's bleak future. Lawyers say the Kremlin is trying to force people to think twice before sharing opinions online -- one of the last remaining spaces where the opposition is relatively free to organise. In one of the incriminating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lanny Davis backs off claims about 'Russia' info...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Lawyer-backs-off-claims-about-information-Cohen-13184027.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former lawyer, is backing away from confident assertions he made that Cohen has information to share with investigators that shows Trump knew in 2016 of Russian efforts to undermine Democratic nominee Hillary Clinton. Lanny Davis, a spokesman and attorney for Cohen, said in an interview this weekend that he is no longer certain about claims he made to reporters on background and on the record in recent weeks about what Cohen knows about Trump's awareness of the Russian efforts. Davis did not rule out that his claims were correct but expressed regret that he did not explain that he could not independently corroborate them, saying that he now believes he "should have been more clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON giving employees gift cards to tweet nice things...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1369802/amazon-is-giving-employees-50-gift-cards-to-tweet-nice-things-about-the-company/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I even get to use a real bathroom when I want."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'KEEPS TO HIMSELF'</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/police-id-madden-19-tournament-shooter-as-gamer-david-katz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News4Jax is learning more about the gunman suspected of carrying out Sunday's mass shooting targeting a Madden NFL 19 tournament at the Jacksonville Landing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis across 80 countries shows how TV damaging sex lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-what-television-does-to-your-sex-life-its-not-pretty-2018-08-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study calculates the impact of TV on a couple’s romantic life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Tycoons About to Learn How Rich They Really Are...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/08/26/these-crypto-tycoons-are-about-to-learn-how-rich-they-really-are#gs.jMcikgA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These Crypto Tycoons Are About to Learn How Rich They Really Are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papal Mass crowds fall well below expected level... </title>
      <link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/pope-francis-in-ireland/crowds-for-phoenix-park-mass-fall-well-below-expected-level-of-500000-37254339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people who turned out for the Papal Mass in Dublin’s Phoenix Park on Sunday appeared to be well short of the expected 500,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Circulating 'Hell List'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2018-midterm-elections-republicans-preparation-investigations-180abf7b-0de8-4670-ae8a-2e6da123c584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They've created a spreadsheet to predict the post-midterms investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Democratic governor --  in Wyoming?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democratic-governor-wyoming-could-happen-again-222020022--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEYENNE, Wyo. (AP) — A Democrat has no chance of becoming Wyoming's next governor, right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No hero to conservatives'...</title>
      <link>https://aminewswire.org/stories/conservatives-john-mccain-leaves-behind-mixed-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;aminewswire.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Luis Arellano    Publicly, Sen. John McCain, the Arizona Republican who passed away yesterday, is being mourned as a statesman and war hero who survived torture in the Hanoi Hilton</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will lie in state at Capitol...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/403638-mccain-to-lie-in-state-at-capitols-in-washington-arizona</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America mourns John McCain, war hero and political icon...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-senator-john-mccain-dead-81-012154116.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America paid tribute Sunday to John McCain, the Vietnam War hero and two-time presidential candidate with a legendary temper whose personal courage and insistence on treating even his foes with respect earned him near-universal admiration. Flags flew at half-mast over the White House and US Capitol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR CAUGHT ON LIVESTREAM</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7106452/jacksonville-landing-shooting-4-dead-shopping-centre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT least four are feared dead and 11 injured after a mass shooting during the live-stream of a video game competition in Jacksonville, Florida today. A gamer reportedly opened fire on fellow contes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden's far-right poised for record election score...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180826/swedens-far-right-poised-for-record-election-gains</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barring a major upset, Sweden's far-right is on course for a record result in September 9 legislative elections, capitalising on the mood of voters who feel they are being left behind in favour of hundreds of thousands of newly-arrived asylum seekers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Holy grail' diet pill... </title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/26/holy-grail-diet-pill-could-help-millions-lose-weight-middle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A breakthrough drug which directly targets middle-aged spread could help millions of overweight Britons to lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHOKE: Burning Man burn out?</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/2018/08/26/burning-man-weather-expect-smoky-windy-start-burn/1104377002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a little smoke and blowing wind today and tomorrow, don't expect weather conditions at this year's burn to be particularly harrowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Six to eight hours sleep best for heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/breaking-news/six-to-eight-hours-sleep-best-for-heart/news-story/64f943368edac8719c02652d1218b6fe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six to eight hours sleep a night is most beneficial for the heart, researchers have suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson compared self to JESUS, lawyer claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/725761/michael-jackson-jesus-Brian-Oxman-whacko-jacko-insults-birthday-60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordic countries not as happy as think...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45308016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report aims to paint a truer picture of life inside some of the world's happiest countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fighting is real at medieval festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/206/fighting-real-serbias-medieval-festival-doc-18l74x4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's U-turn on TESLA deal could intensify his legal, regulatory woes...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/musks-u-turn-tesla-deal-could-intensify-legal-222026774--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explaining his reversal in a late-night blog post on Friday, the billionaire CEO said that taking the company private “would be even more time-consuming and distracting than initially anticipated,” and that “most of Tesla’s existing shareholders believe we are better off as a public company.” It was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Guetta quietly coughs up $9.5 million for Miami Beach condo...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/realestate/hot-property/la-fi-hotprop-david-guetta-miami-condo-20180826-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French DJ and record producer David Guetta has paid $9.5 million for a condo on Miami Beach in a deal completed off-market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glamorous Venice Film Festival courts controversy; NETFLIX, gender...</title>
      <link> https://www.france24.com/en/20180826-glamorous-venice-film-festival-courts-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/mass-shooting-reported-at-gaming-tournament-in-florida/17797704/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Jacksonville, Florida, said there were “multiple fatalities” at a mass shooting Sunday at a bar that was hosting a live gaming event during which 12 gunshots could be heard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/26/multiple-fatalities-reported-mass-shooting-games-tournament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four people were reported dead and eleven injured in a &amp;quot;mass shooting&amp;quot; at a pizza restaurant in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-shooting/multiple-fatalities-in-shooting-at-video-game-tournament-in-florida-sheriff-idUSKCN1LB0M7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a mass shooting at a video game tournament that was being streamed online from a restaurant in Jacksonville, Florida, on Sunday, and the local sheriff's office said there were multiple fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 killed, 11 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-authorities-report-mass-shooting-riverfront-mall-184200664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida authorities are reporting a multiple people dead and "many transported" to hospitals after a mass shooting at a riverfront mall in Jacksonville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS SHOOTING IN JACKSONVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/shooting-at-jacksonville-landing-leaves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say at least eleven people have been shot and four are dead after a shooting at the Jacksonville Landing Sunday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUGHT ON VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://streamable.com/scgs6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;streamable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 DEAD AT ONLINE GAMING TOURNAMENT</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6100355/Four-dead-10-injured-mass-shooting-Florida-Madden-online-gaming-tournament.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mass shooting has been reported at the Jacksonville Landing in Florida on Sunday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shooting at Jacksonville, FL  waterfront... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.firstcoastnews.com/article/news/local/mass-shooting-at-the-jacksonville-landing-multiple-fatalities/77-587766926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.firstcoastnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jacksonville Sheriff's Office is on the scene of a mass shooting at the Jacksonville Landing, multiple fatalities have been reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump won't be present at service...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6100001/Donald-Trump-returns-golf-course-17-hours-John-McCains-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has remained very quiet about the Arizona Republican senator's death, drawing criticism after he posted a meager tweet with his condolences for the McCain family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral speakers expected to include Bush and Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/presidents-lawmakers-laud-mccain-devotion-country-043543645--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two former presidents are expected to speak at Sen. John McCain's service and he will lie in state in both the nation's capital and Arizona as part of a cross-country funeral procession ending with his burial at the U.S. Naval Academy, according to plans taking shape Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Begs for God's forgiveness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-hold-giant-mass-dublin-abuse-victims-rally-030337491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis "begged for God's forgiveness" on Sunday for multiple abuse scandals within the Irish church but faced accusations by a former Vatican official that he had personally ignored allegations against senior clergy. In front of 45,000 supporters at the rain-soaked Knock shrine in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu warns Jews still under threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netanyahu-warns-jews-still-under-threat-162231736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's prime minister said on Sunday that Jews were still at risk even decades after the Holocaust as he wrapped up a groundbreaking visit to Lithuania, a Baltic state once home to his forefathers. Not the attempts to destroy us, they still seek to destroy us," Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/former-us-nuncio-pope-francis-knew-of-mccarricks-misdeeds-repealed-sanction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an explosive testimony, Archbishop Viganò reveals Francis repealed sanctions on McCarrick imposed by Pope Benedict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Vatican Ambassador Says Warnings Ignored...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pope-francis-knew-of-abusive-priest-claims-former-vatican-official-carlo-maria-vigano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Pope Francis must be the first to set a good example to Cardinals and Bishops who covered up McCarrick's abuses and resign along with all of them," writes a former Vatican ambassador to Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Aren't Talking Impeachment But Are Vowing Probes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/26/democrats-aren-t-talking-trump-impeachment-but-are-vowing-probes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Aren't Talking Trump Impeachment But Are Vowing Probes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico to Reach NAFTA Deal Soon as Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/26/u-s-mexico-said-poised-to-reach-nafta-deal-as-soon-as-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S., Mexico Said Poised to Reach Nafta Deal as Soon as Monday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern District of New York Will Tear Into Organization...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2018-08-26/southern-district-of-new-york-will-tear-into-trump-organization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBSHELL: Pope Accused of Covering Up for Abusive Priest...</title>
      <link>http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/ex-nuncio-accuses-pope-francis-of-failing-to-act-on-mccarricks-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ncregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a written testimony, Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò claims Pope Francis withdrew sanctions against Archbishop Theodore McCarrick.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
