<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>One of AMAZON's first employees says company should be broken up...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2019/12/20/21031694/amazon-employee-break-up-paul-barton-davis-marketplace-sellers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos hired Paul Davis to build Amazon’s website. Now Davis wants to break it up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legionaires founder sexually abused 60 boys, religious order's report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-abuse/legionaires-founder-sexually-abused-60-boys-religious-orders-report-says-idUSKBN1YQ02Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexual abuse of minors was rife among superiors of the Legionaires of Christ Cat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide rate rising fast for black youth, report finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/suicide-rate-rising-fast-black-youth-report-finds-n1103956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The gap is narrowing between black and white youth, and we must get at the bottom of why.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New emails give more details on Ukraine aid timeline...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/21/politics/emails-ukraine-aid-timeline/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 90 minutes after President Donald Trump spoke to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on July 25, Trump's political appointees at the White House's budget office were already ordering the Pentagon to freeze security funding for Ukraine, newly released government documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: 7 shot downtown...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-shootings-20191222-5bp26guiizaxdiyvweypicb27e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people, including three teenagers, were shot in downtown Baltimore early Sunday morning, according to Baltimore police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech Could Lose Financial Blessing of Church of England...</title>
      <link>https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/22/12/2019/Big-tech-could-lose-financial-blessing-of-the-Church-of-England</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepeninsulaqatar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church of England has started a review into whether its holdings in big tech firms are compatible with Christian faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN adds non-binary gender booking options...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/american-airlines-adds-non-binary-gender-booking-options/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline has not included the non-binary gender option in their online booking process yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother of 49ERS QB killed in double murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/49ers-quarterback-brother-murdered-casey-beathard-brother-of-backup-quarterback-cj-beathard-killed-in-double-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were stabbed outside The Dogwood bar in Nashville on Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING capsule becomes first to return from orbit, land on ground...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d941852c59a4811603a8ab3611a3cb8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Boeing safely landed its crew capsule in the New Mexico desert Sunday after an aborted flight to the International Space Station that threatened to set back the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandal-plagued city names 3 new police chiefs in 1 week...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/scandal-plagued-vermont-city-names-police-chiefs-week/story?id=67879052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burlington, Vermont, is now hiring a retired former police chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious greenish-yellow liquid gushing onto Detroit highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/oakland/2019/12/21/green-liquid-i-696-lane-closed/2721790001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right lanes will remain closed until Monday after hexavalent chromium oozed from the walls of the I-696 freeway in Madison Heights walls on Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS driver 'worked to death' delivering 240 packages a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/tragic-ups-delivery-driver-worked-21146174</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dad-of-two Paul Crush, 42, collapsed from a suspected heart attack at the end of a 12-hour shift – as workload 'doubled' over Christmas for pressure-hit staff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army to use Kardashian's bottom as new recruiting tool...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7817755/New-campaign-encourages-people-serve-Army-instils-confidence-receiving-likes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mail on Sunday can reveal the concept behind the Army's new advertising campaign is that serving in the Armed Forces instils greater confidence than receiving 'likes' on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba gets first prime minister in over 40 years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuba-gets-first-prime-minister-over-40-years-001102784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba's first prime minister in more than four decades -- long-serving tourism minister Manuel Marrero -- took office Saturday as the country resurrected a post last held by Fidel Castro. The appointment of Marrero, 56, as head of government is part of a process of decentralization and generational</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Us vs. them: President to use to rev up base...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1221d4b055c568daa639663783ffd258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Using stark “us vs. them” language, President Donald Trump and his reelection campaign have begun framing his impeachment not as a judgment on his conduct but as a referendum on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl finds note in Christmas cards from Chinese prison factory 'slave' pleading for help...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10603733/girl-tesco-christmas-cards-note-from-slave-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GIRL aged six discovered a desperate note in her Tesco Christmas cards from caged slaves in China forced to work against their will. Florence Widdicombe, from Tooting, south London, was stunned w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hope for 2-year-old girl's resurrection shifts to memorial service...</title>
      <link>https://www.redding.com/story/news/2019/12/21/hope-girls-resurrection-shifts-bethel-memorial-service/2722748001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.redding.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Facebook post by the Bethel Church on Friday acknowledges an outpouring ofÂ prayers hasn't brought the girl back to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: 13 shot inside memorial party for gunshot victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-englewood-11-wounded-shooting-20191222-mrad2j42ffenpawbh5yo4adzba-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooter opened fire inside a house party early Sunday in the Englewood neighborhood on the South Side, wounding about 11 people, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer plate umps allowed in new MLB labor deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d8760e52b8ced5b8436c60891ea6e877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Computer plate umpires could be called up to the major leagues at some point during the next five seasons. Umpires agreed to cooperate with Major League Baseball in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber attack forces airline to cancel flights in Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/467798874ec33be017978255358e1b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — RavnAir canceled at least a half-dozen flights in Alaska on Saturday — at the peak of holiday travel — following what the company described as “a malicious cyber attack”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 passenger buses engulfed in flames at LAX...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/three-passenger-buses-engulfed-in-flames-at-lax-prompting-traffic-delays/5776402/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three unoccupied passenger buses caught fire Saturday night at Los Angeles International Airport, fire officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soda machine kills 2 MCDONALD's workers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/defective-soda-machine-killed-two-mcdonalds-workers-peru-102255454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defective soda vending machine was responsible for the deaths of two McDonald's cleaners in Peru, the general manager for the Lima franchise told a local news station on Saturday night. Carlos Campos, 19, and Alexandra Porrasa, 18, died late on December 15 as they cleaned the fast food restaurant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's souvenir wine bottle pops up in big-donor debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e14a600779dddcabb8a3a809573285e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On a Saturday evening in June 2018, with temperatures in the 70s and the Red Sox playing at Fenway Park, supporters of Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren gathered at the City...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CHRISTMAS GIFT'</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10604052/kim-jong-un-military-meeting-nuclear-missile-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Jong-un has held a key meeting with North Korea’s military leaders after threatening a nuke launch as a “Christmas gift” for Donald Trump. The despot is understood to have held the talks to ham…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has installed 187 judges to federal bench...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-is-remaking-the-federal-judiciary-14924789.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After three years in office, President Donald Trump has remade the federal judiciary, ensuring a conservative tilt for decades and cementing his legacy no matter the outcome of November's election.  Trump nominees make up 1 in 4 U.S. circuit court judges. Two of his picks sit on the Supreme Court. And this past week, as the House voted to impeach the president, the Republican-led Senate confirmed another 13 district court judges.  In total, Trump has installed 187 judges to the federal bench.  Trump's mark on the judiciary is already having far-reaching effects on legislation and liberal priorities. Just last week, the 5th Circuit struck down a core provision of the Affordable Care Act. One of the two appellate judges who ruled against the landmark law was a Trump appointee.  The Supreme Court - where two of the nine justices are conservatives selected by Trump - could eventually hear that case.  The 13 circuit courts are the second most powerful in the nation, serving as a last stop for appeals on lower court rulings, unless the case is taken up by the Supreme Court. So far, Trump has appointed 50 judges to circuit court benches. Comparatively, by this point in President Barack Obama's first term, he had confirmed 25. At the end of his eight years, he had appointed 55 circuit judges.  Trump's appointments have flipped three circuit courts to majority GOP-appointed judges, including the U.S. Court of Appeals for the 2nd Circuit in New York. The president has also selected younger conservatives for these lifetime appointments, ensuring his impact is felt for many years.  The executor of this aggressive push is Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., who is almost singularly focused on reshaping the federal judiciary, twice ramming through Senate rule...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg shifts to center, embodying Dem primary's rightward drift ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/buttigieg-shifts-to-the-center-embodying-the-democratic-primarys-rightward-drift/ar-BBYe2TL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Unprecedented Move, Movie to Be 'Updated' While In Theaters...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/universal-notifies-theaters-cats-is-being-updated-improved-visual-effects-1264689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move is unheard of for a finished film already in release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plays to 98 in Iowa... </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/biden-plays-to-98-in-iowa-hands-over-mic-to-protester/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is supposedly the Democrat front runner for president, but less than 100 people turned out to see him in Iowa today. Biden was holding a town hall meeting in Ottumwa, and according to a photo of the crowd, only 98 people turned out. Look at this photo from Des Moines Register reporter Stephen …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CHRISTIANITY TODAY' EDITOR IN CHIEF RETIRING...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Christianity-Today-s-op-ed-isn-t-attacking-Trump-14924288.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Galli is retiring in January from his position as editor in chief of Christianity Today, a publication founded by the late evangelist Billy Graham. On Thursday, he decided to go out with a bang by expressing an unpopular sentiment among much of the religious right in an op-ed titled "Trump Should Be Removed from Office," which took off on social media, briefly caused the magazine's website to crash and drew this lamentably predictable response from the president:  "A far left magazine, or very 'progressive,' as some would call it, which has been doing poorly and hasn't been involved with the Billy Graham family for many years, Christianity Today, knows nothing about reading a perfect transcript of a routine phone call and would rather have a Radical Left nonbeliever, who wants to take your religion &amp; your guns, than Donald Trump as your President," Trump said in a series of tweets. "No President has done more for the Evangelical community, and it's not even close."  Trump's defenders are sure to chalk this up as just one more example that shows he is a "counterpuncher," someone who always "hits back" when attacked. But the op-ed isn't an attack - Galli concedes that the debate over impeaching and removing Trump is rife with partisanship, and he grants that reasonable minds can differ about whether impeachment or an election should decide Trump's political fate. Rather, he is defending Christianity after years of its adherents' moral compromises in the realm of politics.  He is clear that he will not immediately change minds and might lose readers: a December NPR-PBS NewsHour-Marist poll found that 80% of white evangelical Christians oppose the Senate removing Trump from office, compared to 49% of the public overall. But on Friday, Galli explained his real mission: "As a Christian," he told CNN's John Berman,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEWITT:  MAGAZINE ONLY HURT ITSELF...</title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2019/dec/21/hugh-hewitt-christianity-today-took-aim-at-trump-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In condemning President Donald Trump from the pages of Christianity Today, the magazine Billy Graham founded, its editor Mark Galli has blindsided more than half of the evangelical Christians in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  6 dead in Las Vegas apartment fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/6-dead-in-downtown-las-vegas-apartment-fire-1919071/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire at a downtown Las Vegas apartment building left six people dead early Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maelstrom sucks in chief justice who shuns politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/impeachment-maelstrom-sucks-in-a-chief-justice-who-shuns-politics/article_0b19e059-46d9-58fb-b691-f077befbe435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As a presidential impeachment trial loomed in 1999, John Roberts thought about William Rehnquist, the U.S. chief justice who was set to preside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA TROUBLES TO ACCELERATE IN 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/media-upheaval-layoffs-newsrooms-revenue-eb68dc5c-1ec7-41ee-8733-cbfb1da30971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was transformative, but it was also one of the most turbulent points in the history of the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog's Life Saved With First-Of-Its-Kind Heart Surgery At Hospital For Humans...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/12/19/sophie-karen-cortellino-penn-school-veterinary-medicine-heart-surgery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her family says Sophie has a heart of gold -- now she also has a heart that's making history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quest to expose whistleblower hard to pull off in Senate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-quest-expose-whistle-blower-110000101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump says his impeachment trial should deliver on a goal he’s nurtured for months: unmasking the whistle-blower who started it all. But that would pose legal and ethical challenges that would be hard to overcome.Federal laws promise anonymity for workers who step forward</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath for impeachment trial stirs partisan rancor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senator-oath-trump-impeachment-trial-110000804.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A 221-year-old Senate impeachment oath has become a focus of partisan bickering, even before lawmakers are asked to take it -- another sign of how contentious the chamber’s trial will be.House Judiciary Chairman Jerrold Nadler and Democratic Senator Chris Coons have said Senate Majority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Entrenched in Pumping Repo Market. How Does It Get Out?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-entrenched-repo-market-does-120000251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- At the Federal Reserve, 2020 will be all about making the repo market boring again. Policy makers will find this easier said than done.The central bank’s liquidity injections -- including almost half a trillion dollars earmarked to ensure New Year’s Eve is a snooze -- and Treasury bill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock Poll: 43% Of Evangelicals Support Trump Removal From Office...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/21/poll-43-percent-evangelicals-trump-removal-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll from Politico/Morning Consult indicates that 43% of evangelical voters would approve of President Donald Trump being removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CATS' CRASHES AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/star-wars-rise-of-skywalker-cats-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywalker saga finale currently estimated for $195 million opening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger the joint, higher the tax? Report weighs California marijuana change...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/california-weed/article238508593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'200 years out of date'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dpa-international.com/topic/pope-quotes-late-cardinal-say-church-200-years-date-urn%3Anewsml%3Adpa.com%3A20090101%3A191221-99-229769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Stories from around the globe brought to you by dpa International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyachts in Caribbean Swell as Wealthy Hit St. Maarten...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/superyachts-in-carribean-swell-as-billionaires-hit-st-maarten</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Superyachts in Carribean Swell as Billionaires Hit St. Maarten</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE NIRO UNHINGED: Trump Needs to Be Humiliated; 'I'd Like to See Bag of Sh*t in His Face'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/robert-de-niro-trump-needs-to-be-humiliated-id-like-to-see-a-bag-of-sht-right-in-his-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro sat down with Michael Moore on his new podcast Rumble with Michael Moore and again unloaded on President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom of Ancient Egypt Might Befall Earth Soon, Archaeologist Warns...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201912211077706034-the-doom-of-ancient-egypt-might-befall-earth-soon-archaeologist-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Describing the downfall of the Old Kingdom of Egypt, the archaeologist who found the tomb of one of the rulers from that time period, warned that history may repeat itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no choice but Trump, voter sues over Minnesota primary...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/challenge-to-trump-only-ballot-leaves-early-voting-in-limbo/566377882/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State election officials sought an expedited decision to meet the Jan. 17 start of early voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed-up French travellers face traffic chaos over festive period...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fed-french-travellers-face-traffic-chaos-over-festive-164132918.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travellers across France scrambled on Saturday to begin their Christmas getaways as trains were cancelled, roads were jampacked and nerves were tested as a strike over a pension overhaul shows no signs of letting up. Hopes of a holiday truce were dashed after talks between the government and union leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Knell of Hollywood Musical...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/why-taylor-swifts-cats-is-the-death-knell-of-the-hollywood-musical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Movie musicals used to celebrate the glory of the human body and voice. “Cats” is about “the perversion of the human body through technology,” writes Corbin Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXODUS: California population growth slowest since 1900 as residents leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-21/california-population-continues-to-decline-with-state-emigration-a-major-factor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California population growth slows to a trickle as immigration changes and residents leave the state for affordable housing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
