<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kim warns NKorea could consider change of tack... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kim-warns-n-korea-could-consider-change-tack-013915619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea could consider a change of approach if the US maintains its sanctions on the nuclear-armed country, leader Kim Jong Un warned in his New Year speech Tuesday after 12 months of diplomatic rapprochement. Kim was referring to his summit with US President Donald Trump in Singapore in June, when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Dives In...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/elizabeth-warren-dives-in-11546298426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’ll counter Trump’s populism with a left-wing economic version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Profit Crunch Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/corporate-profit-crunch-looms-as-stocks-slide-11546261258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the stock market’s swoon began at the end of September, analysts have trimmed their earnings forecasts. And investors are worried the moneymaking outlook for companies will deteriorate further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAGER:  2019 a dark year...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/12/the-left-will-make-2019-a-dark-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rarely make predictions – whether of election results or anything else. My policy has always been to say what I believe should be done, not what will be done. I am making an exception with regard to America in 2019. 2019 will be a dark year in America. Thanks to the left’s control of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Passenger strips naked, walks around plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/12/passenger-strips-naked-walks-around-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may have heard of the TV series “Naked and Afraid,” but there possibly could be one titled “Naked on a Plane” based on the actions of a passenger on a flight over the weekend. A man on an Air India Express flight Saturday from Dubai to Lucknow, India, reportedly stripped off al his clothing […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dem brawl for presidency taking shape...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/warrens-jump-into-the-presidential-campaign-kicks-the-2020-race-into-high-gear/2018/12/31/64adbc50-0d02-11e9-831f-3aa2c2be4cbd_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is expected to be a major contender in a field that is likely to be large and diverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More sick children arriving at US border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/12/31/migrant-illnesses-run-rampant-forcing-u-s-border-patrol-seek-help/2454759002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 450 arrived ill in a week through Sunday and 17 are hospitalized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more shoulders to cry on as couples seek 'woebot' counselors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/no-more-shoulders-to-cry-on-as-couples-seek-woebot-counsellors-x0d99hr75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Couples whose partnership is in difficulties could soon be baring their souls to an AI chatbot instead of a human counsellor, according to the head of Britain’s biggest relationship charity. “We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tough 2018 for Pope Ends With Spokesman's Resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/vatican-spokesman-deputy-resign-capping-difficult-year-pope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican spokesman and his deputy resigned on Monday over disagreements on strategy, ending a year of upheaval in the Holy See's communications structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 stabbed at UK railway station;  'Allahu Akbar!'</title>
      <link>https://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/greater-manchester-news/manchester-victoria-stabbing-eyewitness-claims-15615300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Clack, a BBC producer, was on a platform at Manchester Victoria railway station waiting for a tram when he witnessed the attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Deletes New Year's Eve Tweet Saying It's 'Ready to Drop Something'... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/31/politics/us-military-new-years-eve-bomb-tweet/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Strategic Command, the unified military force that controls the launch of nuclear weapons, tweeted an unusual New Year's Eve message on Monday featuring B-2 bombers dropping 30,000-pound conventional weapons at a test range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Post Worst Year In Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/31/stock-market-wall-street-stocks-eye-us-china-trade-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street concluded a tumultuous 2018 as the major stock indexes posted their worst yearly performances since the financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest ever woman, 122, may have been a fraud...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/historys-oldest-woman-a-fraud-theory-says-122-year-old-jeanne-calment-was-actually-a-99-year-old-imposter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did the real Jeanne Calment die in 1934 at the age of 59?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firm Led by GOOGLE Veterans Uses A.I. to 'Nudge' Workers Toward Happiness...</title>
      <link>https://momogunnews.com/firm-led-by-google-veterans-uses-a-i-to-nudge-workers-toward-happiness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;momogunnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif. — Technology companies like to promote artificial intelligence’s potential for solving some of the world’s toughest problems, like reducing automobile deaths and helping doctors diagnose diseases. A company started by three former [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Smoke Shop Worker Fired After Anti-Trump Rant at Customer...</title>
      <link>https://legalinsurrection.com/2018/12/vape-shop-employees-public-tirade-against-trump-supporter-latest-tds-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;legalinsurrection.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ian Furgeson says Xhale City's corporate office later informed him that the employee was fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Plans Women's Economic Development Push...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ivanka-trump-plans-global-womens-economic-development-push-225225919--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump is set to launch a White House effort aimed at women's global economic empowerment in early 2019. A formal launch for the initiative was planned for next week but has been postponed amid uncertainty about the government shutdown, the White House said Monday. The original plan for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain sends ships to tackle migrant crossing surge... </title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/britain-sends-ships-tackle-migrant-crossing-surge-193851060--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain announced Monday it will deploy two border patrol ships in the Channel in response to a surge in migrants crossing from France in dinghies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human waste, trash overwhelm some national parks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e28b313197bb46bebef0faca24b333ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Human feces, overflowing garbage, illegal off-roading and other damaging behavior in fragile areas were beginning to overwhelm some of the West's iconic national parks on Monday, as a partial government shutdown left the areas open to visitors but with little staff on duty. "It's a free-for-all," Dakota Snider, 24, who lives and works in Yosemite Valley, said by telephone Monday, as Yosemite National Park officials announced closings of some minimally supervised campgrounds and public areas within the park that are overwhelmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC homicide tally lowest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b658df4c890e435ebf824b4481287d92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City could register the fewest number of homicides in several decades in 2018, as the city continues its long battle against violent crime. As of Sunday, the city had recorded five fewer killings than the 292 investigated in 2017, according to preliminary police data provided to The Associated Press. That year's figure was itself the lowest in decades. The New York Police Department said it also had seen a modest decline in shooting incidents in 2018 and an 8 percent drop in robberies. Figures for other categories of crime were not immediately available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revelry, reflection mark transition to new year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7315f44396d74e39b506b6756ed4f51f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fireworks, concerts, spiritual services and political addresses abounded to mark the transition to 2019 as revelers around the globe bid farewell Monday to a year filled with challenges to many of the world's most basic institutions, including political, trade and religious ones. A look at how people around the world are ushering in 2019: LONDON Britons ushered in the new year with the familiar chimes of Big Ben, even though the world famous clock has been disconnected for more than a year because of a conservation project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD won't fly drone in Times Square during rain...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190101004039-ryaet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW-YEAR/USA-NEW YORK (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Glowing New Year's Eve ball rises above a sodden Times Square</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 BEGINS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6541611/2019-nearly-world-gets-ready-new-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Festive lights engulfed the night sky of Downtown Dubai as the city held an extravagant celebration to make sure 2019 arrived with a bang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 PREVIEW: Warren Livestreams Drinking Beer, Cooking...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/davecatanese/status/1079888955661783040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Elizabeth Warren is on Instagram live cooking dinner and drinking a beer. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is picking our next president. We just don’t know it yet.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tech giants turned 'digital wellness' into marketing ploy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-big-tech-co-opted-time-well-spent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the large tech corporations turned "digital wellness" into a Goopified trend that gives them a new way to market themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 stabbed at UK railway station; Attacker 'shouted Allah!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/greater-manchester-news/manchester-victoria-knife-attack-station-15615253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No trams are currently stopping at Victoria and there's a large police presence outside the station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing face-detecting locks in public housing increases citizen surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/31/beijing-facial-recognition-public-housing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing is using smart locks with facial recognition to prevent abuses of public housing, but at a steep cost to privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON DECLARES: I AM GREATEST EVER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-declares-himself-the-greatest-player-of-all-time-because-of-championship-with-cavaliers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James says his 2016 NBA title with the Cavs made him the best ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi says won't resign if indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-i-wont-resign-if-summoned-for-a-hearing-pending-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Imagine if ultimately the case was closed, and a prime minister had been ousted,' Netanyahu says. That would be 'a terrible blow to democracy'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDES WARN: HILLARY COMPARISONS 'REEK SEXISM'</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/elizabeth-warren-2020-campaign/579214/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her 2020 bid, the senator from Massachusetts wants to reclaim her status as a political outsider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Warren's 'psychiatrist' knows whether she thinks she can win White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-on-whether-warren-thinks-she-can-win-the-presidency-youd-have-to-ask-her-psychiatrist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with "Fox &amp; Friends" host Pete Hegseth set to air during the Fox News New Year's Eve Special, President Trump suggested that only Massachusetts Democratic Sen. Elizabeth Warren's "psychiatrist" knows whether she thinks she can win the White House in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horny passengers 'try to mate' with snake!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/31/cane-toads-python-escape-storm-northern-australia-kununurra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amphibian expert says toads were trying to mate with python, as thousands of the invasive pest are flushed out by rising waters in Kununurra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army rescinds unusually specific order banning sex, cuddling...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/europe/army-unit-in-europe-rescinds-unusually-specific-order-banning-sex-and-cuddling-1.562272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas came late for some Army troops on rotation to Europe when officials canceled an order Wednesday that for nine days banned various sexual acts, including cuddling, for a unit’s soldiers in the rotational barracks at the Grafenwoehr Training Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington On Verge of Legalizing Human Composting?</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/washington-may-become-the-first-state-to-legalize-human-composting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's something beautiful in deciding how one's final moments should be confined to the memory of our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-world-cup-host-qatar-introduce-100-percent-booze-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toads ride on Monty the python to escape storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-31/cane-toads-hitch-ride-on-monty-the-python-back/10675944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A farmer in far north WA captures the bizarre sight of a knot of cane toads hitching a ride on a python in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos fortune drops $40,000,000,000+ from peak, but still grew by $24 BILLION this year...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/magazines/panache/tim-sweeney-jeff-bezos-lei-jun-the-worlds-biggest-billionaire-winners-losers-of-2018/articleshow/67320613.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singaporean billionaires fared the best in dollar terms, gaining $2.5 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winds could make Vegas New Year's Eve fireworks dicey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/winds-could-make-las-vegas-new-years-eve-fireworks-dicey-1562570/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service forecasts a high of 49 degrees Monday with winds kicking up and clouds moving out late morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines President Duterte claims he abused maid as teenager...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/30/asia/rodrigo-duterte-comments-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte has claimed he molested a maid while in high school -- comments his spokesman later said were "made up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 BILLION ROBOCALLS IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stop-robocalling-me-i-didnt-11546261200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans’ growing battle against illegal robocallers has reached a boiling point, with victims of one form of phone-related malfeasance now lashing out at those impacted by a different form: phone-number spoofing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Experiment to Stop Latin America Carnage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/inside-the-experiment-to-stop-the-carnage-in-latin-america-11546275481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few places in Ecuador and Colombia are exceptions to the regional surge in homicides. Efforts include turning gang members into garbage collectors, and firing hundreds of corrupt police officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens steal NYC bus; 4-hour joyride...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-teen-thieves-steal-mta-bus-bronx-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A half-dozen teens stole a parked MTA bus from the Bronx and took it on a three-borough joyride — less than 24 hours after a trio of teenagers stole a city bus in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro follows through on gun, 'anti-Marxist' vows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-follows-gun-anti-marxist-vows-193827024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - On the eve of taking office as Brazil's new president on Tuesday, Jair Bolsonaro is making clear he intends to implement the far-right agenda he promised during his election campaign. The announcements underlined Bolsonaro's desire to break with decades of center-left rule in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican spokesman, deputy resign amid crisis for pope...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vatican-spokesman-greg-burke-deputy-resign-suddenly-111645264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican spokesman, Greg Burke, and his deputy resigned abruptly Monday amid an overhaul of the Vatican's communications operations and a crisis period in Pope Francis' papacy. The departures of Burke and his deputy, Paloma Garcia Ovejero, signaled that problems associated with Francis'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless starts fire in front of MANDALAY BAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/homeless-person-causes-fire-in-front-of-mandalay-bay-police-say-1562386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details were not immediately available from the Clark County Fire Department, but Metropolitan Police Department Lt. David Gordon confirmed about 10:40 p.m. that an unknown number of palm trees had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana made big promises on racial equity -- and fell short...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/legal-marijuana-made-big-promises-racial-equity-fell-short-n952376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time is really up on selling your business dream as a social justice movement,” said the president of the Minority Cannabis Business Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian-American Sentenced to Life for Selling Properties to Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com//Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Palestinian-American-gets-life-in-prison-for-selling-properties-to-Jews-575903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, Isaam Akel, was arrested by the PA last October despite holding an Israeli ID card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says ready to work with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-46714985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's latest statement suggests trade negotiations between the two countries are progressing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice to charge day-trippers for access...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbde03ccc904e618443198adab23979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A measure in Italy's 2019 budget law will allow the local government in Venice to charge day-trippers for access to the city's historic center as a way to help defray the considerable costs of maintaining a popular tourist destination built on water, the mayor said. Venice Mayor Luigi Brugnaro said late Sunday on Twitter that the new visitors' tax would "allow us to manage the city better and to keep it clean" and "allow Venetians to live with more decorum."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Investments of 2018? Art, Wine, Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-best-investments-of-2018-art-wine-and-cars-11546232460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury assets, including wine, art, classic cars and fancy colored diamonds, have outperformed stocks and bonds this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious swamp cancer killing ponies on island famous for them...</title>
      <link>https://www.delmarvanow.com/story/news/local/virginia/2018/12/29/chincoteague-pony-euthanized-swamp-cancer/2438186002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delmarvanow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disease killed three other ponies this year, as well as two in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran TV chief sacked over Jackie Chan sex scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46720733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A regional channel showed Jackie Chan's Shinjuku Incident without censoring an "immoral" part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets stagger towards end of worst year since financial crisis... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-rounds-worst-since-2011-gains-034945504--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World stock markets staggered Monday towards the end of their worst year since the global financial crisis a decade ago, rocked by rising interest rates, the global trade war and Brexit, dealers said. London and Paris wobbled in holiday-shortened trade on New Year's Eve -- but nursed dizzying double-digit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: NO wall money...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51dd72d6d19e4d2eb0b73dcd2c45aa27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the U.S. government shutdown (all times local): 11:45 a.m. House Democrats are unveiling legislation to re-open the government without money for President Donald Trump's border wall. The House is preparing to vote on the package Thursday when the new Congress convenes. This is according to an aide who was not authorized to discuss the plan publicly and spoke on condition of anonymity. It will include one bill to fund the Department of Homeland Security at current levels through Feb. 8, with $1.3 billion for border security. The package will also include six other bipartisan bills to fund the departments of Agriculture, Interior, Housing and Urban Development and others closed by the partial shutdown. Some have already passed the Senate. Those bills will provide money through the remainder of the fiscal year, to Sept. 30. The partial government shutdown is in its second week over Trump's demand for $5 billion for the wall. --Lisa Mascaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hold fast': Mattis bids farewell to Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hold-fast-mattis-bids-farewell-pentagon-153201158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Jim Mattis bade farewell to the Pentagon on Monday, telling the US military to "hold fast" after he quit over a series of fundamental differences with President Donald Trump. Mattis resigned December 20, after Trump stunned the US establishment by ordering a full troop withdrawal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER messages unleashed FBI raid on NSA leak suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/31/nsa-hacking-case-twitter-1077013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge reveals that just before Shadow Brokers advertised a major breach, contractor sent suspicious message: “Shelf life, three weeks”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge funds had miserable 2018; Closures, mediocre performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/hedge-funds-hopes-for-2018-dashed-amid-fund-closures-20181224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year was supposed to be when rising volatility and yields brought back the glory days. Instead, returns fell and investors fled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12,000 police on duty in Paris as 'yellow vests' call protests...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/12-000-police-duty-paris-yellow-vests-call-153929643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 150,000 police are set to be on duty around France on New Year's Eve when "yellow vest" protesters have called for another round of anti-government demonstrations. The French capital will be on high alert after repeated clashes over the last month between security forces and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batten Down the Hatches -- Media Storm Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/batten-down-the-hatches-for-2019-a-media-storm-is-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consolidation, an uncertain economy and an unstable presidency is making people nervous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist filmed snorting cocaine off Escobar's grave getting death threats...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/12/31/brit-filmed-snorting-cocaine-off-pablo-escobars-grave-says-death-threats-8295204/?ito=cbshare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Semmens, 35, has lost his family after being kicked out of Colombia where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis CK leaked standup: Jokes about school shooting, Holocaust, trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6541323/Louis-CK-makes-fun-Parkland-shooting-victims-shocking-leaked-stand-audio.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Louis CK, 51, attacked the Parkland high school shooting victims in leaked audio from his December 16 set at the Governor's Comedy Club in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN GETS READY</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c9f36d36633c43d0bee74859a010850a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Elizabeth Warren on Monday took the first major step toward launching a widely anticipated campaign for the presidency, hoping her reputation as a populist fighter can help her navigate a Democratic field that could include nearly two dozen candidates. "No matter what our differences, most of us want the same thing," the 69-year-old Massachusetts Democrat said in a video that highlights her family's history in Oklahoma. "To be able to work hard, play by the same set of rules and take care of the people we love. That's what I'm fighting for and that's why today I'm launching an exploratory committee for president."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown first battle of new era...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b1ca483bfaa646deba4fff1a968b2ade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi often quotes Abraham Lincoln saying public sentiment is everything. It's a theory that will be put to the test when the new House Democratic majority gavels in this week and votes to end the government shutdown without money for President Donald Trump's border wall with Mexico. The high-stakes move to reopen the government will be the first big battle between Trump and Pelosi as Democrats come into control ready to reassert the power of the legislative branch and confront the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Pence-Schumer showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/31/mike-pence-chuck-schumer-government-shutdown-2018-1076615</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men with no shared history or apparent personal chemistry are charged with ending the shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed man wearing surgical mask headed to church to 'fulfill prophecy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kens5.com/article/news/local/armed-man-headed-to-fulfill-prophecy-at-church-is-from-houston-area/273-625427998</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kens5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 33-year-old man was arrested in Seguin Sunday morning after heading to a church a loaded firearm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500-euro note gets last print run...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-500-euro-note-gets-last-print-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;500-euro note gets last print run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers develop artificial fingerprints; Hack smartphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/28/research-claims-fake-fingerprints-could-hack-a-third-of-smartphones.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Academics at New York University and the Michigan State University have developed images of fingerprints that have the potential to unlock devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BIGGEST WINS AND LOSSES...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/30/trump-biggest-wins-losses-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second full year at the helm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Detains American on Spying Charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russia-detains-american-on-spying-charge-11546255397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian authorities said they had detained a U.S. citizen for alleged spying, setting the tone for more confrontation between the two countries in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Right Wing Woos New Audience: Jewish Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/europes-right-wing-woos-a-new-audience-jewish-voters-11546257601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across Europe, anti-immigration parties with ties to far-right movements have stepped up efforts to recruit supporters in the continent’s small Jewish community, often drawing on perceptions in that community about anti-Semitism among Muslims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WELCOMES 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2018/dec/31/new-years-eve-2018-celebrations-around-the-world-live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow all the celebrations as the clock strikes midnight and countries see out 2018 to welcome in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.D. Salinger at 100: 'CATCHER IN RYE' still relevant?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Is-Catcher-in-the-Rye-still-relevant-on-13499289.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catcher in the Rye By J.D. Salinger Little, Brown. 240 pp. $8.99 - - - Tuesday is J.D. Salinger's 100th birthday, but Holden Caulfield is still 17. The iconic teenager of "The Catcher in the Rye" is forever suspended in the amber of our youthful alienation. Although a few pious schools continue to ban Salinger's only published novel, for millions of adults, a faded copy of "The Catcher in the Rye" is a sweet teenage treasure, as transgressive as a trophy from band camp. Ninth-graders who secretly read the book with a flashlight when it came out in 1951 are now in their 80s. To read it again as an adult is to feel Holden's pain lingering like a phantom limb. His righteous cynicism is adolescence distilled into a sweet liquor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican spokesman, deputy resign suddenly...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-spokespersons/vatican-spokesman-deputy-resign-suddenly-idUSKCN1OU0HG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spokesman for the Vatican and his deputy resigned suddenly on Monday, an off...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminist filmmakers tackle adult movie machismo...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-feminist-filmmakers-tackle-adult-movie-machismo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feminist filmmakers tackle adult movie machismo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spaceship zooms toward farthest world ever photographed...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/nasa-spaceship-zooms-toward-farthest-world-ever-photographed-11075422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA:  A NASA spaceship is zooming toward the farthest, and quite possibly the oldest, cosmic body ever photographed by humankind, a tiny, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOTS COULD MAKE ROAD WORK THING OF PAST...</title>
      <link>https://home.bt.com/news/uk-news/futuristic-micro-robots-could-make-roadworks-a-thing-of-the-past-11364321785449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grants totalling £26.6m will fund projects including the development of tiny devices to repair cracks in pipes without the need to dig up roads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WELCOMES 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/new-years-eve-celebrations-watch-fireworks-world-welcomes-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Year's Eve is upon us - catch up on all the celebrations around the world with our live stream of all the best firework displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injection to halt Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/injection-halt-progress-alzheimers-available-within-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An injection capable of halting the progress of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s could be available to patients within a decade, Britain&amp;rsquo;s leading dementia organisation predicts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year Ends on 10th Day of Shutdown as Pelosi Awaits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/year-ends-on-10th-day-of-partial-federal-shutdown-pelosi-awaits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi is set to reclaim the speakerâ€™s gavel on Thursday, when Democrats take control of the House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
