<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'PROPHET OF DOOM'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5112566/frank-james-youtube-channel-brooklyn-subway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE man named as a person of interest in the Brooklyn subway shooting shared chilling videos and posts before the attack. At least 29 people were wounded on Tuesday after a gunman wearing a gas mas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More couples enjoying open relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5111737/open-relationships-soar-since-pandemic-sex-expert/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPEN relationships have soared since the pandemic as couples grow bored with each other, a sex expert is claiming. Romantic burnout caused by spending too much time together during lockdowns has be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian fighter pilots in old jets take on better-equipped Russians...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukrainian-fighter-pilots-in-old-jets-take-on-better-equipped-russians/ar-AAW9Xc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspapers keep eliminating print days...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/newspapers-keep-eliminating-print-days-they-say-it-e2-80-99s-for-the-best/ar-AAW870O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A call, a text, an apology: How abortion arrest shook up TX town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-call-a-text-an-apology-how-an-abortion-arrest-shook-up-a-texas-town/ar-AAWaztC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis takes on DISNEY in culture war with national implications...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/desantis-takes-on-disney-in-a-culture-war-with-national-implications/ar-AAWaDAG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri Republicans target schools, books, race in latest culture war proposal...</title>
      <link>https://www.fltimes.com/news/nation/missouri-republicans-target-schools-books-and-race-in-latest-culture-war-proposal/article_1def38c9-83c6-5816-b4c9-f5f378461007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. — Missouri Republicans gave initial approval Tuesday to legislation that says parents have a right to see the curriculum used in their child’s classroom. The so-called “Parents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUBWAY SUSPECT UNMASKED</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10713233/NYPD-releases-image-person-Brooklyn-subway-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYPD have issued a $50,000 reward for information leading to the capture of Frank James, the suspect in the Brooklyn subway shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Puff Piece Chris Cuomo Aired to Silence Accuser...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/watch-the-corporate-puff-piece-chris-cuomo-aired-to-silence-an-accuser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viewers tuning into CNN on a chilly morning in December 2017 might have been puzzled when a treacly corporate promotion interrupted the network's wall-to-wall news coverage of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million empty spaces: Chronicling COVID's cruel American toll...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/one-million-dead-US-COVID-ea745d462d47a65029a8c507c94e679e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the deadliest day of a horrific week in April 2020, COVID took the lives of 816 people in New York City alone. Lost in the blizzard of pandemic data that’s been swirling ever since is the fact that 43-year-old Fernando Morales was one of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDs surge to record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/apr/12/us-sexually-transmitted-infections-record-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reported cases dropped in early months of Covid-19 pandemic but disrupted healthcare and diverted resources aided sharp rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation accelerates to 8.5% in March; New four-decade high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/12/consumer-prices-rose-8point5percent-in-march-slightly-hotter-than-expected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index for March was expected to increase 8.4% from a year ago, according to Dow Jones estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS TANKS, AX, GUN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/12/i-came-face-to-face-with-brooklyn-subway-shooter-rider/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway rider Fitim Gjeloshi came face to face with the mass shooter who opened fire on a crowded subway in Sunset Park, Brooklyn on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC SUBWAY SHOOTING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brooklyn-subway-shooting-fef3cd9b41a50cfca639897baa52e382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A gunman in a gas mask and construction vest set off a smoke grenade and fired a barrage of bullets in a rush-hour subway train, shooting at least 10 people Tuesday, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT LEAST 29 INJURED</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/brooklyn-shootings-subway-shooting-sunset-park-new-york/11740555/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have identified 62-year-old Frank R. James as a person of interest in a Brooklyn subway shooting that left dozens shot or otherwise injured Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris fined for lockdown parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2022/apr/12/boris-johnson-and-rishi-sunak-fined-for-breaking-covid-lockdown-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM, chancellor and Carrie Johnson given fixed-penalty notices for attending No 10 lockdown party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bird poops on Biden during speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5111480/bird-poops-joe-biden-during-infrastructure-speech-today-iowa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BIRD pooped on President Joe Biden during his infrastructure speech today in Iowa, as he’s been trolled for “talking s***” on Twitter. Biden was in the midst of a speech in Menl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida family accused of kidnapping, beating gay man so badly he was left blinded

...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article260357115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three family members have been charged with a hate crime after kidnapping and beating a gay man so severely that he was permanently blinded, Broward prosecutors said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Urban League says state of Black America grim...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/national-urban-league-says-state-black-america-grim-rcna24011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Figures on Black health disparities, wealth inequality, and more "change so little and so slowly," said National Urban League President Marc Morial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST contributor arrested in Moscow after criticizing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/washington-post-contributor-arrested-in-moscow-after-criticizing-putin/ar-AAW81nn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE Secretly Bought Customer Data from Hackers to Stop Leak. It Failed...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k7w9mv/tmobile-hacked-bought-data-mandiant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After hackers targeted T-Mobile in August, T-Mobile hired a third-party firm that went undercover and bought exclusive access to the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Scientists Identify Personality Traits Of A**holes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/personality-traits-total-ahole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that the most likely people to be the “biggest assholes” in someone's life are middle-aged men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan issues war survival handbook over invasion threat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/12/taiwan-issues-war-survival-handbook-as-chinese-mulls-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan’s military issued its first official war survival handbook this week, advising civilians how to respond to a Chinese invasion similar to Russia’s attacks on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous leaks '776GB of Kremlin files'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5106556/anonymous-leaks-kremlin-files-claimed-hack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANONYMOUS is claiming to have obtained trove of Russian files. The vigilante hacker group is making good on a vow to infiltrate and disrupt the Russian war effort. According to reports, Anonymous h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  South Dakota AG impeached over fatal crash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pierre-south-dakota-impeachments-accidents-b82ddf729c15e95a80e83e88e4a44722</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERRE, S.D. (AP) — The South Dakota House on Tuesday impeached state Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg over a 2020 car crash in which he killed a pedestrian but initially said he might have struck a deer or another large animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron faces angry voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-marine-le-pen-france-europe-presidential-elections-de520ead8c95a5447e527ac9e9460cde</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MULHOUSE, France (AP) — Facing a tougher-than expected fight for reelection, French President Emmanuel Macron has hit the campaign trail at last — and it isn't always proving welcoming. But he's not shying away from angry voters, instead engaging in lively, sometimes confrontational debates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gilbert Gottfried dead at 67...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/celebrity/gilbert-gottfried-iconic-comedian-dies-67-long-illness-rcna24111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gottfried died at 2:35 p.m. ET on Tuesday from Recurrent Ventricular Tachycardia due to Myotonic Dystrophy type II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puppets Go Ballistic Over Fake Russian Slashing Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-s-puppets-go-ballistic-over-fake-russian-slashing-video/ar-AAW8ZLG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Reference Scrubbed From New 'HARRY POTTER' Movie For Chinese Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/gay-reference-scrubbed-from-new-harry-potter-movie-for-chinese-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. has stripped direct references to a gay relationship from Fantastic Beasts: The Secrets of Dumbledore for the film's Chinese release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden scrambles to respond to claims of chemical weapon use...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/12/biden-admin-russia-chemical-weapons-00024709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration has said Russian chemical weapons use in Ukraine would trigger a ‘proportional’ U.S. response. Its pledge may soon be tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Europe's Ex-Royals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/among-europe-s-ex-royals/ar-AAW8WMA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAN in Existential Crisis Amid Mass Exodus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/far-one-america-news-existential-150803409.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyThis reporting appears as one of several scoops featured in this week’s edition of Source Material, the media newsletter that pulls back the curtain to reveal what’s really going on inside the world’s most powerful navel-gazing industry. Subscribe here and send your questions, tips, and complaints here.AT&amp;T-backed satellite provider DirecTV finally made it official last Tuesday, dropping far-right One America News from its lineup, lea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE cancels more flights amid crew shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/travel/jetblue-cancels-flights-crew-shortages-rcna24069</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite hiring more 3,000 employees this year, JetBlue is struggling to staff its operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer than 10,000 people using...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/12/cnn-plus-low-viewership-numbers-warner-bros-discovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The paltry audience casts doubt on the future of CNN+ following the recently completed combination of Discovery and WarnerMedia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zika may be step away from explosive outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-61078867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say we should be on alert for variants which could start another major outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First sitting PM to receive a punishment for breaking the law...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/boris-johnson-and-rishi-sunak-to-be-fined-over-lockdown-breaking-parties-in-downing-street-12577277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opposition politicians immediately called for the prime minister and the chancellor to resign though some Tory MPs who have been critical of the PM over partygate said now was not the right time for him to go given the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspapers keep eliminating print days...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/newspapers-keep-eliminating-print-days-they-say-it-e2-80-99s-for-the-best/ar-AAW870O?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook cautions against antitrust legislation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/3265186-tim-cook-cautions-against-antitrust-legislation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook warned in a speech at a Washington, D.C., conference Tuesday that antitrust legislation aimed at lessening the monopoly power of app stores could harm users. “We are deeply conce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space balloon company offers first look at luxury cabins...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220412-space-balloon-company-offers-first-look-at-luxury-cabins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new entrant in the space tourism market promises customers views of the Earth's curvature from the comfort of a luxury cabin, lifted to the upper atmosphere with a giant balloon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma makes nearly all abortions illegal...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/oklahoma-governor-signs-law-abortion-ban-753a8c12-578a-493d-8932-a44ada8f0f28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person found guilty of providing an abortion would face up to 10 years in prison and a fine up to $100,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Big cuts coming for CNN+ after slow start...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cnn-plus-cuts-warner-brothers-discovery-1be0ac3a-6952-4af0-b8e2-03dd6ae0839c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news giant was initially planning to invest around $1 billion over 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster says Republicans mocking 'child' Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/3264736-gop-pollster-says-republicans-are-mocking-child-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent GOP pollster Frank Luntz said in a recent interview that Republicans in private are mocking former President Trump and they are “tired of going back and rehashing the 2020 election.” Lunt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bracing for coup...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5106646/putin-military-coup-purging-spies-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin is bracing for a possible military coup after he purged 150 spies over Russia’s disastrous invasion of Ukraine. The mad tyrant has launched a “Stalinist” purge of h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purge of spy chiefs as mission stalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10709253/150-Russian-officers-accused-leaks-Kremlin-gears-massive-final-offensive-Donbas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It emerged last night that Colonel General Sergei Beseda, head of the FSB's foreign intelligence unit, has been moved to Moscow's high-security Lefortovo prison after being on house arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Lt Gov arrested in campaign donation scheme...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brian-benjamin-new-york-lieutenant-governor-arrested-3682bc9913a2421f1b1613497286b591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin, whose seven months in that role has been overshadowed by probes into a previous campaign, was arrested Tuesday in a federal corruption investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tech Accurately Predicts If, When Someone Will Suffer Cardiac Arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/algorithm-technology-predicts-cardiac-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new artificial intelligence-based approach can predict "significantly more accurately" than a doctor if and when a patient could die of cardiac arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's not-so-secret weapon: An army of TWITTER bots touting TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musks-not-secret-weapon-120003951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk and Tesla have millions of vocal fans on Twitter. Not all of them are real. Two researchers are trying to figure out who controls the bots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris fined for Covid lockdown breaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/12/covid-lockdown-boris-jonson-and-rishi-sunak-to-be-fined.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson and Finance Minister Rishi Sunak are set to be fined by police for breaching Covid-19 lockdown laws, the government said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow returns to MSNBC, will switch to once a week...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-rachel-maddow-ali-velshi-arts-and-entertainment-094cda977c40fc1d236625760220fd24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — MSNBC's Rachel Maddow returned to the air Monday with some bad news for her fans: Starting next month, she will be doing her prime-time show only once a week. After working her customary five nights a week for the rest of April, Maddow said, she will work on Monday nights only starting in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police under review for blasting DISNEY songs to keep videos off social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/04/12/santa-ana-police-disney-music/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Santa Ana, Calif., were playing Disney songs loudly at night in an apparent attempt to keep a video of them from being uploaded to YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Jews fleeing Ukraine, Passover takes on new meaning...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-africa-europe-berlin-passover-91a86a1668df7fd15cb879911a0d9dcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Good morning! Happy morning!” Rabbi Avraham Wolff exclaimed, with a big smile, as he walked into the Chabad synagogue in Odesa on a recent morning. Russian missiles had just struck an oil refinery in the Ukrainian city, turning the sky charcoal gray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels swap arms for cocaine, fueling Colombia violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-12/mexican-cartels-swap-arms-for-cocaine-fueling-colombia-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney, now GOP maverick, undecided on future in politics...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/senate/3264525-romney-now-a-gop-maverick-undecided-on-future-in-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney (R-Utah) says he hasn’t decided whether to run for re-election in 2024, when he could be on the same ballot as Donald Trump if the former president seeks another bid for the White …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Beach in Zipolite Is LGBTQ Haven. Can It Last?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/12/this-beach-in-mexico-is-an-l-g-b-t-q-haven-but-can-it-last/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ZIPOLITE, Mexico — When the sun starts to slip toward the ocean in this idyllic beach town on Mexico’s Pacific</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From USA to China: 3-Month Quarantine Horror Story...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/12/from-the-u-s-to-china-a-3-month-quarantine-horror-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before boarding his flight from Los Angeles to the Chinese city of Guangzhou, Xue Liangquan, a California-based lawyer, knew he</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
