<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutorial Focus Moves to New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-mueller-report-lands-prosecutorial-focus-moves-to-new-york/ar-BBV83Qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of thousands join referendum protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-47678763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters demand another EU referendum as MPs struggle to agree a way out of the Brexit impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy group sues for release...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435422-privacy-group-sues-doj-for-public-release-of-mueller-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Electronic Privacy Information Center (EPIC) filed a lawsuit on Friday to obtain special counsel Robert Mueller’s final report on his investigation into possible obstruction of justice by President Trump and possible coordination bet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full disclosure battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mueller-probe-apos-end-kicks-080000229.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I intend to consult with Deputy Attorney General Rosenstein and Special Counsel Mueller to determine what other information from the report can be released to Congress and the public consistent with the law, including the Special Counsel regulations, and the Department’s long-standing practices and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Family against billionaire': Battle over Zuckerberg's Hawaiian estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/23/mark-zuckerberg-hawaii-estate-land-parcels-auction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parcels near Facebook CEO’s property auctioned off amid lengthy fight over Native Hawaiian land rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugged orangutan found in airline luggage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/23/drugged-orangutan-found-in-russians-airline-luggage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police at Indonesian airport also found two live geckos and five lizards in suitcase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayday? Pressure builds on PM to quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-betting/mayday-pressure-builds-on-pm-theresa-may-to-announce-plans-to-quit-idUSKCN1R40DN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May was under pressure on Saturday to set out plans for h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLIC STILL IN DARK</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/83d570e5100640f7bf8245045e7c6aee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller closed his long and contentious Russia investigation with no new charges, ending the probe that has cast a dark shadow over Donald Trump's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable viewers digest through Hannity, Maddow...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/301bd7169962433e92430fe9b98aa468</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For Sean Hannity, the "witch hunt" was finally over. Rachel Maddow considered it the start of something. The diametrically opposed opinion hosts, who vie for the distinction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As 'caliphate' ends where is leader Baghdadi?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/baghdadi-ghost-world-jihads-low-profile-boss-145547891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most wanted man who has so far eluded capture, Islamic State group chief Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has seen his "caliphate" crumble and its last shred of territory in Syria evaporate on Saturday. After declaring himself caliph in 2014, Baghdadi held sway over seven million people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian Singer Banned After Claiming Lack Of Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/clevelandbanner/article/62ca9512d1514a6d9e85e66ec496d292/egyptian-singer-banned-after-claiming-lack-free-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — An Egyptian singer has been banned from performing in her home country after suggesting that it does not respect free speech.A video clip circulated online shows Sherine Abdel-Wahab, during a performance in Bahrain, saying: "Here I can say whatever I want. In Egypt, anyone who talks gets imprisoned."Egypt's Musicians Union responded late Friday by barring the singer, popularly known by her first name, from performing. It also summoned her for questioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron to miss playoffs first time since '05...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lakers-james-officially-nba-postseason-picture-055826368--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary superstar LeBron James will miss the NBA playoffs for the first time since 2005 as the Los Angeles Lakers were officially eliminated with a 111-106 loss to the Brooklyn Nets. The four-time league MVP also had his eight-year run to the NBA finals snapped on Friday night as the loss takes the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Investigations Loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-report-concludes-but-other-investigations-loom-11553289647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conclusion of special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia investigation leaves in its wake about a dozen other probes into President Trump and his associates by an array of federal, state and congressional investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concern Grows for U.S. Citizens Detained in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/concern-grows-for-u-s-citizens-detained-in-venezuela-11553302782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department is demanding that a dozen U.S. citizens and permanent residents being held in detention in Venezuela be granted access to proper nutrition and medical care, and be afforded fair judicial treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:   Mueller Must Remain Silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/03/ken-starr-muellers-report-shouldnt-go-congress/585577/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unusual situation facing Robert Mueller does not somehow work a repeal of well-established traditions of confidentiality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UFO community still believes -- and science is starting to listen...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/ufo-sightings-believers-mufon-unidentified-flying-objects-outer-space-20190322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last two years, scientists, politicians, and professionals have increasingly been willing to touch the taboo subject of UFOs and perhaps lend a little credence to those who still believe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streisand says Michael Jackson accusers were 'thrilled to be there' and his 'sexual needs were his sexual needs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-barbra-streisand-michael-jackson-accusers-thrilled-sexual-needs-20190323-7z3b2dqgbzh7jfs4yyhqhdfjyi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barbra Streisand is under fire for comments she made about two men accusing Michael Jackson of sexually assaulting them as children.The legendary singer and actress said that Wade Robson and James Safechuck — whose allegations against the late King of Pop resurfaced in the recent documentary “Leaving Neverland" — “were thrilled to be there” and that what allegedly happened to them “didn’t kill them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>675 DAYS OF INVESTIGATION</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/435383-muellers-investigation-ends-but-the-political-circus-will-continue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats need to face the reality that the only chance they have to beat Trump is at the ballot box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kraft spa tapes may be released to public...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/22/robert-krafts-sexual-and-graphic-spa-tapes-may-be-released-to-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kraft’s powerful legal team is “surprised and disappointed” that prosecutors have denied their request to stop the “sexual and graphic” videos from inside the Asian spa going public. Kraft’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:   Don't expect hysteria to end...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/22/mueller-wraps-up-but-dont-expect-the-hysteria-to-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Bob Mueller has handed in his report, marking the effective end of the three-year Trump-Russia investigation. Hallelujah! This means that Mueller firmly expects to file no more crim…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemalan with no legs tries to sneak cross Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/legless-man-rescued-by-border-patrol-agents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border patrol agents had to rescue a double amputee from an island in the middle of the Rio Grande River this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK:  Five things that didn't happen...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-five-things-that-didnt-happen-in-the-mueller-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller has delivered his report on the Trump-Russia investigation to Attorney General William Barr. Sometime soon, perhaps within hours, Barr will send the report's "principal conclusions" to Congress. It will first go to the chairperson and ranking member of both the House and Senate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculation Begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/22/us/politics/mueller-report-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general, William P. Barr, will determine how much of the special counsel’s Russia report will be shared with Congress or the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER DELIVERED</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/mueller-sends-report-trump-investigation-ag-barr-n974006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transmission of the document ends a lengthy probe into the president and Russian interference in the campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'As much transparency as possible'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Mueller-report-sent-to-attorney-general-13709793.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Special counsel Robert Mueller submitted a long-awaited report to Attorney General William Barr on Friday, marking the end of his investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election and possible obstruction of justice by President Donald Trump.  The submission of Mueller's report ends his closely watched inquiry - a case that has engulfed the Trump administration since its inception, leading to criminal charges against 34 people, including six former Trump associates and advisers.  A senior Justice Department official said the special counsel has not recommended any further indictments - a revelation that buoyed Trump's supporters, even as other Trump-related investigations continue in other parts of the Justice Department. It is also unclear whether a Mueller report that does not result in additional charges could still hurt the president politically.  Justice Department officials notified Congress late Friday that they had received Mueller's report, but they did not describe its contents. Barr is expected to summarize the findings for lawmakers as early as this weekend.  Only a small number of people inside the Justice Department know the document's contents, but it immediately sparked a furious political reaction, with Democrats vying for the presidential nomination in 2020 demanding a public release of the findings and the two top Democrats in Congress, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., calling for the full report and its "underlying documentation" to be provided to Congress.  Trump's supporters viewed the news as an optimistic indication that he was on the cusp of being vindicated.  "The fact that there are no more indictments is a big deal," said David Bossie, a Trump ally. "This president has had his entire two-year presidency under a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry at gym staff, man drives car through front window...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/angry-at-gym-staff-man-drives-car-through-front-window/article_15c05866-1010-5198-b368-88956f9b33e6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A motivational message on the gym’s wall reads: “Set some goals. Then demolish them.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE frees 'Dreamer' flight attendant who was locked up after Mexico flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2019/03/22/ice-locks-dreamer-flight-attendant-texas-am-grad-worked-flight-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flight attendant who grew up in Dallas is being held at an immigration center and faces deportation after she flew to Mexico for her job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC GRIPPED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/22/what-we-know-about-special-counsel-muellers-russia-probe-so-far.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separating fact from conjecture can be difficult amid the noise surrounding the investigation. Here's what we know since the probe began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MORE INDICTMENTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/mueller-report-released-russia-investigation-trump-campaign-election-live-updates-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel has submitted his findings into potential ties between the Kremlin and Trump campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER' head announces resignation...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/22/splc-richard-cohen-resigns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I take responsibility'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The invisible prosecutor who shook White House... </title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/robert-mueller-invisible-prosecutor-shook-white-house-220838817--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a prosecutor, Robert Mueller took on violent Hells Angels, mob bosses and foreign spies. At the end of his career, he was tasked with hunting the biggest quarry of all: the president of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full disclosure battle...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/mueller-submits-report-russia-investigation-221903445--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday submitted his long-awaited report into an explosive two-year investigation of Russian meddling in Donald Trump's 2016 election -- a probe the president denounces as a "witch hunt" and opponents say could fuel impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATION CONCLUDED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/99cb78f4c67b431b9f3823b06a89179b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday turned over his long-awaited final report on the contentious Russia investigation, ending a probe that has cast a dark shadow over Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLIC STILL IN DARK</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-robert-muellers-highly-anticipated-report-handed/story?id=61147281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's report was handed off to the DOJ and he won't recommend any further indictments, a senior DOJ official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN TO LEAKS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190322205621-rhggj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA (URGENT):Mueller sends Russia probe report to U.S. attorney general</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHERN POVERTY 'Highly Profitable Scam', Former Staffer Says...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/21/southern-poverty-law-center-scam-morris-dees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We were part of the con'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Mammoth, snow so deep residents must tunnel out...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-mammoth-snow-20190322-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record-setting snowfall in February has reconnected Mammoth residents to a historic rite of passage in California’s highest town — digging out and coping amid snow tunnels and narrow passageways. “You have to be careful," one resident said. "It’s eerie.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious Hollywood fixer Pellicano released from prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/notorious-hollywood-fixer-anthony-pellicano-released-from-prison-on-th/article_3e1f1af8-d63e-54ce-a5f1-3b0430e62f61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — It was one of the biggest scandals ever to hit Hollywood: a private investigator using wiretaps to secretly gather the secrets of celebrities and entertainment titans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silence Richly Rewarded By Elite...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/anthony-pellicano-prison-release-hollywood-wiretap-scandal-fund-donations-1202580483/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: When Anthony Pellicano walks out of a California prison tomorrow, the once notorious Hollywood P.I. will be welcomed by some of the biggest names in Hollywood with dual gifts of deep app…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory sector softens...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy/in-foreboding-sign-for-u-s-economy-factory-sector-softens-idUSKCN1R31Q6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. manufacturing activity unexpectedly cooled in March, a troubling sign for t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet Ministers War-Gaming Fall of Theresa May...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-22/u-k-cabinet-ministers-are-wargaming-the-fall-of-theresa-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California May Ban All Smartphones At Schools...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/03/22/smartphone-school-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California may ban all students from using smartphones at school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida woman livestreams suicide on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/22/florida-woman-livestreams-suicide-on-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 53-year-old Florida woman killed herself on Facebook Live — as viewers helplessly watched the disturbing footage unfold on their screens, authorities said. Merilee Joyce Turner of Cudjoe Ke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says he's suing opponents for libel over 'treason' claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-says-hes-suing-gantz-yaalon-for-libel-over-treason-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Facebook video, PM lays out 'the facts' of his ties to the submarine case and provides a timeline of his actions, says his opponents are engaged in 'wild incitement' and 'lies'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melting Mount Everest glaciers reveal dead climbers' bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/melting-mount-everest-glaciers-reveal-dead-climbers-bodies-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melting glaciers on Mount Everest are revealing the bodies of dead climbers, sparking concern from the organizers of expeditions to the famous peak, according to the BBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town halts treating water with fluoride amid concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/health/2019/03/22/ida-grove-iowa-halts-treating-water-fluoride-amid-concerns/3246249002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small town in northwestern Iowa has ended its decades-long practice of treating the city's drinking water with fluoride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA POSTS RECORD BUDGET DEFICIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/federal-budget-monthly-deficit-record-ecaf2f50-89a8-4124-bb9a-103b078a8933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The previous record was set in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mumps Spreading Through Philadelphia...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/03/22/mumps-cases-spreading-philadelphia-region-temple-university-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The school says they sent a letter out to parents and guardians Thursday after they were notified by the Montgomery County Office of Public Health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL star boycotting White House visit...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nhl/story/_/id/26332058/caps-g-holtby-declines-white-house-invitation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capitals goalie Braden Holtby says he won't attend the celebration at the White House on Monday for the 2018 Stanley Cup champions. "I have to stay true to my values," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate offers history of sexual conquests...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/hickenlooper-offers-something-different-in-crowded-democratic-field-a-detailed-history-of-his-sexual-conquests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Democratic voters are struggling to see what sets John Hickenlooper apart from the 2020 pack they need to look no further than his autobiography, which outlines in excruciating detail his quest to lose his virginity and, seemingly, every sexual exploit since.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Reporters staking out Mueller; Monitoring lunch, wardrobe...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/830641/mueller-skipping-lunch-dressing-down--reporters-staking-office-are-pumped</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller could wrap up his report any day now. Just ask a group of reporters who've been sitting outside his office for months. As an investigation into possible connections between President Trump's campaign and Russian election interference waged on, journalists â€” namely the so-called #CNNStakeout team â€” have kept an eye on the secretive man at its helm. While they haven't reported any collusion conclusions, they've practically mapped out Mueller's daily schedule â€” and in the last few days, it's seemingly been out of whack. Things started looking fishy last week when Andrew Weissmann, a top member of the Mueller squad, was reported to be headed to a new job. Weissmann even showed up wearing a tan suit, of all things, on Tuesday, while Mueller himself seemed to be dressing more casually, CNN's Evan PÃ©rez said. The obsessive coverage ratcheted up even further on Thursday, when CNN brought an extra-large media crew to Mueller's door, per CNN's Shimon Prokupecz, and caught something big: Mueller didn't leave his office for lunch, as he usually does. While reporters continued to gasp over those implications, CNN's Katelyn Polatz had a few more conclusive signs that something was afoot. As we anticipate the end of Mueller, signs of a wind-down:-SCO prosecutors bringing family into the office for visits-Staff carrying out boxes-Manafort sentenced, top prosecutor leaving-office of 16 attys down to 10-DC US Atty stepping up in cases-grand jury not seen in 2mo â€” Katelyn Polantz (@kpolantz) March 21, 2019 Even bigger news came on Friday: Mueller didn't seem to be in the office at all. Stay tuned to the stakeout feed to see if that means everything â€” or nothing at all. Kathryn Krawczyk Introducing the Mueller Stakeout Index (MSI) â€” a indicator of a potential Special Counsels report delivery. Moderately high reading this AM. pic.twitter.com/N70auw2HoB â€” HansNichols (@HansNichols) March 22, 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar Holding Secret Fundraisers With Islamic Groups Tied to Terror...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/omar-holding-secret-fundraisers-with-islamic-groups-tied-to-terror/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic freshman Rep. Ilhan Omar has been holding a series of secret fundraisers with several groups that have been tied to the support of terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frankfurt flights suspended over drone sightings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9751d99d90914da89bfa29ef065c245d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Flights to and from Frankfurt Airport were interrupted briefly Friday after a drone was seen in the area. Operator Fraport said takeoffs and landings at Germany's busiest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 20-Mile Line Swelled Into $9B Debacle...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-a-20-mile-train-line-swelled-into-a-9-billion-debacle-11553270393</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a project that has tallied one of America’s biggest transit cost overruns, Honolulu officials rushed construction of an elevated railroad before finishing key steps such as a check of native burial grounds, racking up huge delays and ballooning expenses. A grand jury is investigating the stumbles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS now selling CBD products...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/22/cvs-is-now-selling-cbd-products-in-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is among the eight states in which select CVS stores will sell topical products with CBD — such as “creams, sprays, roll-ons, lotions and salves.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police warn YOUTUBE stars after Berlin brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190322-german-police-warn-social-media-stars-after-berlin-brawl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police warn social media stars after Berlin brawl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rendell Sounds Alarm on Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/03/21/rendell_2020_went_from_slam_dunk_to_trouble_for_dems_aoc_does_not_speak_for_the_democratic_party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former DNC chairman Ed Rendell (D-PA) advised 2020 Democratic presidential candidates to look toward the center and not to the far left. "I think all of a sudden, the 2020 election went from a slam dunk for Democrats to something where we're going to have trouble beating this guy because he's going to make Democratic socialism swing to the left, which I don't think is real, but he's going to make it into the issue," the former governor told CNN on Thursday.  "AOC does not speak for the Democratic party," Rendell said of Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-NY) and her growing influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/florida/miami-beach/ocean-drive-party-gets-wild-in-south-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video shows a man punching a woman and knocking her down to the floor on Ocean Drive in South Beach. Another video shows a man driving on the MacArthur Causeway with an open bottle of alcohol and reaching out to a passenger in another car to pour some in her cup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 piglets on loose after crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksdk.com/article/news/local/nearly-3000-piglets-on-the-loose-after-crash-on-i-70-in-illinois/63-eb2c8585-a44e-4210-8b1e-fd1d01e4f742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksdk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Troopers urged drivers to be cautious while they corralled the livestock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS  START NEW SWINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/22/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-as-growth-concerns-persist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped on Friday as jitters over the global economy were sparked by dreadful manufacturing data out of Europe and the Federal Reserve's cautious outlook on the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance Companies May Use Social Media Posts To Determine Your Risk...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/03/21/online-posting-dangerous-selfies-insurance-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What insurance policy holders do in their daily lives may not be so private. If you're posting any information publicly online, your insurance company could be using it to determine your coverage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
