<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Australia cases hit new record as 'reopening' debate heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-victoria-reports-92-local-covid-19-cases-2021-08-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia logged a record 1,323 local COVID-19 cases on Sunday as debate rages on whether the country should start living with the virus in the community, after initially being successful with suppressing coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variant detected in S Africa, most mutated so far...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/new-covid-variant-detected-in-south-africa-most-mutated-variant-so-far-678011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The C.1.2 variant first detected in South Africa is more mutated compared to the original virus than any other known variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza after fire balloons, clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210829-israel-strikes-gaza-after-fire-balloons-border-clashes-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel strikes Gaza after fire balloons, border clashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban 'head of security' at airport linked to terror group...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3558724/talibans-head-security-kabul-airport-isis-k-helped-bomber/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT IS feared that the Taliban’s self-proclaimed head of security at Kabul airport has helped the bomber to cause the devastating explosion which killed at least 169 people. Al-Qaeda terrorist…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: YOUTUBEr creating spike in fake Tourette's symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2021/08/28/study-a-popular-youtuber-is-creating-a-spike-in-fake-tourettes-symptoms-among-adolescents-n412262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I came across this on Twitter this morning and found it pretty interesting. Four psychiatrists from Hannover Medical School (here&amp;#8217;s background on the lead author, Dr. Kirsten R. Müller-Vahl) pub...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will levees hold?</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_f24d728c-082a-11ec-b016-bfe6e434cefd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Ida could bring up to 15 feet of storm surge to parts of the west bank of Jefferson Parish, threatening to push water over the tops of the levees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vaporized' on a tuk-tuk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9936341/Two-ISIS-K-Kabul-bomb-plotters-killed-drone-strike-riding-tuk-tuk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The men, who were described as 'planners', are understood to have been sitting at the back of the moving three-wheeler when they were hit by a missile strike from a MQ-9 Reaper drone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX launches ants, avocados, robotic arm to space station...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/29/spacex-launches-ants-avocados-robotic-arm-to-international-space-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SpaceX shipment of ants, avocados, and a human-sized robotic arm rocketed toward the International Space Station on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuations From Kabul Wind Down as USA Prepares to Pull Troops...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/world/evacuations-from-kabul-wind-down-as-us-prepares-to-pull-last-troops-7476122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The troop departures signaled a tumultuous end to a 20-year war that has left the country awash in grief and desperation, with many Afghans fearing for their lives under Taliban rule and struggling with cash shortages and rising food prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says he will be killed, arrested or re-elected...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-58372754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's right-wing president is trying to rally support ahead of next year's election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German region plans crackdown on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210829083107-pnhkh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (PIX):German region plans tougher restrictions for unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Putin's Shadowy Army of Global Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-vladimir-putins-shadowy-army-of-global-spies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The untold story of how Vladimir Putin created his own foreign intelligence service to shore up his standing in post-Soviet Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why pigeons mean peril for satellite broadband...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-58061230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite internet is a key part of plans to fill broadband "not spots", but simple things can affect it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden in 'loneliest job'; Presidency driven by crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-d7a5461707d1b3d4ad6c78090b42e816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s called the loneliest job in the world for a reason. Surrounded by everything a superpower can offer and watched by all, President Joe Biden wore the weight of a lonely man as he came to grips in recent days with the deadly end of the American effort in Afghanistan and tried to keep the focus on what, to him, is the bottom line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the latest New Orleans, LA Local News, Sports News; US breaking News. View daily Louisiana weather updates, watch videos and photos, join the discussion in forums. Find more news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming embraces Jeffree Star despite homophobia, past...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/wyoming-embraces-jeffree-star-despite-homophobia-his-past/article_0e816afb-8ab5-58b4-9a2a-982e6358836e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CASPER, Wyo. (AP) — Jeffree Star is, inarguably, the biggest celebrity in Casper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f84ZBFuL1s4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medics reveal horror of 'talking dead' patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3560142/medics-reveal-talking-dead-covid-patients-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDICS have revealed the horror of “talking dead” Covid patients who are awake but can’t survive without machines. Things have become so dire in one Tallahassee hospital that staf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  STORM CHASER UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GmphOT-wHyg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=30.500:-94.000:22.000:-80.000&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://radar.weather.gov/?settings=v1_eyJhZ2VuZGEiOnsiaWQiOm51bGwsImNlbnRlciI6Wy05MC40NzQsMjkuODAyXSwiem9vbSI6N30sImFuaW1hdGluZyI6ZmFsc2UsImJhc2UiOiJzdGFuZGFyZCIsImNvdW50eSI6ZmFsc2UsImN3YSI6ZmFsc2UsInN0YXRlIjpmYWxzZSwibWVudSI6dHJ1ZSwic2hvcnRGdXNlZE9ubHkiOmZhbHNlLCJvcGFjaXR5Ijp7ImFsZXJ0cyI6MC44LCJsb2NhbCI6MC42LCJsb2NhbFN0YXRpb25zIjowLjgsIm5hdGlvbmFsIjowLjZ9fQ%3D%3D#/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radar.weather.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST IDA</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/us-gulf-coast-braces-hurricane-ida-after-cuba-takes-hit-2021-08-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Ida on Saturday intensified over warm Gulf of Mexico waters, prompting tens of thousands to flee coastal areas, while President Joe Biden pledged aid to help states quickly recover once the storm has passed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAPID INTENSIFICATION'</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/282051.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge fire erupts near  Camp Pendleton...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3559469/huge-fire-camp-pendleton-southern-california-smoke-marine-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE fire is currently blazing near the Marine Corps base in Camp Pendleton, Southern California as shocking pictures captured from nearby show gigantic plumes of smoke rising above the area. Twi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALERT FOR MORE ATTACKS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-new-attack-against-u-s-forces-kabul-highly-likely-n1277860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. retaliatory strike "was not the last," president says. "We will continue to hunt down any person involved in that heinous attack and make them pay."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=765&amp;initrange=29.750:-93.500:21.250:-79.500&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis statements about COVID death rate get renewed scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gov-ron-desantis-statements-about-florida-s-covid-death-rate-get-renewed-scrutiny/ar-AANQCMp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Multiple times during the COVID-19 pandemic, Gov. Ron DeSantis has pointed to a positive, but still tragic, metric: Florida’s death rate, which was long better than the national average. It was part of a message that the state under his leadership was faring better than most. Now, the delta-fueled surge in COVID cases has significantly increased Florida’s death rate. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Newsom went from landslide victory to fighting for political survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-gavin-newsom-went-from-landslide-victory-to-fighting-for-his-political-survival/ar-AANQy95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom said 'the future belongs to California' when he was elected. But the recall election puts his own future in doubt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Night Harassment Units' gathering on Gaza border...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/night-harassment-units-gathering-on-gaza-border-report-677983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gazan 'Night Harassment Units' began rioting on the border east of Gaza City starting at about 8 p.m. Saturday evening, after issuing a warning earlier in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On front lines of desperate battle to keep fire from hitting Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/on-the-front-lines-of-desperate-battle-to-keep-caldor-fire-from-hitting-lake-tahoe/article_55f7efb7-23de-585d-b657-807ee1bad01a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STRAWBERRY, Calif. — Heading west on Highway 50 from the tiny town of Strawberry was an exercise in blind faith Friday, as even the nearest of pine trees were obscured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq Eyes New Regional Role and Looks for Help to Rebuild...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iraq-eyes-regional-role-looks-095309898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Iraq’s regional allies stressed Saturday the need to provide support to an OPEC member struggling to rebuild after decades of ruinous wars, in a conference that also afforded a platform for meetings between longtime rivals.French President Emmanuel Macron, and his Egyptian counterpart attended the event, along with leaders and top diplomats from the United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Kuwait, Saudi Arabia and Jordan. They were also joined by Turkey’s foreign minister Mevlut Cavusoglu as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrants depart Mexico in caravan...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210828171710-1wo33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-IMMIGRATION/ (PIX):Hundreds of migrants depart southern Mexico in caravan to protest slow asylum process</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knocks oil output by 91%; More than Katrina...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/storm-cuts-u-s-gulf-of-mexico-oil-output-by-91-offshore-regulator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALERT FOR MORE ATTACKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-afghanistan-islamic-state-group-2f53babc274f912fa2c3a2a611aed07c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On alert for new terror attacks, the U.S. military has begun its final withdrawal from Afghanistan in the closing stages of a frantic airlift of Americans, Afghans and others desperate to escape Taliban rule before the evacuation shuts down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Boosters Within 5 Months?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/27/biden-says-us-health-officials-are-considering-covid-booster-shots-within-5-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data from Israel shows a booster dose provided four times as much protection against infection from the delta variant than the previous two-dose regimen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror leader told CNN before attack group was waiting to strike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/569832-isis-k-commander-told-cnn-before-kabul-attack-that-group-was-waiting-to-strike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ISIS-K commander said in a CNN interview conducted two weeks before the terrorist organization’s deadly bombing attack on Kabul’s airport Thursday that the group was waiting for a time to strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Deaths Hit Record; Younger Victims...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-deploys-medical-help-illinois-220130709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Florida reported 1,727 Covid-19 deaths in its latest weekly report, the most on record. A judge blocked Florida from enforcing Governor Ron DeSantis’s ban on mask mandates in schools, clearing the way for educators to require face coverings in classrooms without the threat of retaliation by the state.The origins of the coronavirus pandemic are still uncertain and a lack of cooperation from China is hampering the effort to ever know the truth, the U.S. Intelligence community said i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN STRIKES BACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-evacuations-kabul-islamic-state-group-7f146c8ae5d9e9ab225025527e421226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting swiftly on President Joe Biden's promise to retaliate for the deadly suicide bombing at Kabul airport, the U.S. military said it used a drone strike to kill a member of the Islamic State group's Afghanistan affiliate Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Predicts 100,000 More  Deaths in USA BEFORE Winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-deaths-100k-more-united-states-prediction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is in the grip of a fourth wave of infection this summer, powered by the highly contagious Delta variant, which has sent cases, hospitalizations and deaths soaring again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands in Germany protest restrictions on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/569843-thousands-of-german-protesters-gather-in-opposition-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters gathered in Berlin on Saturday to demonstrate against government leaders considering imposing additional coronavirus restrictions on unvaccinated individuals in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow docket' scrutiny at high court...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/analysis-bidens-supreme-court-losses-153205800.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's administration was dealt a double blow by the conservative-majority Supreme Court this week, raising new questions about how the justices handle cases brought via an emergency process known as the "shadow docket." The court in recent years has increasingly made substantive decisions on major issues via the shadow docket https://www.reuters.com/article/legal-us-usa-court-shadow-video/the-shadow-docket-how-the-u-s-supreme-court-quietly-dispatches-key-rulings-idUSKBN2BF16Q, deciding quickly and sometimes late at night in a process that critics from across the ideological spectrum say lacks transparency. The administration of Biden's Republican predecessor, President Donald Trump, did very well with the process, winning a wide majority of the cases it brought via emergency applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter punched in face while covering anti-mask event...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-6674fab5712fc37808a9fb08386fd8d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAVERSE CITY, Mich. (AP) — A newspaper reporter said he was punched in the face while covering an anti-mask event near Traverse City. The Grand Traverse County sheriff's office is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy family deeply divided over parole for RFK assassin Sirhan Sirhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-rfk-kids-rip-sirhan-sirhan-parole-20210828-dlbbhuey45fdhcqgwwhl6gmmny-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kennedy's kids are divided on the decision to grant parole to his killer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuations From Kabul Wind Down as USA Prepares to Pull Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/28/world/asia/afghanistan-evacuations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of thousands of Afghans are still thought to be seeking to flee the country, but President Biden and other global leaders have acknowledged that many will not get out before the deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Soldier's Afghan Pet Rescue Sparks Row Over Defense Role...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/british-soldier-s-afghan-pet-rescue-sparks-row-over-defense-role</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Soldier’s Afghan Pet Rescue Sparks Row Over Defense Role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands march on Washington in voting rights push...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569837-thousands-to-march-on-washington-in-voting-rights-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands are marching in Washington, D.C. and across the country on Saturday in a push to pass federal voting rights legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOUSANDS FLEE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210828160737-fu09y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. Gulf Coast residents flee 'extremely dangerous' Hurricane Ida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says drone strike killed two 'high profile' ISIS targets...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pentagon-two-isis-k-targets-strike-killed-afghanistan-c27cb5cc-d6b9-42cd-9d95-e54da5b473c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can confirm, two high profile targets were killed and one was wounded."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating apps turning to video and audio to link people up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/28/the-future-of-dating-apps-match-bumble-is-much-more-social.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has caused a level of disruption that's allowed companies to consider what a more-integrated future would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://cdn.star.nesdis.noaa.gov/GOES16/ABI/SECTOR/gm/13/20212400731-20212401201-GOES16-ABI-GM-13-1000x1000.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cdn.star.nesdis.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming embraces Jeffree Star despite homophobia, past...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-philanthropy-74a8d2c121e2a95f1653de597e24087b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CASPER, Wyo. (AP) — Jeffree Star is, inarguably, the biggest celebrity in Casper. The Youtuber-slash-makeup mogul first landed here in December, saying publicly he wanted to work on his autobiography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FALLEN HEROES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9935543/Father-fallen-Marine-says-chaotic-Kabul-airport-withdrawal-not-planned-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kareem Nikoui's father Steve told Fox News on Friday night that he was angry at the conditions the Marines were working in, calling the situation at Hamid Karzai International Airport a 'turkey shoot'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Ida intensifying, forecast to hit Louisiana as CAT 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/hurricane-ida-gulf-coast-landfall-louisiana-new-orleans/1007755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials warned residents that final preparations should be rushed to completion on Saturday as Hurricane Ida lurked in the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer 'Achilles' Heel' Discovered By Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cancers-achilles-heel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The enzyme, called CAIX (Carbonic Anhydrase IX), helps diseased cells spread to other organs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable MORGUES sent to state...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934991/Portable-MORGUES-sent-Florida-states-spiraling-Covid-cases-crematoriums-capacity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Central Florida Disaster Medical Coalition said each hospital system will be sent different amounts of portable morgues depending on the size of the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder private charity was bust, and questions swirl over where money went...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/larry-elders-private-charity-was-a-bust-and-questions-swirl-over-where-the-money-went/ar-AANPg8U </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice film fest returns with blockbuster lineup...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210828-venice-film-fest-returns-with-another-blockbuster-lineup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice film fest returns with another blockbuster lineup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Probes Deaths of Two Who Had MODERNA Shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japan-probes-two-deaths-jabs-101057799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan is investigating the death of two men who received jabs from batches of Moderna's Covid-19 vaccine suspended from use due to contamination, the health ministry said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight by Fight, Jake Paul Strikes for Credibility...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/28/fight-by-fight-jake-paul-strikes-for-credibility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jake Paul has not had a quiet moment to think. Between traveling to Miami to watch his older brother, Logan,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts warn of dangers from breach of voter system software...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-software-election-2020-1341028212960b9b4ed713620d764629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Republican efforts questioning the outcome of the 2020 presidential race have led to voting system breaches that election security experts say pose a heightened risk to future elections.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
