<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA deeply concerned...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-deeply-concerned-by-jerusalem-violence-urges-care-for-temple-mount-status-quo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department says it will continue contact with Israeli, Palestinian officials to deescalate tensions after 185 injured in police crackdown on Muslim rioting at Al-Aqsa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Kindness Strengthens Brain Health...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/15/kindness-cognitive-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing an act of kindness can make you feel good about yourself, and a new study suggests it also benefits the brains of everyone living under one roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF THE 'PINK MOON'</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/space-news/full-pink-moon-rises-saturday-night/1172232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pink Moon will be the main astronomical event in the evening skies this weekend, but some lucky stargazers could be treated to an added celestial bonus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol mulls rolling out hi-tech 'smart walls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10719113/Border-Patrol-talks-roll-hi-tech-smart-walls-detect-intruders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology company DarkPulse claims it has pitched its sophisticated fiber-optic 'smart wall' cables to Department of Homeland Security officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever Starts to Break in Boise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/housing-market-in-boise-idaho-starts-to-crack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing Market Fever Starts to Break in Boise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of conservative CCW event showing racist comments sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/3270390-video-of-las-vegas-conservative-ccw-event-showing-racist-comments-sparks-outrage-responses-from-attending-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (KLAS) — Racist comments made at a conservative political event are sparking outrage. The event, titled the “Vegas CCW” class, was held on Saturday, April 10, at a Las Vegas-Clark Library…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel's 'Great Comeback' Has Price: Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/travels-great-comeback-has-a-price-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arriving at London’s Gatwick Airport for his easyJet flight to Malaga, Spain, with his wife and 12-year-old daughter on April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky-High Pandemic Housing Market Finds Gravity Does Exist...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/the-sky-high-pandemic-housing-market-finds-gravity-does-exist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Solis, a real estate agent in Portland, Ore., marked a milestone weekend late last month. It was the first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Gamble Pivots to Very Different Battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/putins-ukraine-gamble-pivots-to-a-very-different-battlefield/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — There are fields instead of city streets, farmsteads instead of apartment buildings. Open highways stretch to the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 under evacuation orders as New Mexico wildfire rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wildfires-new-mexico-colorado-fires-evacuations-2a4b21f7d5632b010a2b84b4f63bbfc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Douglas Siddens’ mother was among those who made it out with just the clothes on her back when a deadly, wind-fueled wildfire ripped through a mountain community in southern New Mexico. The RV park where she lived was reduced to “metal frame rails and steel wheels,” said Siddens, who managed the site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden prepares for more clashes as far-right demos continue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sweden-europe-riots-b9c19932f7828bb8887ef69d10d568b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Police in Sweden say they are preparing for new violent clashes following riots that erupted between demonstrators and counter-protesters in the central city of Orebro on Friday ahead of an anti-Islam far-right group’s plan to burn a Quran there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War far from over as Kyiv strikes renewed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-kharkiv-moscow-0a9b737d09fec032affe3d9e5e82893a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces resumed scattered attacks on Kyiv, western Ukraine and beyond Saturday in an explosive reminder to Ukrainians and their Western supporters that the whole country remains under threat despite Russia’s pivot toward mounting a new offensive in the east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai's covid siege: Food shortages, talking robots, starving animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/shanghai-e2-80-99s-covid-siege-food-shortages-talking-robots-starving-animals/ar-AAWgba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities seek info after dolphin found impaled on Florida beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/health/authorities-seek-info-after-dolphin-found-impaled-on-florida-beach/article_d17a6427-28cc-5b1d-a3bd-b5cd71016228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are asking for the public’s health to find who was responsible after the body of a dolphin was found on a Florida beach that had been impaled with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER adopts 'poison pill' to thwart Elon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/15/twitter-board-adopts-poison-pill-after-musks-43-billion-offer-to-buy-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board voted unanimously to adopt the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinking of Russian warship offers Ukraine boost...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/3270399-sinking-of-russian-warship-offers-ukraine-a-morale-and-maybe-strategic-boost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sinking of Russia’s Moskva cruiser has dealt a major blow to the Kremlin’s fleet in the Black Sea and offered up a big public relations win to Ukrainian forces.  The warship — which sank Thursd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers explore unlikely treatment for cognitive disorders: Video games...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/04/15/1092804764/video-games-developed-to-treat-cognitive-disorders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video games distract, amuse, and inspire. But new research begs the question: can they heal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful space laser detected by S Africa telescope...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/world/space-laser-megamaser-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have detected a powerful radiowave laser, known as a megamaser, in space. This record-breaking megamaser is the most distant one ever observed at 5 billion light-years away from Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House restarting federal oil lease sales...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/15/white-house-restarting-federal-oil-gas-lease-sales-next-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes almost exactly 15 months after President Biden imposed a moratorium on such sales upon taking office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin dies after beachgoers in Texas try to ride it...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksby.com/news/national/dolphin-dies-after-beachgoers-in-texas-try-to-ride-it-rescue-group-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksby.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dolphin that was stranded on a Texas beach is now dead after a wildlife group said people tried to ride it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon hunts 'extremist or dissident ideologies'; 'Equity' plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pentagon-equity-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense issued an equity report, aiming to equalize outcomes of employees and partners across racial, sexual and gender lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freeze Koala Sperm to Save Species, Researchers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5qegq/koala-sperm-bank-extinction-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are working to find ways to save koalas, which have been devastated by droughts, deforestation, and bushfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZELENSKY:  Prepare for possibility he could use nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/politics/tapper-zelensky-interview-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky told CNN Friday that "all of the countries of the world" should be prepared for the possibility that Russian President Vladimir Putin could use tactical nuclear weapons in his war on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900 civilian bodies found...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-business-black-sea-22d7279f32c15d4a7037a2195113fb57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of more than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia's withdrawal — most of them fatally shot, police said Friday, an indication that many people were "simply executed.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Harris release tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-harris-release-2021-tax-returns-131472fc-c094-4c12-9ff9-db8eec2fc1b3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden and First Lady Jill Biden earned $610,702 in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warship sinks; Pentagon says new Ukraine missile responsible...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ukraine-sank-russias-cruiser-moskva-191621923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moskva made headlines in February after an apparent audio exchange between the vessel and Ukrainian border guards on Snake Island went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The face of NBA's China relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story?id=33723055&amp;_slug_=brooklyn-nets-owner-joe-tsai-face-nba-uneasy-china-relationship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two and a half years after buying the Nets, the billionaire personifies the compromises embedded in the NBA-China relationship, which requires the league to do business with an authoritarian government -- and play by its rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 arrested for dog theft during DC crime spree...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2022/04/7-arrested-in-connection-with-dog-theft-during-dc-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people are in custody in connection the theft of two dogs during a string of robberies earlier this week across the District, police said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did HARVARD Go After One of Best Black Professors?</title>
      <link>https://quillette.com/2022/04/15/why-did-harvard-university-go-after-one-of-its-best-black-professors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;quillette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roland Fryer Jr.’s life is a movie script: A man abandoned by his mom and raised by an alcoholic dad became the youngest black professor to ever secure tenure at Harvard University. After ascending to the academic elite, Fryer didn’t resign himself to irrelevant technical puzzles; he put</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans doc who helps teens transition says now 'gone too far'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/15/transitions-have-gone-too-far-trans-psychologist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender psychologist fears many are making life-changing decisions because it’s “trendy” and pushed on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's pollster on how to 'not get a** kicked' in midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/15/bidens-pollster-midterms-00025482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this week’s episode of Playbook Deep Dive, Ryan Lizza joins John Anzalone, who is best known as President Biden’s pollster, but is also a top adviser to Nevada Gov. Steve Sisolak, who is up for reelection this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight from big cities INCREASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10722017/Record-32-homebuyers-fleeing-coastal-cities-like-San-Francisco-LA-Seattle-Boston.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Redfin, a real-estate brokerage, said 32.3 percent of users were looking to move to a different area in the first quarter of 2022, up from 31.5 percent a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxes too high? Lots of Californians think so...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Taxes-too-high-A-lot-of-Californians-think-so-17083064.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With April 15, the traditional tax day, upon us, a new California poll shows that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save energy and annoy Vlad, Vice-Chancellor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61117828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice-chancellor says they should use bikes and lower the thermostat to use less Russian gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental illness may raise risk of breakthrough virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/3269827-mental-illness-may-raise-risk-of-breakthrough-covid-19-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Story at a glance Researchers at the University of California, San Francisco looked at data from 263,697 U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs patients who had completed their vaccines and had at lea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How BARNES &amp; NOBLE Went From Villain to Hero...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/how-barnes-noble-went-from-villain-to-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years on the decline, Barnes &amp; Noble’s sales are up, its costs are down — and the same people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns USA against sending more arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-warns-us-arming-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diplomatic note used the same type of language Moscow has been offering for some time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penthouses in NKorea mainly for the unfortunate few...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiaone.com/asia/north-korea-penthouses-are-mainly-unfortunate-few</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiaone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL - For people in many countries, living in a penthouse is the dream. In North Korea? Not so much. Leader Kim Jong Un keeps building outwardly glamorous high-rise apartment buildings in the capital, Pyongyang, with the latest being an 80-storey skyscraper completed this week. But defectors and other North Koreans say that unreliable elevators and electricity, poor water supply,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Lee privately trashed 'my friend' Ted Cruz in texts to Mark Meadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mike-lee-privately-trashed-my-friend-ted-cruz-s-efforts-to-overturn-the-election-in-texts-to-mark-meadows/ar-AAWgcTg?cvid=e243d1bd1c9d447bbcfe1f9c17e327c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adopts 'poison pill' measure to thwart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/tech/twitter-elon-musk-poison-pill/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter's board of directors has adopted a limited-term shareholder rights plan called a "poison pill" that could make it harder for Elon Musk to acquire the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow sends Washington formal diplomatic note...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2022/apr/15/joe-biden-russia-ukraine-putin-us-politics-live-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow sends Washington ‘formal diplomatic note’ as Psaki says Biden is not planning to go to Ukraine – follow the day’s news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troop losses hit 20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/5131995/video-ukrainian-vehicle-destroys-russian-tank-donetsk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the astonishing moment a Ukrainian armoured vehicle bravely takes on a vastly more powerful Russian tank in a ferocious firefight – and WINS. The astounding video filmed from a drone …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male porn star 'Sergeant Miles' arrested over Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5130739/porn-star-sergeant-miles-steven-capitol-riot-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PORN star and Iraq war veteran has blasted what he calls a “political witch hunt” after his arrest over the Capitol riot. Steven Miles – known by his stage name Sergeant Miles &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee wins $450K in lawsuit over unwanted birthday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/nation-world/national/article260445977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He told his Kentucky company he did not want a birthday celebration, but they arranged one anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden shakes hands with thin air after North Carolina speech...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/14/biden-shakes-hands-with-thin-air-after-north-carolina-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden was left empty-handed following an address at a North Carolina university Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PUTIN HUMILIATION...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lost-warship-dents-russian-pride-150116721.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's loss of its flagship cruiser Moskva represents a dent in the operational capabilities of the Russian navy and a severe wound to Russian pride at the height of the war against Ukraine, analysts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE TV DECLARES WW3 'HAS ALREADY BEGUN'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/04/15/ukraine-russian-state-tv-warns-world-war-three-has-already-begun-16472787/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin has denied the ship was sunk by Ukraine's military but its propagandists are in meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai's covid siege: Food shortages, talking robots, starving animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/interactive/2022/china-shanghai-covid-lockdown-food-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than three weeks, China’s most populous city, Shanghai, has been under strict lockdown orders in an effort to control a coronavirus outbreak, leaving its 25 million residents trapped at home, struggling to feed themselves or get medical help for sick family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia finds sympathy in Germany's east...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2022/04/15/germany-ukraine-communist-east-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Berlin faces calls to step up its support for Ukraine, attitudes in Saxony show competing pressures on German leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS POLICE VICIOUS IN SHANGHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10721527/Shanghai-rises-against-Communist-Covid-chaos-residents-scuffle-hazmat-suited-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in Shanghai have scuffled with hazmat-suited police who have ordered them to give up their homes to Covid patients, videos on social media show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK VS HOUSE OF SAUD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-has-a-secret-code-to-silence-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire and one of the powerful Saudi princes are opponents in the fight for control of Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER TRAVEL CHAOS: Atlanta Airport terminal evacuated over 'bomb threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5132233/bomb-scare-hartsfield-jackson-airport-atlanta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN airport has been evacuated after a reported bomb threat caused travel chaos for travelers on Easter weekend. Law enforcement quickly evacuated Hartfield Jackson International Airport’s sou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER TWITTER FATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/14/elon-musk-not-sure-hell-be-able-to-buy-twitter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's comments came hours after a regulatory filing revealed that he offered to acquire Twitter for $54.20 per share, or about $43 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's Black Sea flagship sinks in latest setback...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-black-sea-estonia-8ccaa918f813a844321187ed116ff091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The flagship of Russia's Black Sea fleet, a guided-missile cruiser that became a potent target of Ukrainian defiance in the opening days of the war, sank Thursday after it was heavily damaged in the latest setback for Moscow's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid false 2020 claims, Republican states eye voting system upgrade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-business-voting-campaign-2016-87e5516c1960c1eb0027e8d7c490b811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — For years, Tennessee Democratic Senate Minority Leader Jeff Yarbro’s call to require the state’s voting infrastructure to include a paper record of each ballot cast has been batted down in the Republican-dominated Legislature.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
