<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Changing weather prompts more fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Changing-weather-prompts-more-fire-fears-in-15508114.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) - An unwelcome change in the weather, with higher winds, temperatures and lightning that threatens to spark new wildfires was coming Sunday to parched Northern California, where firefighters have for nearly a week battled three huge "complexes" of fires that have destroyed hundreds of homes and forced tens of thousands to flee.  Firefighters made slow but hopeful progress in battling the blazes on Saturday, aided by good weather but hampered by smoky skies that grounded water-dropping aircraft for some of the day. Reinforcements arrived to bolster overwhelmed crews, and evacuation orders were lifted in some areas.  But the changing weather brought fears of new fires overnight and warnings from state and local officials for residents in threatened areas to prepare to flee at any moment.  "There's not a feeling of pure optimism, but a feeling of resolve, a feeling of we have resources backing us up," Sonoma County Supervisor James Gore said.  Since Aug. 15, state fire officials said more than 12,000 lightning strikes across the state have ignited more than 500 wildfires. Of those, about two dozen major fires were attracting most of the state's resources. Most of the damage was caused by three clusters of fire "complexes" that were ravaging forest and rural areas in and around the San Francisco Bay Area. They have burned 1,120 square miles (2,900 square kilometers).  Among the casualties were ancient redwood trees at California's oldest state park, Big Basin Redwoods, plus the park's headquarters and campgrounds. Smoke from the fires made the region's air quality dangerous, forcing people to stay inside.  Overall, the fires have killed five people, torched nearly 700 homes and other structures and forced tens of thousands from their houses.  "Tuesday night when I went to bed I had a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  Claudia  blasts 'selfish' mom; Says White House job 'about money and fame'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1354480/claudia-conway-selfish-mom-kellyanne-money-fame-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KELLYANNE Conway’s daughter Claudia launched a scathing attack on her “selfish” mom for “watching her kids suffer” because of her job. Claudia Conway – the daugh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge brawl erupts as Proud Boys and Antifa fight with bats in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1354432/portland-brawl-breaks-out-proud-boys-antifa-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND descended into violent chaos once again as a huge brawl erupted between hundreds of Proud Boys and Antifa protesters on Saturday. Shocking footage shows the rightwing militia wearing param…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE BATMAN':  First trailer of dark, violent reboot... </title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/the-batman-trailer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See the first footage of dark, gritty reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt masked suspect accused of giving strangers 'covid hugs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1353388/police-hunt-masked-suspect-strangers-covid-hugs-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPS are hunting for a covidiot said to be giving strangers hugs and telling them “you now have COVID” in a Massachusetts Walmart.  “He told the victim, ‘Just giving you a COVID hug.  You now have …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans look to convention for campaign reboot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-looks-to-republican-convention-for-optimistic-campaign-reboot/ar-BB18gpsM?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail-in ballots were part of a plot to deny Lincoln reelection in 1864...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Mail-in-ballots-were-part-of-a-plot-to-deny-15507606.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traveling to Baltimore in the fall of 1864, Orville Wood had no way of knowing he would soon uncover the most elaborate election conspiracy in America's brief history.  Wood was a merchant from Clinton County in the most northeastern corner of New York. As a supporter of President Abraham Lincoln, he was tasked with visiting troops from his hometown to "look after the local ticket."  New York legislators had only established the state's mail-in voting system in April with the intent of ensuring the suffrage of White troops battling the Confederate Army.  The results of the 1864 elections would heavily affect the outcome of the war. Lincoln and his supporters in the National Union Party sought to continue the war and defeat the Confederacy outright. Meanwhile antiwar Democrats, also referred to as Copperheads, looked for an immediate compromise with the Confederate leaders and the end of the abolition movement.  Troops from New York were allowed to authorize individuals back home to cast a vote on their behalf. Along with their mail-in ballots, troops would assign their power of attorney on slips that required four signatures: the voter's, the person authorized as a recipient, a witness to the signed affidavit and a fellow officer. These documents would be sealed in an envelope and shipped back home to be counted in the final vote. This was the process that Orville Wood intended to uphold, he would testify in court later. He quickly found out what a challenge that would be.  Wood arrived at Fort McHenry in Baltimore to visit with the 91st New York Regiment. There, an Army captain suggested that there had been some "checker playing" when it came to the gathering of soldiers' mail-in ballots. These suspicions of fraud were echoed when Wood visited wounded men at the Newton University Hospital. The rumors of wrongdoing led...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis couple charged with waving guns at protesters have long history of not backing down...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/metro/the-st-louis-couple-charged-with-waving-guns-at-protesters-have-a-long-history-of/article_281d9989-373e-53c3-abcb-ecd0225dd287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark McCloskey is almost always in conflict with somebody, typically over control of private property, what people can do on that property, and whose job it is to make sure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT PRESSURES FDA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-pressures-the-fda-claiming-deep-state-slowing-vaccine/ar-BB18fVmT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44 and 45 agreed on one thing in dueling PA visits: Win, or it's apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/election/barack-obama-donald-trump-joe-biden-pennsylvania-20200822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twin Pennsylvania speeches by Trump and Obama show how both parties see this election as an existential fight — and raise questions about how the country will move forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health insurance companies post record earnings amid covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/coronavirus-health-care-legislation-dr-nicole-saphier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our country cannot afford to financially hurt our medical service providers any further with the proposed out-of-network legislation if we want them to stay in business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could hurricanes collide?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/marco-laura-approach-us-packing-double-threat-to-gulf-coast/798759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye Campaign Unraveling; Booted from Ballot in 5 States...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/08/kanye-wests-campaign-is-both-proceeding-and-unraveling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several electors submitted by West’s campaign in Virginia were shocked and dismayed to learn they had signed up to be electors for the rapper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Puerto Rico braces for storm, the earth shakes again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/puerto-rican-town-gu-nica-211342867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Morales was washing dishes in her home in the Puerto Rican municipality of Guánica Saturday morning when the earth began to tremble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus overshadows Trump's legacy in office...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-overshadows-trumps-legacy-office-151846524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Win or lose in November, President Trump already has a legacy of domestic deregulation and global disruption. But his botched response to a deadly pandemic and a deep recession overshadow the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro says Venezuela buying Iranian missiles 'a good idea'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822224540-fbo6k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-IRAN/:Maduro says Venezuela buying Iranian missiles 'a good idea'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy tops 1,000 daily cases for first time since May...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822153530-jkumt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Italy tops 1,000 daily coronavirus cases for first time since May</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German scientists stage concert experiment...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822143027-nqj9g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TEST-CONCERT (TV):How big gatherings spread COVID-19: German scientists stage concert experiment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires burn 1 million acres in California...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9995e3a7bcb32aa9cf0fca3de005896b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Firefighters in California were racing to slow the spread of wildfires that burned nearly one million acres in a week and destroyed hundreds of homes as weekend weather...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belarus blocks over 50 news websites but protests continue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d92cfccbc7cbed1aaab40fd6f0b6e0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINSK, Belarus (AP) — Authorities in Belarus blocked more than 50 news media websites that were covering weeks of protests demanding that authoritarian President Alexander Lukashenko resign but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see racism in mispronunciations of 'Kamala'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d48d55b29bfde0effa345a0e6509593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Bantering during the final night of the Democratic National Convention, actor Julia Louis-Dreyfus and former presidential candidate Andrew Yang repeatedly got the name of “our...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 FREAKOUT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5b5aa6f02afb3fb562f932eb70d749ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — Two tropical storms advanced across the Caribbean on Saturday as potentially historic threats to the U.S. Gulf Coast, one dumping rain on Puerto Rico and the Virgin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes Postal Service bill as data confirms delays...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e2fcd6f1457cd1ddc3d8f85e9548cc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With heated debate over mail delays, the House approved legislation in a rare Saturday session that would reverse recent changes in U.S. Postal Service operations and send $25...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Merchandise Bundles Undid the Album Chart...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/22/how-merchandise-bundles-undid-the-album-chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately half the albums that have topped the Billboard album chart since the beginning of 2019 have been made available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does coronavirus spread at concert? Germans do test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc8833d2fcd394b6e1881ce63eb85476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany held a pop concert Saturday to see how those attending would spread coronavirus. German researchers studying COVID-19 packed part of a Leipzig arena with volunteers,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine That's Injected During Arrests Draws New Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/ketamine-thats-injected-during-arrests-170803241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police stopped Elijah McClain on the street in suburban Denver last year after deeming the young Black man suspicious. Paramedics inject it into people like McClain as a sedative, often at the behest of police who believe suspects are out of control. Officially, ketamine is used in emergencies when there’s a safety concern for medical staff or the patient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galapagos Islands threatened by huge Chinese fishing fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/charles-darwins-famous-galapagos-islands-22562406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Scientists fear the 325-strong flotilla with vessels the size of a football pitch has put endangered species at further risk in the waters around the Galapagos Islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Self-Destructive Syndrome'?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/512604-does-trump-suffer-from-self-destructive-syndrome</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is intelligent and has good instincts, but even die-hard supporters wish he would speak and act presidential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New study reveals appliance that may be spreading...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/22/air-conditioned-rooms-help-spread-covid-19-research-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dry air and air-conditioned rooms can help spread the coronavirus, according to an Indian-German research team that looked at the role of relative humidity in the transmission of infections. For of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE SLAVE MONKEYS OF THAILAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/12444192/monkey-slave-schools-coconuts-supermarket-thailand-sex-street-performers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNATCHED from his mother as a baby, chained up alone and forced to work at a coconut farm for ten hours a day, all little Kulap knows is suffering. The pig-tailed macaque is one of thousands of mon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'DEEP STATE' DELAYING VAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1352011/trump-fda-deep-state-drug-administration-vaccine-after-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has called the FDA part of the “deep state” and accused the drug administration of slow-walking vaccine test until after the election. The president made the conspiracy com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders president to pay legal fees to Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/513212-judge-orders-trump-to-pay-legal-fees-to-stormy-daniels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California court ordered President Trump to pay $44,100 to Stephanie Clifford, the adult-film actress known as Stormy Daniels, to cover her legal fees regarding her nondisclosure agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could hurricanes collide?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/08/22/tropical-storms-laura-marco-collide-fujiwhara-effect-explained/3410073001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storms Laura and Marco are forecast to be in the Gulf of Mexico at the same time. So, could they form a super hurricane? We explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Barr pushed to 'muzzle' FOXNEWS Judge Nap...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/aug/22/william-barr-rupert-murdoch-muzzle-andrew-napolitano-fox-news-trump-critic-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney general met media mogul in October 2019, as Judge Andrew Napolitano said Trump should be impeached</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Dems chase generational change from opposite corners of movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Mass-two-Democrats-chase-generational-change-15507162.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Morse and Joe Kennedy both want to turn the page to a new generation of Democrats, suggesting that entrenched incumbents sometimes just tend to coast.  Who should have the real clout on Capitol Hill?  "It's not those members of Congress who have been there 30 or 40 years," Morse, 31, said Friday in a telephone interview.  "I am running against somebody who's been in elective office in Massachusetts for 47 years," Rep. Kennedy, 39, said Thursday, rattling off the extent of his opponent's career in politics. "I think by all accounts, he was pretty much a figure of the political establishment."  Morse, the four-term mayor of Holyoke in western Massachusetts, is trying to unseat Democratic Rep. Richard Neal, a 30-year incumbent who chairs the powerful House Ways and Means Committee in the state's Sept. 1 Democratic primary. And Kennedy, a four-term member of the House from outside Boston, is running against Democratic Sen. Edward Markey, whose first congressional oath of office in 1977 took place before Kennedy was born.  Yet Morse and Kennedy find themselves in opposite corners of today's Democratic moment, a political interchange that is confusing with its mixed paths of generational challenges and ideological purity tests.  Morse has the full backing of the liberal groups that have helped knock off a handful of veteran Democratic incumbents in the past two years, paving the way to Congress for a younger, more diverse array of lawmakers. Most of the same groups have rallied behind Markey, despite his being a 74-year-old White man, after he forged an ideological alliance with Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., whose upset primary win in June 2018 served as a bolt of lightning for these far-left liberals.  That's left Kennedy running defensively at times, as if he is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hamptons, party hosts pay for rapid tests at door...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/22/us/hamptons-parties-coronavirus-tests-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Asma Rashid goes to a lot of exclusive parties these days -- but for a different reason. In the Hamptons, hosts pay big bucks for her to administer rapid coronavirus test to guests at the door before they can attend social events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says FDA Slowing Virus Research to Hurt Him in Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-says-fda-slowing-virus-research-to-hurt-him-in-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Says FDA Slowing Virus Research to Hurt Him in Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters 'running on fumes,' begging for equipment, manpower amid firestorms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/firefighters-running-fumes-bay-area-120052932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Cruz fire agencies say they are not getting enough help from the state, which admits it is struggling with too many fires and not enough resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid to pass close to Earth day before presidential election...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/trending/asteroid-predicted-pass-close-earth-day-before-presidential-election/7NTEFU5YVVGFXMGT3ADBXNZ7BQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An asteroid discovered in 2018 will fly very close to Earth on Nov. 2 according to The Center for Near Earth Objects Studies at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTIST WARNS CORONAVIRUS WILL BE 'WITH US FOREVER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/coronavirus-uk-pandemic-end-vaccine-flu-ongoing-mark-walport-a9683246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears Going Extinct in Stock Market's $13 Trillion Rebound...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bears-going-extinct-stock-market-201228099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Skeptics are a dying breed in American equities. It’s another illustration of how risky it has become to doubt the resilience of the market’s $13 trillion surge since late March.Going by the short positions of hedge funds, resistance to rising prices is the lowest in 16 years. Bears pulled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy Land 'on brink of war' as doomsday preacher says Bible prophecy 'happening'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/holy-land-on-brink-war-22555929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel has warned Hamas 'if they want war they will get war' and evangelical YouTube sensation Pastor Paul Begley says any more conflict would be the ultimate battle for the 'Holy Land'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customer vows to 'never date again'; AI replicant 'perfect'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-customer-vows-never-22554231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Author and documentary-maker Jenny Kleeman has talked Daily Star Online through the extracts of her new book Sex Robots &amp; Vegan Meat, released this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home sales spike record 24.7% as prices set new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/21/july-home-sales-spike-a-record-24point7percent-as-prices-set-a-new-high.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of existing homes soared 24.7% in July from June, according to the National Association of Realtors. The median price of a home sold in July rose 8.5% annually to $304,100.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rotting food, dead animals and chaos at  facilities amid cutbacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/armageddon-rotting-food-dead-animals-180715834.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounts from employees at California postal facilities provide a glimpse of the chaos amid both the pandemic and widespread cuts imposed by the USPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 scary? Japan offers coffins, chainsaws for stress relief...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822071916-ncbqw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-COFFINS (TV, PIX):COVID-19 scary? Japan group offers coffins, chainsaws for stress relief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderate Tulsa mayor faces fierce political crosscurrents...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e03160a401e9e342265c501142c88ac5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By all accounts, Tulsa Mayor G.T. Bynum has been a fast-rising political star in Oklahoma. Part of a political dynasty whose uncle, grandfather and great-grandfather all served as mayor of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston hit by both?</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/weather/marco-and-laura-headed-in-to-gulf-texas-impacts-possible/39346/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tracks on both storms are still wide and uncertain, as Houston's weather is perfect for prepping your home and family for next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRIVING THROUGH HELL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8653015/Dashcam-captures-terrifying-drive-California-wildfires-killed-six.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying footage (left) shows cars driving through the raging flames of the Hennessey Fire in Napa County Friday, as California continues to be at the peril of 560 fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush Comeback Tactics From 1988 Echo in Race...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/22/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-trump-how-bush-mounted-a-comeback-in-1988/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George H.W. Bush was in trouble. It was July 1988 and Michael Dukakis, the Democratic candidate for president, was on</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
