<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER STOCK TANKS ON DECLINING USERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/business/article/As-Twitter-deals-with-many-woes-user-numbers-13111112.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter might have packed in more characters per tweet — but the move hasn’t helped it assemble more users. In its second-quarter earnings report, the company announced it had 355 million monthly active users, down 1 million from the first quarter. Wall Street closely watches Twitter’s user count as a proxy for the health of the company. Twitter shares dropped 20.5 percent to $34.12 Friday, wiping $6.6 billion off its value. While not as momentous as Facebook’s historic $119 billion loss in market capitalization following an earnings report that showed a slowdown in user growth, it’s the largest drop Twitter’s stock has seen in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUSPICIOUS PACKAGES' FOUND AT TRUMP TOWER...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYPD-Investigating-Suspicious-Packages-Trump-Tower-New-York-City-489381241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD bomb squad is investigating several suspicious packages left outside of Trump Tower on Friday afternoon, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROADCAST ROW ROCKED...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/27/les-moonves-accused-of-sexual-misconduct-by-6-women-in-bombshell-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS chief has been accused of sexual misconduct by six women, including actress Illeana Douglas, in a bombshell new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forcible touching and kissing during business meetings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27bd1ce961f94077bcdc17f36bc47fd8/CBS-looks-into-misconduct-claims-amid-report-on-CEO-Moonves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CBS said Friday it is investigating personal misconduct claims after the company's chief executive, Les Moonves, was the subject of a New Yorker story detailing se</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying tornados of flame...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/arson-wildfire-forces-entire-california-063907460.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — A wildfire that roared with little warning into a Northern California city claimed two lives as thousands of people scrambled to escape before the walls of flames descended from forested hills onto their neighborhoods, officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: CEO To Stay On Job During Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/les-moonves-to-stay-on-the-job-new-yorker-ronan-farrow-cbs-investigation-sexual-misconduct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS CEO Les Moonves plans to stay on the job during CBS's investigation of a Ronan Farrow New Yorker story, an insider says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude sunbathers stunned as migrants storm beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6881644/costa-del-sol-nudist-beach-migrants-north-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the dramatic moment dozens of migrants stormed a Spanish holiday beach popular with Brits today – leaving naked sunbathers stunned. The migrants landed on the shore of Del Canuelo bea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW STRIKES AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2018/08/06/les-moonves-and-cbs-face-allegations-of-sexual-misconduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six women accuse the C.E.O. of harassment and intimidation, and dozens more describe abuse at his company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkey herds dwindle as hungry Venezuelans slaughter for food...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article215644840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burro, or donkey, herds have nearly disappeared in one section of Venezuela as thousands were slaughtered for their meat by hungry Venezuelans suffering through a near-famine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RESILIENT SURVIVOR' ON HOT SEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/leslie-moonves-accused-by-six-women-sexual-misconduct-new-yorker-expos-1085436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I recognize that there were times decades ago when I may have made some women uncomfortable by making advances," admitted the network chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian-spy hookers eye tech big shots at 'cougar nights?'</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/07/27/are-russian-spy-hookers-targeting-tech-leaders-and-vcs-at-infamous-silicon-valley-cougar-nights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The region is crawling with Chinese and Russian spies amid an ‘epidemic’ of espionage, report says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LES: Times when I may have made women uncomfortable by making advances...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/leslie-moonves-sexual-misconduct-new-yorker-ronan-farrow-1202888614/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS chairman-CEO Leslie Moonves has been accused of sexual misconduct by six women, including actress Illeana Douglas, who asserts that Moonves had her fired from a comedy pilot after she rebuffed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISCONDUCT EXTENDED TO OTHER DIVISIONS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/cbs-ceo-les-moonves-sexual-harassment-allegations-1202435122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS chairman and CEO Leslie Moonves is being accused of sexual misconduct by six women in a much-anticipated exposé by New Yorker magazine. Investigative reporter Ronan Farrow interviewed six women…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social, Search Giants Face UK Tax To Fund 'Fake' Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/facebook-twitter-google-face-tech-145524484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Twitter and Google are facing the threat of new taxes to help fund a crackdown on a tide of fake news and misinformation which is poisoning British democracy, according to MPs. A damning report from the Digital Culture Media and Sport Select Committee proposed that Facebook and other social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury developers tout 'mindful mansions' to curb stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/luxury-homes-that-promise-to-reduce-stressfor-4-million-1524146400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury developers are touting wellness real estate, offering private and communal spaces for meditation and yoga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female teacher describes painful year after cleared of sex charges with male student...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/07/26/former-kennebunk-teacher-pressed-by-prosecutor-in-sexual-assault-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After deliberating two hours, a York County jury acquits 30-year-old Jill Lamontagne of 14 charges of sexual misconduct involving a former Kennebunk High student who was 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Special Counsel Witnesses Against Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/special-counsel-releases-witness-list-for-manafort-trial-00fea585-3272-4720-9c08-b9c622087bed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It includes 35 people who could testify against Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronan Farrow Urges Patience...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/RonanFarrow/status/1022934331235463168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A quick reminder that I don’t comment on reporting I haven’t published, and if you’re reading about my work from secondary sources you’re often not getting the full or correct story—especially in cases where parties have an interest in downplaying or otherwise spinning.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 60, NASA shoots for revival of moon glory days...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180727-60-nasa-shoots-revival-moon-glory-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posh dog food linked to heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/27/posh-grain-free-dog-food-may-linked-heart-disease-vets-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gourmet dishes with bison, sweet potato and chickpeas may seem like the perfect way for loving dog owners to treat their pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 4 In 10 Men Experience 'Inexplicable Sadness' After Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-pcd-men-experienced-sadness-after-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having sex may feel like a badge of honor for many men, but for others, it's an act that, once finished, brings about intense feelings of sadness thanks to a condition known as PCD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal housing chief investigated for sex harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/27/federal-housing-chief-sexual-harassment-investigation-714779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage regulator taped making suggestive comments to employee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Flag Found Intact In Rubble Of Veteran's Home...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/27/carr-fire-flag-saved/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Carr Fire is now 44,450 acres and only 3% contained as of 9:17 am Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller defensive after airport pic with Don Jr...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/27/mueller-trump-jr-photographed-waiting-in-same-dc-airport-terminal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One flight out of D.C. certainly brought awkward to new heights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 firefighters dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/27/carr-fire-update-more-overnight-evacuations-as-wildfire-in-redding-area-moves-quickly-and-erratically/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early Friday, Redding police issued mandatory evacuation orders for neighborhoods in the western part of the city of 91,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forces on-air evacuation of TV anchor...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/News/california-fire-forces-air-evacuation-tv-anchor-ive/story?id=56862145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tamara Damante, an anchor at ABC affiliate KRCR in Redding, California, was forced to evacuate the news station as she reported on the Carr Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Whale-Dolphin Hybrid Discovered Off Hawaii...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/27/whale-dolphin-hybrid-hawaii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the researchers discovered was a hybrid of a melon-headed whale and a rough-toothed dolphin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ART OF THE SQUEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-debuts-the-art-of-the-squeal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tape Trump’s former would-be fixer has shared with the public seems to underscore the absence of a tape he’d need to cut a deal with his prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist Gets Locked Inside Historic NYC Fortress...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/26/tourist-accidentally-gets-locked-in-old-governors-island-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A curious tourist accidentally took a trip back to 1865 when she wandered into a century-old fortress and former prison on Governors Island — and got locked inside. Shakira Stover, 35, who is Ameri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Work Advocates Interrupt Bill Clinton Speech...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/protesters-interrupt-bill-clinton-speech-demanding-decriminalization-of-sex-workers-worldwide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norman Lear SONY Deal...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/norman-lear-all-in-the-family-the-jeffersons-good-times-maude-and-mary-hartman-mary-hartman-reboots-first-look-deal-with-sony-pictures-tv-1202434917/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norman Lear continues to defy convention about career longevity and age. The TV icon, who today celebrates his 96th birthday, and his Act III production company have signed a two-year first look de…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADHD kids? Get rid of sugar, add yoga...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/living/health-fitness/article214584480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technologies built around brain waves are helping kids with ADHD to focus and sharpen their concentration. Also helping to calm the mind: yoga, meditation and getting rid of added sugar and processed foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADMITS TO 'SHADOW BANNING' REPUBLICANS?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/blog/twitters-statement-dont-shadow-ban-kinda-sounds-like-shadow-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a Twitter use is de facto banned from joining the conversation and isn't informed of that fact, "shadow ban" seems like a perfectly fine shorthand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli forces raid al-Aqsa mosque after clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israeli-forces-raid-al-aqsa-mosque-clashes-171824661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Sinan Abu Maizar and Nidal al-Mughrabi JERUSALEM/GAZA (Reuters) - Israeli troopers entered Jerusalem's al-Aqsa mosque, the third-holiest shrine in Islam, and carried out arrests on Friday in what police described as a pursuit of youths who had lobbed rocks and fireworks during clashes with its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHILLY SHUNS ICE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/228bf1d2d1394578b039707a8a08a977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Philadelphia will stop sharing real-time arrest data with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement.        Democratic Mayor Jim Kenney announced Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican meets #MeToo: Nuns denounce their abuse by priests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f7ec3cec9a4b46868aa584fe1c94fb28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The nun no longer goes to confession regularly, after an Italian priest forced himself on her while she was at her most vulnerable: recounting her sins to him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARES SLIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/27/cbs-falls-on-report-ceo-moonves-to-be-accused-by-new-yorker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS Falls on Report CEO Moonves to Be Accused by New Yorker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARES SLIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/27/cbs-drops-5-percent-after-report-that-les-moonves-accused-of-sexual-m.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Leslie Moonves Accused of Sexual Misconduct in Ronan Farrow Expose... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/leslie-moonves-accused-sexual-misconduct-ronan-farrow-expose-1130268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS CEO, one of the most powerful men in Hollywood, is accused of unwanted kissing and touching in a New Yorker article set to be published Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Called Cohen 'Honest and Honorable' Weeks Ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/heres-rudy-giuliani-calling-michael-cohen-an-honest-honorable-lawyer-just-8-weeks-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador President says Julian Assange MUST leave embassy!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6877922/wikileaks-julian-assange-leave-ecuador-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULIAN Assange’s legal team says Ecuador is seeking assurances he won’t be EXECUTED if he is forced to leave its embassy in London. Speculation about Assange’s future has grown in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP 4.1%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/27/us-gdp-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gross domestic product grew at a solid 4.1 percent pace in the second quarter, its best pace since 2014, boosting hopes that the economy is ready to break out of its decade-long slumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW TWITTER STOCK TANKS ON DECLINING USERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/27/twitter-earnings-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Twitter experienced 24 percent year-over-year revenue growth and exceeded projections this quarter, the company projected lower than expected monthly active users. Monthly active users were down 1 million compared to last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS FACE TOUGHEST ELECTION MAP IN 88 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republicans-incumbents-midterm-elections-dave-wasserman-f2481902-67ba-469a-90ac-c140dec05e85.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are defending 42 open or vacant seats, a record since at least 1930.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT UNLEASHES...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5999289/Trump-denies-knowing-infamous-2016-Trump-Tower-meeting-calls-Michael-Cohen-liar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump denied he had any advance knowledge of a now-infamous 2016 meeting attended by his son, his son-in-law, his campaign chairman and a Russian lawyer with Kremlin ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl Breaks Out at Trump's Star on Hollywood Blvd...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/shocking-video-brawl-breaks-out-at-trumps-star-on-hollywood-blvd-youth-pastor-youtuber-assaulted-and-robbed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Rich; Slash Military...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/27/trevor-noah-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-agenda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is an excellent, excellent question'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY, FOX shareholders approve blockbuster $71-billion deal...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-disney-fox-shareholders-approve-deal-20180727-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney and Fox's concurrent shareholder meetings, which took place in the same Manhattan hotel, and the overwhelming vote marked a milestone in the more than yearlong deal approval process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Temps FALLING for 8,000 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.iceagenow.info/temperatures-have-been-falling-for-8000-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iceagenow.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A picture is worth a thousand words. ______________ Temperatures have been FALLING for 8,000 years By Ray Kraft Short term variations, local record hots and colds, don’t mean much, that’s just weather. What matters is long term global trend lines over decades, centuries, millennia, eons, epochs. . The only ‘normal’ in climate is constant change ... Read moreTemperatures have been FALLING for 8,000 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOING A LOT HIGHER'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/27/trump-were-going-to-go-a-lot-higher-than-4point1percent-gdp-number.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier Friday the government announced that the economy grew in the second quarter at the fastest pace in nearly four years. The nation's GDP grew 4.1 percent, in line with estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?449055-1/president-trump-delivers-remarks-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump delivers remarks on the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Cortez Risky Road Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-report/articles/2018-07-27/alexandria-ocasio-cortezs-risky-road-show </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutated HIV strains may cause quicker illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/jul/27/canada-hiv-mutated-strain-rapid-development-aids-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strains circulating in Saskatchewan, where nearly 80% of infected are indigenous, may lead to faster progression of related illnesses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly California wildfire 'taking down everything in path'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/northern-california-wildfire-taking-path/story?id=56859441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bulldozer operator has died in the wildfire raging in Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin 'ready to go to Washington,' invites Trump to Moscow...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5999443/Russian-President-Vladimir-Putin-says-invited-President-Donald-Trump-visit-MOSCOW.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin says has invited President Donald Trump to visit him in Moscow and also said he is ready to go to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VETERAN, MAN IN TRUMP SHIRT VIOLENTLY ATTACKED IN LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/marine-veteran-man-wearing-trump-shirt-violently-attacked-near-trump-star-in-l-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mob also attacks cameraman filming the fight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Do Cortez supporters understand socialism?</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would these people think when asked how socialism is working in Venezuela?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's So Secret About WHOLE FOODS? Under AMAZON, a Lot It Seems...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/07/27/what-s-so-secret-about-whole-foods-under-amazon-a-lot-it-seems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s So Secret About Whole Foods? Under Amazon, a Lot It Seems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than three dozen lion trophy permits issued as Trump rolls back protections...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/399140-more-than-three-dozen-lion-trophy-permits-issued-as-trump-rolls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than three dozens permits to import lion trophies have been issued since 2016, according to documents obtained by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study warns plastics could be shrinking penises...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6871840/plastic-chemicals-food-packaging-make-penis-smaller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE’S lots of reasons not to use plastic – but this one might come as a shock. Chemicals in everyday items, from household cleaners to food packaging, can damage a man’s penis &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Teen Breaks Into House, Demands WiFi Password...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/26/police-burglar-wifi-password/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager in California is in serious trouble after going on a crime spree when his phone reportedly ran out of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug-sniffing dog famous in Colombia. Now, smugglers have put bounty on head...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Sombra-the-police-drug-sniffing-dog-is-famous-in-13109837.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like a cocaine-fueled Homeric epic, Colombia's long tragic battle with the drug cartels has produced countless heroes and villains. But one figure cutting across the country's current narco battlefield, a name drawing praise and hate alike, is actually a six-year-old German Shepard you can find trotting through the country's airports. Sombra - "Shadow" in English - is a drug detection dog with the Colombian National Police. Over the last few years, her radar nose has led to more than 200 arrests and the seizure of at least 9 tons of illicit drugs. That success has turned the dog into something of a folk hero in a country consumed by ongoing bloodshed piled on top of a long legacy of drug violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jilt turns to gilt as man wins $8.8M from wife's boyfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldsun.com/news/local/crime/article215577310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldsun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Durham County judge awarded Keith King, which owns a BMX stunt show show, more than $8.8 million in criminal conversation, alienation of affection lawsuit that claimed ex-wife’s lover ruined his marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti says more women paid hush money...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/399133-avenatti-claims-three-more-women-were-paid-hush-money-by-trump-cohen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Michael Avenatti claimed late Thursday that he is representing three other women who say they were paid hush money either by President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen, on behalf of Trump, or by publishing compa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley Became Den of Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/07/27/silicon-valley-spies-china-russia-219071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West Coast is a growing target of foreign espionage. And it’s not ready to fight back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bans Alex Jones for 30 days...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/2018/07/27/alex-jones-30-day-ban/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's treading on thin ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behold the Amazonian eco-warrior drag queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/behold-amazonian-eco-warrior-drag-queen-060752899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bare chested, wearing an ankle-length dress, painted yellow, green and red, with flowers or leaves in his hair, it takes Brazil's Emerson Munduruku two hours to transform into Uyra Sodoma, his drag queen alter ego. Whether carrying seeds, branches and other natural materials, Munduruku's creation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Macau greyhounds await their forever homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/hundreds-of-macau-greyhounds-await-their-forever-homes-10567638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a sweltering afternoon in Macau, panting greyhounds lie in tiny concrete kennels at the gambling enclave's notorious dog-racing track, waiting ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untouched ocean habitats rapidly shrinking: study...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180727-untouched-ocean-habitats-rapidly-shrinking-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and CNN: President and TV network at loggerheads...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180727-trump-cnn-president-tv-network-loggerheads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame game blows up over deadly Greek wildfires...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180727-blame-game-blows-over-deadly-greek-wildfires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Orca mom mourns calf's death by carrying the body for days...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/26/orca-mom-mourns-calfs-death-carrying-body-days/846285002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, the mother entered her third day of pushing her calf's carcass. "It's still happening," Ken Balcomb of the Center for Whale Research, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers Aboard Diverted Flight Sickened by 'Dirty Socks' Odor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Spirit-Airlines-Flight-Diverted-LaGuardia-Florida-Myrtle-Beach-Hazmat-Odor-489318601.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flight from NYC to Florida was diverted to South Carolina after passengers aboard complained of burning throats and chest pains due to a potential hazmat situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality Show Fame More Lucrative Than OXFORD Education...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/07/26/love-island-fame-is-more-lucrative-than-an-oxbridge-education</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reality Show Fame Is More Lucrative Than an Oxbridge Education</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE: 'MISSION' OPENING FRANCHISE RECORD?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/tom-cruise-mission-impossible-fallout-opening-weekend-1202434739/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Paramount/Skydance’s Mission: Impossible – Fallout is having a great Thursday night, and we’re hearing that the sixthquel is grossing around $5M-plus in previews tonigh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Seek to Question Trump Organization Finance Chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/prosecutors-seek-to-question-trump-organization-s-finance-chief/17727607/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators in Manhattan have asked to interview Allen Weisselberg, the chief financial officer of the Trump Organization, as part of their investigation into President Donald Trump’s former lawyer Michael D. Cohen, according to two people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Watch Longest 'Blood Moon' Eclipse of Century...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-how-to-see-longest-blood-moon-eclipse-mars-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record-setting lunar eclipse paired with an extra-close Mars will soon have sky-watchers seeing red.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-results-stock/zuckerberg-loses-more-than-15-billion-in-record-facebook-fall-idUSKBN1KG1TN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg's fortune took a more than $15 billion hit on Thursday, as the social media company suffered the biggest one-day wipeout in U.S. stock market history a day after executives forecast years of lower profit margins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE FRIDAY:  'Climate change' supercharging hot and dangerous summer... </title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/environment/index.ssf/2018/07/climate_change_global_warming_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brutal weather has been supercharged by human-induced climate change, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua in 'undeclared state of siege' as hooded gunmen rule streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/world/article215568330.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Ortega claims that he’s restored calm to Nicaragua, but it’s been through the terrifying use of paramilitary gunmen who patrol in masks. His countrymen scurry off the streets at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5%?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-durable-orders-rose-1-0-in-june-1532608467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several forecasters tempered their high expectations for U.S. economic growth in the second quarter—a day before the gross domestic product report is released—due to some underwhelming economic data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUCCI Profit Soars on Surging Demand for Luxury Items...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gucci-profit-soars-on-surging-demand-for-luxury-items-1532630488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating profit at Gucci soared in the first half of the year, as shoppers flocked to the Italian fashion house amid surging global demand for luxury goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN GALACTIC spaceplane smashes altitude record in latest test flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/virgin-galactic-spaceplane-smashes-altitude-record-latest-test-flight-ncna894981 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sleek craft climbs to 32 miles over California’s Mojave Desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP BLOWOUT?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-investors-cant-remember-the-last-time-a-gdp-report-held-such-import-2018-07-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street investors just traversed a gantlet: the busiest week of corporate quarterly results, fresh developments in global trade relations and a historic stock tumble in Facebook Inc. However, the headliner of this jam-packed week may be GDP, the official scorecard of the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen claims Trump knew in advance of Russian Trump Tower meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/26/politics/michael-cohen-donald-trump-june-2016-meeting-knowledge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former personal attorney, claims that then-candidate Trump knew in advance about the June 2016 meeting in Trump Tower in which Russians were expected to offer his campaign dirt on Hillary Clinton, sources with knowledge tell CNN. Cohen is willing to make that assertion to special counsel Robert Mueller, the sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight breaks out between pilots at 37,000 feet... </title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-fight-breaks-out-in-cockpit-at-37000-feet-between-iraqi-airways-pilots/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthing mysteries of 'Egypt' in dunes of California Coast...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/travel/la-tr-california-guadalupe-dunes-ten-commandments-movie-artifacts-20180726-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artifact is from Hollywood, having been part of the set of the 1923 silent film "The Ten Commandments." It's on display at a little known archaeological center on the central coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO BOMB IRAN?</title>
      <link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-27/donald-trump-may-be-prepared-to-strike-iran-sources-say/10037728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior figures in the Turnbull Government say they believe the Trump administration is prepared to bomb Iran's nuclear capability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates hack tablet system, steal $225,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.localnews8.com/news/prison-officials-idaho-inmates-hacked-jpay-tablet-system/773579341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.localnews8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idaho prison officials say 364 inmates hacked the JPay tablets they use for email, music and games and collectively transferred nearly a quarter million dollars into their own accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person dead at 117, just after GUINNESS certifies...</title>
      <link>http://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/news/2018/7/oldest-person-title-officially-achieved-by-117-year-old-chiyo-miyako-before-her-d-534017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.guinnessworldrecords.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chiyo Miyako, 117, was the oldest living woman when she passed away on Sunday 22 July</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big stink as thousands of deceased fish blanket Mystic River...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/07/26/nothing-fishy-officials-say-thousands-fish-washed-everett-but-likely-from-natural-causes/w9xdiPhyxyPJKXbQRdL58J/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fish blanketed the shoreline near a Costco store — and customers said the smell was unpleasant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Secret Wars In Africa Rage On...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/26/us-special-operations-africa-green-berets-navy-seals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Operations forces in Africa are supposed to be training and advising, but they keep ending up in situations that are indistinguishable from combat.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
