<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BLM takes aim...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/blm-demands-defunding-police-banning-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black Lives Matter released an updated set of demands and is giving people the opportunity to sign their name onto the new list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic unity makes Biden's ambition possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/05/03/democratic-unity-makes-bidens-ambition-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANALYSIS — Despite their narrow majorities in Congress, Democrats are sticking together on almost all votes, boding well for Biden’s agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27-Year-Old  Now World's Youngest Crypto Billionaire...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/05/etherum-founder-buterin-billionaire-cryptocurrency-surge-bitcoin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian-Canadian programmer created Ethereum in 2013 at the age of 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Prices Hit $5 In CA; Nearly $100 To Fill Tank!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/02/gas-prices-continue-to-climb-in-socal-for-9th-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gas prices continued to increase in or around Southern California for the ninth day in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KROGER Joins Drone Delivery Race...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kroger-joins-drone-delivery-race-100000277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Kroger Co. is diving into drone delivery, starting a pilot at a store near its Cincinnati headquarters.The supermarket chain is partnering with Drone Express, a unit of Telegrid Technologies, to deliver groceries from a store in Centerville, Ohio, later this spring, the companies said in a statement Monday. The technology allows for deliveries of up to five pounds to customers’ homes or wherever they may be, enabling cookout supplies to be sent directly to a park in as little as 15 minutes, the companies said.They plan to expand the test to an additional store in California this summer.“We can enable Kroger customers to send chicken soup to a sick friend or get fast delivery of olive oil if they run out while cooking dinner,” Beth Flippo, Telegrid’s chief technology officer, said in the statement.Kroger follows rival Walmart Inc., which has several drone tests underway. Last September, the world’s biggest retailer announced plans to use drones from Israeli startup Flytrex to make deliveries in Fayetteville, North Carolina. Walmart is also testing using drones to drop Covid-19 diagnostic kits to customers in two markets, and has teamed with a company called Zipline to deliver health and wellness products to shoppers near its Arkansas headquarters.While drone delivery promises to reduce labor and fuel costs to make e-commerce fulfillment more profitable, hurdles such as weather, privacy and insurance remain sticking points. To date, United Parcel Service Inc., Alphabet Inc.’s Wing and Amazon.com Inc.’s Prime Air remain the only Federal Aviation Administration-sanctioned drone delivery operators.Drone Express’s robots are part of a program by the FAA called Beyond, which aims to bring private companies and state and local governments together to develop drone use in areas like small-package delivery and infrastructure inspection.Drug chain Walgreens Boots Alliance Inc., which has partnered with Kroger on merchandising and purchasing initiatives, began testing deliveries using Wing drones in 2019.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST PAINFUL SINCE CARTER?</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/get-ready-for-the-most-painful-inflation-since-the-jimmy-carter-years-of-the-1970s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are too young to have been alive during the 1970s, you might want to read up on that decade, because current economic conditions are starting to become eerily similar to what we experienced back then. In the 1970s, an energy crisis caused tremendously long lines at gas stations all over the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINESE TVs CAUGHT SPYING ON OWNERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/china/chinese-smart-tvs-have-hoovered-up-data-without-telling-anybody</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of millions of Chinese consumers could be sharing personal info without their knowledge or consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad goes to save daughter in pool  -- they both drown...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article251111274.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 17-year-old who went in the pool after them is in critical condition, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ON THE DOCKET:  FACEBOOK TO REVERSE BAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/facebook-set-to-decide-whether-trump-will-be-allowed-back-on-platform/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook Oversight Board, a sort of supreme court that delivers rulings and can overturn moderation decisions made by the platform, will deliver its decision on the fate of former President Donald Trump’s page this week. “The Oversight Board will announce its decision on the case concerning former US President Trump… on May 5, 2021, at approximately 9:00 a.m. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian archaeologists unearth rare tombs dated back to BEFORE Pharaohs...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/egyptian-archaeologists-unearth-rare-tombs-dated-back-to-before-pharaohs-666565</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They also found tombs nearby from the later Hyksos period (1650 to 1500 B.C.), when Western Asian migrants took over the country, putting an end to Egypt's Middle Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions boil as May sets up to be fraught month in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/tensions-boil-as-may-sets-up-to-be-a-fraught-month-667046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of flashpoints events and the cancellation of Palestinian elections may lead to even more violence in the West Bank in the coming weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen carjack Maserati in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-searching-for-maserati-carjackers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD wants to find two suspects who carjacked the driver of a Maserati at gunpoint in Midtown Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUFFETT WARNS 'VERY SUBSTANTIAL INFLATION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/03/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-is-seeing-very-substantial-inflation-and-raising-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are seeing very substantial inflation," Buffett said. "We are raising prices. People are raising prices to us and it's being accepted."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROWING BATTLE IN AUSTIN OVER HOMELESS CAMPS...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2021/04/30/how-fed-up-citizens-armed-with-a-petition-took-on-leftists-over-austins-homeless-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Every time I have to pick up human sh-t, my liberal-ness just got lowered what one more notch,' says one Austin woman of the city's homeless problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastest Spaceship Ever Getting Terrifyingly Close to Sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxz9w/how-the-fastest-spaceship-ever-is-getting-terrifyingly-close-to-the-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Szabo and Betsy Congdon, two leads on the Parker Solar Probe, discuss the mission’s discoveries and its daredevil future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eilish says all her age group have suffered sexual exploitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/may/02/billie-eilish-says-all-her-age-group-have-suffered-sexual-misbehaviour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US singer, 19, made claim in Vogue interview when discussing new single about abusive relationship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamer found dead clutching XBOX controller after all-night session...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2805269/gamer-found-dead-clutching-xbox-controller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GAMER was found dead still clutching his Xbox controller after an all-night session, an inquest heard. Simon Shanks, 43, was discovered slumped on his sofa in front of his screen with the gaming …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 3 Say Best Sex Partner -- Themselves!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/partner-best-orgasm-themselves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Moscow, Big Brother Is Watching and Recognizing Protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/in-moscow-big-brother-is-watching-and-recognising-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow's massive facial recognition camera network is being deployed to crush dissent against President Putin. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confronting shifting climate, how will California grow?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Confronting-a-shifting-climate-how-will-16124888.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUENOC VALLEY, Calif. - This land burns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney called 'traitor' and 'Communist' at Utah Republican convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2021/05/01/mitt-romney-booed-raucous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Sen. Mitt Romney booed by the more than 1,900 Republican delegates who packed into the Maverik Center for the party’s state convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected human smuggling boat capsizes off San Diego coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-05-02/boat-capsizes-off-coast-of-point-loma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The overloaded 40-foot cabin cruiser broke apart near the Cabrillo National Monument</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines tells Communists 'get the f*ck out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-foreign-minister-issues-expletive-laced-tweet-over-china-sea-dispute-2021-05-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philippine foreign minister on Monday demanded in an expletive-laced message on Twitter that China's vessels get out of disputed waters, marking the latest exchange in a war of words with Beijing over its activities in the South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TYSON, BEYOND face off with new plant-based burgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tyson-foods-beyond-meat-face-off-with-new-plant-based-burgers-2021-05-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyson Foods Inc (TSN.N) is launching plant-based hamburgers and sausages ahead of the summer grilling season, the company said on Monday, increasing competition for Beyond Meat (BYND.O) as it releases an updated version of its own faux burger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Quietly Preparing for Food Stamp Increase Without Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/newsfront/biden-food-stamp-programs/2021/05/02/id/1019794/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is quietly laying the groundwork for a long-term increase in food aid for tens of millions of Americans, without going through the ordeal of a fight with congressional Republicans.The instrument is an obscure U.S. Department of Agriculture shopping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China already 'engaging in irregular war' with US in 'grey zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/china-already-engaging-in-irregular-war-with-us-in-the-grey-zone/news-story/8cabbb1179b77d2845f6e700bbfad62f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s war. But not as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many police officers spurn as departments avoid mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/many-police-officers-spurn-coronavirus-vaccines-as-departments-hold-off-on-mandates/ar-BB1ghSFC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low immunization levels suggest vaccine hesitancy is pervasive among emergency workers, posing risks to public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black man enslaved by White restaurant manager should be awarded more than $500,000, court says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/black-man-enslaved-by-white-restaurant-manager-should-be-awarded-more-than-24500000-court-says/ar-BB1giabD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Christopher Smith, who was enslaved at a South Carolina restaurant for years, should be awarded $546,000, an appellate court said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX turns toward flying private citizens to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-another-human-spaceflight-success-spacex-turns-toward-flying-private-citizens-to-space/ar-BB1ghYqm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX's next mission involves sending private citizens to orbit in a step toward space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did you get enough steps in today? Ask your 'smart' shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/did-you-get-enough-steps-in-today-maybe-one-day-you-e2-80-99ll-ask-your-e2-80-98smart-e2-80-99-shirt/ar-BB1gjb89 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristi Noem Rising Quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/why-kristi-noem-is-rising-quickly-as-a-republican-prospect-for-2024/ar-BB1ghiaP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERRE, S.D. — With Republicans hungry to cultivate their next generation of national leaders, it is not a Capitol Hill comer or a veteran battleground-state politician who is stirring interest by fusing Trumpism with a down-home conservatism spin. It is the first-term governor of South Dakota, Kristi Noem, a rancher who delights in sharing images of herself shooting pheasants and riding horses. Ms. Noem began drawing wider attention last year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperman on Stock Bubble:  'Not going to end well'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-not-going-to-end-well-billionaire-leon-cooperman-says-stock-market-will-be-lower-a-year-from-now-11619797332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire investor Leon Cooperman says he's a “fully invested bear” with “an eye on the exit.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA asteroid simulation ends in unavoidable disaster for Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/space/asteroid-2021-earth-nasa-simulation-b1841219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX boss Elon Musk says failed exercise proves ‘we need larger and more advanced rockets’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear kills woman walking her dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article251109644.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wildlife officials later killed the female black bear and its cubs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan, Ex-Prince American mega-celebs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Meghan-and-Harry-are-becoming-your-typical-16147013.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Montecito, Calif., a 9.3-square-mile coastal enclave nestled between the Santa Ynez...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kissinger warns of 'colossal' dangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210430-kissinger-warns-of-colossal-dangers-in-us-china-tensions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kissinger warns of 'colossal' dangers in US-China tensions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio calls NYC workers back to offices; Some aren't happy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/de-blasio-calls-workers-back-to-offices-some-arent-happy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio said it is safe for municipal workers to return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's 'uncontrolled' descent of rocket 'risks hitting USA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinas-uncontrolled-descent-20-tonne-24028208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space experts have criticised China's space agency as 20-tonne "Long March" booster could reportedly crash into Earth almost anywhere between New York and southern Chile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke sub missile 'could destroy any city in America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinas-new-nuclear-submarine-armed-24026967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Type 094A, or Jin-class, nuclear-powered ballistic missile submarine is one of three powerful new military craft announced by the Chinese Navy on its 72nd anniversary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI overtake human intelligence in 2020s?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/scientists-warning-before-robot-beat-24026812</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chess grandmaster Garry Kasparov's defeat at the hands of a computer in 1997 signalled to scientists that AI could become more intelligent than humans sooner than we think</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chameleon effect'? Looking at phone makes other people do same, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9537321/Looking-phone-makes-people-study-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say copying someone by looking at our phone is a form of social mimicry, just like when we subconsciously replicate another person's yawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZON offloads YAHOOAOL for $5 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/03/verizon-sells-yahoo-and-aol-businesses-to-apollo-for-5-billion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sale signals that Verizon will focus on its internet-provider businesses as rivals continue to explore media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Munger: Crypto 'contrary to interests of civilization'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/01/charlie-munger-calls-bitcoin-disgusting-and-contrary-to-the-interests-of-civilization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Of course I hate the bitcoin success," the 97-year-old Munger said during a Q&amp;A session at Berkshire's annual shareholder meeting Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid vaccinations slowing as supply outstrips demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/30/covid-vaccinations-in-us-are-slowing-as-supply-outstrips-demand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meeting existing vaccine demand is no longer the main challenge, and states are employing strategies to address access and hesitancy barriers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSD, Cargo Shorts and Fall of High-Flying Tech CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-03/lsd-cargo-shorts-and-the-fall-of-a-high-flying-tech-ceo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Zhu’s $2 billion startup was doing great, but an unorthodox style and tension with investors cost him his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Buying Up Colorado Town. Locals Freaked...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/billionaire-buying-small-colorado-town-091127492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyThe mountain hamlet of Crested Butte, Colorado, covers less than a square mile and, at an elevation of nearly 9,000 feet, it is taller than it is wide. So when a Chicago-based billionaire began quietly buying up its historic buildings, residents took note.“I was alarmed that someone would come in and buy up so much commercial property in the community,” former Gunnison County Commissioner Jim Starr told The Daily Beast. “That had not happened before. We've got few owners who own two or three different commercial properties. But the scale of this was larger than what we have seen previously.”The billionaire in question is investment banker Mark Walter. An intensely media-averse figure, the CEO of Guggenheim Partners has accumulated a net worth of approximately $5.3 billion, according to Forbes, with little fanfare. His most overtly public move came in 2012, when Walter joined forces with Magic Johnson and several other entertainment figures to buy the Los Angeles Dodgers for a record-breaking $2.15 billion.But Walter’s activity in Crested Butte has drawn lots of local attention among its population of about 4,700. This year alone, Walter purchased six commercial properties, including several historic buildings downtown and a family resort called the Almont, which sits at the intersection of the East and Taylor rivers. Walter closed the deals under limited liability companies registered to his work address in Chicago“He’s been very—I wouldn’t say ‘secretive’—but certainly not forthcoming with what he’s going to be doing with the buildings,” Crested Butte Mayor Jim Schmidt told The Daily Beast. Realtor Eric Roemer echoed the uneasy feeling: “Nobody really knows what his game plan is.”Zuckerberg Gobbles Up Another Big Chunk of Hawaii Beachfront“I have no idea what Mr. Walter is planning to do,” writer and Gunnison County resident George Sibley said, “and I don’t think anyone else does either—possibly including Mr. Walter.”Among his new investments, Walter acquired a building called the Forest Queen for $1.55 million, a commercial property containing a spa and tattoo shop for $1.85 million, a restaurant called the Wooden Nickel for $1.85 million, a health club for $1.7 million, an undeveloped lot for $5.5 million, and the resort for $6.3 million. All together, the new purchases totaled more than $20 million.Walter did not respond to multiple requests for comment. This is something of a pattern for him; in an opinion piece for the Crested Butte News, local writer Mark Reaman described contacting the CEO’s realtor to see if he would discuss future plans. “After she finished laughing,” Reaman wrote, “she basically indicated I probably had a better chance of getting Donald Trump to chat with me about Almont.”Even Roemer, who owned the Wooden Nickel before Walter bought it, said he hadn’t been able to get any information about the plans. “The only thing that we’ve been told by his representatives is that, at least with the Wooden Nickel, he’s interested in continuing the operation as it has been,” Roemer said. “Whether it’s been modified no one knows at this time. But he's planning on opening that business towards the end of May.”The purchases left Schmidt somewhat confused, as commercial property in ski towns can make for tricky economics. Usually, he said, commercial buildings sell at about three times the price of local residences. But in high-end ski regions where homes get so expensive, the math can make it harder for smaller businesses to turn a profit. “You’d have to charge way too much for hamburgers,” he said. “That’s the challenge.”A lingering question for residents is what Walter will do with the undeveloped lot on the north edge of town, heading towards the ski slopes. The sprawling property, known locally as the “Sixth Street Station,” was approved for a massive hotel and residential building in 2017. According to Schmidt, it would be the largest hotel in Crested Butte. But it remains unclear if Walter plans to proceed with the construction project..Walter has had a quiet presence in the Crested Butte area for the past decade. He and his wife have owned a home in the neighboring town of Mt. Crested Butte since 2009, and in 2011, he bought a commercial complex known as the Grubstake Building for $766,700. The Grubstake housed a tea house, a cafe, an art gallery, and a fishing shop, which Walter has kept active.For a time, the CEO went through a local permitting process to convert the building into a music and dance venue. According to Starr and Schmidt, he later backed off the plans over the town’s required one-time payment for street parking.“He did not like the parking-in-lieu charges which we apply to all businesses,” Schmidt said. “Frankly, I was a little surprised that he thought the amount was excessive, considering what he pays a third string outfielder for the Dodgers.”For a time several years ago, the town had an advertising slogan: "Crested Butte—what Aspen used to be, and Vail never was." The joke was that Crested Butte was “the last great Colorado ski town,” one that hadn’t yet been bought up by even wealthier outsiders looking for a seasonal stay. But some residents are concerned that Walter’s investments may change that.“One of the concerns, of course, is that when people have more of the commercial properties like that, the rents tend to go up, which makes it harder for the business owners,” Starr said. “And we've got a real severe affordable housing shortage here, so this eventually could exacerbate that problem as well.”But Sibley pointed out that Walter followed a long line of wealthy investors coming to Colorado. “There would not even be Colorado towns were it not for outside money basically,” he said, citing some Kansas bankers who’d invested in the ski slopes in Crested Butte and a Texas refining company that operated a nearby mine.“Before that of course, it was a coal mining town and it was essentially a company town for Colorado Fuel and Iron, which is based in Pueblo,” Sibley said. “So it’s always been pretty much a wholly owned subsidiary of outsiders.”But Walter’s investment may herald a wave of a new strain of outsiders. “I’ve heard folks say, ‘We've reached the point where the billionaires are pushing out the millionaires,’” Starr said, “which a lot of us who’ve lived here for quite a while had hoped would never happen.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trump effect' propels Hollywood political hopefuls...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/551229-from-mcconaughey-to-jenner-trump-effect-propels-hollywoods</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More and more famous faces are dipping their toes in the political waters, and some Hollywood stars are ready to dive into the deep end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech therapist teaches dog to speak!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/01/this-speech-therapist-taught-her-dog-to-speak-heres-how-you-can-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A speech therapist taught her own dog to speak — and she reveals how you and your pup can do the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing tops NYC in number of billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/01/beijing-tops-nyc-in-number-of-billionaires-on-latest-forbes-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese capital has exactly one more billionaire than Gotham, 100 to 99, according to Forbes’ recently released list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Captured, Tortured, and Cleared Him. He's Still in GITMO...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-captured-tortured-cleared-him-090554898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/AP IamgesIt’s been 19 years since U.S. forces captured Zayn al-Abidin Muhammad Husayn and declared him one of the senior leaders of al Qaeda. It’s been 15 years since the CIA quietly revoked that assessment once it was done torturing him. Today, Huseyn, a forgotten man, remains locked inside Guantanamo Bay, a living symbol of the permanent damage wrought by the War on Terror.As the Biden administration performs the latest government review into closing Guantanamo, attorneys for Husayn, better known as Abu Zubaydah, have decided they’ve waited long enough. They filed a petition on Friday with the U.N. Working Group on Arbitrary Detention seeking his release from his 19 years of captivity. They want the panel to exercise its “urgent actions” procedures to appeal to Washington for his freedom, citing his counsel’s “serious concerns for his physical and mental health and welfare [stretching back] for years.”The attorneys note that the military has yet to vaccinate Abu Zubaydah and the other Guantanamo detainees for COVID-19. “After 19 years of arbitrary detention, the only appropriate legal remedy for Abu Zubaydah is release and rehabilitation,” said the lead lawyer behind the U.N. appeal, Helen Duffy.History Lesson: Gitmo Started as a Detention Camp for ImmigrantsThe U.N. is an unlikely route through which Abu Zubaydah might go free, but nothing else has worked, including a federal habeas corpus case. The few consistencies in Abu Zubaydah’s Kafkaesque past 19 years have nothing to do with the law and everything to do with the prerogatives of covering up what the U.S. did to him. In 2018, one of Abu Zubaydah’s habeas attorneys marveled that his unlikely goal was to get the U.S. to prosecute his client—just so Abu Zubaydah’s permanent incommunicado captivity would end.Once Abu Zubaydah was said to be one of the most important al Qaeda captives of all. An infamous August 2002 memo from the Justice Department, instrumental to authorizing the CIA to torture him—and after him, at least 118 others—called him the “third or fourth man in al Qaeda.” But there were doubts inside the CIA at the outset. According to the landmark Senate torture report, on Aug. 16, 2006 the agency formally concluded that Abu Zubaydah “was not a member of al Qaeda.”Instead of freeing him, the U.S. brought Abu Zubaydah to Guantanamo Bay the following month, where he became the forgotten man he currently is. Some politicians, like Rep. Elissa Slotkin (D-MI), a former CIA analyst and Pentagon official, have recently declared that the 9/11 era is “over.” But Abu Zubaydah’s ongoing and entirely uncontroversial confinement proves the opposite. He is one of 40 men, few of them charged with any crime even before a dysfunctional military tribunal, who languish at Guantanamo Bay. Abu Zubaydah’s captivity has influenced every one of them.Abu Zubaydah came into U.S. custody after a gunfight in Faisalabad, Pakistan, that left him badly wounded in his stomach, leg, and testicles. One of his FBI interrogators, Ali Soufan, wrote in his 2011 book The Black Banners that Abu Zubaydah was “not a member of al Qaeda,” but still an important figure, tied to the eastern Afghanistan terror training camp known as Khalden, helping jihadists transit out to Pakistan. The origin of the claim that Abu Zubaydah was one of the seniormost members of al Qaeda, according to the Senate’s 2014 report, was “single-sourced reporting” from the CIA that “was recanted prior” to the Justice Department’s 2002 torture memos.The Last Thing We Need Is Another War on TerrorSoufan famously lost a bureaucratic fight with the CIA against torturing Abu Zubaydah. The CIA, through contractors James Mitchell and Bruce Jessen, instead wanted to beta-test a regimen of brutality meant to induce a psychological concept called “learned helplessness.” It meant, among other tortures, locking Abu Zubaydah in coffin-sized and even smaller boxes for 12-1/2 cumulative days; keeping him awake for extended periods through painful body contortions; and, 83 times, drowning him through a simulation called waterboarding. The ostensible point was to get Abu Zubaydah to reveal al Qaeda secrets that they were unswervingly and baselessly certain he possessed.There were more vindictive impulses as well. One of the CIA’s waterboarders was known as the “Preacher,” Mitchell later testified at Guantanamo, who would douse men’s heads in a pantomimed baptism, an assertion of religious domination. CIA records from Abu Zubaydah’s August 2002 interrogations, published in the Senate torture report, record extreme discomfort among other CIA personnel, “some to the point of tears and choking up.” Abu Zubaydah, in one of his few public statements, recalled that his waterboarders would mock him in between submergings. “I tell him, ‘If you want to kill me, kill me,’” he said.The Senate torture report records that Abu Zubaydah was almost instantly “compliant.” CIA medical staff found that he was willing to cooperate even before he was tortured. But the brutality was so severe that within days of the “aggressive phase” of his interrogation, Abu Zubaydah would go to the waterboard when his interrogator “snapped his fingers twice.” He would frequently spasm and grow hysterical from the drownings. At least one of them, per the torture report, left him catatonic and unresponsive, with bubbles forming in his “open, full mouth.”It took six days, on Aug. 9, for CIA interrogators on scene to conclude that Abu Zubaydah had no actionable intelligence. The next day, they re-emphasized it was “highly unlikely” he had the sort of information they sought. When an apparently frustrated CIA official warned Langley they were at the “legal limit” of what they could do to Abu Zubaydah, the head of the Counterterrorism Center, Jose Rodriguez, responded on Aug. 12 that “any speculative language as to the legality of given activities” was “not helpful.” Years later, Rodriguez and his deputy, who had been one of the chiefs of the Thailand black site where the CIA first tortured Abu Zubaydah, destroyed over 90 videotapes of Abu Zubaydah’s torture. The deputy and black site chief, Gina Haspel, went on to become CIA director, from 2018 to January 2021.Within months of Abu Zubaydah’s torture, versions of his torture regimen were used first on other CIA captives and then, in modified form, on military detainees at Guantanamo Bay, Afghanistan, and Iraq.Detainees Describe an American Presence in Their Torture ChambersCaptivity by the U.S. cost Abu Zubaydah an eye—it remains unclear exactly how—and a testicle. In 2007, during a nonjudicial hearing at Guantanamo Bay, he bemoaned that he was “losing my masculinity. Even my beard is falling out.” He apologized, saying that “I don’t like to admit I’m a sick person… almost half of my body is not good.” The Justice Department 2002 torture memo has been criticized for permitting the CIA to inflict pain up to the limit of “organ failure” or long-term psychological damage. Even by those highly narrow criteria, Abu Zubaydah surely qualifies as having been tortured.In the same hearing, he described “another form of torture”: his separation from the diary he kept for 16 years. Everything the U.S. would need to “refute the accusations against me” is in that diary, which the U.S. took from him, he said. In Abu Zubaydah’s telling, he was a Pakistan-based coordinator of “two guest houses” to get trainees in and out of the Khalden camp. There they would train in “defensive jihad,” by which he meant striking military targets of non-Muslim invaders of Muslim land, “Russia against Chechnya, and of course, Israel against Palestine.” Abu Zubaydah, who was not himself a trained fighter, said he thought bin Laden was too brutal: “Bin Laden wanted al Qaeda to have control of Khalden, but we refused, since we had different ideas.” Seemingly referring to his CIA captors, he told the Guantanamo officers, “They told me, ‘sorry, we discover that you are not No. 3, you are not even a fighter.’”The War on Terror was disinterested in the distinctions between self-described facilitators of jihadi trainees and al Qaeda. Even taking the CIA at its face-value assertion that its torture program was about intelligence production and not revenge, Abu Zubaydah’s case demonstrates that the CIA predicated its torture program on a false test case, a man whom the CIA brutalized before admitting he was not who they thought he was.That, Abu Zubaydah’s lawyers suspect, is why the U.S. has never charged Abu Zubaydah with an offense in either military or civilian court. “Had those assertions been true,” wrote attorney Charles R. Church in 2018, “Abu Zubaydah would have been prosecuted long ago rather than being immured in a top-secret military prison.” Before Abu Zubaydah’s torture, according to the Senate torture report, the CIA’s Bin Laden Unit reported that “all major players are in concurrence that [Abu Zubaydah] should remain incommunicado for the remainder of his life.”In that respect, their campaign worked. Abu Zubaydah has had practically no contact with the outside world. Much of what has emerged has been his disturbing artwork depicting naked men strapped to chairs and stuffed into coffins while watched by men clad all in black. In 2016, the military’s assertions against Abu Zubaydah were downgraded to running a “mujahideen training network,” “possibly” knowing in advance about the 1998 bombings of two U.S. embassies, and other aspects of what the New York Times called a “much-modified but still rather vague description of his history.” Yet the military continued to detain Abu Zubaydah without charge, and inspired little outrage. There is only so much attention the world has shown it is willing to pay to those inside Guantanamo Bay. It pays less with each passing year.Gitmo Judge Convicts U.S. General—Because He Stood Up for Detainee RightsYet Abu Zubaydah has also won vindications. In 2015, the European Court of Human Rights ordered Poland, which hosted the second black site where the CIA held Abu Zubaydah, to pay restitution. Lithuania, which hosted Abu Zubaydah’s captivity from February 2005 to March 2006, appears to be stonewalling on a similar investigation, although the court already ruled Lithuania to be complicit in Abu Zubaydah’s torture. In December 2017, the U.N. formally removed Abu Zubaydah from its al Qaeda blacklist. And this week, the Supreme Court agreed to hear a case emerging from Abu Zubaydah’s European human-rights litigation that tests the government’s powers to block him from obtaining testimony from Mitchell and Jessen on state-secrets grounds.The U.N. panel on arbitrary detention has no power to compel the Biden administration to release the now 50-year old Abu Zubaydah. In February, the administration said it has a review underway to determine how it will close Guantanamo, distinct from its broader counterterrorism review. A senior administration official did not provide The Daily Beast with more information about the timetable for the review or subsequent action, saying only that its review is broadly consultative across the government. The U.S. military’s Southern Command, which oversees Guantanamo, reiterated that it is committed to “safe, humane and legal” detentions.“The torture and detention without charge or trial of Abu Zubaydah for 19 years epitomizes the worst of the War on Terror,” said Duffy, his attorney. “As the 20th anniversary looms, it’s past time to release him, to reveal the truth about his case, and to commit to effective security based on the rule of law.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists scramble to see why even vaccinated can get infected...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-scramble-see-why-rare-120012555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts expected some vaccinated people to contract COVID-19. But more research is needed on exactly why it is happening now, in small numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ether Hits $3,000 as Bitcoin Dominance Declines...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ether-hits-3-000-bitcoin-021316724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin’s domination of total cryptocurrency market value is declining as its next-biggest rival Ether reaches the $3,000 milestone.The rise of Ether suggests there’s room for more than one winner among digital tokens as the sector evolves. Bitcoin now accounts for about 46% of total crypto market value, down from roughly 70% at the start of the year, and Ether makes up 15%, according to tracker CoinGecko. Bitcoin remains the biggest cryptocurrency but the momentum in other tokens is drawing increasing interest. Proponents argue investors are getting more comfortable with a variety of tokens, while critics contend the sector may be in the grip of a stimulus-fueled mania.Cryptocurrencies were broadly higher on Monday. Bitcoin climbed above $58,000, while Ether jumped 6% to $3,151 as of 8:17 a.m. in New York.“Ethereum is rising and not much seems to be in its way,” Edward Moya, a senior market analyst at Oanda Corp., wrote in a note Friday, adding that other tokens were also seeing “fresh interest.”The current distribution of market share also reflects an April shakeout in the cryptocurrency sector. Bitcoin has yet to recover all the ground it lost after tumbling from a mid-April record of almost $64,870.Last month’s listing of crypto exchange Coinbase Global Inc. in the U.S. is the latest sign of how more investors are embracing the sector despite risks from high levels of volatility and expanding regulatory scrutiny.Ether is currently occupying the limelight. An upgrade of the affiliated Ethereum blockchain as well as the network’s popularity for financial services and cryptocollectibles are among the factors cited for the rally. Evercore ISI strategist Rich Ross has set a target of $3,900 for the token.Other cryptocurrencies have jumped too. The price of Binance Coin is up 3,460% over the past 12 months, according to CoinGecko. Dogecoin, a token started as a joke in 2013 but now a social-media favorite touted by the likes of Elon Musk, has surged 15,000% to a market value of around $50 billion.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Currency Surges Past Deposits of Most Banks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crypto-shadow-currency-surges-past-111500954.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tether, the crypto stablecoin backed one-for-one by fiat currencies, surpassed $50 billion in circulation, a sum that’s more than the insured deposits at all but 44 of the thousands of U.S. banks.It’s a remarkable milestone for a token that enjoys wide use as a method of payment in the crypto ecosystem, even as the eponymous private company behind it has endured regulatory scrutiny for its opacity on where it holds the enormous sum of reserves that back the token.Tether is set to release the first quarterly statement on its reserves to the New York Attorney General this month. The disclosure is part of a settlement of a long-running dispute with state regulators over whether it actually has the reserves, but it is unclear whether investors will get a glimpse at it.Not that Tether investors seem to care either way. The token’s popularity has only grown amid the legal hubbub, as it became the most traded cryptocurrency in the world, exceeding even the volume of market leader Bitcoin. Traders and speculators use it as a conduit to conduct transactions on crypto-only exchanges such as Binance and to park assets to avoid the sector’s extreme price volatility.“At those offshore exchanges Tether is the main collateral and margin type,” said Nic Carter, co-founder of researcher Coin Metrics. “Exchange volumes are way up and Binance volume is way up. For traders to get access to these crypto-only exchanges they often prefer a stablecoin like Tether. You can think of the supply of Tether as a transparent proxy for the balance sheet of both the crypto-only exchanges as well as the funds trading crypto on those exchanges.”About 66% of Bitcoin is bought using Tether, according to data tracker CryptoCompare. And Tether’s use is likely to expand since Coinbase Global Inc., the largest U.S. crypto exchange, is planning to allow trading of the stablecoin on its Coinbase Pro platform.The quarterly report will be released to New York in May, according to Stuart Hoegner, general counsel for the crypto exchange Bitfinex and Tether. The companies, which are based primarily in the British Virgin Islands, settled without admitting or denying any wrongdoing.When the settlement was announced, New York Attorney General Letitia James said “Bitfinex and Tether recklessly and unlawfully covered-up massive financial losses to keep their scheme going and protect their bottom lines. Tether’s claims that its virtual currency as fully backed by U.S. dollars at all times was a lie.”The cryptosphere saw few ripples in the wake of the settlement, with the amount of Tether created continuing to surge after the announcement. Market participants anticipate a similar reaction no matter what that quarterly report reveals.“The fact that Coinbase added it tells you everything you need to know,” said Kyle Samani, co-founder of Multicoin Capital.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euphoric clubbers hit dance floor again as Spain trials digital pass...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210502105246-1roh2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-REOPENING (PIX, TV):Euphoric clubbers hit dance floor again as Spain trials digital COVID-19 pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Haunts Traders in Blockbuster Earnings Season...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/inflation-haunts-stock-traders-in-blockbuster-earnings-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greed, Bankers and Politics Star in Danish Negative-Rate Debacle...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/greed-bankers-politics-star-danish-040000695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The country with the longest history of negative interest rates just hit a milestone that may offer a glimpse of what’s to come elsewhere.In Denmark, commercial banks have had to absorb negative rates since they were first introduced by the central bank in 2012. By 2019, the industry started sharing the cost of that policy with retail depositors. Today, Danes are the world champions in bearing the burden of negative rates together with their banks, with 35% of deposits affected.Last week, the government in Copenhagen decided to step in. The minister in charge of bank legislation, Simon Kollerup, turned to social media to launch an attack on the financial sector, and the “greed” he said it represents.“Banks have recently been lowering the bar for negative rates,” he said. “And this simply has to stop.”He commented a day after Danske Bank, Denmark’s biggest lender, said it was following others in the industry and more than halving its threshold for imposing a rate of minus 0.6%. As a result, retail depositors with more than 100,000 kroner ($16,000) will pay 0.6% to park savings exceeding that amount with the bank.“My worry is that banks will continue tightening the screws on negative rates so that average Danes need to pay to keep their money in a bank,” the minister said in a written comment to Bloomberg.Kollerup, who summoned the bankers’ association to talks, says there’s no excuse for passing negative rates on to private customers, and rejects the idea that monetary policy plays a role in determining commercial bank rates.Rate PoliticsThe battle that’s now unfolding between Danish banks and the government gives a sense of where the limits of negative rates may lie, and shows that those limits might be political, not monetary.Negative rates have become the lightning rod that Kollerup has seized to wage “a confrontation with greed, income inequality and division in society,” said Helle Ib, a political commentator at Borsen, Denmark’s biggest business newspaper.The bankers’ association, Finance Denmark, has questioned the merits of Kollerup’s economic reasoning. And the central bank issued a reminder on Friday, pointing out that its negative policy rates (which are necessitated by the krone’s peg to the euro) influence deposit and lending rates throughout the broader economy. It also hinted that politicians shouldn’t interfere in the process. “Banks’ interest rates are a matter for them and their customers,” central bank Governor Lars Rohde said.The central bank’s verbal intervention prompted a member of the opposition bloc in parliament to weigh in. Alex Vanopslagh, the leader of the Liberal Alliance party, told Berlingske he’s summoned Kollerup to a hearing to explain his comments on negative rates. “I trust the minister will say that he crossed the line, and that he lacks a basic grasp of how monetary policy works,” Vanopslagh said.Carsten Egeriis, the chief executive of Danske Bank, points out that Danes also enjoy low interest rates on their mortgages, which he called “the other side of the coin.” That dynamic “most of the time far outweighs the cost of negative interest rates on the deposit side,’ he said.Denmark is two years ahead of the euro zone, which first introduced negative rates in 2014. Jesper Rangvid, a professor of finance at Copenhagen Business School, says there are some lessons to be drawn from the Danish experience for euro-zone economies.He also notes that negative bank rates aren’t the destructive force once imagined. In fact, Rangvid points out that after years of zero, and ultimately negative retail deposit rates, Danish deposits have continued to rise.“The most important takeaway is that clients haven’t been leaving banks,” he said by phone. “That was the fear in the beginning, and that has not happened.”Ib at Borsen says it’s not a given that Kollerup will actually intervene. Ultimately, it’s probably more a case of “sending a signal than a hardcore revolution of economic policy,” she said.(Updates with reference to Kollerup being summoned to parliamentary hearing)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Billionaire Quietly Becomes Influential Force Among Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/03/swiss-billionaire-quietly-becomes-influential-force-among-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — He is not as well known as wealthy liberal patrons like George Soros or Tom Steyer. His political</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reaching 'Herd Immunity' Unlikely in USA, Experts Now Believe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/03/reaching-herd-immunity-is-unlikely-in-the-u-s-experts-now-believe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early in the pandemic, when vaccines for the coronavirus were still just a glimmer on the horizon, the term “herd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clarence Thomas, Long Silent, Has Turned Talkative...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/03/justice-clarence-thomas-long-silent-has-turned-talkative/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Justice Clarence Thomas, who once went a decade without asking a question from the Supreme Court bench, is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India court urges govt action as hospitals cry help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-india-coronavirus-health-1b0c55592798a33d41b38f81629dc904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — With Indian hospitals struggling to secure a steady supply of oxygen, and more COVID-19 patients dying amid the shortages, a court in New Delhi said it would start punishing government officials for failing to deliver the life-saving items. On Sunday, India recorded a slight drop in new infections with 392,488 from a high of 401,993 in the previous 24 hours. It also reported 3,689 additional deaths, bringing the total to 215,542. Experts believe both figures are an undercount. The government has been using the railroad, the air force and the navy to rush oxygen tankers to worst-hit areas where overwhelmed hospitals are unable to cope with an unprecedented surge in patients gasping for air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffett warns not to gamble...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/warren-buffett-health-coronavirus-business-15afc2aa02d5d027e0731a4268cec100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — Billionaire Warren Buffett warned people not to think investing is an easy way to make a fortune as he answered a variety of questions at Berkshire Hathaway's annual meeting Saturday. Buffett said it can be tough to pick the long-term winners. He pointed out that in 1903 there were more than 2,000 car companies, and nearly all of them failed even though cars have transformed the country since then. “There’s a lot more to picking stocks than figuring out what will be an incredible industry in the future,” said Buffett, who is known for his remarkably successful investing record. “I just want to tell you that it’s not as easy as it sounds.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico groans; Economy suffers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/puerto-rico-economy-business-financial-markets-pandemics-86591ae020b9ea4c117a1364661e5a1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — Puerto Rico seemed to be sprinting toward herd immunity this spring before people began letting their guard down against COVID-19 and new variants started spreading across the U.S. territory. Now, a spike in cases and hospitalizations has put medical experts at odds with the government, which is struggling to protect people’s health while also trying to prevent an economic implosion on an island battered by hurricanes, earthquakes and a prolonged financial crisis. “The difficulty here is how do you find a Solomonic decision ... to give people the opportunity to work and be responsible and also maintain health as a priority,” said Ramón Leal, former president of Puerto Rico’s Restaurant Association. “These are hard conversations.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rap rhythm from Rio favelas causing stir...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/latin-america-rio-de-janeiro-arts-and-entertainment-entertainment-music-e5a8e95f9ba8e366eb2ff11874185129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — First, Vitor Oliveira sold the ground floor of the bare-bones brick building he constructed near the top of his sprawling favela in Rio de Janeiro. Then he sold one of two second-floor apartments. Then his car. It’s all for the music -- for trap de cria, a new kind of hip hop that evokes gang life in Rio’s favelas. Oliveira, 31, plowed the proceeds into constructing a tiny recording studio and editing room in the building’s final apartment. He returns there from his job -- driving his motorcycle taxi up and down Rocinha, one of Latin America’s largest slums -- to work at churning out 18 tracks and accompanying videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa turns down 71% of available jabs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iowa-health-coronavirus-bed1e61831c0485d967ca3687bc84377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Iowa is turning down nearly three quarters of the vaccine doses available to the state from the federal government because demand for the shots remains weak. The Iowa Department of Public Health and Safety said the state asked the federal government to withhold 71% of the 105,300 vaccine doses that were available for the week of May 10. This is the second week in a row that the state has asked the federal government to hold back part of its allocation of vaccine doses. Department spokeswoman Sarah Ekstrand told  the Des Moines Register that 88 of Iowa's 99 counties have told the state they don't need all or part of their weekly vaccine allocations for that week. That's an increase from the 80 counties that declined vaccine shipments for this week and the 43 counties that declined all or part of their allocations last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR TRAVEL PANDEMIC HIGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-lifestyle-travel-air-travel-33687841a92e90a34d13370271c58039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States set another record for the number of air travelers since the pandemic set in, although passenger numbers remain far below 2019 levels. Nearly 1.67 million people were screened at U.S. airport checkpoints on Sunday, according to the Transportation Security Administration. That was the highest number screened since March 12 of last year when air travel began to plummet. However, it was still 35% below the number of airport travelers reported on the comparable Sunday in 2019, according to TSA figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Portuguese bridge not for the faint-hearted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-environment-and-nature-c85a892423abb723e024e23a3a0ba5ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AROUCA, Portugal (AP) — It's probably best if you gird yourself before you look down from the Arouca Bridge. The narrow footbridge suspended across a river canyon in northern Portugal claims to be the world’s longest pedestrian bridge and was officially inaugurated Sunday. The Arouca Bridge offers a half-kilometer (almost 1,700-foot) walk across its span, along a metal walkway suspended from cables. Some 175 meters (574 feet) below, the Paiva River flows through a waterfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU proposes reopening external borders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-lifestyle-travel-health-8eb8b459191d5dae8ea01c12d7e0539a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — In an announcement sure to be welcomed by travelers worldwide, EU officials on Monday proposed easing restrictions on visiting the 27-nation bloc as vaccination campaigns across the continent gather speed. Travel to the European Union is currently extremely limited except for a handful of countries with low infection rates. But with the summer tourist season looming, the bloc's European Commission hopes the new recommendations will dramatically expand that list. The Commission hopes the move will soon allow travelers reunite with their friends and relatives living in Europe and support the bloc's economy this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity politicians test voter interest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/campaign-2016-celebrity-entertainment-election-2020-arts-and-entertainment-9b18436c896067016734fb50a386cb69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — From Ronald Reagan and Arnold Schwarzenegger to Al Franken and Donald Trump, there’s a rich history of celebrities trying out new careers in politics. The list could soon grow. In California, former Olympian Caitlyn Jenner is running for governor. In Texas, Oscar-winning actor Matthew McConaughey has said he is considering a run for governor. In New York City, Andrew Yang , a businessman who gained fame during his quixotic 2020 presidential run, is a leading contender for the Democratic mayoral nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE app store goes on trial over 'illegal monopoly'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/apple-inc-trials-lifestyle-technology-business-ab4cdc38a09734e3632c25228636bdd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN RAMON, Calif. (AP) — On Monday, Apple faces one of its most serious legal threats in recent years: A trial that threatens to upend its iron control over its app store, which brings in billions of dollars each year while feeding more than 1.6 billion iPhones, iPads, and other devices. The federal court case is being brought by Epic Games, maker of the popular video game Fortnite. Epic wants to topple the so-called “walled garden” of the app store, which Apple started building 13 years ago as part of a strategy masterminded by co-founder Steve Jobs. Epic charges that Apple has transformed a once-tiny digital storefront into an illegal monopoly that squeezes mobile apps for a significant slice of their earnings. Apple takes a commission of 15% to 30% on purchases made within apps, including everything from digital items in games to subscriptions. Apple denies Epic’s charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY DAYS:  64% OF AMERICANS OPTIMISTIC</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/country-optimistic-bidens-1st-100-days-poll/story?id=77440236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden completes his first hundred days in office with a country that is more optimistic about the coming year, according to a new ABC/News Ipsos poll.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
