<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMY DETERIORATING FAST</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/U-S-economy-deteriorating-faster-than-15147050.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy is deteriorating more quickly than was expected just days ago, as extraordinary measures designed to curb the coronavirus keep 84 million Americans penned in their homes and cause the near-total shutdown of most businesses.  In a single 24-hour period, the governors of three of the largest states - California, New York and Illinois - ordered residents to stay home, except to buy food and medicine, while the governor of Pennsylvania ordered the closure of nonessential businesses. Across the globe, health officials are struggling to cope with the growing number of patients, with the World Health Organization noting that while it required three months to reach 100,000 cases, it took only 12 days to hit another 100,000.  The resulting economic meltdown, which is sending several million workers streaming into the unemployment line, is outpacing the federal government's efforts to respond. As the Senate on Friday raced to complete work on a financial rescue package, the White House and key lawmakers were dramatically expanding its scope, pushing the legislation far beyond the original $1 trillion price tag.  With each day, an unprecedented stoppage gathers force, as restaurants, movie theaters, sports arenas, and offices close to shield themselves from the disease. Already, it's clear that the initial economic decline will be sharper and more painful than during the 2008 financial crisis.  Next week, roughly 3 million Americans will file first-time claims for unemployment assistance, more than four times the record high set in the depths of the 1982 recession, according to Bank of America Merrill Lynch. That's just the start of a surge that could send the jobless rate spiking to 20 percent from today's 3.5 percent, a JPMorgan Chase economist told clients on a conference call Friday.  Estimates of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Much of life comes to standstill as countries shut themselves off from rest of world... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Much-of-life-comes-to-a-standstill-as-countries-15147058.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European truck drivers stuck in miles-long backups. Asylum seekers stranded in Mexico. Cities and states within countries - from Rio de Janeiro to Tasmania - sealing themselves off from the rest of their nations.  In a world where the once-steady march of globalization hit strong head winds in recent years from nationalist governments, the novel coronavirus pandemic has done more to suddenly halt and reverse the notion of open - and easily crossed - borders than perhaps any other event in modern history.  The impact to the global economy will be severe. Yet the larger question arising from empty international airports and backed-up land borders may be the long-haul effect of the pandemic on everything from freedom of movement to asylum claims to trade.  "The question is, when the health crisis recedes, be that six months, one year, or two years from now, are we going to see the protectionist measures related to the health crisis recede too?" said Stephanie Segal, a former senior economist at the International Monetary Fund and a senior fellow at the Washington-based Center for Strategic and International Studies. "Certainly they will, but will they ever go back to precrisis levels?"  In the meantime, the pandemic is stranding travelers and upending everything from refugee flows to wedding rites.  In South America, still less impacted than other regions, many nations are striving to keep it that way by imposing some of the strictest border controls in the world. Peru and Bolivia have suspended international flights, restricted crossings at land borders, and deployed police and the military on the streets.  As concerns mount about the ability of crisis-plagued Venezuela to control the pandemic, its neighbors have sealed its borders. The closures have raised fears of a bottleneck that could force migrants - as well as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress may move to remote work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-lawmakers-begin-falling-ill-from-coronavirus-congress-may-move-to-remote-work/ar-BB11siWH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lou Dobbs in self-quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/488758-fox-business-host-lou-dobbs-in-self-quarantine-after-staffer-tests-positive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television host Lou Dobbs is in self-quarantine after a staffer on his Fox Business show tested positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To release or not to release? Music's dilemma over virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/release-not-release-musics-dilemma-over-virus-183603746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian hit-machine Weeknd held his nerve and dropped the 14-track "After Hours" Friday, with the cult British artist Baxter Dury also going ahead even though he admitted that "it's terrible timing". The Weeknd's new album for Universal had been heavily trailed on his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acts of kindness abound...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-acts-kindness-abound-us-182309839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From grocery shopping for the elderly to delivering meals or offering free classes online, acts of kindness during the coronavirus pandemic are providing uplifting moments of joy in a United States beset by anxiety. In California, the most populous state in the nation and one of the hardest hit by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, WALMART Workers Push for Paid Leave, Better Protections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-walmart-workers-push-paid-233035655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A group of workers from Walmart Inc., Amazon.com Inc. and other big retailers demanded paid leave for those affected by the coronavirus outbreak and better protective measures from their employers.The group, United for Respect, held a media call Friday with U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominican govt orders curfew...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200320233808-y5m7x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DOMINICAN REPUBLIC:Dominican government orders curfew to slow spread of coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President considers national quarantine; Only drug, grocery stores open...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/breaking-trump-eyes-2-week-quarantine-only-drug-grocery-stores-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump, moving with haste to slow the spread of the coronavirus, is preparing a plan to mobilize the National Guard to help enforce a two-week quarantine of the public if his tough-love efforts so far fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock moment wheezing man collapses on New York subway... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/568784/coronavirus-new-york-city-subway-shocking-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARROWING video shows a man who collapsed on the subway in New York City, where residents remain gripped by the coronavirus outbreak. A witness said the man had been sleeping on the R train in Broo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20% OF POPULATION NOW ON LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/568703/illinois-pritzker-stay-home-order-coronavirus-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ILLINOIS joined New York and California in lockdowns to curb coronavirus spread, as the Governor announced a “shelter in place” order on Friday. The order, limiting all residents to sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffer in Pence office tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/staffer-us-vice-presidents-office-tests-positive-virus-233451710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer in the office of US Vice President Mike Pence, the pointman for Washington's response to the coronavirus outbreak, has tested positive for the illness, a spokeswoman said Friday. Pence has appeared at Trump's side at the daily White House press conferences to announce developments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch destroy millions of flowers as sales wilt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dutch-destroy-millions-flowers-coronavirus-wilts-sales-172310836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's tulip season in The Netherlands but this year growers are destroying millions of flowers a day, in unprecedented scenes as the coronavirus pandemic has cut demand. Brightly coloured blooms that might normally have been destined for a romantic gesture or Mothers Day are scooped up by diggers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires suspected short-range missiles...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200320230104-0ahbq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (UPDATE 3, TV):UPDATE 3-North Korea fires suspected short-range missiles, S.Korea says, amid coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVO'S ANDY COHEN SICK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/andy-cohen-tests-positive-coronavirus-1202889098/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Cohen has revealed he’s tested positive for coronavirus, and his Watch What Happens Live @ Home edition is on hold for now. “After a few days of self-quarantine, and not feeling gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demands for resignations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d0279fc73d040a1a287f47ed20b4fd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing public outrage, senators in both political parties denied Friday that they exploited advance knowledge when they dumped stocks and other financial holdings before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing faces new headwind: Lab supply shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4aac3a10664097f38633149367ac3928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First, some of the coronavirus tests didn't work. Then there weren't enough to go around. Now, just as the federal government tries to ramp up nationwide screening, laboratory...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California awakes to new reality: Homebound amid outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30e5ec0a1967d46c4afbf1b11ff33f17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — While California awoke Friday to the reality of a near lockdown to prevent the spread of coronavirus, it was business as usual for Rick Curnutt and his family, who were hunkered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH:  UP TO 70,000 CASES NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nih-director-70k-coronavirus-cases-confirmed-us-end/story?id=69717284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NIH directo told employees Friday up to 70,000 coronavirus cases could be confirmed in the U.S. by the end of next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Had 'Quarantined' Mingle With Healthy Ones...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/army-had-quarantined-troops-mingle-with-healthy-ones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounts from Fort Bliss and Fort Hood describe porous quarantine conditions–as well as Army officials scrambling to do better against a pathogenic enemy they didn’t expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg's Billion Dollar Bust...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/20/mike-bloomberg-pumped-nearly-1b-into-failed-presidential-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Mike Bloomberg’s failed White House bid cost the media mogul nearly $1 billion, according to a new FEC filing — double what was previously reported. The total cost of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring break over: Miami Beach almost unrecognizable as partying ends...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spring-break-over-miami-beach-194008977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Beach, usually bustling with spring breakers at this time of year, has gone almost silent amid the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First inside Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/488688-air-force-reports-first-two-coronavirus-cases-inside-pentagon-building</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An active-duty airman and an Air Force contractor who both visited the Pentagon in recent weeks have tested positive for the coronavirus, the Air Force said Friday, in the first confirmed cases of the virus inside the world’s biggest office buildi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Selfie app' to keep track of quarantined Poles...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/selfie-app-keep-track-quarantined-poles-202517173.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland on Friday launched a smartphone app allowing people under a mandatory 14-day quarantine for coronavirus to send selfies to let authorities know they are indeed staying home. "People in quarantine have a choice: either receive unexpected visits from the police, or download this app,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Arrest Homeowner For Hosting 'Pop-Up Wedding'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/20/coronavirus-latest-lakewood-police-arrest-homeowner-for-hosting-pop-up-wedding-with-more-than-50-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier in the week, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy banned gatherings of 50 or more people in an effort to stop the spread of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow tumbles 900 points...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks turned lower Friday as investors concluded a week of wild swings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'True Fighter': 90-Year-Old Recovers After Contracting Virus At Seattle Senior Facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-90-year-old-woman-seattle-recovering-covid-19-life-care-center-kirkland-washington-geneva-wood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm going to fight this for my family and make everyone proud," Geneva Wood told her daughter when she was put in isolation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Staffers Losing Jobs -- Despite Promise...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/mollyhensleyclancy/michael-bloomberg-dnc-organizers-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He’s chopping his employees in a pandemic,” said one staffer in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Sales Spike...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/craziest-i-have-ever-seen-it-coronavirus-strains-gun-industry-background-check-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has put a strain on the gun and ammunition industry, as well as the FBI's background check system, due to surging demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputies pull over stolen trailer full of toilet paper...</title>
      <link>https://www.wect.com/2020/03/20/deputies-pull-over-stolen-trailer-full-toilet-paper-guildford-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wect.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Guilford County Sheriff’s Office issued a news release saying that deputies on Wednesday spotted the driver of an 18-wheeler and determined the trailer was stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases among troops surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2020/03/20/number-of-coronavirus-cases-among-troops-jumps-nearly-25-percent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military is seeing a steady rise in cases daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois 'to announce shelter-in-place order'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8136133/Illinois-announce-shelter-place-order-NY-California-shut-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Governor of Illinois is expected to announce a shelter-in-place order on Friday, making it the latest state to shut down after New York and California ordered their 60million combined residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WARNS SYSTEMS COLLAPSING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/20/coronavirus-who-says-health-systems-collapsing-this-isnt-just-a-bad-flu-season.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, the number of people who have died from COVID-19 in Italy surpassed that of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Brady BUCS Deal Worth $50M...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-to-the-buccaneers-heres-how-much-brady-will-earn-in-tampa-bay-per-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports indicate the longtime Patriots QB will get a significant raise in 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada To Send Back Illegal Border Crossers...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/20/republican-ken-buck-criticized-trump-over-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Colorado Rep. Ken Buck on Wednesday criticized President Donald Trump over the way he has been handling the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SHUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11219137/uk-pubs-restaurants-and-leisure-centres-to-close-nationwide-tonight-amid-coronavirus-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUBS, restaurants and leisure centres across the whole of Britain will shut “as soon as possible” tonight amid the spiralling coronavirus crisis. Boris Johnson made the unprecedented an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Chinese urge kin to leave virus-hit Europe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anxious-chinese-urge-kin-leave-virus-hit-europe-073147558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under pressure from anxious parents, Chinese citizens living in virus-hit Europe are flocking back home, with some even flying on private jets to escape the spiralling number of infections overseas. With new domestic coronavirus cases falling to zero in China, the country where the disease first emerged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa's busiest airport says foreigners can't disembark...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9634f62c20a5926b4ad94f5d301b1c5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Anxiety rose in Africa as two major airlines announced sweeping cancellations of international flights on Friday over the coronavirus and the continent's busiest airport said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Is Not Recession. It's Ice Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/03/quantifying-coming-recession/608443/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one alive has experienced an economic plunge this sudden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed begins pumping municipal bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Federal-Reserve-backstops-muni-bond-market-as-15145736.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve capped off an unprecedented week of action Friday by extending a lifeline to cash-strapped state and local governments that are about to borrow large sums as they deal with skyrocketing costs from coronavirus safety measures.  There has been a large selloff in municipal debt in recent days, driving up the borrowing costs for many states and localities that need to pay their bills.  This is the ninth major action by the Fed this week to try to stabilize financial markets, prevent the downturn from worsening and keep credit flowing to companies and households.  The Fed will make loans available to financial institutions that can be secured by "high quality" state and local bonds. This will make owning these tax-exempt municipal bonds more attractive and should help ensure there is plenty of demand for these bonds as many states and cities begin to issue more debt in the coming weeks and months.  "The Federal Reserve Board on Friday expanded its program of support for the flow of credit to the economy by taking steps to enhance the liquidity and functioning of crucial state and municipal money markets," the Fed said in a statement.  Earlier this week, the central bank slashed interest rates to zero, re-started massive purchases of U.S. Treasury debt and mortgage-backed securities, began making 0.25% loans to banks and announced backstops for numerous parts of the credit market.  Goldman Sachs predicted Thursday that over 2 million Americans likely lost their jobs this week and many companies could go bankrupt in the next three months if they do not get aid. The Fed's actions are an effort to make as many cheap loans and lines of credit available to households and businesses as possible to make it through the coronavirus recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW SOON IS TOO SOON FOR JOKES? </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241363811.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN PREDICTS -24% GDP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/20/goldman-sees-an-unprecedented-stop-of-economic-activity-with-2nd-quarter-gdp-contracting-by-24percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman economists had expected a decline of 5% in the second quarter, but they said social distancing measures have affected many sectors and will hit hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More survivors speak out on illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article241363476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed begins pumping municipal bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/20/the-federal-reserve-is-expanding-its-asset-purchases-to-include-municipal-bonds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thus far, the central bank has limited its efforts to Treasurys and mortgage-backed securities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN PREDICTS -24% GDP</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/903646/goldman-sachs-devastating-revision-gdp-growth-predictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs predicts the coronavirus crash will be bigger than it originally thought. In a Friday research note, the bank projected a 24 percent drop in the U.S. GDP in the second quarter â€” a stark revision from its prediction of a five percent drop earlier this week. Goldman Sachs does see a slight rebound in Q3 and Q4 of 12 percent and 10 percent, respectively, but that still leaves the GDP down 3.8 percent at the end of the year. A truly stunning and brutal economic forecast from Goldman Sachs: pic.twitter.com/2gvvs15RhF â€” James Pethokoukis (@JimPethokoukis) March 20, 2020 Goldman Sachs formulated its prediction by looking at past unemployment rates, the effects of Hurricane Katrina, and 'job losses by sector and occupation.' And it all forecasts a far more economically brutal future than the one the bank saw just a few days ago. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Porn Stars in 'Better Spot' Than Hollywood Actors Amid Shutdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/porn-stars-coronavirus-filming-shutdown-pornhub-sarah-vandella-maitland-ward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has brought Hollywood to its knees. The spread of COVID-19 has also done the same to San Fernando Valley (porn) productions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/nbc-news-employee-dies-after-testing-positive-coronavirus-n1164696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Edgeworth "was the guy you wanted by your side no matter where you were," NBC News Chairman Andy Lack wrote to staff members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN: Jobless claims may reach 2.25 million next week!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/jobless-claims-may-reach-225-million-goldman-sachs-economist-estimates-2020-03-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first real bad U.S. economic data from the coronavirus outbreak was released on Thursday, as initial jobless claims surged 70,000 to 281,000, the highest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power industry may ask staff to live on site...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/488609-power-industry-may-ask-staff-to-live-on-site-as-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archbishop: This Is The Time To Go Into Our Personal Prayer Life...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/20/coronavirus-in-philadelphia-archbishop-nelson-perez-says-now-is-time-to-go-into-our-personal-prayer-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyewitness News spoke with Archbishop Nelson Perez Friday morning about the coronavirus’s impact on the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church forgives sins of those stricken by virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/church-forgives-sins-those-stricken-virus-144837990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic Church on Friday granted forgiveness -- under certain conditions -- for the sins of the faithful struck by the novel coronavirus. A decree published by the Vatican also covers healthcare workers and those who pray for their wellbeing. Relatives who care for their sick family members may</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nature is taking back Venice': Wildlife returns to tourist-free city...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/mar/20/nature-is-taking-back-venice-wildlife-returns-to-tourist-free-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the cruise ships gone and the souvenir stalls closed, the coronavirus lockdown has transformed La Serenissima’s waterways</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Reports Staffer Has Died...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nbc-reports-one-of-its-news-staffers-larry-edgeworth-has-died-from-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chairman Andy Lack said in a memo early Friday that coworkers said the employee was a “gentle giant who would give you the shirt off his back.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says successfully tested hypersonic missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/usa/483638-pentagon-test-launch-hypersonic-glide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has announced that it has successfully tested a hypersonic glide body, saying that the launch will play an important role in future hypersonic technology development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demands for resignations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/20/richard-burr-kelly-loeffler-urged-to-resign-for-selling-stocks-after-coronavirus-briefing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dianne Feinstein and Jim Inhofe sold as much as $6.4 million worth of stock, as Richard Burr, Kelly Loeffler were urged to resign over coronavirus stock trades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Official: Brady Signs With BUCS...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/03/20/its-official-tom-brady-signs-his-contract-with-tampa-bay-buccaneers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were hoping Tuesday's news that Tom Brady was going to sign with the Tampa Bay Buccaneers was some sort of nightmare, it's time to wake up. Brady is officially a swashbuckler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-control teens coughing on grocery store produce...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trending-out-of-control-teens-coughing-on-grocery-store-produce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idle teenagers are participating in a “disturbing trend” of coughing on grocery store produce and posting their pranks online as the nation fights the coronavirus, which is known to spread from human “droplets” spraying from mouths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Locust crisis poses a danger to millions, forecasters warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2020/mar/20/locust-crisis-poses-a-danger-to-millions-forecasters-warn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts fear swarms like those seen in Africa will become more common as tropical storms create favourable breeding conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot firm selling 'anti-bacterial' dolls for self-isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-firm-selling-anti-21725476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex robot manufacturer RealDoll told people self-isolating from the coronavirus outbreak that they do not need to refrain from using its dolls because they are "naturally anti-bacterial"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four senators offloaded stock after classified briefings about coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8132245/GOP-senator-gave-dire-coronavirus-warning-heeled-constituents-Capitol-Hill-social-club.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans Richard Burr, Kelly Loeffler and James Inhofe, and Democrat Dianne Feinstein, all offloaded large amounts of stock between late January and early February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet Traffic Surging But Pipes Aren't Bursting Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/internet-traffic-is-surging-but-the-pipes-aren-t-bursting-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet Traffic is Surging But The Pipes Arenâ€™t Bursting Yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Industry Braces for Disruptions From Ill Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-20/threat-of-sick-workers-at-u-s-meat-plants-forces-policy-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's virus kills priests who bless the dying...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italys-virus-kills-priests-bless-dying-112825691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diocese of Bergamo northeast of Milan appears to have been ravaged the most by the stealth killer. All these parishes are clustered in Italy's north, the virus's target from the day the Catholic country's first death was reported four weeks ago. Italy has taken over the grim title of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From plague to coronavirus, French brotherhood keeps burying the dead...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200320105732-whhbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-PALLBEARERS (TV, PIX):From plague to coronavirus, French brotherhood keeps burying the dead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chilling' Plans: Who Gets Care When Hospitals Reach Max?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/20/chilling-plans-who-gets-care-when-washington-state-hospitals-reach-their-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — Medical leaders in Washington State, which has the highest number of coronavirus deaths in the country, have quietly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents, police struggle to herd the young...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6eb1c0c83b87eac98611ac45625de63f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teen: “I can't stay here all day. What about my friends!?” Parent: “Are you kidding? This is serious!" The adolescent brain is definitely in play as authorities around the globe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Others Sold Holdings Around Same Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/aoc-calls-senate-intel-chair-richard-burr-resign-stock-selloff-n1164401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Carolina Republican dumped up to $1.6 million of his holdings in mid-February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second dog tests positive as owners warned not to abandon pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/second-dog-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-as-owners-warned-not-to-abandon-pets-2020-03-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hong Kong government has urged people not to abandon their pets and to stop kissing them after a second dog repeatedly tested positive for coronavirus....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Best-Case Outcome, and Worst...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/20/the-best-case-outcome-for-the-coronavirus-and-the-worst/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s the grimmest version of life a year from now: More than two million Americans have died from the new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland World's Happiest Country...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/20/smile-the-results-from-the-2020-world-happiness-report-are-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might seem an odd time to release a report ranking which countries are happiest. After all, who can really</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX, YOUTUBE reduce resolution as virus hits web...</title>
      <link>http://www.anews.com.tr/economy/2020/03/20/netflix-and-youtube-reduce-resolution-as-virus-hits-web</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.anews.com.tr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix and YouTube reduce resolution as virus hits web</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Hopkins plays piano for cat during quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/19/anthony-hopkins-plays-piano-for-cat-while-at-home-amid-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Niblo is making sure I stay healthy,” the Oscar winner said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE IN THE BUBBLE</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-patients-apocalypse-ward-gasp-21723273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients are seen lining walls throughout a Bergamo hospital in bubble helmets as medics desperately plea for the UK to lock down or face the same horrors they have - with the Italy death toll having surpassed China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELAY REPORTING NUMBERS?</title>
      <link>https://www.fxstreet.com/analysis/trump-asks-states-to-hide-unemployment-claim-data-202003200202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fxstreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKMAN:  We need to get Fed out of way. We need higher interest rates not lower...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/stockman-coronavirus-sparking-financial-crisis-wall-street-is-toast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former OMB director David Stockman believes Main Street is better equipped to deal with a recession than Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE-WIDE LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/19/california-governor-issues-statewide-order-to-stay-at-home-effective-thursday-evening.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Governor Gavin Newsom on Thursday issued a statewide order for all residents to 'stay at home' amid a coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia deploys innovative, if invasive, tech to curb virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asia-deploys-innovative-invasive-tech-curb-virus-015625449.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Electronic bracelets and phones that report your whereabouts, text messages if you stray too far from quarantine and digital detectives tracking where you've been -- Asian countries have embraced innovative, if somewhat invasive, tech to counter the coronavirus pandemic. When Hong Kong stylist Declan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  2nd Republican senator dumped millions after briefing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sen-kelly-loeffler-dumped-millions-in-stock-after-coronavirus-briefing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Georgia Republican is the second senator who has gotten rid of their holdings right as the stock market went bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP URGES DELAY OF NUMBERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/19/business/economy/coronavirus-employers-unemployment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New filings for unemployment benefits rose 30 percent last week amid cutbacks and shutdowns over the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak: A Cascade of Warnings, Heard but Unheeded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/coronavirus-outbreak-a-cascade-of-warnings-heard-but-unheeded/ar-BB11pYY1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Vice President Candidates? Party Leaders Favor Former Rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/biden-vice-president-candidates-party-leaders-favor-former-rivals/ar-BB11qB8I?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
