<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Aloha shirts on 'boogaloos' link symbol of peace to violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-race-and-ethnicity-elections-hawaii-civil-wars-c91fbd31b1eadae3179bdfabf174dbac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — People following a violent movement that promotes a second U.S. civil war or the breakdown of modern society have been showing up at recent protests across the nation armed and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope again cancels appearances due to nerve pain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-vatican-city-pope-francis-4e1aa0c402e6d6c5895a1f1c8656e972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis is once again canceling public appearances due to nerve pain. Francis will not participate in three events over the coming days “due to a recurrence of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 78 and oldest president, Biden sees world changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-race-and-ethnicity-ronald-reagan-pennsylvania-48d1659d4469999be87fbd87d560a52c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Joe Biden took the oath of office as the 46th president, he became not only the oldest newly inaugurated U.S. chief executive in history but also the oldest sitting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ, FBI debate not charging some of the Capitol rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/doj-capitol-rioters-charges-debate/2021/01/23/3b0cf112-5d97-11eb-8bcf-3877871c819d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials are considering forgoing charges against those who went into Congress but are not linked to violence, threats or destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why McConnell Dumped Donald...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/02/01/why-mcconnell-dumped-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Capitol assault—and after losing his perch as Majority Leader—the senator finally denounced the outgoing President. Was it a moral reckoning or yet another act of political self-interest?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17% of America has been infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/01/23/covid-cases-updates-larry-king-dies-after-being-hospitalized-covid-19/6674844002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A model estimates 168,000 more U.S. COVID-19 deaths before May. Meanwhile, about 5% of Americans have received a vaccine dose. Latest COVID-19 news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests of Biden leadership, and GOP willingness to cooperate, come quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/tests-of-biden-e2-80-99s-leadership-and-gop-e2-80-99s-willingness-to-cooperate-come-quickly/ar-BB1d1NFv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president hopes to show government can work effectively to combat the pandemic and revive the economy while trying to change the political climate in the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barred From USA Under Trump, Muslims Exult in Biden Open Door...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/23/barred-from-u-s-under-trump-muslims-exult-in-bidens-open-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya — As the results of the American presidential election rolled in on Nov. 4, a young Sudanese couple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Find Weather May Have Effect On Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/weather-effect-stock-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the reasons for the ups and downs of the stock market, weather is rarely given any credit. Certain meteorological events, like devastating hurricanes or tornadoes, obviously have at least a short-term effect on market events. But researchers have found correlations between the stock market an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 most memorable...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/01/23/here-are-larry-kings-10-most-memorable-interviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry King conducted more than 50,000 interviews during his storied career. Here are some of his most memorable: Frank Sinatra Larry King interviewing Frank Sinatra in 1988. King called his 1988 si…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin defied...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98not-afraid-e2-80-99-protesters-across-russia-defy-putin-in-marches-for-jailed-opposition-leader-navalny/ar-BB1d19Pk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police made widespread arrests as protests took place from the Far East to Moscow in a powerful message to the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile systems deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1387983/China-Taiwan-latest-news-World-War-3-fears-conflict-invasion-war-missile-fighter-bomber</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has breached Taiwan's Air Defence Zone with eight bombers and four fighter jets in a blatant provocation against the autonomous island, sending a clear signal to new US President Joe Biden in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro could face charges in The Hague over rainforest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/23/jair-bolsonaro-could-face-charges-in-the-hague-over-amazon-rainforest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indigenous leaders and human rights groups accuse Brazilian president of crimes against humanity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing numbers choose own spiritual path; Reject traditional faiths...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2021/jan/23/atheists-agnostics-non-believers-on-the-meaning-of-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around the world, growing numbers of people are rejecting traditional faiths and choosing their own spiritual path. Eight atheists and agnostics open up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang of 100 monkeys raid farm to steal food after lack of tourists cut off supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9176511/Gang-100-monkeys-raids-farm-steal-food-Thailand-Covid-19-cut-food-supply.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video footage shows adult and baby monkeys - which are normally fed by tourists - racing to grab chunks of corn to eat in Thailand's Nakhon Ratchasima province on January 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I've never learned anything while I was talking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/23/us/larry-king-dies-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry King, the longtime CNN host who became an icon through his interviews with countless newsmakers and his sartorial sensibilities, has died. He was 87.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests across Russia demand Navalny release; Hundreds arrested...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vladimir-putin-moscow-arrests-europe-russia-56e06f50eab494213d09346a5d9b4e69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Protests erupted in cities across Russia on Saturday to demand the release of opposition leader Alexei Navalny, the Kremlin's most prominent foe. Police arrested more than 1,600...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's GOAT? Rodgers-Brady Debate Plays Out in NFC Title Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/college/cal/news/rodgers-brady-nfc-title-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Cal star Rodgers has been better this season, but he must prove it again Sunday when Packers face Buccaneers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer's 99 problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/23/chuck-schumer-mcconnell-problems-461406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Senate majority leader faces a "perfect storm" as his tenure begins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxygen Shortage Plunges Amazon Capital Into Covid Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/oxygen-shortage-plunges-the-amazon-s-capital-into-a-covid-nightmare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oxygen Shortage Plunges the Amazon's Capital Into a Covid Nightmare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French doctors: Don't talk on public transport...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210123134926-iugyt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-METRO (PIX):Don't talk on the subway, say French doctors, to limit COVID-19 spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Being 'Fat But Fit' Is Myth...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fat-but-healthy-is-a-myth-heart-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compared to inactive normal weight people, those who are active and obese are still around twice as likely to have high cholesterol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALK LEGEND LARRY KING DEAD IN LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9112391/Larry-King-dies-age-87-poor-Brooklyn-kid-legendary-TV-host-conducted-50-000-interviews.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary late night host, Larry King's incredible rags to riches story that resulted in a 65-year-long career on radio and TV - interviewing presidents, celebrities, world leaders and athletes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Consciousness? Scientists Compete to Find Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/what-is-consciousness-scientists-around-the-world-compete-to-find-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What Is Consciousness? Scientists Compete to Find Out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan reports large incursion by Chinese air force...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-china-security-idUSKBN29S0BK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight Chinese bomber planes and four fighter jets entered the southwestern corner of Taiwan's air defence identification zone on Saturday, and Taiwan's air force deployed missiles to "monitor" the incursion, the island's Defence Ministry said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top astronomer says solar system teeming with alien tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstatesman.com/science-tech/space/2021/01/harvard-s-top-astronomer-says-our-solar-system-may-be-teeming-alien</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you could fly two billion miles in the direction of the Pegasus constellation, and knew where to look, you would find a thin, flat object, about the size of a football field and up to ten times more reflective than the average comet. If you watched it for a while, you would notice that it is tumbling as it moves away from the sun, turning end over end roughly every seven hours. This object passed the Earth in October 2017. As it began its return to interstellar space, the Canadian astronomer Robert Weryk identified it among the images from what was then the world’s most powerful camera, a telescope in Hawaii called Pan-STARRS1. The astronomers in Hawaii called it ‘Oumuamua, a Hawaiian word meaning “first scout from a distant place”. ‘Oumuamua was the subject of great excitement. It was the first object humans have observed travelling through the solar system from interstellar space. But it also became controversial: its shape, the way in which it approached us, and the way it moved away are not consistent with the behaviour of an asteroid or comet. For 11 days, the world’s telescopes searched for meaning from this strange visitor. A year later, the debate about ‘Oumuamua intensified when one of the world’s foremost astronomers, Avi Loeb, submitted a paper to the Astrophysical Journal Letters. In it, Loeb and his colleague, Shmuel Bailey, argued that ‘Oumuamua’s strange properties indicated that it was “a new class of thin interstellar material, either produced naturally, through a yet unknown process […] or of an artificial origin”. Since then, Loeb has maintained that the most rational, conservative explanation is that ‘Oumuamua was produced by an alien civilisation. We will almost certainly never see ‘Oumuamua again, because it is heading away from the solar system at 30 kilometres a second. But Loeb says scientists must prepare now for what happens when the next such object arrives, as he believes it will very soon. If he is right, these objects surround us in numbers that are almost unimaginable. *** Avi Loeb is a fast talker; he has the rapid fluency of someone who has spent decades giving lectures, but there is also an unpractised enthusiasm to his speech. He keeps the accent of his native Israel, though he has lived in the US since 1988, when he took a fellowship at Princeton University. His first interview was with the famous physicist Freeman Dyson, who was also well known for theorising about alien civilisations. Loeb spent almost a decade as chair of Harvard’s astronomy department, the longest any scientist has held that position. He has made or helped to make a number of major breakthroughs in our understanding of the universe, including different ways of detecting exoplanets – planets orbiting stars other than the sun. He has correctly predicted incredible phenomena, such as stars that streak across the depths between galaxies at nearly half a billion miles an hour. He is the founding director of Harvard’s Black Hole Initiative, part of the Event Horizon Telescope project that in April 2019 presented to the world the first photograph of a black hole. Practically all of Loeb’s predictions have had the backing of his peers, except one. In the autumn of 2019, Loeb and a colleague – a senior astronomer at Harvard – attended a seminar on ‘Oumuamua. “After it ended,” Loeb told me, “I left the room together with a colleague of mine who is a conservative, mainstream astronomer, and he said: ‘This object is so weird – I wish it never existed.’” This is, Loeb says, “a terrible thing to say for a scientist… you should accept with open arms anything that nature gives you”. But he has also found such attitudes to be common. There is, he says, a widespread “taboo” on talking about extraterrestrial intelligence. Why does Loeb believe that ‘Oumuamua was alien technology? First, unlike most things in space, ‘Oumuamua was not moving relative to what astronomers call the local standard of rest. Loeb calls this a “very special frame of reference, sort of the galactic parking lot”. It was not that ‘Oumuamua visited us but that the sun and its attendant planets, moving through space at 450,000 miles an hour, moved past it, the sun’s gravity bumping it as a ship’s wake disturbs a piece of flotsam. But what really excites Loeb is what happened next. ‘Oumuamua “showed an excess push away from the sun, in addition to the sun's gravitational force acting on it”. This happens with comets, which can speed up as the frozen material on them vaporises, causing them to swerve through space and producing a distinctive “tail”. Based on the change in its speed, Loeb says ‘Oumuamua would have had to lose “about a tenth of its mass. That's quite a lot… we should have seen a very clear cloud of gas around it.” But ‘Oumuamua had no tail. Close observation by the Spitzer Space Telescope saw nothing around it; it did not even radiate any heat. And it did not move erratically, as comets do, but accelerated smoothly away from the sun. The most rational explanation for this, Loeb says, is that it was pushed by sunlight itself. ‘Oumuamua’s shape is also distinct from almost everything else we have observed in space. Its brightness varied by a factor of ten every eight hours, suggesting “a very extreme geometry”. The most popular depiction of ‘Oumuamua is of a long, cigar-shaped rock, but research by Sergey Mashchenko, a computational astrophysicist at McMaster University in Canada, suggests a 91 per cent chance that it is disc-shaped. Each of these factors is highly unlikely for any astronomical object. Taken together, Loeb says, they make ‘Oumuamua “a very rare object, if it's coming from the same reservoir of objects [asteroids and comets] that we are familiar with”. For Loeb, the rational answer is to find something that fits the data and is familiar to us. Astronomers were able to do this in September, when another object, called 2020 SO, was discovered in orbit around the Earth. Just like ‘Oumuamua, 2020 SO appeared to have been pushed from its gravitational course by sunlight. And this time, Nasa confirmed that 2020 SO was artificial. It was a piece of a Centaur rocket, launched from Florida in 1966, that had been recaptured by the Earth’s gravity. For Loeb, 2020 SO “illustrates the fact that we can identify an object that behaves in a peculiar fashion, that has no cometary tail, and yet it exhibits an extra push. And if ‘Oumuamua, indeed, was that kind of an object, the question is: who produced it?” *** Loeb’s biggest concern about ‘Oumuamua is not that it has disappeared from sight, but that the response to it “betrays the culture of science”. The Copernican principle, the change in thinking that allowed humanity to begin modern astronomy, states that we are not at the centre of the universe. To pretend, in the face of confounding data, that ‘Oumuamua is just another asteroid is to act as if we are. Loeb’s sense of scale and probability is informed by a long study of the early universe. In a 2014 paper, he described the likelihood that rocky planets with liquid water provided the chemistry to support life when the universe was as little as ten million years old. In the 13.8 billion years since that time, billions of galaxies – each home to billions of Earth-like planets – have formed. To say that life, intelligence and civilisation have emerged only once in such an expanse of time and space is, he argues, a radical view. [see also: How Chinese novelists are reimagining science fiction] “There is nothing more conservative than saying that if you arrange for the same circumstances, you get the same outcome,” he says. For Loeb, the conservative assumption about humanity is “that we are a middle-of-the-road kind of life that exists everywhere. I don't think that we are special or unique.” But if we are not unique, it follows that ‘Oumuamua is not unique, either. Pan-STARRS began searching for near-Earth objects in early 2014, and discovered ‘Oumuamua in under four years. Applying the Copernican principle, we should assume that we will see another object once every three or four years. But this frequency may change, because our ability to see them is about to increase. This year, the telescope at the Vera C Rubin Observatory in Chile will take its first test pictures – astronomers call this “first light” – of the night sky. Even more powerful than Pan-STARRS, this will repeatedly photograph everything visible in the sky using a mirror more than eight metres across and the biggest digital camera in the world. “We could then find one such object every month,” says Loeb, “because, you know, there should be many more out there.” The question of how many ‘Oumuamuas are out there is the point at which the inferences become dizzying. If we see one every few years, Loeb infers that “there should be one in every volume roughly the size of the orbit of the Earth around the sun”. This is a vast area in human terms, but in the immensity of space, “it's pretty small. So it means that there are plenty of them, a quadrillion of them, inside the Oort cloud. Inside the solar system. There are lots of them.” It is difficult to reconcile the idea that we are surrounded by trillions of pieces of alien technology with scientific conservatism. Humanity’s understanding of itself would be radically changed if we knew that other life had once built such things. But Loeb believes, as he explains in his compelling and personal new book on ‘Oumuamua, Extraterrestrial: The First Sign of Intelligent Life Beyond Earth, that humanity’s understanding of itself should change now. The book is not so much a claim for one object as an argument for a more open-minded approach to science – a combination of humility and wonder that he worries has been supplanted by elitism and “intellectual gymnastics”. “The crime here,” he tells me, is that a whole branch of astronomy, “a subject that is so appealing to the public, that the scientific community can address with its instruments and methodology, is not being addressed at all.” But if Loeb is right, we may soon have no choice but to wonder. Next month, on 18 February, the Perseverance rover will land on Mars to search for signs of life. Any evidence, even of ancient microbes, on our celestial neighbour would suggest that life is far more abundant than is generally accepted. “We might learn much more in the coming year,” says Loeb. “So, let's wait and see.” [see also: M John Harrison: “A number of novels don’t sit well in their genre of origin”]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot 'brain' chip unleashes physical potential of machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/robot-brain-ai-artificial-intelligence-b1791243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robomorphic computing could ‘unlock exciting behaviours’, says Boston Dynamics engineer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanist sex robots, vampire dolls hailed 'perfect' by customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/satanist-sex-robots-vampire-dolls-23371522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A RealDoll worker received the requests after sharing images of some of the company's models on social media. Sex robot "humanoids" have previously been linked with satanism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny wife detained as protests in his support sweep across Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/23/europe/russia-navalny-oposition-demonstrations-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yulia Navalnaya, the wife of the detained Kremlin critic Alexey Navalny, has been detained in Moscow on the sidelines of a protest held in support of her husband on Saturday, according to a video posted on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Hospitalized With Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/larry-king-dies-age-87/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He died Saturday in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pandemic Plight: Hospitals Running Out of Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/23/new-pandemic-plight-hospitals-are-running-out-of-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus tears across much of Texas, Dr. Esmaeil Porsa is grappling with one of the most formidable challenges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaves a Broadcast Legacy Of Stars and Infomercials...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/23/rip-larry-king-dies-of-covid-related-pneumonia-at-age-87-leaves-a-broadcast-legacy-of-stars-and-infomercials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overnight, Larry King has died at Cedars Sinai Hospital in Los Angeles from COVID. He never made it out even though on Monday I reported he was supposed to leave the hospital. He did leave, I am to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALK LEGEND LARRY KING DEAD IN LA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/los-angeles-larry-king-media-celebrity-coronavirus-pandemic-391f55fabb843d14a2635a9bd55880d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Larry King, the suspenders-sporting everyman whose broadcast interviews with world leaders, movie stars and ordinary Joes helped define American conversation for a half-century,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French doctors: Don't talk on public transport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-united-nations-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-asia-pacific-77fdfef687dbb5f635ec4eb6c16e83a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — French doctors have new advice to slow the spread of the virus: stop talking on public transport. The French Academy of Doctors issued guidance Friday saying people should “avoid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Hospitalized With Covid...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/american-tv-host-larry-king-died/story?id=75443074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pellicano Back in Business and Working for Joel Silver...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/anthony-pellicano-joel-silver-daryl-katz-1234889846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Pellicano, the former private eye who spent 16 years in federal prison, is back in business as a Hollywood fixer. Pellicano confirmed to Variety that he is working for Joel Silver, the &amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census estimates show population decline in 16 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/01/21/census-estimates-show-population-decline-in-16-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low birth rates, COVID-19 deaths and immigration cutbacks contributed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA PEAK DEATH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-reports-277-covid-19-225900932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Florida’s daily COVID-19 death toll hit 277 Friday, tying the state record for resident and non-resident deaths from the disease. Florida reported 13,719 new coronavirus cases on Friday and another 272 new resident deaths linked to COVID-19. The state has now reported 1,627,603 cases since the pandemic began. The death toll tied the state record set Aug. 11, as the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App gives men '24-hour consent contract' to have sex after Denmark passes controversial rape law...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2186952/fury-at-app-that-gives-24-hour-consent-contract-to-have-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW app that gives men a “24 hour consent contract” to have sex has sparked fury. The launch comes in response to a new rape law, which criminalises sex without explicit consent in De…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLMERT: I hate everything Sheldon Adelson loved about Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/opinion/olmert-i-hate-everything-sheldon-adelson-loved-about-israel-opinion-656289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything I love about Israel has nothing to do with Adelson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden officials weigh releasing Trump tax records sought by House panel...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-officials-weigh-releasing-Trump-tax-records-15891567.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats have renewed their long-stalled demand for former president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOC plans to vaccinate every Olympic athlete to save Tokyo games...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210122203254-t21a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPICS-2020/WHO (URGENT):IOC plans to vaccinate every Olympic athlete to save Tokyo games -Telegraph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium bans leisure travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-pandemics-europe-leisure-travel-south-america-5e820f285a726db40debd0d6eb96c73d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Belgium is banning all leisure travel abroad for its citizens as of next week and until March, in an effort to contain the spread of COVID-19 and its virulent variants....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Guard in DC forced to sleep in garages, sparking outcry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-riots-6c9bd3ed150cbb6c3cf0b90084440293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Images of National Guard soldiers camped in a cold parking garage after being sent to protect Washington sparked new calls Friday for investigations of the U.S. Capitol Police,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden thanks with chocolate chip cookies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-jill-biden-b766529a8dd024ba37a2265cf97667b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — New first lady Jill Biden took an unannounced detour to the U.S. Capitol on Friday to deliver baskets of chocolate chip cookies to National Guard members, thanking them “for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYPILLOW CEO Hires GAWKER-Killing Lawyer to take on DAILY MAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mypillow-ceo-mike-lindell-hires-charles-harder-to-go-after-daily-mail-for-jane-krakowski-affair-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tabloid story “damaged my integrity as a Christian,” Lindell said to The Daily Beast in confirming he has retained the Trump lawyer most infamous for taking on media outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED AIRLINES TO REQUIRE JAB FOR ALL EMPLOYEES?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/united-airlines-ceo-wants-to-make-covid-vaccines-mandatory-for-its-employees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines CEO wants to make Covid vaccines mandatory for the company's employees, a stance that differs from other airlines and sectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But prospects erode?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/22/politics/senate-republicans-trump-impeachment-case/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path in the Senate to convict Donald Trump is extremely slim, with a growing number of Republicans expressing confidence that the party will acquit the former President on a charge that he incited the deadly insurrection aimed at stopping President Joe Biden's electoral win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Tax Hike Coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/pete-buttigieg-puts-gas-tax-hike-table-during-confirmation-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two days in office and the Biden administration is already considering breaking President Biden’s campaign promise that “anyone making less than $400,000 a year won’t pay a penny more” in taxes.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;During his Senate confirmation hearing for Transportation Secretary, Former Mayor Pete Buttigieg told members of the Commerce, Science and Transportation Committee that a gas tax increase is “on the table” as a means to pay for infrastructure spending.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;When asked directly by Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists make paralyzed mice walk again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/22/german-scientists-make-paralyzed-mice-walk-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German researchers have enabled mice paralyzed after spinal cord injuries to walk again, re-establishing a neural link hitherto considered irreparable in mammals by using a designer protein injecte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  NOTHING CAN CHANGE TRAJECTORY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/biden-says-nothing-can-change-the-trajectory-of-covid-pandemic-over-the-next-several-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES ousts editor who had 'chills' watching plane land...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/22/ny-times-ousts-editor-who-said-she-had-chills-watching-biden-plane-land/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York Times editor’s contract has been cancelled after she tweeted she had “chills” watching Joe Biden’s plane ahead of his inauguration. “Biden’s plane lan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Pentagon Chief Unloads: 'This f*cking place is rotten'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/01/embedding-with-pentagon-leadership-in-trumps-chaotic-last-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout the final, frenzied days of the Trump administration, a reporter rode shotgun with the outgoing acting defense secretary, Christopher Miller, the man who, under the distracted eye of his commander in chief, became America’s de facto guardian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems float 14th Amendment to bar from office...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/535467-democrats-float-14th-amendment-to-bar-trump-from-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are mulling whether they can use the 14th Amendment to prevent former President Trump from ever holding office again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giant suspends second AI ethics researcher...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-suspends-second-ai-ethics-165936450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google has suspended an artificial intelligence ethics researcher weeks after dismissing another member of the team, a recently formed union said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy takes action against TIKTOK following girl's death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sicily-italy-dad71e550ff2f8d3fca56d0f40e3c95e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy’s data protection authority said Friday it was imposing an immediate block on TikTok’s access to data for any user whose age has not been verified. The authority said it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada ramps up deportations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-canada-deportation/exclusive-canada-deporting-thousands-even-as-pandemic-rages-idUSKBN29R1EL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada deported thousands of people even as COVID-19 raged last year, data seen by Reuters shows, and lawyers say deportations are ramping up, putting people needlessly at risk in the midst of a global health emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Packed like sardines': Struggles to contain Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/22/national-guard-coronavirus-461340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Guard members who poured into Washington after the Jan. 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol have tested positive for Covid-19 or are quarantining in nearby hotels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Reportedly Cancels Editor Who Tweeted 'Chills' on Inauguration Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-york-times-cancels-contract-of-editor-who-tweeted-having-chills-on-biden-inauguration-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times has reportedly terminated the contract of an editor who tweeted that she had "chills" while watching President Joe Biden's plane land.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
