<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rebels defy mandates with coughs, 'corona parties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/22/coronavirus-rebels-defy-mandates-coughs-corona-par/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young German adults hold “corona parties” and cough toward older people. A Spanish man leashes a goat to go for a walk to skirt confinement orders. From France to Florida to Australia, kitesurfers, college students and others crowd the beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of cases may be 'silent carriers', classified Chinese data suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3076323/third-coronavirus-cases-may-be-silent-carriers-classified</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 43,000 people in China had tested positive without immediate symptoms by the end of February and were quarantined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hottest Parties in Town Now Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news/the-hottest-parties-in-town-are-now-online/ar-BB11wffr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Catholic Church Bells To Ring 5 Times A Day As Call To Prayer...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/chicago-catholic-church-bells-to-ring-5-times-a-day-as-call-to-prayer-during-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic church bells will be ringing throughout Chicago every three hours as a call for all to unite in prayer during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Writes to Kim Jong-un Offering Help in Virus Fight, NKorea Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-writes-to-kim-jong-un-offering-help-in-virus-fight-north-korea-says/ar-BB11wg3x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC officials publish guide to intimacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8138777/New-York-City-officials-publish-graphic-guide-getting-intimate-coronavirus-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYC Health issued a two-page memo Saturday listing its advice on how people can enjoy a - literally - healthy sex life while still protecting themselves from being infected with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE NEGATIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/olivianiland/mike-karen-pence-coronavirus-test-staffer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president got tested after a staffer came up positive. The White House encouraged Americans who are not displaying symptoms to not be tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's worst-hit region announces stricter measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51991972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4,825 people have died in Italy since the coronavirus outbreak began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems grow nervous over delays...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/488685-democrats-grow-nervous-over-primary-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are increasingly nervous about the coronavirus pandemic upending the Democratic primary calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll companies trying to cash in...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/21/naturally-antibacterial-sex-doll-companies-trying-to-cash-in-on-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex doll companies have an important public service message: Self-isolating can be fun and safe at the same time. Abyss, the maker of sex robots RealDolls, assured potential buyers that its dolls a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air quality picking up in quarantined countries...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/air-quality-picking-quarantined-countries-094306534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air quality is improving in countries under coronavirus quarantines, experts say, but it is far too early to speak of long-term change. Images by the US space agency NASA are clear, in February the concentration of nitrogen dioxide (NO2) fell dramatically in Wuhan, China, the epicentre of the COVID-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspired By Italy, Dallas Residents Sing From Apt Windows...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/03/21/819603870/inspired-by-italy-dallas-residents-sing-together-from-their-apartment-windows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an act of solidarity amid social distancing and the coronavirus pandemic, residents of a Dallas apartment complex leaned out of their windows to sing "Lean on Me."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader refuses US help, citing conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5f39091afda3b07a70464e602d844ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — The arrival of the coronavirus in the Gaza Strip, an impoverished enclave where the health care system has been gutted by years of conflict, raised fears Sunday the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to quarantine all arrivals to state for 14 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a9267e5e23aa5cd66b1d407e13550e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii's governor has instituted a mandatory 14-day self-quarantine starting Thursday of all people traveling to the state as part of efforts to fight the spread of coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea praises Trump for coronavirus outreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/22/north-korea-donald-trump-letter-offers-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump sent a personal letter to North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, seeking to maintain good relations and offering cooperation in fighting the viral pandemic, Kim’s sister said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUSTRALIA SHUTS DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8139579/Australia-SHUTS-Scott-Morrison-orders-restaurants-pubs-close-TOMORROW.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister met with state and territory leaders on Sunday night to discuss further measures to stem the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-ins enjoy sales boom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-korea-drive-cinemas-enjoy-sales-boom-over-053925730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long queue of cars forms in front of a drive-in cinema in Seoul, as South Koreans look for safer spaces to enjoy a movie without the risk of contracting the coronavirus raging across the world. Box office numbers in South Korea -- which has 8,897 confirmed virus cases -- have plummeted in recent weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus advances around the world as medical supplies dwindle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/86ca5e1f6032314115176190c380818d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOAVE, Italy (AP) — Italy, Iran and the United States reported soaring new death tolls as the coronavirus pandemic marched relentlessly across the globe Sunday, prompting a scramble in hard-hit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas also at risk from coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ccca2d0e218411cb6b8aa8d60f8357c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAMPALA, Uganda (AP) — As the coronavirus infects more people around the world, conservationists are warning of the risk to another vulnerable species: Africa's endangered mountain gorilla....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could peak in 32 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-york-surgeon-warns-coronavirus-015200406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the hospital system at risk of being overwhelmed, Dr. Craig Smith issues a warning: &amp;quot;The hard data has become alarming.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Who lives and who dies': Crisis to test medical ethics
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/03/22/coronavirus-crisis-medical-ethics-guide-decisions-doctors-cant-help-all/2882738001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals might not have enough ventilators to care for coronavirus patients. Ethics could guide doctors' decisions on who gets care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain deploys robots that 'test 80,000 patients a day'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/spain-deploys-coronavirus-robots-test-21733020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Spanish government is planning to test 80,000 patients a day using robots in a bid to fight against the coronavirus outbreak ravaging the country following a surge of cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinic worker found dead in her kitchen while waiting for delayed test results...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/572255/39-year-old-new-orleans-woman-dies-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 39-YEAR-old medical clinic worker has been found dead in her kitchen while waiting for her delayed coronavirus test results. Natasha Ott told her partner she felt the beginnings of a cold coming …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's death toll feeds fear of what lies ahead in Europe and USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Italy-s-coronavirus-death-toll-feeds-fear-of-what-15148487.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The locus of the coronavirus shifted to Europe on Saturday, with Italy bearing the brunt of the pandemic's unceasing spread. Italian officials announced that 791 people had succumbed to the virus in a single day. The staggering number brought the nation's total dead to more than 4,800, the most for a single country.  As death tolls mount across the continent, Italy has become a symbol of the enormous challenges facing public health authorities, in Europe and in the U.S., who are struggling to contain the virus.  Eleven days into Italy's nationwide lockdown, which includes travel restrictions and the closure of most stores apart from groceries and pharmacies, the number of confirmed cases still soared, with 6,557 new cases since Friday. Hospitals and morgues were overwhelmed. The government has reported 53,578 total cases, with the northern part of the country bearing the brunt.  Italy's struggle to keep up with the virus offered a glimpse into what U.S. health officials fear could be ahead in New York and elsewhere: shortages of respirators, basic medical equipment and beds in intensive-care units.  Among the help coming to northern Italy is a team of 65 Cuban doctors and nurses with experience in battling Ebola outbreaks, Italian health officials said. In Bergamo, among the most devastated areas, military trucks have lined up outside a hospital to take the dead to faraway crematoriums.  Italy now stands atop a grim list of global statistics, surpassing the death toll in China, where the virus originated. But surging rates of infection were not limited to the country.  In Spain, nearly 5,000 new cases were reported Saturday. The nation's death toll, which was about 1,000 on Friday, ticked up to 1,326 in a single day. Spain's military was called in to convert a convention center in Madrid to a field hospital with 5,500...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 50 NYPD officers infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/over-50-nypd-officers-test-positive-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to NYPD Commissioner Dermot Shea, over 50 police officers have tested positive for COVID-19, but only one has been hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY in Trouble? Media Giant Seeks $6 Billion With New Debt Offering...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-looks-to-raise-6-billion-with-new-debt-offering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company plans to use funds for "general corporate purposes"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. intelligence reports from January and February warned about likely pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Intelligence-officials-early-alarms-about-15147137.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. intelligence agencies were issuing ominous, classified warnings in January and February about the global danger posed by the coronavirus while President Donald Trump and lawmakers played down the threat and failed to take action that might have slowed the spread of the pathogen, according to U.S. officials familiar with spy agency reporting.  The intelligence reports didn't predict when the virus might land on U.S. shores or recommend particular steps that public health officials should take, issues outside the purview of the intelligence agencies. But they did track the spread of the virus in China, and later in other countries, and warned that Chinese officials appeared to be minimizing the severity of the outbreak.  Taken together, the reports and warnings painted an early picture of a virus that showed the characteristics of a globe-encircling pandemic that could require governments to take swift actions to contain it. But despite that constant flow of reporting, Trump continued publicly and privately to play down the threat the virus posed to Americans. Lawmakers, too, did not grapple with the virus in earnest until this month, as officials scrambled to keep citizens in their homes and hospitals braced for a surge in patients suffering from covid-19, the disease caused by the coronavirus.  Intelligence agencies "have been warning on this since January," said a U.S. official who had access to intelligence reporting that was disseminated to members of Congress and their staffs as well as to officials in the Trump administration, and who, along with others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe sensitive information.  "Donald Trump may not have been expecting this, but a lot of other people in the government were - they just couldn't get him to do anything about it," this official said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could take bailout cash to save his hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/572160/trump-coronavirus-hurting-hotels-hundreds-fired-mar-a-lago-closed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has admitted the coronavirus pandemic is “hurting” his hotels after “hundreds of workers were fired and Mar-a-Lago closed,” reports say. And the President refus…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Drops Deficit Dogma...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/germany-drops-deficit-dogma-as-deaths-surge-in-italy-spain/ar-BB11vRQG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Americans stranded abroad as money, patience run out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/thousands-of-americans-stranded-abroad-as-money-patience-run-out/ar-BB11vJu2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu implores Gantz to join gov't, vows to rotate as PM without tricks...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-says-unity-deal-with-Blue-and-White-reached-621811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I will leave office on the agreed date, there will be no shticks and tricks. Millions of Israelis are waiting for us."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I don't know what government assistance would be for what I have'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/21/trump-i-dont-know-if-my-businesses-will-receive-coronavirus-aid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I just don't know what the government assistance would be for what I have," President Donald Trump said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia now looks safer than USA?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mess-america-why-asia-now-231402220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a clear sign that the U.S. botched its coronavirus response, some Americans are relieved they stayed in countries closest to the outbreak's origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain tells shoppers to stop panic-buying...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-tells-shoppers-stop-panic-buying-195358294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With supermarket shelves still being stripped of essential items, including toilet paper, officials said there was no need for panic. "There's no risk of food running out," Environment Secretary George Eustice told reporters at the government's daily Downing Street briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Sao Paulo braces for two-week shutdown, Bolsonaro blasts 'hysteria'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200321185230-0kvnz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Brazil's Sao Paulo braces for two-week coronavirus shutdown, Bolsonaro blasts 'hysteria'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symptoms often linger before worsening...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/slow-burn-coronavirus-symptoms-often-linger-worsening-n1164756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some patients may feel better before winding up in the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia testing vaccine on animals in top secret bio weapons lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-testing-coronavirus-vaccine-primates-21731700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soviet-era complex Vector is one of the world’s leading anti-virus centres and has channelled resources into finding a Covid-19 cure by conducting tests on lower primates and “ferrets”, says a leading scientist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines warn of 'draconian' steps if Congress fails to help...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-airlines-warn-draconian-steps-congress-fails-help-211224987.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executives of the largest US airline companies asked Congress Saturday for urgent help avoiding widespread layoffs among the industry's 750,000 employees. "Unless worker payroll protection grants are passed immediately, many of us will be forced to take draconian measures such as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK HOSPITALS UNDER PRESSURE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48740e4bdefbb0e2459359a5eda2fdd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said the state is scouring the globe for medical supplies and scouting temporary hospital locations in and around New York City. Flights were briefly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY CASES SOAR AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3dcb3392a3c566a1caad7444e93fc7e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The coronavirus pandemic took an increasingly bleak toll Saturday in the U.S. and in Europe, producing staggering caseloads in New York and Italy and setting off a desperate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE MILILTARY TOP SECRET PLANS IF OUTBREAK CRIPPLES GOVT...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/exclusive-inside-militarys-top-secret-plans-if-coronavirus-cripples-government-1492878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence To Be Tested After Staffer Positive...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/488808-pence-says-he-will-be-tested-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Pence said Saturday that he and second lady Karen Pence will be tested for the coronavirus after a member of the vice president’s staff tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Orders Residents To Stay At Home, Bans All Gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-in-new-jersey-gov-phil-murphy-to-make-major-announcement-regarding-efforts-to-curb-spread-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, the governor signed an executive order for New Jerseyans to stay indoors in an effort to curb the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: Half State's Cases Are People Under 50 Years Old...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/half-of-all-coronavirus-cases-in-new-york-are-people-under-50-years-old-gov-cuomo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You’re not superman and you're not superwoman. You can get this virus and you can transfer the virus,” the New York Governor said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People turning to dogs, cats, chickens to cope with self-isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Alone-no-more-People-are-turning-to-dogs-cats-15146418.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a normal Sunday at the PetSmart in Gaithersburg, Maryland, Lucky Dog Animal Rescue would hold an adoption event and find homes for about 15 dogs.  But as coronavirus news started to spread this past week, the waiting list skyrocketed from 10 to 40 would-be adopters. "And we had 30 adoptions in three hours at that event alone," said Mirah Horowitz, the rescue's executive director.  Forget, toilet paper, milk and hand sanitizer: There's now a rush to stock up on real necessities, such as cats and dogs. And rabbits and fish, even a couple of chickens.  As millions of people across the U.S. work from home and schools close, the promise of companionship even in a time of isolation is prompting some to take in animals. Many say they finally have the time to properly train and care for a new pet. Animal rescuers across the country say they are seeing spiking interest in adoption and fostering, as well as offers to help everywhere from open-admission shelters to smaller nonprofit groups.  In California, where 40 million residents were ordered on Thursday night to stay home except for essential jobs or trips, like getting groceries, Gov. Gavin Newsom noted an important exemption.  "You can still walk your dog," he said.  That was part of the appeal for Kathy Shield, a University of Berkeley graduate student. After years of wanting a dog, Shield on Thursday adopted a 2-year-old brown and white dog from the Milo Foundation shelter in Point Richmond, California and named him Atom.  "I'm a nuclear scientist so it's very on brand," said Shield.  The timing was ideal, because Shield is working from home and can help the Atom adjust to his new environment. She's also excited to have someone to talk to, even if he doesn't have much to say back.  Plus, it will help keep her on schedule....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking stock of strange days: The week that America changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a82294fc0723630d850603dd7b016ad5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Change came to the United States of America during the third week of March in 2020. It did not come all at once, though it came quite rapidly. As had happened in other lands, there was no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election limbo as outbreak upends primaries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ca82f2fd0b4df4ee7633c6deb20d997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — U.S. elections have been upended by the coronavirus pandemic. At least 13 states have postponed voting and more delays are possible as health officials warn that social distancing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA gives up on containing; Tells doctors to skip testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-20/coronavirus-county-doctors-containment-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision by L.A. County's public health system not to test patients with coronavirus symptoms could make it difficult to know how many are infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javits Center To Become Massive Field Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-update-nycs-javits-center-to-become-massive-field-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Cuomo announced the Javits Center, previously used for big conventions, tops his list as one of several field hospitals treating the COVID-19 outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Terrified' Package Delivery Employees Going to Work Sick...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/21/terrified-package-delivery-employees-are-going-to-work-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hour after hour, day after day, the packages keep arriving: food, medicine, clothes, toys and a million other items brought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Sees Spike In Severe Child Abuse Cases...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/03/20/texas-hospital-spike-severe-child-abuse-cases-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors at Cook Children’s believe the stresses from the COVID-19 pandemic are linked to six cases of severe child abuse seen this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People moved here to escape big city drama. With coronavirus, that's impossible...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/People-moved-here-to-escape-big-city-drama-With-15147904.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILLCOX, Ariz. - Several employees wore medical masks and almost all wore plastic gloves, a jarring sight for some customers who appeared visibly taken aback as they entered their local Safeway store.  Even in this small town of roughly 3,500 people, the scene wasn't much different than stores in the big city: aisle after aisle of empty shelves where the toilet paper, hand soap and sanitizer used to be. All the Tylenol was sold out, along with cans of beans, cartons of eggs and all the milk - the nondairy kind, too.  And good luck finding a thermometer. Amid the growing concern over the coronavirus, the stock had been cleaned well over a week ago. At first, the pharmacist sent folks over to the Dollar General, but then she'd heard they were out, too.  "I tried to order them, but they're just gone," she said, apologetically.  Up and down the aisles, people shook their heads at the strange scene in a community distant enough to be spared the drama of places like Tucson or Phoenix. This was the place where people came to escape, a small town surrounded by even smaller ones where social distancing was kind of the point.  But all through town, things felt eerie. Restaurants and businesses that were never closed were dark and empty. The dining room at the McDonald's was closed. As shoppers drove into the Safeway parking lot, they passed a panhandler who waved a sign that simply read, "WTF?"  When a Safeway cashier in a medical mask held up the check-out line to wipe down the register area with disinfectant, tensions boiled over. "I mean, this is crazy!" a man said loudly. He ignored fliers posted at the lanes that urged customers to stay at least two shopping carts away from others in the store, inching uncomfortably close to two women ahead of him in line. "This is just too...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will govt nationalize BOEING?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-government-nationalize-boeing-013447260.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 12 years after the US government bailed out General Motors and Chrysler, Washington policymakers are debating how to throw Boeing a lifeline as it reels from dual crises over the coronavirus and 737 MAX. The aerospace giant, which manufactures the US presidential jet Air Force One in addition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLION people confined to homes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nearly-one-billion-people-confined-homes-globally-curb-134625492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close to one billion people worldwide were confined to their homes on Saturday as the global coronavirus death toll shot past 11,000 and US states rolled out lockdown measures already imposed across swathes of Europe. The pandemic has completely upended lives across the planet, restricting movement,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How It All Came Apart for Bernie Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/21/how-it-all-came-apart-for-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In mid-January, a few weeks before the Iowa caucuses, Senator Bernie Sanders’s pollster offered a stark prognosis for the campaign:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House members, Senate aides also traded shares...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/21/coronavirus-trading-house-senate-140260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Susan Davis, a California Democrat, sold shares in Alaska Air and Royal Caribbean cruise lines on Feb. 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcists storming heavens with prayers to end pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.philstar.com/headlines/2020/03/21/2002427/priests-seek-exorcise-pandemic-through-prayer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic exorcists are storming the heavens with prayers to end the global scourge of the coronavirus disease 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NJ health official says EVERYONE will get infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2020/03/im-going-to-get-it-we-all-are-njs-top-health-official-says-as-she-leads-the-states-coronavirus-war.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judith Persichilli, a former ICU nurse with working-class New Jersey roots, says her whole life has prepared her for this moment as she leads the fight against COVID-19 disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Exit strategy' could be months -- or years -- away...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-exit-strategy-could-be-months-or-years-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn to love your lockdown, experts say — because it may not end anytime soon. The coronavirus threat will continue to loom for months or even years before mass vaccinations or natural immunities …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Drop Kale and Quinoa to Lock Down With Chips and Oreos...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-drop-kale-quinoa-lock-130000446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Out with the Tuscan kale and acai berries, in with the Spam and popcorn.In a stark reversal, American shoppers who were taking up healthier eating are gravitating back to old ways as they hunker down to weather the coronavirus pandemic. They are loading up on shelf-stable items from canned</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
