<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Vanessa Williams to Sing 'Black National Anthem' at Capitol Celebration...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/vanessa-williams-sing-black-national-170912173.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American actress and singer Vanessa Williams will perform the song "Lift Every Voice and Sing," which has become known as the "black national anthem," at the annual A Capitol Fourth televised celebration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt opens strategic Mediterranean naval base...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210703-egypt-opens-strategic-mediterranean-naval-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt opens strategic Mediterranean naval base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Wave of Automation May Be Bad News for Workers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/03/pandemic-wave-of-automation-may-be-bad-news-for-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Kroger customers in Cincinnati shop online these days, their groceries may be picked out not by a worker in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMOLITION TOMORROW...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-hurricane-irma-surfside-building-collapse-313072caccc14b2597daa4f3b04bc21a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — Demolition workers planned to bring down the remainder of a collapsed condo building on Sunday ahead of an approaching storm that added to worries that the damaged structure could come down on its own, officials said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spokane-Coeur d'Alene housing market booming, prices rising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wa-state-wire-id-state-wire-coeur-dalene-spokane-lifestyle-f39d38d5805bb85c744bbe57763c32d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOKANE, Wash. (AP) — The way Darin Watkins sees it, the real estate boom in the once-sleepy Spokane, Washington, metropolitan area is a numbers problem. Far too many people are moving in, far too few homes are being built and prices have skyrocketed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas bouncing back, but virus on rise too...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/las-vegas-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-travel-business-9c92392362a55b9392e4c9ef0502bf03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Fifteen months after the pandemic transformed Las Vegas from flamboyant spectacle to ghost town, Sin City is back. Tourists are streaming in again, gambling revenue has hit an all-time high, the Las Vegas Strip has its first new casino in a decade,  and big concerts are starting at a gleaming new stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden hosts 1,000 for Independence Day, desire to declare victory collides with need for caution...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-prepares-to-host-1000-for-independence-day-desire-to-declare-victory-collides-with-need-for-caution/ar-AALJAmp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House wants to celebrate the country’s big strides toward normalcy. But a victory lap could suggest the crisis is over, a potentially dangerous message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Recognize Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9752493/Massachusetts-cops-issue-urgent-shelter-place-warning-eight-heavily-armed-men-run.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A state trooper spotted the men pulled over by the side of Interstate 95 between the towns of Wakefield and Reading at 1.30 on Saturday morning, and asked them for identification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos, Gates back fake meat, dairy made from fungus as next big alt-protein...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/03/bezos-gates-back-fungus-fake-meat-as-next-big-alt-protein-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos, Bill Gates back Nature's Fynd, an alt-meat company whose fungus-based breakfast patties, nuggets and cream cheese are headed to grocery stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctica hit record-high temp in 2020, scientists confirm...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/equilibrium-sustainability/561463-antarctica-hit-record-high-temperature-in-2020-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antarctica logged a new high temperature record of 64.94 degrees Fahrenheit (18.3 Celsius) in 2020, scientists with the World M</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 people in custody after hourslong armed standoff on I-95...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/armed-standoff-wakefield-massachusetts-9ee61b69ca96bb5ce212f56651f0dd11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAKEFIELD, Mass. (AP) — Massachusetts state police said nine suspects have been taken into custody following an hourslong standoff that prompted the partial closure of Interstate 95. Police said the suspects include two people who were arrested earlier on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Supreme Court greenlights investigation of Bolsonaro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-brazil-coronavirus-pandemic-health-courts-8bd3f0402a44fea594a6ce84ef76b747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — A Brazilian Supreme Court justice has authorized a criminal investigation into President Jair Bolsonaro’s response to allegations of potential corruption within his Health Ministry involving a vaccine deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican court indicts cardinal and nine others for alleged financial crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210703-vatican-court-indicts-cardinal-and-nine-others-for-alleged-financial-crimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Vatican judge on Saturday ordered 10 people, including an Italian cardinal, to stand trial for alleged financial crimes including embezzlement, money laundering, fraud, extortion and abuse of offic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian warplanes practice bombing enemy ships in Black Sea drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210703100959-ea774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-MILITARY/ (PIX):Russian warplanes practice bombing enemy ships in Black Sea drills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gs3Yz6Cy9aE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Least 6 Firefighters Test Positive For Covid At Surfside Search Site...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/02/covid-surfside-search-site/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID has reared its ugly head once again, this time at the search site of the Surfside collapsed condo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents slam school rules forcing kids to always smile...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15466959/furious-parents-slam-school-rules-kids-leicestershire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS parents have slammed school rules which force kids to always smile, never look out windows and respond to teachers’ whistles. The new rules implemented by a headteacher in Melton Mowbray, L…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Of North Miami Beach Condo Evacuated After Structure Deemed Unsafe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/north-miami-beach-condo-building-closed-evacuated-after-structure-deemed-unsafe/2486856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A building in North Miami Beach has been closed and residents in the 156-unit condo building are being evacuated Friday after an audit and building inspection report outlined unsafe structural and electrical conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread ransomware attack affects hundreds of businesses... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-technology-3011c6037bda9ac11b1249a4beb13b06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A ransomware attack paralyzed the networks of at least 200 U.S. companies on Friday, according to a cybersecurity researcher whose company was responding to the incident. The REvil gang, a major Russian-speaking ransomware syndicate, appears to be behind the attack, said John Hammond of the security firm Huntress Labs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condo association accused Surfside of 'holding up' major repairs three days before collapse, emails show...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/condo-association-accused-surfside-of-holding-up-major-repairs-three-days-before-collapse-emails-show/ar-AALIer2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — The association of owners of the Champlain Towers South condominium knew their building needed repairs — a lot of them and soon — and by May they were trying in earnest to get town approval for their major renovation plans, according to emails between the association and town officials obtained by The Miami Herald. The town building department wasn’t always responsive. Emails show ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer dreams dry up on the Russian River...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/summer-dreams-dry-russian-river-120015472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This part of the Sonoma wine country has endured fire, flood, intense heat and lightning bolts the last five years. Now it faces ever-more severe water restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarmingly low rain levels prime California for fire danger...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/alarming-low-levels-rain-prime-163641869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worsening drought is further drying out parched vegetation, which could be fuel for a disastrous fire season.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
