<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>House Dems to subpoena Don Jr. first...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/house-dems-to-subpoena-donald-trump-jr-first-in-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats probing allegations that the Trump presidential campaign worked with Russian operatives to win the 2016 election plan to issue their first subpoena to Donald Trump Jr., according to a top lawmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  CNN TOPS FOX; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLE NEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did CIA Director Gina Haspel run a black site at Guantanamo?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/guantanamo/article223835570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A declassified argument by a lawyer with top secret clearance appears to disclose an unknown chapter of CIA Director Gina Haspel’s covert career: that she served at Guantánamo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech wall plan on display at CES...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190108-high-tech-border-wall-plan-display-ces</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-tech border wall plan on display at CES</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE $140 BILLION DIVORCE: BEZOS, WIFE ANNOUNCE SPLIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6573485/Amazon-CEO-Jeff-Bezos-novelist-MacKenzie-Bezos-getting-divorce.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos, who is worth $140 billion, and novelist MacKenzie Bezos have announced they are divorcing, through a joint statement on Wednesday posted to the Jeff's Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two women arrested for alleged assault of trans in bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/two-women-charged-with-assault-on-transgender-person-at-glenwood-south-bar/18110722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women have been charged with assaulting a 29-year-old transgender person in a bathroom at Milk Bar on Glenwood South in Raleigh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA screeners quitting...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/01/09/tsa-union-officers-quitting-over-shutdown-posing-security-threat/2522906002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TSA union official warned that the situation poses a "massive security risk for American travelers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number migrant families crossing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/09/migrant-caravan-trump-crackdown-has-not-slowed-flow-families-us/2523034002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is trying to stop Central American migrants from entering the U.S., but new figures show they continue to stream toward the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's May suffers parliament defeat as Brexit debate restarts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu/britains-may-suffers-parliament-defeat-as-brexit-debate-restarts-idUSKCN1P30ML</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May suffered an early defeat to her Brexit plans ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey Manager May Be Key Witness in Sexual Assault Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-spaceys-manager-may-be-key-witness-sexual-assault-case-1174686 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evan Lowenstein — who is said to have spearheaded the "Let Me Be Frank" Christmas Eve video by the actor — was also present at the Nantucket restaurant the night of the alleged assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Samuel L. Jackson Became Hollywood's Most Bankable Star...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-samuel-l-jackson-became-hollywoods-bankable-star-1174613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The box office king and Trump golf antagonist beat a crack addiction to build a film career unrivaled in modern stardom, and the 70-year-old 'Glass' actor aims to work well into his 80s — if Marvel and the rest of Hollywood can afford him: "I'm a gunslinger now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed official warns of recession risk if rates go much higher...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190109-fed-official-warns-recession-risk-rates-go-much-higher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed official warns of recession risk if rates go much higher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE $140 BILLION DIVORCE: BEZOS, WIFE ANNOUNCE SPLIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/jeff-bezos-and-wife-mackenzie-are-divorcing-.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The couple announce the split three days before Bezos' 55th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: President Losing Argument...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/view/trump-speech-president-is-losing-the-shutdown-argument</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longer the shutdown drags on, the more impressed voters will be with politicians who seem most interested in ending it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Jerry Jones $250M Yacht Size Of Football Field...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/cowboys-owner-jones-reportedly-buys-250-yacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the yacht's manufacturer, Oceanco, the vessel features a garage for smaller boats or jet skis, a full gym and a spa complete with a sauna and massage room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown impacting everyday Americans in unexpected ways...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/09/federal-shutdown-impacting-everyday-american-life-jobs-vacations/2519465002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Americans are increasingly feeling the impact of the federal shutdown impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican House Increased Debt $7.9 Trillion in 8 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/republican-house-increased-debt-79-trillion-8-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Paul Ryan and House Speaker John Boehner, March 19, 2013. (Getty Images/T.J. Kirkpatrick) The recently deposed Republican majority increased the federal debt by $7.9 trillion in the eight years it controlled the House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 millennials with debt expect to die without ever paying it off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/1-in-5-millennials-with-debt-expect-to-die-without-ever-paying-it-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 60 percent of millennials with debt don't know when, or if, they'll ever be able to pay what they owe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Clash Over Global Right to Be Forgotten Returns to Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/google-clash-over-global-right-to-be-forgotten-returns-to-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Clash Over Global Right to Be Forgotten Returns to Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Vest Protesters Call for Huge Run on French Banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c8646ad291c440978c5d8a260a11d454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Yellow vest activists are urging French citizens to empty their bank accounts and spark a massive run on French banks in their long-standing fight with the government. Ahead of a ninth straight weekend of planned protests in Paris and across France, yellow vests are issuing calls on social media for massive cash withdrawals from banks. Protesters hope the move will force the government to listen to their demands, notably their call for more direct democracy through the implementation of popular votes that allow citizens to propose new laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China orders video apps to censor ALL content...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/china-orders-short-video-apps-101829134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have introduced detailed regulations covering the country’s thriving short video industry, singling out 100 categories of banned content, from smearing the image of Communist Party leaders to sexual moaning, in the latest ongoing effort to clean up its cyberspace that has more than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Key to bringing down El Chapo? Flipping his IT guy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/08/el-chapo-was-brought-down-by-his-own-it-guy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secret to bringing down a notorious Mexican cartel kingpin? His IT guy. Jurors in the trial of Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman on Tuesday listened to damning phone calls of the diminutive drug lord r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking Toll On Farmers...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/government-shutdown-taking-a-toll-on-illinois-farmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many farmers count on government help, especially this time of year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Companies Flag New Risk: AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-companies-flag-a-new-risk-artificial-intelligence-11547035202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlyle Group, Overstock.com and AmTrust Financial Services are among the growing ranks of companies whose annual shareholder reports now include artificial intelligence as a risk factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars collecting data on everything from weight to music tastes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-ces-monitoring/move-aside-backseat-driver-new-tech-at-ces-monitors-you-inside-car-idUSKCN1P219H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As vehicles get smarter, your car will be keeping eyes on you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela military personnel increasingly jailed, tortured amid coup fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article224089810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report by Human Rights Watch and Foro Penal says Venezuelan military officials, and their families, are increasingly being detained and tortured amid coup fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After guilty verdict, prosecutors seek to strip biker gang of trademarked logo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-mongol-trademark-20190109-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors asked a jury to strip the Mongol biker gang of the trademarks it holds over its coveted insignia in ta novel legal fight to dismantle the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Traditional masculinity' deemed harmful by medical group...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/american-psychological-association-deems-traditional-masculinity-harmful-could-lead-to-sexual-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Psychological Association for the first time in its history released guidelines concerning men and boys, saying that the so-called “traditional masculinity” not only is “harmful” but also could lead to homophobia and sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Supreme Leader Calls US Officials 'First-Class Idiots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1e036a680a1240898d9cb6477195314a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's supreme leader on Wednesday called U.S. officials "first-class idiots," mocking American leaders as U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo toured the Mideast to promote the White House's tough stance on Iran. Ayatollah Ali Khamenei's comments were unusually harsh, reflecting the broader tension between Iran and the United States after President Donald Trump withdrew America from Tehran's nuclear deal with world powers. Khamenei, speaking to a group from Iran's religious capital of Qom, made the remark while recounting a story about a U.S. official once predicting he'd celebrate Christmas in Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon: Military Not Ready for War With ChinaRussia...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/pentagon-military-logistics-system-not-ready-for-war-with-china-or-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strategic American military system for moving troops, weapons, and supplies over long distances has decayed significantly and needs rapid upgrading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRYSLER Building, Famed Slice of Manhattan Skyline, Up for Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chrysler-building-a-famed-slice-of-manhattan-skyline-is-on-the-block-11547035200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s famed Chrysler Building is up for sale, as the art deco landmark’s owners face high costs and stiff competition from new towers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars collecting data on everything from weight to music tastes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/01/09/car-spying-vehicles-collecting-data-everything-weight-music/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the dawn of the automobile age, drivers were persuaded and cajoled into buying cars solely because they were attractive, or fun to drive, or had features like leather seats and a good sound system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREEN BOOK' Won Big At GLOBES; Hold Up Under Scrutiny?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/Green-Book-won-big-at-the-Golden-Globes-will-13518376.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES - When "Green Book" won three Golden Globes on Sunday, a number of narratives began to take shape: The awards - for best comedy or musical, best screenplay and Mahershala Ali's supporting performance - were among the biggest surprises of the night, upsetting such supposed front-runners as the multi-nominated "Vice" or "Mary Poppins Returns." What's more, "Green Book" arrived at the ceremony dogged by on-screen and off-screen controversies, including criticism from the family of Ali's character, the pianist Don Shirley, as well as accusations that the film is "divisive," perpetuating racist stereotypes of white saviors and "magical Negroes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microbes on Space Station mutating to survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/space-bacteria-earth-alien-mutating-survive-disease-international-station-a8717976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug to clear 'zombie cells' from body in first anti-aging treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/techandscience/drug-to-clear-zombie-cells-from-body-could-be-first-anti-ageing-treatment-after-%E2%80%98impressive%E2%80%99-human-trial/ar-BBRZpiV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein departure said imminent...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/rosenstein-expected-depart-doj-coming-weeks-attorney-general/story?id=60252611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple sources told ABC News Rosenstein's departure is imminent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Daring clandestine op to crack El Chapo encrypted comms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/08/nyregion/el-chapo-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cristian Rodriguez was hired by the Sinaloa drug cartel to create a secure encrypted communications network. Then he helped the F.B.I. break into it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: City living giving animals cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6569765/City-life-giving-animals-CANCER.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big polluted cities such as New York and London increase the likelihood that animals will get cancer. Birds, squirrels, rats, mice and hedgehogs are some of the affected wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FIGHT GOES PRIME TIME!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cb9df4c458e647db9866ffa4c0db1fa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump made a televised plea for border wall funding Tuesday night, seeking an edge in the shutdown battle with congressional Democrats as he declared there is "a humanitarian crisis, a crisis of the heart and a crisis of the soul." Addressing the nation from the Oval Office for the first time, Trump argued for funding on security and humanitarian grounds as he sought to put pressure on newly empowered Democrats amid an extended partial government shutdown. Trump called on Democrats to return to the White House to meet with him, saying it was "immoral" for "politicians to do nothing."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police serve warrant for male staff DNA samples where vegetative patient gave birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.azfamily.com/news/investigations/hacienda_healthcare/phoenix-pd-obtain-dna-samples-from-hacienda-healthcare-staff-week/article_cba20c0c-13a3-11e9-85a3-e396464e906c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azfamily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hacienda HealthCare confirmed the search warrant for DNA samples Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact widens on 18th day of govt shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-shutdown-departments-factbox/factbox-impact-on-us-government-widens-on-18th-day-of-shutdown-idUSKCN1P22AB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shutdown of about a quarter of the U.S. government reached its 18th day on Tue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Deficit Climbs Again, On Track for $1,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/08/us/politics/budget-deficit-trillion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate tax receipts are falling and federal spending is rising. More revenue from tariffs isn’t enough to bridge the gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese middle class buying up US residential real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/chinese-middle-class-buying-up-american-residential-real-estate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese consumers have been the top foreign buyers in both units and dollar volume of residential housing for six years straight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How author uncovered secret plot to kill George Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brad-meltzer-new-book-the-first-conspiracy-plot-to-kill-george-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best-selling author details an effort to undermine the American Revolution just before the signing of the Declaration of Independence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sealed v Sealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/18/sealed-v-sealed-robert-mueller-mysterious-case-subpoena</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretive dispute over subpoena revealed to concern an unnamed corporation, but many questions remain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey claims alleged victim lied about age, welcomed flirtation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-ent-kevin-spacey-says-victim-lied-about-age-20190108-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey claims his alleged sex assault victim lied about his age and encouraged a mutual flirtation, according to a Nantucket District Court filing obtained by the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Penny Found in Child's Lunch Money Could Auction for $1.7M...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/culture/rare-penny-found-in-boys-lunch-money-could-fetch-up-to-1-7-million-in-auction-1768904/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare 1943 copper Lincoln cent — found by a Massachusetts teenager in his change after he paid for lunch at a school cafeteria — is expected to fetch up to $1.7 million when …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama warns drivers not to stop and eat chicken tenders spilled on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/nation-world/national/article224080395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alabama Emergency Management Agency issued a hazard warning this week, telling people not to eat hundreds of chicken tenders spilled across a state highway. It happened Sunday in Cherokee County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Journalist Jailed for 'Paradise Papers' Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.icij.org/investigations/paradise-papers/turkish-journalist-sentenced-to-prison-over-paradise-papers-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.icij.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Istanbul court has sentenced ICIJ member Pelin Ünker to imprisonment for 13 months after being found to have defamed her nation’s former prime minister and two of his sons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB scores record revenue as attendance dips, player salaries fall...</title>
      <link>https://mlb.nbcsports.com/2019/01/07/a-warning-about-major-league-baseballs-record-revenues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mlb.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Making money is a good thing, but Major League Baseball’s gravy train seems unsustainable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home security cam catches prowler licking doorbell for 3 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/video-prowler-spends-3-hours-licking-doorbell-at-ca-home/5033951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are trying to track down a man who spent three hours licking a doorbell at a California home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Undecided on Emergency Declaration for Border... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-undecided-on-emergency-declaration-for-border-wall-officials-say-11546959778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump isn’t expected to declare a national emergency at the southern border when he addresses the nation Tuesday night about his request for funding for his long-promised wall along the U.S.-Mexico boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Psychiatrist Can See Your Child Now, Virtually...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-psychiatrist-can-see-your-child-now-virtually-11546877610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a growing shortage of psychiatrists and other mental-health professionals for children and adolescents, more health-care providers are turning to technology to fill the gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court declines to intervene in mysterious Mueller subpoena fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/08/supreme-court-declines-to-intervene-in-mysterious-mueller-subpoena-fight-1088050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court declined to intervene in a fight apparently involving a foreign-government-owned company and the special counsel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans Warm to Facial Recognition Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/01/survey-americans-warming-use-facial-recognition-tech/153987/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans do not favor strict limits on facial recognition technology, according to a new national survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin brothers both serving prison time for separate killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-twin-brothers-prison-sentences-evanston-20190107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominic Connerly was sentenced for the fatal shooting of an Evanston man to 15 years in prison. Connerly's twin brother Darien is already in prison on a murder conviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple CEO confident of prospects despite naysayers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/apple-ceo-confident-prospects-despite-naysayers-192510373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Apple nudged higher on Tuesday after Chief Executive Tim Cook touted the company's technology pipeline and characterized worries about the company's future as overwrought. Cook, in an interview with CNBC just six days after a sales warning sent shares skidding, highlighted a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Dems identify as liberals for first time...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/245813/leans-conservative-liberals-keep-recent-gains.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's ideological balance held steady in 2018, with conservatives and moderates each at 35% and liberals remaining at last year's record high, 26%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Workers Start Driving For UBER, LYFT...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/federal-workers-going-to-work-for-lyft-uber-during-government-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The partial government shutdown is wreaking havoc on the ride-sharing industry, especially in the nation's capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt shutdown starting to affect air travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0034bf33e214cd6b6a85ae1c23bdcaf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — The partial government shutdown is starting to affect air travel. Over the weekend, some airports had long lines at checkpoints, apparently caused by a rising number of security officers calling in sick as they face the prospect of missing their first paycheck this week. Safety inspectors aren't even on the job. A Federal Aviation Administration spokesman said Monday that inspectors are being called back to work on a case-by-case basis, with a priority put on inspecting airline fleets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM May defeated in parliament, lawmakers create new obstacle to no-deal Brexit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190108190607-wbrpf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/NODEAL (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-UK PM May defeated in parliament, lawmakers create new obstacle to no-deal Brexit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May defeated in parliament... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-nodeal/may-defeated-in-parliament-mps-create-new-obstacle-to-no-deal-brexit-idUSKCN1P21BD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May's government suffered a defeat in parlia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT REDACTIONS REVEALED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6570217/Paul-Manafort-shared-campaign-polling-data-Russian-spy-ran-Trumps-White-House-bid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Donald Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort sent campaign polling data to an alleged Russian spy in the midst of the 2016 campaign, an incorrectly redacted document reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMSUNG users shocked: Can't delete FACEBOOK app...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-08/samsung-phone-users-get-a-shock-they-can-t-delete-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractor driver levels ATM in heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/washingtoncounty/2019/01/tractor-driver-levels-wells-fargo-atm-in-hillsboro-heist-police-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver and a second person, who had been waiting in a U-Haul van, stole an undetermined amount of cash, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa awkwardly interrupts tech exec during demo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-amazon-alexa-awkwardly-interrupts-tech-executive-20190108-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems as if Amazon’s Alexa actually has a mind of its own, after the device awkwardly interrupted a tech executive at a press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers: Manafort suffers from depression, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/608b9fcbca5941348e2ac8796e94c8cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort is suffering from depression and anxiety and is at times confined to a wheelchair because of gout. That's according to a court filing from defense lawyers Tuesday responding to allegations that Manafort has repeatedly lied to special counsel Robert Mueller's team of investigators. Manafort's lawyers say he was awakened before dawn on the days he was interviewed and normally spent the entire day talking with investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN! Heathrow flights grounded after drone spotted...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8149197/heathrow-airport-flights-grounded-after-drone-spotted-over-runway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEATHROW Airport flights have been grounded amid reports of a drone sighting today just weeks after the chaotic Gatwick shutdown. The airport has said they have stopped departures while they invest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst measles outbreak in decades sweeps New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6569129/Worst-measles-outbreak-decades-sweeps-New-York-cases-surge-Oregon-Washington-abroad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 160 cases of measles have been reported in New York with most spreading among unvaccinated religious communities. Measles outbreaks have cropped up in over 20 US states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-felons begin registering to vote in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0086670a6df42c9a3d2857d1606e027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The right to vote was restored for most Florida felons as of Tuesday, increasing the pool of eligible voters by as many as 1.4 million people in a battleground state infamous for its narrow margins in key elections. The Florida Rights Restoration Coalition planned to get people together over breakfast before registering online or going to their local election supervisors' offices to fill out the forms. "We are encouraging our members to celebrate," said organization's president, Desmond Meade. "Our members are going into the supervisor of elections with their loved ones. And that is very key— with their loved ones— because we really want to highlight that concept of love."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor who called Orlando massacre victims 'scum' ousted over prostitution allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/fort-worth/2019/01/08/fort-worth-pastor-called-orlando-massacre-victims-scum-earth-ousted-prostitution-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fort Worth pastor known for praising the Pulse nightclub shooting and condemning the victims will be replaced Sunday, after accusations that he'd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK 'cult-like' workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/facebook-culture-cult-performance-review-process-blamed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Facebook employees detailed how the company's leadership and performance review system have created a "go along" culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Facility CEO resigns after woman in vegetative state gives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bill-timmons-hacienda-healthcare-ceo-nursing-facility-vegetative-woman-gave-birth-resigns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Timmons quit days after baby was born to woman patient in vegetative state; CBS affiliate reports claim that he covered up prior incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Denies Making Secret Overtures to Tehran...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-denies-making-secret-overtures-to-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Tuesday denied claims by senior Iranian officials that the United States has been making secret overtures to Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian attorney charged with obstruction of justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/russian-attorney-natalia-veselnitskaya-charged-with-obstruction-of-justice-in-us-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian attorney Natalia Veselnitskaya, who was at the center of a controversial 2016 Trump Tower meeting, was charged in federal court on Tuesday with obstruction of justice in connection to a civil money laundering and forfeiture case involving a Russian tax refund fraud scheme, first uncovered by the late Sergei Magnitsky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Teen Girl Violent MCDONALD'S Rampage After Asked To Leave Kids' Play Area...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/video-teens-allegedly-start-violent-melee-in-inland-empire-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teenage girls were caught on camera hurling heavy objects at McDonald's employees in Moreno Valley after being asked to leave a children's play area – causing thousand dollars worth of damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks to carry Pelosi, Schumer rebuttal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9f3362c235dd47f6ac0ae580ae7265e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and the partial government shutdown (all times local): 10:55 a.m. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer will give the Democratic response to President Donald Trump's remarks to the nation Tuesday on his proposed wall on the U.S.-Mexico border. An impasse over wall funding has led to a partial government shutdown, now in its third week. Pelosi and Schumer have flatly refused to pay for the wall. They said Tuesday they will deliver their response to Trump after his address at 9 p.m. EST. Trump says there is a security crisis at the U.S.-Mexico border that can be addressed only by spending $5.7 billion on a wall as a way to prevent people from crossing into the U.S. illegally.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
