<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Woman faces Texas murder charge after 'self-induced abortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.valleycentral.com/news/local-news/starr-county-woman-arrested-for-self-induced-abortion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.valleycentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STARR COUNTY, Texas (ValleyCentral) — A woman has been charged with murder after authorities say she performed a “self-induced abortion.” Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested on Thur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Campaign for Sex-Free Internet...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/04/09/the-new-campaign-for-a-sex-free-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex, money, and the future of online free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Bitcoin Party: Bros, Believers, Bottle Girls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-bitcoin-party-bros-believers-040821212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastMIAMI—It’s 2 a.m. and a group of four men and I are trying to get into E11even, a trendy downtown dance spot that doubles as a strip club and is best known for being the spot where Drake and Rihanna were spotted kissing in 2016. At this point in the night, the line is so long that people are spilling into the street. There is a woman walking around in stilts and lingerie and another dressed like a cat and tied to a leash, held by yet another woma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FDA'S FOOD FAILURE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2022/fda-fails-regulate-food-health-safety-hazards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POLITICO investigation based on more than 50 interviews finds the FDA is failing to meet American consumers expectations on food safety and nutrition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL QB Haskins Dead After Hit By Dump Truck...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/pittsburgh-steelers-qb-dwayne-haskins-struck-killed-by-car-in-south-florida/2732756/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pittsburgh Steelers quarterback Dwayne Haskins, 24, was struck and killed by a dump truck in Broward County on Saturday morning. According to Florida Highway Patrol, Haskins was attempting to cross the westbound lanes of I-595 on foot for unknown reasons. Haskins was then struck by an oncoming dump truck and was pronounced dead on the scene, according to FHP. “I…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian rioters vandalize Joseph's Tomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-703723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The vandalism of Joseph’s Tomb is a grave event and a serious violation of freedom of worship in one of the holiest places for every Jew," said Defense Minister Benny Gantz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson surprise Kyiv visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/09/europe/ukraine-uk-boris-johnson-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSIONS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-tel-aviv-west-bank-religion-71bd1f3e308f8e52bca6815f058ede77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Palestinians set fire to a West Bank shrine revered by Jews as Israeli forces operated in the occupied territory following a spate of recent Palestinian attacks in Israel , the Israeli military said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves Hit on New Scam: Synthetic Identity Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/04/07/thieves-hit-on-a-new-scam-synthetic-identity-fraud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Your wallet and your purse could be a crime scene any day of the week.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Orban be wedge Vlad drives between Western allies?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/will-hungarys-orban-be-the-wedge-putin-drives-between-western-allies/ar-AAW23gH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-LGBTQ Proposals Flooding State Legislatures at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-lgbtq-proposals-are-flooding-us-state-legislatures-at-a-record-pace/ar-AAW0kr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge appears likely to allow Jan 6-related candidacy challenge against Greene...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/08/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-candidacy-challenge-lawsuit/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge signaled Friday that she'll likely allow a group of Georgia voters to move forward with their constitutional challenge against GOP Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, which claims she can't run for reelection because she aided the January 6 insurrectionists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakeholder Musk tweets 'Is Twitter dying?'</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-twitter-stakeholder-elon-musk-tweets-is-twitter-dying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter's newest board member and largest stakeholder Elon Musk tweeted Saturday to ask if the social media network was "dying" and to call out users such as singer Justin Bieber, who are highly foll…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sour and angry America poised to punish Dems this fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/09/angry-voters-biden-inflation-midterms-00024218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and his top advisers know that the window to change the economic narrative through executive action is rapidly closing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we witnessing beginning of de-dollarization?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/3262514-are-we-witnessing-the-beginning-of-de-dollarization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hegemony of the U.S. dollar was reliant on America’s hegemonic status in the world. With the world moving toward multipolarity and with the U.S. no longer the world’s largest trading nation (it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In outcome of Whitmer case, some see freedom, others danger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whitmer-kidnap-plot-trial-adam-fox-gretchen-whitmer-presidential-elections-violence-e2f805952538cdbef69c3dca82ddbfd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside the Michigan courthouse where a jury did not convict any of the four men charged with planning to kidnap Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEELERS QB Haskins Dies After Hit By Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/5088876/dwayne-haskins-dead-steelers-nfl-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star Dwayne Haskins has died after being hit by a vehicle while training with the Steelers just weeks after signing a new contract with the team, according to reports. Football fans mourn the f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stop the Steal' Rally Organizer Agrees to Cooperate with Jan. 6 Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-trump-stop-the-steal-rally-organizer-agrees-to-cooperate-with-jan-6-criminal-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activist and Trump rally organizer Ali Alexander has agreed to cooperate with the committee investigating the January 6 attack on the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson surprise meeting with Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/boris-johnson-ukraine-zelensky-2283122f-3d5a-487a-91df-95eb62d81f5b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Right now Boris Johnson's visit to Kiev began with a tet-a-tet meeting with President Zelensky," a Ukrainian official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loses his NINTH colonel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10702421/Ukraine-war-Putin-loses-NINTH-colonel-tank-commander-latest-Russian-officer-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A funeral was held for Colonel Alexander Bespalov on Friday in the closed Russian city of Ozersk, according to a local announcement, which said he was killed during 'special operation'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE TURNS RIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-france-prepares-for-first-round-of-tight-macron-re-election-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France on Saturday prepared for the first round of presidential elections projected to produce a run-off rematch between President Emmanuel Macron and far-right leader Marine Le Pen that will be far…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow First Default in Century Looks All But Inevitable Now...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-first-default-century-looks-073000013.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Sanctions Against Putin’s Daughters, IMF AccountNations Eye Modern Arms for Ukraine as Soviet-Era Stocks DwindleFinland Hit by Cyber Attack, Airspace Breach as NATO Bid WeighedDHL Jet Skids Off Runway, Breaks Up After Emergency LandingShanghai, Guangzhou Plan More Mass Tests as Covid Cases RiseRussia’s first external default in a century now looks all but inevitable after another brutal week for the country’s finances.First, the Treasury hal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson, COVID and retirement show Congress' partisan path...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-ketanji-brown-jackson-us-supreme-court-covid-business-f5a7b68b0a4e0c17792de15412c87e8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A milestone Supreme Court confirmation that endured a flawed process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses Of Afterlife? 'Near-Death Experiences' Aren't Hallucinations, Scientists Conclude...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/08/near-death-brain-activity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A review of research exploring what people experience when they’re close to death reveals “that near-death experiences” are a real thing, even if we can’t explain them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal referrals of former Trump officials pose thorny questions for DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/3262936-criminal-referrals-of-former-trump-officials-pose-thorny-questions-for-doj/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tough decisions are piling up at the Justice Department (DOJ), which is now weighing three criminal referrals from Congress directed at former Trump White House officials.   The referrals…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians Turn on One Another Over War...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/09/spurred-by-putin-russians-turn-on-one-another-over-the-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marina Dubrova, an English teacher on the Russian island of Sakhalin in the Pacific, showed an uplifting YouTube video to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president offers voters chance to kick him out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mexico-e2-80-99s-president-offers-voters-the-chance-to-kick-him-out/ar-AAW1sGm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lachlan Murdoch, once ambivalent FOX heir, makes his views clear...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lachlan-murdoch-once-the-ambivalent-fox-heir-expresses-his-views/ar-AAW2c9B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Haitian migration routes change, compassion tested in Florida Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-haitian-migration-routes-change-compassion-is-tested-in-florida-keys/ar-AAW24Gz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask, no mask: Biden pandemic practices vary as covid risks grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mask-no-mask-biden-e2-80-99s-pandemic-practices-vary-as-covid-risks-grow/ar-AAW0L6M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 dead in train station attack as Russian troops regroup in east...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/50-dead-in-train-station-attack-as-Russian-troops-17068393.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KRAMATORSK, Ukraine -- At least 50 people were killed and 98 injured in what Ukrainian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissatisfied With Party, Wealthy Republican Donors Form Secret Coalitions...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/06/dissatisfied-with-their-party-wealthy-republican-donors-form-secret-coalitions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coalition of wealthy conservative benefactors that says it aims to “disrupt but advance the Republican agenda” gathered this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food prices soar to record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-health-europe-united-nations-fe2cc912195478f0dd861e6252c8f3b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Prices for food commodities like grains and vegetable oils reached their highest levels ever last month largely because of Russia's war in Ukraine and the “massive supply disruptions” it is causing , threatening millions of people in Africa, the Middle East and elsewhere with hunger and malnourishment, the United Nations said Friday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
