<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bacon prices reach record levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/bacon-prices-have-reached-record-levels-heres-why-they-might-not-go-down-anytime-soon/37791555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of one of your favorite breakfast items is on the rise. Here's how long it could last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New, 'first-class' high-rise will house homeless on LA skid row...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/new-high-rise-to-house-homeless-people-on-l-a-s-skid-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction kicked off Tuesday on a 19-story homeless housing project designed to reshape a corner of skid row in the image of more well-to-do environs. The 278-unit Weingart Tower will replace a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Bush strategist to run as Dem for Texas lieutenant governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/politics/article/Matthew-Dowd-former-George-W-Bush-strategist-16495798.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Dowd called Patrick 'cruel and craven' while announcing his candidacy for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming for K-12 Students...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/29/vaccine-mandates-coming-for-k-12-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Diego becomes latest school district to require teen jabs. But is it good policy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video apparently shows shootout that left KGB officer, IT worker dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/29/video-apparently-shows-murder-of-kgb-officer-it-worker-in-belarus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video apparently captured a shootout between Belarusian security forces and a man reported to be an IT worker with a US company, amid a crackdown on pro-democracy protestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Couric's new book sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10037351/Katie-Courics-new-book-sparks-outrage-rips-ex-boyfriends-former-NBC-CBS-colleagues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com has read the manuscript for Katie Couric's book ' Going There' , which is out in late October and will be accompanied by an 11-city book tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 High School Refs Barricaded Inside Locker Room After Altercation With Coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/general/news/seven-ohio-high-school-football-referees-claim-they-were-barricaded-inside-of-locker-room-after-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Grove City High School assistant coach 'charged' the referees in a 'very threatening manner' on the field before the officials moved to the locker room</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal gathering sends Australian region into lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/australia/australia-covid-news-live-lockdowns-case-numbers-and-vaccinations/news-story/ba54d427d65e0df8cd2ef80842f5a54f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Wednesday’s coverage of Australia’s Covid-19 situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain workers warn of 'system collapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/29/business/supply-chain-workers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seafarers, truck drivers and airline workers have endured quarantines, travel restrictions and complex Covid-19 vaccination and testing requirements to keep stretched supply chains moving during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mice experiencing defeat get depressed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/mental-health/574535-mice-vicariously-experiencing-defeat-get-depressed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a study focused on the pathophysiology of depression, researchers look at how the brains of mice change when experiencing ‘second-hand’ psychological stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Happiness Prevents Dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/happiness-young-adulthood-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study reveals a 73-percent higher chance of cognitive impairment among those with more depressive symptoms during young adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA considers wide-ranging requirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-los-angeles-public-health-fe955da901bddcb53a82307566986161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles City Council will vote Wednesday on a proposed ordinance to require people to have proof of full vaccination against COVID-19 to enter a wide range of businesses and venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VP Harris to student who accused Israel of 'genocide': Your truth must be heard...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/american-politics/vp-harris-to-student-who-accused-israel-of-genocide-your-truth-must-be-heard-680603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Vice President Kamala Harris applauded a student who accused Israel of "ethnic genocide," saying "your truth cannot be suppressed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Dems seek to purge term 'moderate'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/574399-progressive-democrats-seek-to-purge-the-term-moderate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are imploring fellow Democrats to stop using the term “moderate” to describe some lawmakers in their party, arguing it inaccurately labels those holding up President Biden’s agenda as merely staking out a middle-ground approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health workers once saluted as heroes now get threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-missouri-omaha-b73e167eba4987cab9e58fdc92ce0b72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — More than a year after U.S. health care workers were saluted for saving lives in the COVID-19 outbreak and celebrated with nightly clapping from windows and balconies, some are being issued panic buttons in case of assault and ditching their scrubs before going out in public for fear of harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong 'BBC' ordered to support China national security...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/asia/china/hong-kong-rthk-china-b1929323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese government angry at broadcasters coverage of 2019 riots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Kraft Called Belichick 'Biggest F***ing A**hole In My Life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/bill-obrien-was-trying-to-get-fired-by-texans-to-take-over-for-bill-belichick-in-new-england-book-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill O'Brien, head coach of the Patriots? It apparently almost happened</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of 'overemployed' workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20210927-the-overemployed-workers-juggling-remote-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now out of the daily eye of managers, people are taking on additional, secret jobs. What could go wrong?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slovenia uses water cannons at pass protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-europe-health-european-union-slovenia-f1b6e3486d51778ad058b68781ec1ad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LJUBLJANA, Slovenia (AP) — Police fired tear gas and water cannons in Slovenia’s capital on Wednesday at thousands of protesters who oppose tough anti-coronavirus measures in the small European Union nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Society Angrier Than Ever Before?</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/28/anger-management-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In public and across social media, anger is boiling over. Arguments are quick to erupt and sometimes turn physical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Wins Premiere Week by Largest Margin in Ratings History...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nbc-premiere-week-ratings-win-viewership-svu-sunday-night-football-chicago-pd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC won 2021 premiere week in TV ratings and viewers, pulling ahead of its competition by the largest margin in ratings history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Paul Thomas Anderson Goes Back to the Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/27/trailer-a-hollywood-almost-famous-as-bradley-cooper-plays-jon-peters-in-paul-thomas-andersons-licorice-pizza-based-on-producer-gary-goetzmans-childhood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  YOUTUBE CEO claims free speech 'core value' after REMOVING Putin critic videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/technology/youtubes-ceo-says-free-speech-is-a-core-value-even-after-removing-videos-by-putin-critic-alexey-navalny/ar-AAORY5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wojcicki said free speech was a 'core value,' but that there were 'multiple considerations' when dealing with a country like Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans check their smartphones 96 times a day!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/americans-check-their-smartphones-96-times-a-day-survey-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research said Americans check their phones 96 times a day — which is about once every 10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking 3D tech brings 2,000-year-old mummies faces back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/groundbreaking-3d-tech-brings-faces-25094014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technology has allowed scientists to digitally visualise the faces of Egyptian mummies using extractions of their DNA - showing the 2,000-year-old bodies as 25-year-olds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies after waking up with bat on neck...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wbbm780/news/local/elderly-illinois-man-dies-of-rabies-after-finding-bat-on-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illinois has recorded its first human case of rabies since 1954, state and suburban public health officials said Tuesday. An elderly Lake County man was the victim of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least one long-term symptom seen in 37% of patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210929110533-5nvns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/OXFORD-STUDY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-At least one long-term symptom seen in 37% of COVID-19 patients -study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police warn parents about cannabis candy ahead of Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/bensalem-police-halloween-candy-childrens-safety-child-care/11057472/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Halloween may be a month away, police warn parents to take a good hard look at their child's candy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Reactions: 'Absurd... powerful... fitting farewell'</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/no-time-to-die-first-reactions-premiere-1235022188/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The James Bond film has had its premiere and first press screenings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:   Virus fears linger after inoculation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-illinois-e2d3f24eb72fd6aaa7074f5d3ac8754a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Bronwyn Russell wears a mask anytime she leaves her Illinois home, though she wouldn’t dream of going out to eat or to hear a band play, much less setting foot on a plane. In Virginia, Oliver Midgette rarely dons a mask, never lets COVID-19 rouse any worry and happily finds himself in restaurants and among crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA officials to consider requiring proof of vax to enter indoor restaurants, gyms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/574448-la-officials-to-consider-requiring-proof-of-vaccine-to-enter-indoor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles officials are set to consider Wednesday a sweeping law that would require adults to show proof of full coronavirus vaccination to enter indoor public places in the city,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Koch network disavows critical race theory bans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iowa-philanthropy-evan-feinberg-f2680a1c7c1f84c8f69d63eaa631908a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — As conservative political groups mobilize to ban in schools what they call critical race theory, one prominent backer of Republican causes and candidates is notably absent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High court could add more contentious cases to busy lineup...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-religion-courts-us-supreme-court-33db4e5b3e3a8baaab27c6e86a759e6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court term that begins next week is already full of contentious cases, including fights over abortion and guns. But the justices still have a lot of blank space on their calendar, with four more months of arguments left to fill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big institutional investors don't see large stock returns continuing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/29/big-institutional-investors-dont-see-large-stock-returns-continuing-and-are-getting-more-active.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock returns are likely to be much more muted going forward, according to big investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady chases all-time yards passing record in reunion game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-super-bowl-new-york-giants-new-york-jets-c09f7a15371177f051a97c803f4fc76e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometime in the first half Sunday night, Tom Brady should add another record to his already impressive haul of them. It couldn't come in a more appropriate location. With 68 yards passing in his return to New England, Brady will surpass Drew Brees' mark of 80,358 yards that stands as the most ever in the regular season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlog Of Cargo Ships At Port Of LA Reaches Boiling Point; 500,000 Containers!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/09/28/backlog-of-cargo-ships-at-port-of-la-reaches-boiling-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few are more frustrated about the backlog at the Port of Los Angeles and Long Beach, than truck drivers in the chaos. They say that a trucker shortage is not the problem, instead the port needs to speed up their wait times and have more dock help ready to off load.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstar Russian actress flying to ISS to film space film...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3758679/russian-actress-iss-film-crew-space-movie-tom-cruise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN actress is set to take off for the International Space Station (ISS) next week to shoot the first movie in outer space. Alongside two cosmonauts and a director, Yulia Peresild, 37, will l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE BANS 'ANTI-VAX' CONTENT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/youtube-is-banning-prominent-anti-vaccine-activists-and-blocking-all-anti-vaccine-content/ar-AAOXmdF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google-owned video site YouTube previously only banned misinformation about coronavirus vaccines. Facebook made the same change months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After contentious hearing, Pentagon leaders to face more questions over Afghanistan exit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/afghanistan-withdrawal-house-hearing-09-29-21/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House lawmakers will grill Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs Gen. Mark Milley and the leader of US Central Command Gen. Frank McKenzie on the Afghanistan withdrawal. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Confidence in ability eroding...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/critical-moment-confidence-bidens-ability-handle-range-issues/story?id=80290520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As President Joe Biden faces a critical moment for his agenda, Americans’ confidence in his handling of a range of issues is eroding, a new ABC News/Ipsos poll finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired doctor license suspended after state found she mailed fake vax exemption forms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/retired-doctor-e2-80-99s-license-suspended-after-state-found-she-mailed-fake-vaccine-exemption-forms-e2-80-98let-freedom-ring-e2-80-99/ar-AAOWWJC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before her name and contact information, the doctor added: “Let freedom ring!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK police officer murdered woman after false coronavirus arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210929-uk-police-officer-murdered-woman-after-false-coronavirus-arrest-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK police officer murdered woman after false coronavirus arrest: court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most Believe Market  Rigged, and They're Right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-09-29/is-stock-market-rigged-insider-trading-by-executives-is-pervasive-critics-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research shows insider trading is everywhere. So far, no one seems to care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Food Costs at Risk of Soaring as China Faces Tough Harvest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-food-costs-risk-soaring-084117551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China is set for a difficult harvest season as a severe energy crunch hurts the outlook for booming production, a development that risks triggering a renewed surge in world agriculture and food prices. Most Read from BloombergThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in LondonThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionHow Los Angeles Became the City of DingbatsWhy the Gaza Strip May Be the City of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Luster Dims as Stumbles and Congress Sniping Take Toll...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-luster-dims-stumbles-congress-060000180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The weekly trip to the grocery store keeps getting more expensive. Gas prices are rising and winter heating bills look ominous. Supply chain problems loom over the holidays. Covid-19 rages on. Forests are burning in the West and people are drowning in basement apartments in the East. Most Read from BloombergThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in LondonThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway Expansi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rags to riches: Boxing great Pacquiao announces retirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-boxing-philippines-manila-manny-pacquiao-56fe48ebed5de2b043fde3ae9c42438d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — Boxing legend Manny Pacquiao is officially hanging up his gloves. The eight-division world champion and Philippine senator on Wednesday announced his retirement from the ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief sees rising threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-7d957f74410074dab59b62bb3c389a25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The newly installed chief of the U.S. Capitol Police says the force, still struggling six months after an insurrection that left its officers battled, bloodied and bruised, “cannot afford to be complacent.” The risk to lawmakers is higher than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Daniel Craig's Final Bond Movie Pulls Out All Stops for Explosive Finale -- or Cliffhanger...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/28/review-daniel-craigs-final-james-bond-movie-no-time-to-die-pulls-out-all-the-stops-for-an-explosive-cliffhanger-of-all-cliffhangers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raves Raise Hopes for Moviegoing Revival...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/rave-james-bond-reviews-raise-hopes-for-moviegoing-revival-1.1659052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rave reviews for the long-delayed James Bond movie “No Time to Die” could finally entice people away from Netflix and into theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney judge to consider requests to terminate conservatorship... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/sep/28/britney-spears-conservatorship-date-court-hearing-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-stakes hearing comes just days after a new documentary alleges that Jamie Spears had his daughter’s conversations monitored</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hinckley freedom unprecedented. Others who tried to kill presidents faced very different fates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/john-w-hinckley-jrs-freedom-is-unprecedented-others-who-tried-to-kill-presidents-faced-very-different-fates/ar-AAOUK77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is what happened to the men and women who tried to assassinate a president or presidential candidate, from Andrew Jackson in 1835 to Gerald Ford in 1975.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The corner of Costa Rica where people live on, and on...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210929-the-corner-of-costa-rica-where-people-live-on-and-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The corner of Costa Rica where people live on, and on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here comes $90 oil?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/27/investing/oil-price-forecast-goldman-sachs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The V-shaped recovery in the oil patch continues to take even the biggest bulls on Wall Street by surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador prison riots leave 24 dead, dozens injured as gangs fight for control...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Ecuador-prison-riots-leave-24-dead-and-dozens-16494935.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 24 inmates were killed and dozens more injured on Tuesday in Ecuador's largest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN preparing for 'potentially catastrophic' US credit default...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/574385-dimon-says-jpmorgan-preparing-for-potentially-catastrophic-us-credit-default</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said that the multinational investment bank has started to prepare for a "potentially catastrophic" situation in which the United States could de</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Every Young Person in America Watching 'SOPRANOS'?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/29/why-is-every-young-person-in-america-watching-the-sopranos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. In August,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Man's Endless Hunt for Dopamine Rush in Virtual Reality...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/29/one-mans-endless-hunt-for-a-dopamine-rush-in-virtual-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a recent Thursday evening at the City Life Community Center in Missoula, Mont., Wolf Heffelfinger played laser tag. Wearing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA declares 23 species extinct, underscoring what scientists say is acceleration...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-declare-23-species-including-ivory-billed-woodpecker-extinct-ap-2021-09-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ivory-billed woodpecker and 22 more birds, fish and other species will be declared extinct by the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service on Wednesday, U.S. media reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON robot roams around your house...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/28/amazon-event-2021-live-updates-amazons-set-to-announce-new-products.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon announced a home robot named Astro, a new Echo Show 15 smart screen, a thermostat, a new fitness tracker and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivermectin disinformation leads to new kinds of chaos...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/574397-ivermectin-disinformation-leads-to-new-kinds-of-chaos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An avalanche of misinformation about the antiparasitic drug ivermectin’s ability to treat COVID-19 has caused a series of national problems, from increased calls to poisoning centers to a shortage of the medicine itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA STARS PUSH BACK ON VAX</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/574387-nba-struggles-with-vocal-vaccine-holdouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate over COVID-19 vaccine mandates has spilled into the NBA, exposing divisions within the league over how to keep players safe from the fast-spreading virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign of progress, Biden digs in to strike deal on $3.5T plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-0b4e92eeb7622250e1aa5e12839b1294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pressure mounting but with signs of progress, President Joe Biden will hunker down at the White House to try to strike a deal and win over two holdout Democratic senators whose support is needed for his potentially historic $3.5 trillion government overhaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems scramble to scale back $3.5 trillion tax-and-spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-scramble-to-scale-back-35-trillion-tax-and-spending-bill/ar-AAOVifA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In private meetings and public comments, party leaders increasingly have come to acknowledge that there is no chance they can adopt a measure with such a sky-high price tag, especially given the stated opposition to that spending aired by centrist Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron says he got dosed despite skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/lebron-james-covid-vaccine-nba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I felt like it was best suited for not only me but for my family and my friends," James said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Science fiction'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-unveils-science-fiction-robot-211721304.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon revealed a camera-equipped home robot Tuesday that users can deploy to patrol their houses, a device that one of the project's developers said was making science fiction a reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says it tested new hypersonic missile...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210928211642-qo76s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (URGENT):North Korea says it test-fired new hypersonic missile - KCNA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears' dad to be 'investigated for secretly recording daughter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3745401/britney-spears-dad-jamie-investigated-recording-bedroom-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ dad Jamie will be “seriously investigated” for allegedly “secretly recording his daughter in her bedroom” and “may face jail time,” The Sun can reveal.  Following the shocking …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Course for Traumatized Journalists Advises: 'Take Time To Be Sexual With Yourself'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/journalism-self-care/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American journalists are increasingly struggling to cope with the on-the-job stress and trauma of reporting the news and posting about it on Twitter. "I crawled in bed and cried for our pre-pandemic lives," CNN's Brian Stelter wrote in April 2020."Tears that had been waiting a month to escape."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says it tested new type of hypersonic glide vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20210929000400325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.yna.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
