<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA, allies quietly prepare for Ukrainian govt-in-exile and long insurgency...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/U-S-and-allies-quietly-prepare-for-a-Ukrainian-16979802.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian military has mounted an unexpectedly fierce defense against invading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST removes bylines...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/597004-washington-post-removes-bylines-to-protect-reporters-amid-russias-new-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post announced that the newspaper would be removing bylines and datelines from certain coverage to protect their staff after Russian President Vladimir Putin signed a law that targets independent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI-powered tech landed man in jail with scant evidence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-algorithm-technology-police-crime-7e3345485aa668c97606d4b54f9b6220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Michael Williams’ wife pleaded with him to remember their fishing trips with the grandchildren, how he used to braid her hair, anything to jar him back to his world outside the concrete walls of Cook County Jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky pleads for fighter jets, Russian oil embargo in call with senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/volodymyr-zelensky-ukraine-russian-righter-jets-c7a0e94a-07a1-49bf-aebc-abb8e4d1ba63.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"These planes are very much needed. And I will do all I can to help ... facilitate their transfer," Schumer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Fracturing of American Attention...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2022/03/americans-focus-attention-span-threat-democracy/626556/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why resisting distraction is one of the foundational challenges of this moment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasingly isolated, Putin finds few allies in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/increasingly-isolated-putin-finds-a-few-allies-in-latin-america/ar-AAUEgro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the queer vanguard of country music...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/05/entertainment/lgbtq-country-music-orville-peck-patrick-haggerty-lavender-cec/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered corpses. Rain of rockets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scattered-corpses-rain-rockets-week-130059916.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swathes of Ukraine have fallen into Russian hands. Corpses scattered in the snow. Rockets rain daily on civilians. The capital, Kyiv, waits in cruel limbo for advancing Russian forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Coachella approaches, Kanye legacy hangs by thread...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coachella-approaches-kanye-wests-legacy-214909025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ye's discography and celebrity mean he can still headline mega music festivals. But his latest outbursts and threats may be too much for fans to bear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Faces Reckoning for Relying on Putin for Cheap Energy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/germany-faces-reckoning-relying-putin-050000464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For years, the U.S. warned Germany of building up a dangerous energy dependence on Russia, the source of more than half of its fossil fuel imports. Now that the war in Ukraine has shocked Berlin into the same conclusion, the government is finding that changing course might be too late. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: UN Council to Meet, Safety Corridors Set UpUkraine Update: Kyiv Offers to Hold Talks With Russia on MondayRussian Forces Occupy Site of Nuclear Plant as Fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE: 'BATMAN' SET FOR $120 MILLION OPEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/the-batman-box-office-opening-1235104983/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starring Robert Pattinson, the superhero pic will easily score the second best debut of the pandemic era behind 'Spider-Man: No Way Home.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Blood Test Detects Over 50 Genetic Neurological Diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/03/05/revolutionary-blood-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An international team of scientists are cutting down all the pricking and prodding in doctor visits by creating a single blood test to find over 50 genetic diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies Focus on Security of Zelensky, Other Ukraine Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/05/u-s-and-allies-discuss-security-of-ukraines-leaders-amid-fears-for-zelenskys-safety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Allied governments have been discussing how to secure the line of succession in Ukraine in the event President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Gripped by Violence and Misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/05/tiktok-is-gripped-by-the-violence-and-misinformation-of-ukraine-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bre Hernandez used to scan TikTok for videos of makeup tutorials and taco truck reviews. Since Russia invaded Ukraine, the 19-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's far right in quagmire over Kremlin links...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/europe/europes-far-right-in-quagmire-over-ukraine-war-and-putin-links/articleshow/90009824.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe News: BERLIN: Russia's invasion of Ukraine has plunged far-right movements across Europe into an identity crisis, as they struggle to square their loyalty t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says it seeks to 'resolve' Taiwan question, amid comparisons to Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/China-says-it-seeks-to-resolve-Taiwan-question-16979419.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is committed to "resolving the Taiwan question in the new era," it said in its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein busted for smuggling MILK DUDS into jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-harvey-weinstein-milk-duds-los-angeles-jail-20220304-3q3iyp6ebjhmzfddr7lr2ys3aq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A search of the imprisoned Oscar-winning producer uncovered a stash of Milk Duds after a Los Angeles meeting with his attorney in a jail medical facility in downtown Los Angeles, according to a report Thursday by Variety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odessa readies for brutal push up Black Sea coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-s-venerable-odessa-readies-for-russia-s-brutal-push-up-the-black-sea-coast/ar-AAUCJQ0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke experts fear what's to come...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-ukraine-power-plant-fire-was-contained-but-nuclear-experts-fear-what-s-to-come-in-russia-s-war/ar-AAUD6Nk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive early midterm successes reignite debates over electability...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/what-so-many-people-told-us-was-impossible-progressive-dems-tout-early-midterm-success/ar-AAUCgbO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local churches shun Vatican's moderate stance on Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-pope-francis-business-religion-88fb4df0efb29e9007a5a4fb0e77a07b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The head of the Polish bishops’ conference has done what Pope Francis has so far avoided doing: He publicly condemned Russia’s invasion of Ukraine and urged the head of the Russian Orthodox Church to use his influence with Vladimir Putin to demand an end to the war and for Russian soldiers to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA BOMBS EVACUEES?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4827762/russia-ukraine-ceasefire-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA breached a ceasefire just hours after agreeing to allow civilians to escape from two besieged cities. Vladimir Putin’s forces had agreed to halt their bombardments on the strategic por…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much porn makes bad in bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4826685/porn-blokes-bad-bedroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOO much porn makes blokes bad in the bedroom — and women better. Scientists found men who watch large amounts of X-rated material suffer a dip in sexual performance and are less able to please the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Success In Life -- Agreeableness?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/agreeableness-career-life-success/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests having the personality trait agreeableness can improve your job performance and help you win at life in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN, ABC, CBS stop broadcasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10579867/CNN-ABC-CBS-BBC-CBC-Bloomberg-stop-broadcasting-Russia-fake-news-law-comes-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has said it would stop broadcasting in Russia while Bloomberg and the BBC said they would temporarily suspend the work of their journalists there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's praise of Putin, 'America First' view tested by war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-donald-trump-campaigns-foreign-policy-4625a28e59996ff16085fdf30910a449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — From the earliest days of his first presidential campaign, Donald Trump aggressively challenged the pillars of Republican foreign policy that defined the party since World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia cracks down on dissenting media, blocks FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-business-europe-latvia-efe42bcc2d4ffd71711bcc6e9f95cdc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUSSELDORF, Germany (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Friday intensified a crackdown on media outlets and individuals who fail to hew to the Kremlin line on Russia's war in Ukraine , blocking Facebook and Twitter and signing into law a bill that criminalizes the intentional spreading of what Moscow deems to be “fake” reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Freedom Convoy' set to roll into DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/04/us/trucker-convoy-protest-washington-dc/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convoy groups led by American truckers are making their way toward the nation's capital to demand an end to all Covid-19 mandates and restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence swings at the Don: No room in party for Putin apologists...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/596926-pence-no-room-in-gop-for-apologists-for-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence on Friday will rebuke those in the Republican Party who have praised Russian President Vladimir Putin in recent weeks, including most prominently former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Mulls Russian Oil Ban...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oil-extends-wild-week-gain-235213193.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Oil posted its biggest weekly gain on record with prices swinging in a $20 range since Russia invaded Ukraine and sparked fears of a major supply crunch.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: UN Council to Meet, Safety Corridors Set UpRussian Forces Occupy Site of Nuclear Plant as Fire ContainedUkraine Update: Russian Troops Occupy Nuclear Plant SiteWhite House Weighs Ban on Russian Oil Imports as Congress FumesPutin’s Financial Isolation by World’s Powerful Is a Cautionary Tale</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZON phone outages across East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/verizon-sees-phone-outages-across-u-s-east-coast/ar-AAUCKHp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VP Harris to visit Poland, Romania...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Live-updates-Fire-at-Ukraine-nuclear-plant-16976507.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest developments on the Russia-Ukraine war:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. Milley Personally Delivers Javelins, Stingers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/04/as-russia-pounds-ukraine-nato-countries-rush-in-javelins-and-stingers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEAR UKRAINE’S BORDER — Some 14 wide-bodied aircraft transported a bristling array of Javelin antitank missiles, rocket launchers, guns and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone enthusiasts sign up to repel forces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-technology-business-europe-47dfea7579cedfe65a70296eb0188212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In better times, Ukrainian drone enthusiasts flew their gadgets into the sky to photograph weddings, fertilize soybean fields or race other drones for fun. Now some are risking their lives by forming a volunteer drone force to help their country repel the Russian invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN YANKS BROADCAST</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-cnn-to-stop-broadcasting-in-russia-will-continue-to-monitor-the-situation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia amid the invasion of Ukraine, according to a tweet from CNN senior media reporter Oliver Darcy. Darcy tweeted that a CNN spokesperson has said that the cable network "will stop broadcasting in Russia while we continue to evaluate the situation and our next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKY NEWS' harrowing account of violent ambush...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/sky-news-teams-harrowing-account-of-their-violent-ambush-in-ukraine-this-week-12557585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded. Their experience illustrates the scale of the mayhem and violence as Russia's invasion enters a new and deadlier phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO MORE top commanders killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/17847821/two-more-russian-top-commanders-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO more of Vladimir Putin’s top military chiefs have been killed after personally charging to the battlefield to rescue their stalled invasion. As well as sniping General Andrei Su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Incapable of Complex Operations?</title>
      <link>https://rusi.org/explore-our-research/publications/rusi-defence-systems/russian-air-force-actually-incapable-complex-air-operations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rusi.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a week into the Russian invasion of Ukraine, the Russian Air Force has yet to commence large-scale operations. Inactivity in the first few days could be ascribed to various factors, but the continued absence of major air operations now raises serious capability questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS defense reporter challenges war comments on air...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-arts-and-entertainment-army-tucker-carlson-europe-7d0f7212e07ecb8657f3e94b851710db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News national security correspondent Jennifer Griffin couldn't hold back when following a retired U.S. Army colonel on the air recently, saying she barely had time to correct all of his “distortions.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
