<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pellicano Back in Business and Working for Joel Silver...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/anthony-pellicano-joel-silver-daryl-katz-1234889846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Pellicano, the former private eye who spent 16 years in federal prison, is back in business as a Hollywood fixer. Pellicano confirmed to Variety that he is working for Joel Silver, the &amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census estimates show population decline in 16 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/01/21/census-estimates-show-population-decline-in-16-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low birth rates, COVID-19 deaths and immigration cutbacks contributed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA PEAK DEATH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-reports-277-covid-19-225900932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Florida’s daily COVID-19 death toll hit 277 Friday, tying the state record for resident and non-resident deaths from the disease. Florida reported 13,719 new coronavirus cases on Friday and another 272 new resident deaths linked to COVID-19. The state has now reported 1,627,603 cases since the pandemic began. The death toll tied the state record set Aug. 11, as the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App gives men '24-hour consent contract' to have sex after Denmark passes controversial rape law...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2186952/fury-at-app-that-gives-24-hour-consent-contract-to-have-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW app that gives men a “24 hour consent contract” to have sex has sparked fury. The launch comes in response to a new rape law, which criminalises sex without explicit consent in De…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLMERT: I hate everything Sheldon Adelson loved about Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/opinion/olmert-i-hate-everything-sheldon-adelson-loved-about-israel-opinion-656289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything I love about Israel has nothing to do with Adelson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden officials weigh releasing Trump tax records sought by House panel...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-officials-weigh-releasing-Trump-tax-records-15891567.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats have renewed their long-stalled demand for former president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOC plans to vaccinate every Olympic athlete to save Tokyo games...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210122203254-t21a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPICS-2020/WHO (URGENT):IOC plans to vaccinate every Olympic athlete to save Tokyo games -Telegraph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium bans leisure travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-pandemics-europe-leisure-travel-south-america-5e820f285a726db40debd0d6eb96c73d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Belgium is banning all leisure travel abroad for its citizens as of next week and until March, in an effort to contain the spread of COVID-19 and its virulent variants....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Guard in DC forced to sleep in garages, sparking outcry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-riots-6c9bd3ed150cbb6c3cf0b90084440293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Images of National Guard soldiers camped in a cold parking garage after being sent to protect Washington sparked new calls Friday for investigations of the U.S. Capitol Police,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden thanks with chocolate chip cookies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-jill-biden-b766529a8dd024ba37a2265cf97667b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — New first lady Jill Biden took an unannounced detour to the U.S. Capitol on Friday to deliver baskets of chocolate chip cookies to National Guard members, thanking them “for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYPILLOW CEO Hires GAWKER-Killing Lawyer to take on DAILY MAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mypillow-ceo-mike-lindell-hires-charles-harder-to-go-after-daily-mail-for-jane-krakowski-affair-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tabloid story “damaged my integrity as a Christian,” Lindell said to The Daily Beast in confirming he has retained the Trump lawyer most infamous for taking on media outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED AIRLINES TO REQUIRE JAB FOR ALL EMPLOYEES?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/united-airlines-ceo-wants-to-make-covid-vaccines-mandatory-for-its-employees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines CEO wants to make Covid vaccines mandatory for the company's employees, a stance that differs from other airlines and sectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But prospects erode?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/22/politics/senate-republicans-trump-impeachment-case/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path in the Senate to convict Donald Trump is extremely slim, with a growing number of Republicans expressing confidence that the party will acquit the former President on a charge that he incited the deadly insurrection aimed at stopping President Joe Biden's electoral win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Tax Hike Coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/pete-buttigieg-puts-gas-tax-hike-table-during-confirmation-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two days in office and the Biden administration is already considering breaking President Biden’s campaign promise that “anyone making less than $400,000 a year won’t pay a penny more” in taxes.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;During his Senate confirmation hearing for Transportation Secretary, Former Mayor Pete Buttigieg told members of the Commerce, Science and Transportation Committee that a gas tax increase is “on the table” as a means to pay for infrastructure spending.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;When asked directly by Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists make paralyzed mice walk again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/22/german-scientists-make-paralyzed-mice-walk-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German researchers have enabled mice paralyzed after spinal cord injuries to walk again, re-establishing a neural link hitherto considered irreparable in mammals by using a designer protein injecte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  NOTHING CAN CHANGE TRAJECTORY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/biden-says-nothing-can-change-the-trajectory-of-covid-pandemic-over-the-next-several-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES ousts editor who had 'chills' watching plane land...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/22/ny-times-ousts-editor-who-said-she-had-chills-watching-biden-plane-land/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York Times editor’s contract has been cancelled after she tweeted she had “chills” watching Joe Biden’s plane ahead of his inauguration. “Biden’s plane lan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Pentagon Chief Unloads: 'This f*cking place is rotten'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/01/embedding-with-pentagon-leadership-in-trumps-chaotic-last-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout the final, frenzied days of the Trump administration, a reporter rode shotgun with the outgoing acting defense secretary, Christopher Miller, the man who, under the distracted eye of his commander in chief, became America’s de facto guardian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems float 14th Amendment to bar from office...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/535467-democrats-float-14th-amendment-to-bar-trump-from-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are mulling whether they can use the 14th Amendment to prevent former President Trump from ever holding office again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giant suspends second AI ethics researcher...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-suspends-second-ai-ethics-165936450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google has suspended an artificial intelligence ethics researcher weeks after dismissing another member of the team, a recently formed union said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy takes action against TIKTOK following girl's death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sicily-italy-dad71e550ff2f8d3fca56d0f40e3c95e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy’s data protection authority said Friday it was imposing an immediate block on TikTok’s access to data for any user whose age has not been verified. The authority said it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada ramps up deportations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-canada-deportation/exclusive-canada-deporting-thousands-even-as-pandemic-rages-idUSKBN29R1EL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada deported thousands of people even as COVID-19 raged last year, data seen by Reuters shows, and lawyers say deportations are ramping up, putting people needlessly at risk in the midst of a global health emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Packed like sardines': Struggles to contain Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/22/national-guard-coronavirus-461340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Guard members who poured into Washington after the Jan. 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol have tested positive for Covid-19 or are quarantining in nearby hotels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Reportedly Cancels Editor Who Tweeted 'Chills' on Inauguration Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-york-times-cancels-contract-of-editor-who-tweeted-having-chills-on-biden-inauguration-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times has reportedly terminated the contract of an editor who tweeted that she had "chills" while watching President Joe Biden's plane land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes cleared to play...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-bashaud-breeland-football-kansas-city-chiefs-chad-henne-f0bacd534687665df83828a222132267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — Chiefs quarterback Patrick Mahomes was cleared Friday from the league's concussion protocol after his third consecutive day of practice and will be under center when Kansas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first for Spain, Jesuits admit to decades of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/international-news-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-spain-bd48515c52e036fcaa96dcf4edb488d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — The first comprehensive internal inquiry on sex abuse allegations by a religious order in Spain has identified 81 children and 37 adult victims of 96 Jesuits since the late 1920s, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany To Put Right-Wing Party Under Surveillance For Violating Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/01/22/959264440/germany-expected-to-put-right-wing-afd-under-surveillance-for-violating-constitu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's Federal Office for the Protection of the Constitution has wrapped up a two-year investigation into the Alternative for Germany. The party's far-right branch is already under surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign paid $2.7M to organizers of rally ahead of Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/535440-trump-campaign-paid-27-million-to-organizers-of-rally-ahead-of-capitol-riot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump’s campaign had paid out more than $2.7 million to several individuals and firms behind the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED ALERT: China Authorizes Coast Guard to Fire on Foreign Vessels...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-coastguard-law/china-authorises-coast-guard-to-fire-on-foreign-vessels-if-needed-idUSKBN29R1ER</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China passed a law on Friday that for the first time explicitly allows its coast guard to fire on foreign vessels, a move that could make the contested waters around China more choppy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People happier when they make more money...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/new-wharton-study-people-are-happier-when-they-earn-more-money.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous research suggested that the correlation between money and happiness levels off once someone makes $75,000 a year, but a new The Wharton School study reveals more nauance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHPOST Memory-Holes Kamala Joke About Inmates Begging for Food, Water...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/01/22/the-washington-post-memory-holed-kamala-harris-bad-joke-about-inmates-begging-for-food-and-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when legacy publications are increasingly seen as playing for one political "team" or the other, this type of editorial decision will not do anything to fix that perception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers faking negative tests -- and getting away with it...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/22/these-travelers-faked-negative-covid-tests-got-away-with-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This potentially dangerous end-around shows a huge loophole in coronavirus travel restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE bans German channel that spread virus misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/misinformation-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-87d59ab59cc194d3b674e2f44a87dd47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Google says it has banned a prominent German user of its YouTube video platform who had repeatedly posted false claims about the coronavirus outbreak. Google said Friday that a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans quietly lobby to convict...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/22/politics/mcconnell-trump-impeachment-conviction-republicans/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the House prepares to send articles of impeachment to the Senate on Monday, CNN has learned that dozens of influential Republicans around Washington -- including former top Trump administration officials -- have been quietly lobbying GOP members of Congress to impeach and convict Donald Trump. The effort is not coordinated but reflects a wider battle inside the GOP between those loyal to Trump and those who want to sever ties and ensure he can never run for President again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMP:  Ally got $750k in unsuccessful pardon push...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-ally-got-750k-amid-unsuccessful-pardon-push-0f3d0d1a-8342-42b7-9325-479df84aabf1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The payment shows how lucrative Trump connections became.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MORNING JOE' Questions if Should Exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/morning-joe-fox-news-exist-capitol-riot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anand Giridharadas said Fox News viewers "are brain-mashing victims" and called for "justice" when it comes to the "media ecosystem"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3,000 per child in new stimulus?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Senior-Democrats-drafting-plan-to-give-parents-15890604.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior Democratic lawmakers are moving to fulfill President Joe Biden's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic sleeping pods for homeless installed in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/homeless-sleeping-pods-germany-ulm-b1791217.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests are underway to if the pods protect against frostbite. If so, they could be rolled out across Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking laser link could test of Einstein's relativity theory...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-01-record-breaking-laser-link-einstein-theory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from the International Centre for Radio Astronomy Research (ICRAR) and the University of Western Australia (UWA) have set a world record for the most stable transmission of a laser signal through the atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Market For Covid Vaccine Booming...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/01/21/covid-vaccines-coronavirus-internet-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shortage of COVID-19 vaccines has prompted some to try and get it on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Man who stole ambulance caught in JACK IN THE BOX drive-thru...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/texas-ambulance-thief-caught-712309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 22--While paramedics were on a call, a Texas man last night jumped into an ambulance and drove the vehicle, with its lights flashing, to a Jack in the Box, where he ordered food at the drive-t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3,000 per child in new stimulus?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/01/22/biden-childtaxcredit-stimulus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Democratic lawmakers are drafting legislation to have the Internal Revenue Service send recurring monthly payments to tens of millions of American families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLE TROUBLE:  Fears 2,500 Bitcoin 'whales' who own 40% of market could cause crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/13822372/bitcoin-whales-crash-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BITCOIN ‘whales’ who hold staggering sums of the cryptocurrency could crash the market, experts have warned. It comes as Bitcoin soars to record sums, currently valued at £23,000 ($32,0…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK BORIS:  NEW STRAIN MORE DEADLY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/boris-johnson-evidence-new-covid-variant-associated-with-higher-mortality-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is "some evidence" a new Covid variant first identified in the U.K. could be more deadly than the original strain, British Prime Minister Boris Johnson said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANK ARON DEAD AT 86...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-atlanta-braves-hank-aaron-coronavirus-pandemic-0fa32aff826d18bbeb9efedd42cd81a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Hank Aaron, who endured racist threats with stoic dignity during his pursuit of Babe Ruth’s home run record and gracefully left his mark as one of baseball’s greatest all-around...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Dems in Control, Investors High on Cannabis...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmal.com/news/with-democrats-in-control-investors-are-high-on-cannabis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Democrats in Control, Investors Are High on Cannabis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaman Admits: I Was Duped...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/qanon-shaman-jacob-chansley-disowns-trump-saying-he-was-duped</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Referring to his client as “the guy with the horns and the fur,” attorney Al Watkins said the rioter “regrets very, very much” that he was tricked by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Joe Plans to Beat Obstructionism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/01/joe-biden-democrats-midterms-2022-obama/617716/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;History suggests that Joe Biden and the Democrats are going to have a tough two years and a disaster in the midterms. Here’s their plan to avoid that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader vows 'revenge' on Trump with pic of drone strike on golf course...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2188710/iran-supreme-leader-revenge-trump-drone-golf-course/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWITTER has suspended Iran’s supreme leader after he vowed revenge on Donald Trump with a picture showing a drone about to attack him on the golf course. The move comes after the tech giant w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enemies, a Love Story: Inside 36-year Biden and McConnell Relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/01/22/joe-biden-mitch-mcconnell-relationship-460385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two 78-year-old deal-makers have been parties to the collapse of Capitol culture. Now they’ll need to make Washington work again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Foes Face Uphill Fight in Getting Cable Network Dropped...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/fox-news-foes-face-uphill-fight-in-getting-cable-network-dropped/ar-BB1cZy9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight against election misinformation has a new target: your cable company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Chappelle Positive for Covid After String of Live Club Shows, Viral Backstage Photo...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/comic-legend-dave-chappelle-tests-positive-for-covid-after-string-of-live-club-shows-viral-backstage-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary comic Dave Chappelle has tested positive for COVID-19 in the middle of a live show residency in Austin, and after maskless backstage photos with the likes of Elon Musk and Joe Rogan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Rodgers, entering showdown with Brady, has gone from chippy to chill...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Aaron-Rodgers-entering-a-showdown-with-Tom-15890104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a peace about Aaron Rodgers now, a feeling different from his normal vibe of cool detachment. He is invested in the moment, and only the moment. No mistrust of others. No dismissiveness. No streak of rebellion. Just appreciation and focus.  He stands neither as desperate, at age 37, to win a second Super Bowl nor burdened by the challenge of facing Tom Brady, the ultimate ring collector, in a divine NFC championship game showdown. No doubt, he understands the historical implications. As a competitor and future first-ballot Hall of Famer, he surely cares about the personal opportunity to enhance his legend. But more than anything, he just wants to see this joyful Green Bay Packers season through.  It's strange to observe Rodgers, wondrous yet temperamental, without a hint of edginess.  "I talk about a lot how thankful I am to be in this opportunity," Rodgers said. "To be the starting quarterback here - to be relied upon for my play, my leadership, my presence, my daily preparation - there's no greater feeling. This is such a special honor. It's one of the greatest honors of my life, definitely up to this point, to be able to lead this team and be counted on by my teammates to bring not just my physical play but my presence, my emotions, my words. I'm thankful for the opportunity to still be here and still be the guy. And I'm excited about what we can accomplish together."  Before the 2020 season began, the conversation centered on how much longer he would be in Green Bay. After all, the Packers drafted quarterback Jordan Love in the first round last April, reminiscent of when Green Bay selected Rodgers in 2005 to be the eventual successor to Brett Favre. Rodgers was perturbed. Speculation about an awkward, if not volatile, situation ensued. Then Rodgers defied the low expectations. Instead of succumbing to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Patent Shows Plans to Revive Dead Loved Ones as Chatbots...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/microsoft-chatbot-patent-dead-b1789979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patent also mentions using 2D or 3D models of specific people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Gives 7,500 Vaccinated Health Care Workers Free Super Bowl LV Tickets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/nfl-gives-7500-vaccinated-health-care-workers-free-super-bowl-lv-tickets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Football League announces it will give 7,500 health care workers free tickets to Super Bowl LV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic showing which friendships worth keeping...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/The-pandemic-is-showing-us-which-friendships-are-15890068.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the pandemic, Sherilyn Carlton's family was so accustomed to her friends popping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Russia vows crackdown on Navalny protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210122-russia-vows-crackdown-on-navalny-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia vows crackdown on Navalny protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas doctor stole vaccine, gave to family, friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2021/01/22/texas-doctor-stole-coronavirus-vaccine-gave-it-to-his-family-and-friends-authorities-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harris County doctor has been fired and faces a criminal charge after authorities say he stole a vial of coronavirus vaccine and gave it to friends and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third round of executive orders to boost food benefits, workers' rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/22/covid-stimulus-update-biden-to-sign-executive-orders-on-hunger-workers-rights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden has already signed executive orders to offer coronavirus relief as he tries to pass a $1.9 trillion aid package in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hundreds of National Guard members banished to Senate parking garage...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/This-is-absurd-Hundreds-of-National-Guard-15890217.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At least hundreds of National Guard members were forced out of a U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA Warns Policy Fueling Bubble in Wall St Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/bofa-warns-u-s-policy-is-fueling-a-bubble-in-wall-street-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BofA Warns U.S. Policy Is Fueling a Bubble in Wall Street Prices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANK AARON DEAD AT 86...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/hank-aaron-atlanta-braves-home-run-king-dead-86/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hank Aaron, Braves legend who once held the record for most career home runs, died on Friday [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDARD HOTEL in West Hollywood shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/standard-hotel-west-hollywood-shutting-215526899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Standard hotel in West Hollywood on the Sunset Strip is set to close Friday. It said its lease price made the location unsustainable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia With No GOOGLE? Bitter Fight Behind Drastic Threat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/22/an-australia-with-no-google-the-bitter-fight-behind-a-drastic-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY, Australia — In a major escalation, Google threatened on Friday to make its search engine unavailable in Australia if</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California keeps key virus data from public...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sacramento-california-coronavirus-pandemic-gavin-newsom-38bb44ea7cb39eab9f6f6c621daeaf10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California Gov. Gavin Newsom has from the start said his coronavirus policy decisions would be driven by data shared with the public to provide maximum transparency....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONDAY: IMPEACHMENT II TRIAL BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-biden-cabinet-trials-462425af29b02c43e24913b6fd191b6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi plans to send the article of impeachment against Donald Trump to the Senate on Monday, launching the start of the former president's trial on a charge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Orthodox attack Israeli police amid tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/international-news-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-riots-tel-aviv-9a347a277e691befcbe137099e81a253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Ultra-Orthodox Jews attacked an unmarked Israeli police vehicle overnight, pelting it with stones and smashing the windows while officers were inside, and igniting a riot in which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucky few hit jackpot for rare extra doses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-1e6792a0bd4695487313fb3430429d94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortune struck one man in the bakery aisle at the supermarket. Two others were working the night shift at a Subway sandwich shop. Yet another was plucked from a list of 15,000 hopefuls. With...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
