<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Highbrow Return of Nicolas Cage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/07/nicolas-cage-pig-movie-review/619466/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor may have retreated from the mainstream, but his latest film is a reminder that he’s always been a magnetic screen presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boredom link to mental illnesses, brain injuries, dysfunctional behaviors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/boredom-s-link-to-mental-illnesses-brain-injuries-and-dysfunctional-behaviors/ar-AAMgjFd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early research often dismissed the psychological state as temporary and inconsequential. But recent work reveals its troubling connections with various disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria investigating 'Havana syndrome' among U.S. envoys...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717120140-sn1o3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ENERGYATTACK/AUSTRIA (PIX):Austria investigating reported 'Havana syndrome' cases among U.S. envoys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to unveil new fighter jet at Moscow air show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-europe-russia-moscow-aec52e68fc3b482dfc6a4132a2bafcbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian aircraft makers say they will present a prospective new fighter jet at a Moscow air show that opens next week. The new warplane hidden under tarpaulin was photographed being towed to a parking spot across an airfield in Zhukovsky, outside Moscow, where the MAKS-2021 International Aviation and Space Salon opens Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Great Salt Lake shrinking fast. Fear turning toxic dustbin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/17/us/great-salt-lake-drought-dying/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great Salt Lake is also known as America's Dead Sea -- owing to a likeness to its much smaller Middle Eastern counterpart -- but scientists worry the moniker could soon take new meaning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie Brinkley non-negotiable daily habit: Gratitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/17/christie-brinkley-at-67-her-non-negotiable-habit-for-energy-and-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermodel Christie Brinkley says practicing gratitude is the one non-negotiable habit that she does every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-Founder Says Safety Concern Has Him Quitting Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/ethereum-co-founder-says-safety-concern-has-him-quitting-crypto/ar-AAMeULB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Di Iorio, a co-founder of the Ethereum network, says he’s done with the cryptocurrency world, partially because of personal safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future JEEPS will be able to drive underwater, CEO says...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/auto/future-jeeps-will-be-able-to-drive-underwater-ceo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeep CEO Christian Meunier said the brand may one day sell electric vehicles that can be driven entirely underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs 'Just Get' Humans In Ways Other Animals Simply Can't...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-just-get-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man’s best friend has actually evolved to understand human gestures and look to humans for help in a way that no other animals do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba president confronts nation in crisis. Among challenges: 'He's no Fidel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-e2-80-99s-president-confronts-a-nation-in-crisis-among-his-challenges-e2-80-98he-e2-80-99s-no-fidel-e2-80-99/ar-AAMge05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters and analysts wonder whether Cuba is at a tipping point that will usher in economic reforms — or simply lead to more repression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can USA 'restore' internet to island?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-restore-internet-cuba-013344937.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's suggestion that Washington bring full internet access to Cuba following government restrictions could break new ground on digital rights but face major technical and geopolitical hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand say 'huge focus' on trans trailblazer...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-new-zealand-say-huge-focus-on-trans-trailblazer-at-tokyo-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand say 'huge focus' on trans trailblazer at Tokyo Olympics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe picks through rubble from deluge as death toll soars...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-europe-picks-through-rubble-from-deluge-as-death-toll-soars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe picks through rubble from deluge as death toll soars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes awaits Palme d'Or winner after vintage year...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-cannes-awaits-palme-d-or-winner-after-vintage-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannes awaits Palme d'Or winner after vintage year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to require negative test within 24 hours for arrivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210717-france-to-require-24-hour-old-covid-test-for-some-unvaccinated-eu-arrivals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France said Saturday it would require people not fully vaccinated and arriving from some European countries to show a negative Covid test taken within the previous 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music banned on Mykonos in new COVID restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717102637-87qks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GREECE-MYKONOS:Music banned on Greece's Mykonos in new COVID-19 restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany cuts short warmup with allegations of racism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-africa-germany-middle-east-03672d7998b1c1772968b8aa33e80fc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAKAYAMA, Japan (AP) — Germany’s Olympic soccer team walked off the field during a preparation match for the Tokyo Games on Saturday in response to alleged racist abuse from an opposing Honduras player toward German defender Jordan Torunarigha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First covid case inside Olympic Village days before Opening Ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/first-case-of-coronavirus-infection-inside-olympic-village-confirmed-six-days-before-opening-ceremony/ar-AAMfNa4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first positive coronavirus case has been confirmed inside the Olympics Village just six days before the Opening Ceremony, officials confirmed Saturday, amid growing fears about the spread of the virus during the Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Missing, Scores Dead as Raging Floods Strike Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-floods-954655c9382a9b8c12a230bdd8cd5b3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The death toll from disastrous flooding in Western Europe rose above 150 on Saturday as rescue workers toiled to clear up the devastation revealed by receding water and prevent further damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico new home for many of world's refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/final-destination-many-worlds-refugees-mexico-new-home-rcna1316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, Mexico has gone from being a transitory country for refugees seeking to go to the U.S. or other places to becoming their final destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney tightens new lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9797037/Harsher-lockdown-looms-Sydney-111-new-cases-crackdown-rules-breakers-launched.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sydney's numbers headed in the wrong direction again with 111 new Covid cases recorded on Saturday after three weeks of lockdown. Gladys Berejiklian's response was dramatic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON asked APPLE to remove app that spots fake reviews, and APPLE agreed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/16/apple-removes-fakespot-from-app-store-after-amazon-complains.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fakespot is a well-known app used to help shoppers detect fraudulent reviews on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears 'went missing for 24 hours and was found on the street by surfers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/15612648/britney-spears-missing-24-hours-found-surfers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears went missing for 24 hours and was found by strangers on the street, one of her former best pals has revealed. The bombshell revelation was made by one of her closest confidantes in a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid 'paranoia' at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/16/team-gb-have-covid-paranoia-at-olympics-admits-bianca-walkden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taekwondo fighter Bianca Walkden says Team GB athletes at the Tokyo Olympics are paranoid about catching Covid and missing competition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pingdemic:  Brit app sent half a million exposure notifications in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pingdemic-englands-covid-app-sent-half-a-million-exposure-notifications-in-a-week/ar-AAMeOiZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Factories, pubs, restaurants and schools are reporting staff shortages after so many urged to stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Florida police officers charged in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-fla-police-officers-charged-in-new-proud-boys-indictment-in-capitol-riot/ar-AAMf8YQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-defendant case grows with three arrests, including the husband of a sheriff’s deputy. Indictment spotlights law enforcement ties to accused right-wing group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Guests Find Damp Towels, Trash Piles in Worker Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/hotel-guests-find-damp-towels-trash-piles-amid-worker-shortage/ar-AAMeujG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Busted shower handles. Soiled sheets. Trash piling up in the hallways. James Androuais saw it all during the 100-plus nights he spent on the road last year, as low occupancy rates and Covid-19 precautions pushed hotel operators to let traditional service standards slide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed supper club coming to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/16/luxury-micro-dosing-supper-club-coming-to-tribeca/?_ga=2.257876162.890470292.1626489596-1784295609.1625614900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is a space to celebrate the intersection of fine dining and cannabis … Medly Supper Club is designed to encourage conversation amongst our guests.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rare monkeypox virus reported in Dallas resident...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/dallas-resident-has-texas-first-ever-case-of-monkeypox-but-it-s-not-a-reason-for-alarm/ar-AAMf1Lw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Updated at 6:30 p.m.: Revised to include comments from Dr. Philip Huang, Dallas County’s public health director. A Dallas resident has been diagnosed with monkeypox, the first case of the virus ever reported in a human in Texas, officials said Friday. But they stressed that the risk posed to the general public was very low. The patient flew to Dallas Love Field from Atlanta on July 9 after ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After conquering Earth, Bezos eyes new frontier in space...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conquering-earth-bezos-eyes-frontier-013259124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos sets his sights on a new frontier in space in the coming days after building a gargantuan business empire which has in many ways conquered the Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney tightens new lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717005253-91n1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Sydney tightens lockdown as Australia's COVID-19 cases rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand bans public gatherings as deaths hit daily record...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717004423-fav93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/THAILAND (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Thailand bans public gatherings as coronavirus cases and deaths hit daily records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER TRAVEL HELL:  Lawmaker quizzes airlines on delays, worker shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-6bc47103625a126d4194ae515cc6a7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A key senator is asking six U.S. airlines to explain the high rates of delayed and canceled flights this summer, and she's asking whether there are labor shortages despite the airlines getting billions in federal aid to keep workers on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE NIGHTMARE FOR 'DREAMERS'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-immigration-f01fc0f485a8983b5f072e7af324c43f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigrants and advocates are urging Democrats and President Joe Biden to quickly act on legislation to protect young immigrants after a federal judge in Texas on Friday ruled illegal an Obama-era program that prevents the deportation of thousands of them brought into the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Suspends Reporter Who Didn't Disclose Michael Phelps Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ny-times-suspends-reporter-karen-crouse-who-failed-to-disclose-her-michael-phelps-book-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her ethical conflict was revealed, Crouse was yanked off the paper’s Olympic coverage team and taken off the swimming beat, multiple sources told The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare case of monkeypox found in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rare-case-monkeypox-found-texas-resident-who-had-traveled-internationally-n1274163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials say any threat to the general public is low — mainly because the patient and fellow airline passengers were wearing masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans 'disappointed' with lack of Biden action...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210716-cubans-disappointed-with-lack-of-biden-action</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cubans 'disappointed' with lack of Biden action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERVAIS:  'I Can't Name A Funny Woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3297788/no-funny-women-teases-ricky-gervais/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OUTSPOKEN comic Ricky Gervais is inviting trouble in a new stand-up routine — by claiming he can’t name one funny woman. The Office creator, 60, pokes fun at sitcom star Miranda Hart and says the o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Crack Down On Brothers Behind 45 Million Illegal Robocalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/robocalls-ftc-crack-down-telemarketing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlawful telemarketing campaign included millions of calls to those on FTC's Do Not Call Registry, agency says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone rattled by swarm of over 140 earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article252835908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t panic. The current alert level at the Yellowstone Volcano Observatory is green, which is normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS BACK IN VEGAS,</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-las-vegas-coronavirus-pandemic-d106142a8c0a2710a770c9687514ed7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Masks are back in Las Vegas, after regional health officials on Friday cited a rising number of coronavirus cases and advised everyone — vaccinated or not — to wear facial coverings in crowded indoor places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON PLAGUED BY WIDESPREAD VACANCIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/16/pentagon-weapons-vacancies-china-499838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has been slow to announce nominees for the 58 Senate-confirmed positions at the Pentagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House in touch with FACEBOOK to ensure correct 'narratives'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/16/psaki-white-house-in-touch-with-facebook-to-push-true-narratives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki on Friday said the Biden administration is “in regular touch” with Facebook to ensure correct “narratives.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-foot-4 Chinese teen girl dominating on the court...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/16/7-foot-4-chinese-teenager-zhang-ziyu-is-getting-comparisons-to-yao-ming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7-foot-4 adult is rare. A 7-foot-4 14-year-old is unheard of. Enter Zhang Ziyu, a teenage girl from East China’s Shandong Province, after a video of her notching 42 points, 25 rebounds…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film Producer Charged With Operating Escort Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/producer-dillon-jordan-charged-prostitution-service-1234983221/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California movie producer was arrested Thursday on a New York indictment accusing him of using a movie production company to operate an international prostitution business. Dillon Jordan, 49, of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA will spend record amount on homelessness...</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/national/california-will-spend-a-record-amount-on-homelessness-heres-where-its-going/article_9f5eb79c-2313-5348-8ad9-b596ad95333f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California will spend a record $4.8 billion over two years to alleviate homelessness after legislators Thursday unanimously passed key details of a new state budget. The package, once signed into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Can't Resist Using, Abusing Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/16/federal-agencies-cant-resist-using-and-abusing-facial-recognition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some agencies don't even know ways their employees are using facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says socials carrying misinformation 'killing people'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210716181832-3l3m5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FACEBOOK (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Biden says social media carrying COVID misinformation is 'killing people'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Destroy 1,069 Bitcoin Miners With Steamroller...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kv739/police-destroy-1069-bitcoin-miners-with-big-ass-steamroller-in-malaysia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malaysian authorities did not mess around when they broke up a cryptocurrency mining farm and charged the operators with stealing electricity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL accounts for 20% of ALL new infections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/563402-white-house-florida-accounts-for-20-percent-of-all-new-covid-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 20 percent of the nation's new coronavirus infections are now happening in Florida alone, according to a White House official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned 'Medicaid' Expansion Would Pay for Abortions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/07/democrats-plan-for-new-medicaid-like-program-would-pay-for-elective-abortions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will pro-life Senator Joe Manchin insist on an alternative that doesn’t fund abortion as part of the reconciliation bill?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Just 7% of our DNA is unique to modern humans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-4edeb2256900dd182f5cac5f26b8aa66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — What makes humans unique? Scientists have taken another step toward solving an enduring mystery with a new tool that may allow for more precise comparisons between the DNA of modern humans and that of our extinct ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LA family's $18-million fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-07-16/covid-fraud-conspiracy-los-angeles-ayvazyan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Fernando Valley family was caught creating fake businesses to get pandemic disaster loans, then spending the money on houses, gold and diamonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS 'Evening News' head departs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cbs-evening-news-head-departs-c99c37e9-e849-4ed9-97fd-8a7cd982b948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The program has struggled to compete for ratings with other evening news at ABC and NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK DAILY CASES TOP 50K FOR FIRST TIME SINCE JANUARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3295736/uk-covid-cases-surge-january/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAILY Covid cases have today passed the 50,000 mark for the first time since mid-January – with a further 49 deaths recorded.  Infections rose by 51,870, bringing the total to 5,332,371.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines headed to protect embassy in Haiti, but no troops, says Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2021/07/16/marines-headed-to-protect-embassy-in-haiti-but-no-troops-to-stabilize-nation-says-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden signaled he was not open to the request for U.S. troops, which comes as he is drawing down U.S. forces in Afghanistan this summer.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
