<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>West Sobered by Imminent War, Gives Iran Reasonable Doubt...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2020-01-09/west-backs-off-of-blaming-iran-despite-evidence-in-ukraine-jet-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alt-right author Brimelow sues NYT for $5M over 'White Nationalist' claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/09/brimelow-new-york-times-lawsuit-097095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Brimelow is suing the newspaper over a Jan. 15 article that offered a chronology of racist and inflammatory comments by Rep. Steve King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking number of young Americans say other countries are better...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=14195</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out the stats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Probe If Russia Targeting Biden in 2020 Meddling...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-10/us-probes-if-russia-targeting-biden-to-help-trump-win-re-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bc4445d8fbfbe3a45fb012a3beaa829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said Friday the House will take steps next week to send articles of impeachment to the Senate ending Democrats' blockade of President Donald Trump's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran 'has fleet of killer dolphins trained to blow up ships'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/iran-fleet-killer-dolphins-trained-21254757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Originally trained by the Soviet Union in Russia, the aquatic squadron of mammalian 'mercenaries' could still be alive and ready to harpoon frogmen in the Persian Gulf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED KEEPS PUMPING</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/federal-reserve-temprorary-liquidity-89c59d7e-7c47-4663-ae55-33b5b55b39f3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That strategy played no small part in the stock market's 30% gain in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mendes war epic of grandfather's heroics shakes Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mendes-war-epic-grandfathers-heroics-shakes-hollywood-145723438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Mendes says that "1917" is his "most personal" film, and it could yet be his most praised after it ripped up the form books to win him best film and best director at the Golden Globes earlier this week. "It was clearly a technical challenge," Mendes told AFP before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Moves To Have Media Tossed Out Of Rape Trial Courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-media-shut-out-jury-selection-motion-1202826722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of the first official week of Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial began Friday with a new legal grenade being tossed into the proceedings. “Most people don’t speak in front of the international m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Journalist Wins Pay-Discrimination Case Against BBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2020-01-10/female-journalist-wins-pay-discrimination-case-against-bbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare 'Homeland Security' Warning: Update FIREFOX Browsers Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90450626/firefox-attacks-homeland-security-urges-mac-users-to-update-browsers-immediately-in-rare-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers can take over your computer if you don’t upgrade–and Homeland Security says they’re already doing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 29,000</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/10/dow-futures-on-the-back-of-easing-tensions-in-the-middle-east.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose to record highs on Friday despite weaker-than-expected jobs data as Wall Street concluded a volatile week chalk full of geopolitical concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Intel Alert: Suspected Suicide Bomber en Route to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/01/09/exclusive-border-patrol-circulates-intel-alert-titled-suspected-suicide-bomber-en-route-to-the-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are on alert after receiving a law enforcement intelligence warning about a possible suicide bomber heading north toward the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran uses bulldozers to clear plane crash site?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10711754/iran-plane-crash-bulldozers-debris-shot-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has used bulldozers to clear debris from the plane crash site while slamming the “big lie” that they shot it down. The Ukrainian passenger jet came down hours after Tehran launched a barrage o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy has another video of Nimitz UFO encounter yet to be released...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/navy-confirms-another-video-nimitz-21253169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy said the video of the USS Nimitz UFO has been classified "secret". A former US Air Force intelligence expert has since told Daily Star Online this video could be "clearer" and at least "10 minutes long"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBS GROWTH SLOWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/10/us-nonfarm-payrolls-december-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. jobs market ended 2019 on a sour note, with December's payroll and wage growth missing expectations, according to Labor Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Crisis in Venezuela Has Nearly Everyone Depressed and Medicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/crisis-in-venezuela-has-nearly-everyone-depressed-and-medicated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone I Know Is Depressed and Medicated: Life in Caracas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Mansion Sale for $262 Million Set to Shatter Record!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/london-mansion-for-over-262-million-set-to-shatter-u-k-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Mansion for Over $262 Million Set to Shatter U.K. Record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD AMERICANS WORKING...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/record-158803000-americans-employed-185m-year-year-increase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since December 2018, 1,858,000 more workers have been added to American payrolls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Highly likely' shot down...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/highly-iran-shot-ukrainian-airliner-us-official-confirms/story?id=68173173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. intelligence is confident that Iran painted the Ukrainian airliner with radar and fired two surface to air missiles that brought down the aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close call with medical helicopter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/local-news/colorado-to-deploy-more-teams-to-investigate-mystery-drones-after-close-call-with-medical-helicopter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado Department of Public Safety will start using more ground-based teams and aircraft to investigate the mysterious drones seen in Colorado in recent weeks after a medical helicopter pilot reported a drone coming “in dangerous proximity” to the aircraft on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of Americans favor wealth tax on very rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-inequality-poll-idUSKBN1Z9141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea of imposing a wealth tax on the richest Americans has elicited sharply ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 29,000?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dow-set-to-29000-as-wall-street-awaits-key-jobs-report-2020-01-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks look likely to carve out fresh records on Friday, and the Dow industrials may trade at the psychologically significant level of 29,000 for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Standoff May Be Near End With Pelosi Allies Stumped...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-allies-stumped-impeachment-standoff-090000314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Lawmakers expect House Speaker Nancy Pelosi will soon end her delay of President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial without any notable concessions from Senate Republicans, leaving her allies stumped about her strategy in the three-week standoff.Senior Democrats in the House insisted publicly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter million people urged to flee...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200110073105-9i8ao</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities sent emergency texts to 240,000 people in Victoria, telling them to evacuate, as soaring temperatures and erratic winds fanned bushfires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden sees drop in plane travel as 'flight shame' movement bites...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/sweden-flight-shame-movement-arlanda-airport-gotherburg-climate-change-a9277936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2020 bed makers reassure athletes recycled beds won't collapse during sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/olympics/tokyo-2020-beds-athletes-sex-collapse-recycled-cardboard-condoms-how-many-a9277846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong winds create Australian 'megablaze'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/strong-winds-create-australian-megablaze-095322522.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gale-force winds in Australia merged two enormous fires into a megablaze spanning an area four times the size of Greater London on Friday, while tens of thousands rallied to again demand action on climate change. "The conditions are difficult today," said Shane Fitzsimmons, rural fire service</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals face extinction...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australian-animals-face-extinction-threat-bushfire-toll-mounts-050702353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When volunteer Sarah Price found a baby kangaroo frightened but miraculously alive in the pouch of its dying mother surrounded by the embers of Australia's bushfires, it seemed fitting to name him Chance. The furry pair had survived flames that have ripped through much of southeastern Australia,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Would Ban Cellphone Use For Anyone Under 21 In Vermont...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesargus.com/news/local/bill-would-ban-cellphone-use-for-those-under/article_2e4064f1-892f-5a83-95a2-d8a4272942d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesargus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTPELIER — A bill has been introduced in the state Senate that would make it illegal for anyone under the age of 21 to use or possess a cellphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Made 532 TV Shows in 2019, and It's Going to Make More!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/hollywood-made-532-tv-shows-in-2019-and-it-e2-80-99s-going-to-make-more/ar-BBYNoEQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-ROYALS HEAD TO HOLLYWOOD?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/meghan-markle-prince-harry-hollywood-deals-after-royal-duties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What will Meghan Markle and Prince Harry do next after announcing their "step back" from the Royal Family? Endorsements deals, according to experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK tabloids were royal pain... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Analysis-U-K-tabloids-were-a-royal-pain-14963503.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Prince Harry and his wife, Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, made their shocking announcement Wednesday on Instagram - that they plan to step back as senior royals and split their time between the United Kingdom and North America - they also encouraged their 10.4 million followers to visit their new website, SussexRoyal.com, to find more information.  One part of the glossy site that hinted at a possible reason behind their bombshell decision? The "Media" section.  In several long paragraphs, Harry and Meghan explained that they will be taking a "revised media approach" in their new roles. Most significantly, they will no longer be a part of the "royal rota" system - essentially a press pool - in which a group of U.K. outlets get exclusive access to royal events and share that information with other publications.  However, the couple emphasized that they will "provide access to credible media outlets focused on objective news reporting," adding that they understand that there is great interest in them as members of the royal family. "They welcome accurate and honest media reporting as well as being held to account if appropriate," the website reads.  The key words here, of course, are "credible," "accurate" and "honest," apparent digs at the brutal tabloid stories that Harry and Meghan have endured for the past several years. In the fall, the couple sued the Mail on Sunday newspaper for publishing a private letter that Meghan wrote to her estranged father after her wedding; Harry also filed a lawsuit against The Daily Mirror and The Sun, claiming they hacked his phone.  Royal experts and observers say there are many complicated reasons behind Harry and Meghan's new path. But it seems clear that intrusive tabloid coverage added to their motivation to step away from royal tradition.  "I think it had a significant impact,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT TRIAL 'SOON'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3b2714efc1f153d3192b138d3c33521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said Thursday she will "soon'' transmit the articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump, signaling a potential thaw in the standoff with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Employees Mocked FAA in Internal Messages...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200110012845-3329i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOEING-737MAX/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Boeing releases internal messages on 737 MAX, calls them 'completely unacceptable"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia calls for another mass evacuation as monster bushfires return...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-bushfires/australia-calls-for-another-mass-evacuation-as-monster-bushfires-return-idUSKBN1Z730R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian authorities urged another mass evacuation across the heavily populate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUFTHANSA flight 'turned around'...</title>
      <link>https://www.flightglobal.com/air-transport/iran-surface-to-air-missile-downed-ukraine-737-canadian-and-us-officials/136070.article</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.flightglobal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian and US officials believe Iranian military forces, possibly by mistake, shot down the Ukraine International Airlines Boeing 737-800 that crashed outside Tehran on 8 January, killing 176 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan flees to Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7870677/Prince-Harry-Meghan-Markle-left-young-Archie-Canada.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Mail has learnt that Meghan Markle has returned to North America, where her and Prince Harry's eight-month-old son, Archie, had been left with his nanny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women with transplanted uterus gives birth to 'miracle' baby...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8c4a4da006bf965b6706dc7ac6962b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who gave birth to a boy she carried inside a transplanted womb said Thursday that the experimental procedure delivered a “miracle.” Jennifer Gobrecht and her husband, Drew Gobrecht,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7870409/Video-appears-surface-air-missile-hitting-Ukrainian-plane-moments-crashed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was released hours after Pentagon officials said they believe the Ukrainian Airlines flight which crashed in Tehran killing 176 people Wednesday was shot down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/09/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-us-iran-tensions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks jumped to record highs on Thursday as tensions between Iran and the U.S. eased for the time being, with tech shares outperforming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby Blames #MeToo For Conviction...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/09/bill-cosby-appeal-blames-metoo-sexual-assault-conviction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cosby filed the appeal with the Pennsylvania Supreme Court, which does not have to take the case, on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA: Perhaps 'Unintentional'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-crash-canada/canada-pm-says-evidence-indicates-iran-shot-down-ukraine-jet-idUSKBN1Z82JZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada has intelligence from multiple sources indicating a Ukrainian airliner th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg drops annual challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-zuckerberg-goals/facebook-ceo-zuckerberg-drops-annual-challenges-to-focus-on-longer-term-goals-idUSKBN1Z82IN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc's Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg said on Thursday he ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA coach under fire for calling team 'bunch of thugs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/28453087/sources-john-beilein-meets-cavaliers-players-gives-emotional-apology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cavaliers are planning to continue with John Beilein as coach after he made an emotional apology to his players and met with GM Koby Altman on Thursday, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell backs measure to change rules, dismiss...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/477587-mcconnell-backs-measure-to-change-senate-rules-dismiss-impeachment-without</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is backing a resolution to change the Senate’s rules to allow for lawmakers to dismiss articles of impeachment against President Trump before the House sends them over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic conference call...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/09/harry-reportedly-held-epic-post-megxit-conference-call-with-royals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen, Prince Charles, Prince William and Harry burned up the phone lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border arrests drop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6a1d7f4d132225c902e93e3a9b5cd6ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The number of people arrested or stopped entering the United States along the Mexico border fell for a seventh straight month in December. with Mexicans making up a larger than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN CRIME STORY: IMPEACHMENT' Delayed Until 2020 Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/american-crime-story-impeachment-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third season of FX's "American Crime Story" on the Impeachment of Bill Clinton will not air in September as it was originally scheduled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance video from Epstein's first 'suicide' attempt 'no longer exists'... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/surveillance-video-jeffrey-epstein-s-first-apparent-suicide-attempt-no-n1113166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at the federal jail housing Epstein preserved video from the wrong floor due to a clerical error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>61% of say too much economic inequality...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/09/61-percent-of-americans-say-theres-too-much-economic-inequality-in-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Americans agree that the unequal distribution of income and opportunity between different groups has gotten to be too much. But less than half rate it a priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: '60 MINS' MEETS THE REAL JOAQUIN PHOENIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/60-minutes-meets-joaquin-phoenix-2019-01-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dark, complex characters may be a trademark, but Joaquin Phoenix showed 60 Minutes a different side when he met Anderson Cooper. See the full interview, Sunday on CBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Issued No-Fly Order Hours Before...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-issued-no-fly-order-over-iran-iraq-hours-before-ukrainian-plane-downed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just hours before a Ukrainian plane was shot down Wednesday over Iran, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration issued a no-fly order over Iran and Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAG-AFTRA Office Evacuated for Second Time in 3 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sag-aftra-la-office-evacuated-second-time-3-days-1268363</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another phone threat was called in, and police are additionally searching the New York offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Infrared Blips'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/iran-commander-vows-harsher-revenge-against-us-relief-in-tehran-today-after-trump-speech-2020-01-09/#post-update-ca108587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is set to vote Thursday on a resolution that would limit President Trump's ability to engage in hostilities against Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considers Ban On Gas-Powered Garden Tools...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/08/california-considers-statewide-ban-on-gas-powered-garden-tools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any gas-powered gardening tools, you may be forced to give them up soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL offering $100,000 salary amid mounting worker shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/taco-bell-offering-24100000-salary-amid-mounting-worker-shortage/ar-BBYMNIM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  42% CHANCE ON WINNING NOMINATION...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-primary-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2020 Democratic presidential primary election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's Lee Will Vote to Remove?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-utah-mike-lee-might-123233527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Get Jonathan Bernstein’s newsletter every morning in your inbox. Click here to subscribe.I had a Twitter discussion awhile ago in which I argued that Utah Senator Mike Lee was one of the three or four most likely Republicans to vote to convict and remove President Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER tests ways to limit online abuse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/twitter-test-ways-limit-online-abuse-151540387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has announced it will test new ways to limit online abuse by offering users control over who can reply to tweets. "We want to help people feel safe participating in the conversation on Twitter by giving them more control over the conversations they start," the company tweeted. Company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane turned back before crashing?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-probe-finds-ukrainian-plane-turned-back-problem-064526868.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian authorities have said a Ukrainian airliner, which crashed outside Tehran with the loss of all 176 people on board, had turned back after suffering a problem, as Ukrainian experts joined the investigation Thursday. Both Canada and the United States called for a full investigation to determine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan aim to control media image...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d3ca824003dac85311b8e884918e94e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The relationship between Britain’s royals and the media is awkward, mistrustful — and seemingly inescapable. But now Meghan and Harry want out. After years of growing tension...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Iran shot down Ukrainian jetliner!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a2dc1478299d83e233c2cb4d4cd1891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two U.S. officials said Thursday it was “highly likely” that an Iranian anti-aircraft missile downed a Ukrainian jetliner late Tuesday, killing all 176 people on board....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue mocking Trump torched in Slovenia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0bcc73fa8eac7ceef4f2f9791297e2ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LJUBLJANA, Slovenia (AP) — A wooden statue mocking U.S. President Donald Trump was burned to the ground Thursday in Slovenia, the birthplace of his wife Melania, authorities said. The nearly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg won't release women who sued him from secrecy agreements...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bloomberg-wont-release-women-sued-secrecy-agreements/story?id=68171036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg spoke out about the controversy over the non-disclosure agreements while on the campaign trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator: 'Trump's stock level at all-time high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/gop-senator-trumps-stock-level-at-all-time-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key Republican senator on Wednesday said that respect for President Trump has surged since he ordered the killing of Iran’s top military leader, and he gave credit to the White House and Pentagon for reinvigorating U.S. deterrence power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON CLAIM:  Iran shot down Ukrainian jetliner!</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/downing-street-calls-for-urgent-inquiry-pentagon-confirms-plane-in-iran-was-shot-down-by-a4330741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing Street has said it was looking into "very concerning" reports about the Tehran airliner crash following speculation that the jet was shot down by a missile.  Asked whether there were any concerns about the cause of the disaster, the spokesman said: "I'm not going to speculate on this but the reports we have seen are very concerning and we are urgently looking into them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYALS ROCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/prince-harry-queen-meghan-markle-defied-plans-senior-royals-a4330341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry defied clear instructions from the Queen not to announce that he and Meghan are to quit as “senior” royals, the Evening Standard has been told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bots Destroying Political Discourse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2020/01/bots-are-destroying-political-discourse-we-know-it/162285/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re mouthpieces for foreign actors, domestic political groups, even the candidates themselves. And soon you won’t be able to tell they’re bots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: 92-year-old woman murdered, left bleeding on NYC street...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/92-year-old-woman-found-dead-in-queens-was-murdered-nypd/2257158/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a 92-year-old woman was found unresponsive on the streets of Queens, police initially thought she had fallen — now authorities believe she was murdered. Police say they received a 911 call about Maria Fuertes just after midnight on Monday. She was found lying along 127th Street in Richmond Hill, not far from her home. She was later pronounced dead…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegals rescued from top of 30-foot border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/illegal-immigrants-rescued-from-top-of-30-foot-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Mexicans trying to sneak into the United States had to be rescued from the top of a 30-foot tall section of the border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSILE MYSTERY...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/explanations-for-ukrainian-air-crash-elusive-amid-political-tensions-with-iran-154827922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior official in Ukraine says the authorities in Kyiv are looking into whether a missile brought down a passenger aircraft that crashed in Iran on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Strikes Out in Attempt to Get New Judge...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-judge-rejection-jury-selection-1202825580/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge in Harvey Weinstein’s New York rape trial won’t be stepping down today from the case nor putting the brakes on it, despite a harsh January 8 request by the disgraced producer’s defense te…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
