<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Italy's first sex doll brothel 'booked for weeks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-italys-first-sex-doll-13189650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
'Like Roman orgy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/727312/sex-doll-brothel-robot-group-sex-lumidolls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot boat sails into history by finishing Atlantic crossing...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/robot-boat-sails-history-finishing-atlantic-crossing-57585858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All summer, the small boat drifted steadily eastward across the churning North Atlantic until it neared the Irish coast, where it made history by becoming the first unmanned sailboat to cross the Atlantic. The SB Met, built by Norwegian company Offshore Sensing AS, reached the finish line...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roe v. Wade Likely to Play Starring Role...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/roe-v-wade-likely-to-play-starring-role-at-kavanaugh-hearings-1536058800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since President Trump announced his nomination of Brett Kavanaugh to the Supreme Court, Democrats and abortion-rights activists have expressed alarm about the fate of Roe v. Wade. Here’s a Q&amp;A about the abortion legal landscape, how it could change, and what to expect at the hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret to couple's 80 years of marriage: Wife's patience...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-ageing-oldest-couple/secret-to-japan-couples-80-years-of-marriage-wifes-patience-idUSKCN1LK0XH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan is known for its abundance of centenarians and can now lay claim to having the world's oldest living married couple, with a combined age of 208 - a feat the wife credits to her patience during 80 years of marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No place like home: Dorothy's ruby slippers recovered 13 years later...</title>
      <link>https://www.mprnews.org/story/2018/09/04/stolen-dorthy-ruby-slippers-wizard-of-ozrecovered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mprnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The famous slippers, worn by Judy Garland's character Dorothy as she clicked her heels and repeated "there's no place like home," have been missing since August of 2005, when they were stolen in a smash-and-grab burglary at the Judy Garland Museum in Grand Rapids, Minn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says space station leak could be deliberate sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-09-russia-space-station-leak-deliberate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia launched checks Tuesday after its space chief said an air leak on the International Space Station last week could have been caused by deliberate sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going up! Japan to test 'space elevator'...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-09-japan-mini-space-elevator.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Japanese team working to develop a "space elevator" will conduct a first trial this month, blasting off a miniature version on satellites to test the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts congressional match-up mirrors New York upset...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-massachusetts/massachusetts-congressional-match-up-mirrors-new-york-democratic-upset-idUSKCN1LK0Y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 10-term Democratic congressman will try to fend off a challenge on Tuesday from a Boston city councilor who could become Massachusetts' first black congresswoman in a race with parallels to a New York upset that rattled the party in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Weigh Abandoning Second Phase of Tax Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/republicans-weigh-abandoning-second-phase-of-tax-cuts-after-salt-backlash-1.1132462</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Persists...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mueller-persists-despite-trump-teams-080002086.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation should have just gone out of business -- or at least into a two-month deep freeze -- if you take Rudy Giuliani’s word for it. Giuliani, President Donald Trump’s lawyer, has maintained for weeks that Saturday, Sept. 1, was a deadline under Justice Department</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte orders arrest of loudest, most prominent critic...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/philippine-president-dutertes-plan-for-his-most-vocal-critic-lock-him-up-1536049895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte ordered the arrest of his loudest and most prominent critic as he intensifies a crackdown on his political opponents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Warfare Erupts Between NBCNEWS and Ronan Farrow...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/09/nbc-news-andy-lack-memo-harvey-weinstein-ronan-farrow-explanation-not-airing-new-yorker-1202456410/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 9:54 PM: If NBC News chairman Andy Lack thought his detailed memo and fact sheet dropped today on what supposedly really went down with Ronan Farrow’s scrapped probe into sexual harassment …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Dems widest advantage since '06...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/energized-donald-trump-democrats-reach-14-midterms/story?id=57538542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new ABC News/Washington Post poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJs, Swim Briefs, $25 Coladas: In Vegas, Party's at Pool...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/04/travel/las-vegas-pools.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city has long been known for its night life. Now, day clubs are the destination of the moment, with nonstop music, tropical cocktails and the inevitable red-velvet ropes. The water can get wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water levels continue to drop at Lake Mead, Lake Powell; 'Crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/09/03/lake-mead-lake-powell-drought-colorado-river/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water levels at Lake Mead and Lake Powell are dropping to dangerous levels, reflecting the Colorado River’s worsening “structural deficit,” scientists said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former president Kirchner appears in Argentine court over corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/former-president-kirchner-appears-argentine-court-over-corruption-180512727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former president Cristina Kirchner appeared in court on Monday for the second time in relation to a corruption case that has rocked Argentina's political and business elites. Two weeks after the Senate voted to partially lift senator Kirchner's congressional immunity so that investigators could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had relics from around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/burned-national-museum-rio-had-relics-around-world-212842927.html'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil's National Museum in Rio de Janeiro, which suffered a massive fire late Sunday, boasted the largest archive of historical artifacts and documents in Latin America, some 20 million pieces from around the globe. Museum officials say it's too soon to say what had been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg Standard: 'No hints, no forecasts, no previews'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kavanaugh-and-the-ginsburg-standard-1536010512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘No hints, no forecasts, no previews,’ she said in 1993, responding to a question about discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran struggles with wealth-poverty disparity visible on streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/san-francisco-rich-and-poor-turns-to-simple-street-solutions-that-underscore-the-citys-complexities/2018/09/03/d6cf321a-ad4d-11e8-8a0c-70b618c98d3c_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor London Breed trades liberal-laboratory governance for practical approaches: “I want people to walk around this city and think, ‘Wow, it’s so clean here.’ ”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNHEALTHY LIFESTYLES PUT 4 IN 5 ADULTS AT RISK OF EARLY DEATH...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/sep/04/four-in-five-adults-at-risk-of-early-death-heart-age-test-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors call figures for England alarming and urge people to adopt healthier lifestyles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON BOOTED FROM NY'ER FEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/03/arts/bannon-new-yorker-festival-remnick.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Mulaney, Jim Carrey and Patton Oswalt were among celebrities who said they would not appear at the festival next month if Stephen K. Bannon remained its headliner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS MAKES HIS MOVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1011912/theresa-may-leadership-challenge-boris-johnson-brexit-Lynton-Crosby-Chequers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May could face a fresh leadership challenge as her former election guru has launched a ‘revenge’ plot to set up Boris Johnson as prime minister, an insider has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOURS before confirmation hearing, lawyer releases 42,000 PAGES of documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Hours-before-Kavanaugh-confirmation-hearings-13202217.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Hours before the start of hearings on Brett Kavanaugh's nomination to the Supreme Court, the lawyer for former president George W. Bush turned over 42,000 pages of documents from the nominee's service in the Bush White House, angering Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer who issued what is certain to be a futile call to delay the proceedings. "Not a single senator will be able to review these records before tomorrow," Schumer, D-N.Y., tweeted Monday evening. Taylor Foy, a spokesman for Senate Judiciary Committee Chairman Chuck Grassley, R-Iowa, responded that "our review team will be able to complete its examination of this latest batch in short order, before tomorrow's hearing begins." The hearings are scheduled for 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>87 elephants killed near sanctuary...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-45396394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservationists found 87 elephant carcasses while conducting a wildlife survey in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings could fall even further this season...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/03/why-nfl-ratings-could-fall-even-further-this-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL ratings are facing yet another brutal blitz this fall — and few pundits are betting that they won’t get sacked. With ratings having plunged 8 percent in 2016 and nearly 10 percent last year, ex…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions flare...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/rios-200-old-national-museum-hit-massive-fire-001902679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later, police granted access to the site's perimeter, which protesters surrounded in a symbolic "embrace." The rumbling tensions reflect anger over the destruction on Sunday of the much-loved yet dilapidated museum, which suffered from declining federal funding. It stirred emotions in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians see metaphor for their struggles in museum fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7810839883784c838189beeec7b377b9/Brazilians-see-metaphor-for-their-struggles-in-museum-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Firefighters dug through the burned-out hulk of Brazil's National Museum on Monday, a day after flames gutted the building, as the country mourned the irrepl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global debt levels raise red flags... </title>
      <link>http://www.savannahnow.com/news/20180903/global-debt-soars-along-with-fears-of-crisis-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.savannahnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten years after the worst financial panic since the 1930s, growing debt burdens in key developing economies are fueling fears of a new crisis that could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump accuses Sessions of hurting Republican congressional races...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/03/trump-slams-sessions-on-twitter-says-ag-is-hurting-gop-in-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump lashed out at Attorney General Jeff Sessions in a string of tweets on Monday, accusing him of hurting Republican chances in the upcoming midterm elections with a series of Justice Department investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS CHIEF: WEINSTEIN STORY WASN'T READY!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6128543/NBCs-Andy-Lack-says-didnt-kill-Ronan-Farrows-Weinstein-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News chairman Andy Lack has defended his network's decision not to air Ronan Farrow's Harvey Weinstein expose, insisting that the story 'wasn't ready to air' at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewinsky walks out of interview after Clinton question...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/404843-monica-lewinsky-walks-off-stage-during-interview-after-being</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Lewinsky ended a live discussion and walked off stage at an event in Jerusalem on Monday night after being asked a question involving former President Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Gogh was murdered claims new film...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/van-gogh-murdered-claims-film-venice-175704466.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new film about the artist Vincent Van Gogh claims that he was murdered rather than having shot himself. "At Eternity's Gate" starring Willem Dafoe as the tortured genius, was premiered Monday at the Venice film festival. While most historians agree that Van Gogh killed himself, renowned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China investments in Africa raise 'new colonialism' fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-raises-fears-apos-colonialism-173840507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping on Monday pledged $60 billion in financing for projects in Africa in the form of assistance, investment and loans, as China furthers efforts to link the continent's economic prospects to its own. Speaking to a gathering of African leaders in Beijing, Mr Xi said the figure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks crop Farrakhan out of pic on stage with Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/sep/2/networks-crop-farrakhan-clintonjacksonsharpton-ima/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was an image that caused quite a stir Friday afternoon. There on the stage presiding over Aretha Franklin’s epic funeral extravaganza was former President Bill Clinton alongside former presidential candidates Jesse Jackson and Al Sharpton. And immediately next to those three, in the same honored position as the ex-president and the civil rights leaders was anti-semite, Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey woes could be just start as record global debt bills come due...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/turkeys-woes-could-be-just-the-start-as-record-global-debt-bills-come-due/2018/08/28/f9f144c6-a231-11e8-8e87-c869fe70a721_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lira’s decline is only a preview of what could happen, economists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmadinejad Backs QB...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/sep/03/colin-kaepernick-nike-just-do-it-campaign-nfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quarterback was one of first players to kneel during anthem, leading to Trump slamming the protests and no team signing him up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope views fuel 'blue wave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/09/03/kavanaugh-democrats-strategy-trump-supreme-court-health-care-806034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If they can’t beat Kavanaugh, they’ll use his conservative views to fuel their &amp;quot;blue wave.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Ready Investigative Onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/03/us/politics/democrats-trump-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their confidence growing, House Democrats are preparing an onslaught of investigations that would put President Trump on defense and slow talk of impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Sights Set On Online Ad Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/03/business/media/amazon-digital-ads.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The online retailer is moving aggressively into digital advertising, emerging as a major competitor to Google and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red-state Dems in tight spot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/red-state-democrats-tight-spot-over-kavanaugh-confirmation-n905551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vulnerable Democrats argue that Kavanaugh’s confirmation is not on top of most voters’ minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So long, Zuckerberg: Small businesses ditch...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/goodbye-facebook-why-some-small-businesses-are-quitting-social-network-n905171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“One of the Facebook policy changes decreased my income from Facebook by 60 percent, overnight. No explanation," said one small business owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado city to lower voting age to 16?</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/09/03/golden-minimum-voting-age-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Golden will decide in November whether to move ahead with lowering the voting age to 16 when it comes to municipal issues and candidates only. The city would become the first in Colorado …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABOR DAY: Bernie Ups Bezos Bashing At AFL-CIO Breakfast...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/09/03/speech-sanders-steps-bezos-criticism/LTdvR9OV7w09ABporzxEfN/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator reprises the income inequality themes that fueled his 2016 presidential run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU's Vestager Calls to Resist Nationalist Lure; Vision Suggests Ambition...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-03/eu-s-vestager-echoes-macron-with-call-to-resist-nationalist-lure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems turn to therapy dogs to encourage youth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-03/-30-million-poured-into-effort-to-energize-young-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS CHIEF: FARROW STORY WASN'T READY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/nbc-news-andrew-lack-ronan-farrow-weinstein-1202925479/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News Chairman Andrew Lack sent employees a detailed memo and an 11-page analysis Monday spelling out why the news organization felt it could not air journalist Ronan Farrow’s 2017 investi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Five Eyes' Govts Call For Encryption Backdoors -- Or Else...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/09/03/five-eyes-governments-call-on-tech-giants-to-build-encryption-backdoors-or-else/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pact of five nation states dedicated to a global “collect it all” surveillance mission has issued a memo calling on their governments to demand tech companies build backdoor access to their users’ encrypted data — or face measures to force companies to comply. The international …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US service member killed in Afghanistan; 2nd 'insider attack' in as many months...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/insider-attack-eastern-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waitress files human rights complaint after boss demands she wear bra...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/09/02/waitress-suing-former-boss-who-demanded-she-wear-a-bra-to-work-7905950/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christina Schell says she was fired after refusing to sign a dress code agreement dictating she must wear a bra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON BOOTED FROM NY'ER FEST...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/09/03/celebrities-pull-out-of-new-yorker-festival-in-protest-of-steve-bannon-appearance-yes-the-new-yorker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: David Remnick has disinvited Bannon from the Festival. He wrote to the staff: “”I don’t want well-meaning readers and staff members to think that I’ve ignored their concerns. I’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big spending abroad fuels growing domestic backlash...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-africa-20180903-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's big spending on the Belt and Road Initiative in Africa and elsewhere faces a growing domestic backlash  – from influential academics to ordinary Chinese on social media websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Bad online restaurant review led to drive-by shooting...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox35orlando.com/news/local-news/deputies-shots-fired-into-home-because-of-bad-restaurant-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox35orlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Walley was sitting on the couch, watching television, when a bullet whizzed by his head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trillion-ton iceberg spinning, headed for huge collision...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6128021/Trillion-ton-iceberg-cracked-Antarctica-year-spinning-heading-huge-collision.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polar oceanographer Mark Brandon, who spotted the movement using temperature data collected by the Suomi NPP satellite said A68 has started to swing northwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals warn Feinstein...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/404652-feinstein-under-the-microscope-for-kavanaugh-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.) is under intense pressure heading into Brett Kavanaugh's Supreme Court confirmation hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blames Sessions for indictments of Republican lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/03/trump-blames-sessions-for-indictments-of-gop-lawmakers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump interrupted his Labor Day holiday to launch a raging mid-afternoon tweetstorm at Attorney General Jeff Sessions — apparently blaming him for last month’s indictments of a pair of “v…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents' Jobs Increasingly Shape How Far Kids Get in Life...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/economics/2018/09/03/parents-jobs-increasingly-shape-how-far-kids-get-in-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research adds to evidence it's become harder in recent decades for Americans to get ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne says moving to Israel when 'CONNERS' premieres...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/03/entertainment/roseanne-barr-moving-israel-conners/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roseanne Barr says she plans to be abroad when "The Conners" premieres without her this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Face of NIKE Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2793994-colin-kaepernick-named-face-of-nikes-30th-anniversary-of-just-do-it-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike selected former San Francisco 49ers quarterback Colin Kaepernick as the face of its "Just Do It" campaign, which is celebrating its 30th anniversary...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL EYES ON KAVANAUGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/09/03/donald-trump-supreme-court-nominee-brett-kavanaugh-gets-senate-test/1180524002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh faces Senate Judiciary Committee grilling about his views on abortion, guns, health care – and President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy nudes to have 'gender equality' in new post-#MeToo exhibition...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/03/royal-academy-nudes-have-gender-equality-new-post-metoo-exhibition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Royal Academy is to ensure its next exhibition of nudes has an equal gender split of naked men and women, as it navigates the post-Me Too era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Terrorist who stabbed American in Amsterdam names Wilders, cites 'insults' to Islam...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amsterdam-station-stabbing/man-who-stabbed-american-tourists-in-amsterdam-names-wilders-cites-insults-to-islam-idUSKCN1LJ1WZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who stabbed two American tourists at Amsterdam's central station last week named Dutch, anti-Islam lawmaker Geert Wilders during police questioning and said he was motivated by perceived insults to Islam in the Netherlands, prosecutors said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors INVENT new tool to remove 23inch sex toy from man...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7161755/doctors-invent-new-tool-remove-23-inch-sex-toy-stuck-24-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOCTORS were forced to improvise when it came to removing a sex toy from one unlucky patient. The unnamed man turned up at A&amp;E with a 23 inch dildo lodged inside him, having struggled to remove…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moose drowns after people crowding to take pics scare into water...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/moose-dead-drowns-crowded-vermont-wildlife-lake-a8521281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exhausted animal had swum several kilometres to cross Lake Champlain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General's text messages misfire to old number...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israeli-assigned-top-generals-number-got-texts-calls-062309135.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — An Israeli businessman on Monday said he received calls and messages from senior Israeli and foreign military officials after he was assigned the former phone number of Israel's military chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER alleged UFO sighting in NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article217635470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another alleged reported UFO sighting near Charlotte has popped on Facebook. Javion Hill, 35, of Kings Mountain posted a photo on Aug. 28, showing a square craft fringed in lights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kindergarten parents horrified by pole-dancing act...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-education-poledancing/parents-at-chinese-kindergarten-horrified-by-pole-dancing-act-idUSKCN1LJ0ZB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents attending a ceremony at a kindergarten in the southern Chinese city of Shenzhen on Monday were horrified when a scantily clad pole dancer took to the stage and proceeded with a well-oiled number in plain view of their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo mistakenly says major community figure dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/03/andrew-cuomo-mistakenly-says-major-community-figure-is-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo was met with loud gasps Monday at the breakfast preceding the West Indian Day parade when he mourned the passing of Una Clarke, a major figure in the Caribbean-American community.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Runs in PA...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5385423/joe-biden-running-pittsburgh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'So he's running after all'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Try to Shut Chicago Highway...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-kennedy-expressway-protest-chicago-20180904-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kennedy Expressway O'Hare protest noon Monday Chicago violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone ban at school: French children forced to hang up...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6126849/France-BANS-mobile-phones-school-combat-bullying-spread-pornography-pupils.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new rule was a campaign pledge of President Macron and sees all French children under 15 banned from having phones, tablets and smart watches at school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK AUTUMN CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6124919/Boris-Johnson-slams-Theresa-Brexit-compromise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister is facing a pincer movement from both wings of her party after former foreign secretary Mr Johnson accused her of flying the 'white flag' in negotiations with the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka emerges as jobs czar; Focus on heartland...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/ivanka-emerges-as-trumps-jobs-czar-focus-on-forgotten-men-and-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump never planned to become her father’s jobs czar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin blasts U.S. spy efforts...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/kremlin-says-u-spy-efforts-show-meddling-russias-111941674--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin said on Monday the United States was "crudely" trying to recruit Russian nationals to act as its agents, adding that this showed Washington was meddling in Russian affairs. Kremlin spokesman Dmitry Peskov was asked during a conference call to comment on a report in the New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone ban at school: French children forced to hang up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67d5ee7673e549639a1119e16876284f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French children who are going back to school Monday after summer vacation will have to do so without their mobile phones.        The government passed a law ba</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military hardware company swamped with orders for bulletproof schoolbags as school starts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/military-hardware-company-swamped-orders-113936306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli company that designs military-grade vests, uniforms and helmets has developed a bulletproof backpack for school students – and orders are pouring in from the US. Masada Armour created the bag, which costs upwards of £385, in response to the sheer number of shootings at American secondary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  GOOGLE Cut Secret Deal with MASTERCARD to Track Offline Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/30/google-and-mastercard-cut-a-secret-ad-deal-to-track-retail-sales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alliance gave Google an unprecedented asset for measuring retail spending, part of the search giant’s strategy to fortify its primary business against onslaughts from Amazon.com Inc. and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White South African workers protest against black share scheme...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/white-sasol-workers-stage-protest-over-black-share-093109552--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers from South Africa's mainly-white Solidarity union staged a go-slow protest at the petrochemicals firm Sasol on Monday over a share scheme offered exclusively to black staff, and said they would begin a full strike on Thursday. South African companies are required to meet quotas on black</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure rises for surveillance of Germany's far-right AfD party...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/pressure-mounts-surveillance-germanys-far-afd-party-113214687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week skinheads clashed with police soon after a Syrian and an Iraqi were identified as the main suspects, and a number of xenophobic attacks were reported, exposing bitter divisions over Chancellor Angela Merkel's liberal immigration policy. Neighboring Lower Saxony will also observe the local</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling MTV tries to tap into resistance with 'Rock the Vote' redux...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/sep/2/mtvs-1thevote-voter-drive-moves-millennials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MTV supercharged the Rock the Vote movement years before Hollywood joined the resistance to President Trump. The erstwhile music channel wants to do it again with +1thevote, a campaign to increase millennial turnout for the Nov. 6 midterm elections by leveraging social networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE STAYS SILENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/under-attack-pope-calls-silence-prayer-140408631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Monday said "silence and prayer" were the answer to those seeking "scandal and division", amid a barrage of attacks from ultra-conservative Catholics. "With people who lack goodwill, with people who seek only scandal, who seek only division, who seek only destruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Death of local news...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/793309/death-local-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The watchdogs of America's local and state governments are disappearing. Can they be saved?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding cuts blamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-45398084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire wrecked Brazil's main museum and one of the region's largest natural history collections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER: TROP STORM TAKES AIM AT GULF</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-09-03-tropical-storm-gordon-forecast-florida-gulf-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gordon has developed near southern Florida and will quickly move to near the Gulf Coast by later Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article217756285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm raining all over South Florida’s Labor Day weekend is now officially Tropical Storm Gordon, the National Hurricane Center announced Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar court sentences REUTERS reporters to 7 years in jail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd0f856e7eaa46ffb744d1909c29d9f1/Myanmar-court-sentences-Reuters-reporters-to-7-years-in-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YANGON, Myanmar (AP) — A Myanmar court sentenced two Reuters journalists to seven years in prison Monday for illegal possession of official documents, a ruling met with internatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day 2040: What Happens When Robots Do All the Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/labor-day-2040-what-happens-when-robots-do-all-the-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Holiday Weekend From Hell: Humans Still Drove Cars and Flew The Planes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian rial hits record low...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180903122646-a680o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ECONOMY/RIAL (URGENT):Iranian rial hits record low at 128,000 to the dollar- Bonbast website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes High as States Gear Up to Pick Govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stakes-are-high-as-states-gear-up-to-pick-governors-1535976001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 36 contested races for governor this election year have outsized significance because many of the new crop of state leaders will have some say over the redrawing of legislative and congressional maps in 2021.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
