<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Howie Mandel rushed to hospital after fainting at STARBUCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3850916/howie-mandel-rushed-hospital-fainting-starbucks-low-blood-sugar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOWIE Mandel was rushed to the hospital after fainting at a Starbucks in Los Angeles. The America’s Got Talent judge thinks the incident was due to low blood sugar. Sources told TMZ that Howi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS Carrier Killed By Masked Gunman While Delivering Mail...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/13/longmont-postal-worker-killed-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longmont police say a postal employee was shot and killed in a neighborhood near Heatherhill Street and Renaissance Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic Troops Can Refuse Shot, Archbishop Declares...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/policy/2021/10/catholic-troops-can-refuse-covid-vaccine-archbishop-declares/186056/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“No one should be forced to receive a COVID-19 vaccine if it would violate the sanctity of his or her conscience,” Broglio wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect arrested...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oslo-norway-bow-arrow-attack-24095a6b0e2bd26d08a145078d242529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM, Sweden (AP) — A man armed with a bow and arrows killed several people and wounded others Wednesday near the Norwegian capital of Oslo before he was arrested, authorities said. The police chief in the town of Kongsberg said there was “a confrontation” between officers and the assailant, but he did not elaborate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers bringing record number of guns to airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/13/politics/tsa-guns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline passengers are bringing guns to the airport in numbers never seen before, and it is a "huge problem," the Transportation Security Administration chief told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tallest living woman is 24-year-old from Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/13/europe/tallest-woman-turkey-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old Turkish woman who stands 215.16 centimeters (7 feet, 0.7 inches) tall has been confirmed as the world's tallest living woman by Guinness World Records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School cancels Halloween parade; 'Marginalizes students of color'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/13/seattle-school-cancels-halloween-parade-because-it-marginalizes-students-of-color/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Seattle elementary school canceled its annual Halloween parade this year, saying it “marginalizes students of color who do not celebrate the holiday.” The decision…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trans employees to walkout to protest Chappelle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/trans-netflix-employees-will-stage-walkout-to-protest-controversial-chappelle-special/ar-AAPtHyI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trans Netflix employees and allies will take 'a day of rest' Oct. 20 in protest of their company's decision to release Dave Chappelle's 'The Closer.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro decides not to get jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211013-brazil-s-bolsonaro-decides-not-to-get-vaccinated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's Bolsonaro decides not to get vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many dead... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1505606/Kongsberg-attack-Norway-bow-and-arrow-man-dead-killed-terror-latest-news-updates-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN has gone on a rampage with a bow and arrow in Norway today - leaving multiple people dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN: Hypersonic nukes capable of wiping out US cities already 'on alert'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3849670/putin-boasts-hypersonic-nukes-on-alert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin today boasted that Russian hypersonic nukes capable of wiping out entire US cities are already “on alert”. The Russian leader sparked World War III fears as he revealed h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK changes rules on attacking public figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-facebook-change-rules-attacking-public-figures-its-platforms-2021-10-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc will now count activists and journalists as "involuntary" public figures and so increase protections against harassment and bullying targeted at these groups, its global safety chief said in an interview this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Havana Syndrome feels like: 'Seized by some invisible hand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/seized-some-invisible-hand-what-it-feels-have-havana-syndrome-n1281326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor said "it's like you aged 20 years all at once," said Kate Husband, diagnosed with a brain injury "related to a directional phenomenon exposure.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN's star faces criticism over sending story to NFL exec to 'edit'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/576505-espns-schefter-faces-criticism-over-sending-story-to-nfl-exec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN's top NFL reporter Adam Schefter is facing blowback from some in the sports journalism community after it was revealed this week he sent an unpublished story to a source for review before submitting it to his editors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayor boots Thomas Jefferson from City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/13/de-blasio-booting-founding-father-jefferson-from-city-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city’s Public Design Commission has listed “the long term loan” of the 1833 bronze cast of Jefferson to the New-York Historical Society on its “consent” agenda for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heating bills set to soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prices-inflation-28e1231bdb445d482bb2d2e25dff1983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Get ready to pay sharply higher bills for heating this winter, along with seemingly everything else. With prices surging worldwide for heating oil, natural gas and other fuels, the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF survivors experience anxiety, fatigue 6 months later...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10088131/More-HALF-Covid-survivors-experience-symptoms-six-months-recovering-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Penn State find more than half of COVID-19 survivors will suffer from some sort of long term symptoms up to six months after recovery. Anxiety and fatigue were among the most common.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOCS: AMAZON copied products, rigged search results to promote own brands...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/amazon-india-rigging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of Amazon documents reveals how the company ran a campaign in India of creating knockoff goods and manipulating search results to boost its own products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jewish supremacy' conspiracy theory spread on Irish parliament floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/jewish-supremacy-conspiracy-theory-spread-on-irish-parliament-floor-681758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term “Jewish supremacy” is an accusation of Jews trying to take over the world lobbed at Israel by its opponents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-soldier storms animal shelter to get cat back...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ex-soldier-storms-animal-shelter-to-get-his-cat-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ex-soldier stormed an animal shelter in full combat gear and held an employee hostage in an effort to free his cat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheds Tears After Flight:  'Most Profound Experience'...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/william-shatner-becomes-the-oldest-person-to-travel-to-space-with-jeff-bezos-blue-origin-173606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 90-year-old 'Star Trek' star completed his trip on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK 60 YEARS AGO:  Ham  became space pioneer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bangkokpost.com/opinion/opinion/2059923/a-chimp-that-became-a-space-pioneer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bangkokpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today marks the 60th anniversary of the first chimpanzee in space. Not a lot of people know that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film TV workers union says strike to start NEXT WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/hollywood-strike-date-iatse-producers-1234855030/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with AMPTP response, more details and text to IATSE members: IATSE president Matthew Loeb says that the union will go on strike Monday unless a deal is reached in the next few days. Loeb sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Hidden camera catches intruder having sex with horse...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/animals/vero-beach-barn-bust-015728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 12--Suspecting that someone had entered a barn on her property without permission, a Florida Woman set up a trail camera that subsequently recorded a laborer having repeated sexual contact w</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS closing more stores in San Fran due to organized theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/san-francisco-walgreens-close-due-to-organized-retail-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens will close five additional stores in San Francisco citing “ongoing organized retail crime,” a spokesperson confirmed to KCBS Radio on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Social Giant Welcomes Regulations, Specifically Those That Hurt Competition...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/13/facebook-welcomes-regulations-specifically-those-that-hurt-its-competition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giants expressing openness to amending Section 230 are doing so out of naked self-interest, not the goodness of their hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film TV workers union says strike to start NEXT WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-business-hollywood-north-america-arts-and-entertainment-19f0f96c3847d7efe47dc5d9c3d375cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The union representing film and television crews says its 60,000 members will begin a nationwide strike on Monday if it does not reach a deal that satisfies demands for fair and safe working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year of country music controversies has left fans disappointed -- and wondering whether should keep listening...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/music/news/a-year-of-country-music-controversies-has-left-some-fans-disappointed-e2-80-94-and-wondering-whether-they-should-keep-listening/ar-AAPsCZT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the stereotype is that all country fans are conservative, plenty have grown disillusioned with singers in the genre, such as Jason Aldean and Morgan Wallen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLDEST IN SPACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10087899/William-Shatner-three-set-launch-62-miles-Earth-Blue-Origins-New-Shepard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Shatner, 90, is one-step close to earning the the title of oldest person in space, as he and three people prepare to launch into space aboard Blue Origin's New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanded operations at Port of Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-los-angeles-port-operations-expand-28fd72ef-0d28-4bd8-a154-6ada93a478b3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will meet with port leaders today to address the shipping logjam problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian population decline largest ever recorded...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/russia/576522-russian-population-decline-largest-ever-recorded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past year, Russia had its most significant peacetime population decline of all-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHATNER BLASTOFF!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/shatner-blue-origin-launch-09705724072c0ecad2674c8511f0fcab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VAN HORN, Texas (AP) — Hollywood's Captain Kirk, 90-year-old William Shatner, climbed aboard a rocket ship along with three fellow passengers for a real-life ride into space Wednesday, courtesy of “Star Trek” fan Jeff Bezos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Dogs Now Have Rifles Mounted On Backs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42717/robot-dogs-can-now-have-6-5mm-assault-rifles-mounted-on-their-backs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot dogs have been met with equal parts fascination and fear by the public, but their utility for military applications is becoming undeniable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half of Bay Area residents plan to leave permanently...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/576496-more-than-half-of-bay-area-residents-plan-to-leave-permanently-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of the residents living in the San Francisco Bay Area say they are considering moving out of the area permanently, according to a poll from Joint Venture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uEhdlIor-do</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Shepard’s 18th mission, NS-18, will lift off on Wednesday, October 13, carrying four astronauts, Dr. Chris Boshuizen, Glen de Vries, Audrey Powers, and W...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious financial problems afflict 40% households...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/oct/12/us-households-financial-problems-medical-care-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Households struggle to afford medical care and food, with figure rising to 59% for those with income under $50,000 a year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The VR porn revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10084523/Tracey-Cox-says-virtual-reality-porn-norm-2026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most new things with technology, VR seems sci-fi right now, but it will quickly become the norm for many people in the next few years, according to Tracey Cox, who says it's the next big sex trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WV program to pay people $12k to move to coal country gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/courage-strength-optimism/full-steam-ahead-west-virginias-program-to-pay-people-12k-to-move-to-coal-country-gains-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGANTOWN, West Virginia — Quintina Mengyan needed some air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's top 'tech cop' ready to take on Big Tech with America...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/13/global-insider-margrethe-vestager-big-tech-515851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margrethe Vestager says the Biden administration is a “dream come true.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrencies could lead to financial instability, author warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/13/cryptocurrencies-could-lead-to-financial-instability-author-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency enthusiasts say the digital money will democratize finance. One economist has some more unsettling predictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early-season snowstorm snarls travel throughout Rocky Mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/rocky-mountains-october-snowstorm/1032344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorful leaves were still clinging onto trees across the Rockies when the region was buried by an early-season snowstorm — one that required a yardstick to measure snowfall totals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security COLA largest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/social-security-cola-increase-4f2cd7b763371b91923227be883e367e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Millions of retirees on Social Security will get a 5.9% boost in benefits for 2022. The biggest cost-of-living adjustment in 39 years follows a burst in inflation as the economy struggles to shake off the drag of the coronavirus pandemic .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish man sentenced to death by antisemitic judge. Now, he could get second chance...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-Jewish-man-was-sentenced-to-death-by-an-16529258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For much of his life, Randy Halprin struggled with his Jewish identity. Throughout...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 GALLON IN NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-prices-hit-5-in-manhattan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eye-popping gas prices have returned to New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Secret Blacklist of 'Dangerous' Groups, People...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/10/12/facebook-secret-blacklist-dangerous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the public deserves to see the list, a clear embodiment of U.S. foreign policy priorities that could disproportionately censor marginalized groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'chaos' as Italy adopts tough Covid pass regime...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fears-chaos-italy-adopts-tough-112444339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy from Friday will require all workers to show a coronavirus health pass, one of the world's toughest anti-Covid regimes that has already sparked riots and which many fear will cause "chaos".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators seek answers from TESLA over lack of recall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-software-881ef270cbfdc6e4f62b88400588686f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — U.S. safety investigators want to know why Tesla didn't file recall documents when it updated Autopilot software to better identify parked emergency vehicles, escalating a simmering clash between the automaker and regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to reopen land borders in November for fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-covid-19-pandemic-travel-4826edefa498139ebd37684e4f64d553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. will reopen its land borders to nonessential travel next month, ending a 19-month freeze due to the COVID-19 pandemic as the country moves to require all international visitors to be vaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest white rhino dies in Italian zoo aged 54...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211013-world-s-oldest-white-rhino-dies-in-italian-zoo-aged-54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World's oldest white rhino dies in Italian zoo aged 54</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to test thousands of Wuhan blood samples in Covid probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/12/asia/china-wuhan-blood-samples-covid-19-probe-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is preparing to test tens of thousands of blood bank samples from the city of Wuhan as part of a probe into the origins of Covid-19, according to a Chinese official. The move comes amid increasing calls for transparency over the emergence of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS closing more stores in San Fran due to organized theft...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/576482-walgreens-closing-more-stores-in-san-francisco-due-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens is closing more stores in San Francisco due to organized retail theft in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burry Posts TWITTER Rant Over Taxing Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/michael-burry-of-e2-80-98big-short-e2-80-99-fame-posts-twitter-rant-over-taxing-the-rich/ar-AAPsyP6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Burry, whose huge, profitable bets against the housing bubble were made famous in “The Big Short,” denounced what he called U.S. class warfare and challenged the notion that the rich don’t pay enough taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen arrested after refusing to wear mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wyoming-teenager-arrested-after-refusing-to-wear-mask-on-school-grounds-family-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;16-year-old Grace Smith says she was arrested at her Wyoming high school after she refused to wear a mask on school grounds. The teen says she's faced three separate two-day suspensions for not abiding by the school's mask mandate, and received $1,000 in trespassing fines for refusing to leave the campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Sees European Crisis as Russia's Golden Chance...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/putin-sees-european-gas-crisis-as-russia-s-golden-opportunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin Sees European Gas Crisis as Russia’s Golden Opportunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Warns of Tougher Response If Beijing Flights Get Too Close...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/taiwan-warns-of-tougher-response-if-china-flights-get-too-close-kup9kjp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan Warns of Tougher Response If China Flights Get Too Close</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used ASTON MARTIN $114,500 Price Tag Attests to Chip Squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/used-aston-martin-114-500-095901111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Like NowNYC's Waldorf Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's OverreachThey Invented the Must-Have Instrument for the Burning Man Set. Now They Want to Kill It OffWhat Comes After GE’s 129 Years of Greenhouse GasUsed-car sellers are enjoying a boom in demand in the U.K. as the pandemic puts a squeeze on the supply of chips f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Meteor Explode Over New Hampshire?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/did-a-meteor-explode-over-new-hampshire-that-may-explain-the-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists said that a bolide, a type of large meteor explosion in the atmosphere, might have been the source of a disturbance that was widely reported on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell gets wake-up call...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/576461-mcconnell-gets-gop-wake-up-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The backlash Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (Ky.) received from fellow Republican senators last week is a wake-up call to the GOP leader that he doesn’t have any more political capital to spend on helping Democrats raise the debt limit aga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100K threaten strikes as unions flex muscles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/576456-more-than-100k-workers-threaten-strikes-as-unions-flex-muscles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers in various industries nationwide are threatening to go on strike in a sweeping effort to secure higher pay and better working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steaks Could Become Luxury...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steaks-could-soon-become-champagne-150022224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The boss of Europe’s top meat processor said beef will become a luxury like champagne because of the climate impact of producing it. Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Like NowNYC's Waldorf Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's OverreachTycoon Behind a Crisis-Era Property Crash Now Sits on a $9 Billion Debt MountainThey Invented the Must-Have Instrument for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Pristine Beach Is One of Japan's Last. Soon It Will Be Filled With Concrete...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/13/this-pristine-beach-is-one-of-japans-last-soon-it-will-be-filled-with-concrete/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KATOKU, Japan — Standing on its mountain-fringed beach, there is no hint that the Japanese village of Katoku even exists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stock Market Malaise With Shadow of '70s-Style Stagflation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/13/a-stock-market-malaise-with-the-shadow-of-70s-style-stagflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine mandates seem to be working, younger children may be approved for shots by Halloween, and the coronavirus appears to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trans activists, comedians grapple with Chapelle special...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/comedians-defending-dave-chapelle-netflix-special-trans-lgbtq-214359105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian was no holds barred in his latest Netflix special, and some comics say that's a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Burn Infected Couple's Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxewa/vietname-dogs-killing-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What started as a heartwarming story of human kindness has within days evolved into a national reckoning on animal abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With flight, more than 20 civilians will have reached space this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-william-shatner-e2-80-99s-flight-more-than-20-civilian-astronauts-will-have-reached-space-this-year/ar-AAPsESJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor will join a private space movement that has picked up speed and outpaced NASA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area woman charged with hosting teen sex parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/los-gatos-woman-charged-with-hosting-alcohol-sex-parties-for-teens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Bay woman has been charged for hosting secret teen parties with alcohol and sex, according to charges filed by the Santa Clara County District Attorney’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART, FEDEX, UPS move to 24/7 model to address bottlenecks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/576463-white-house-says-walmart-fedex-ups-will-move-to-24-7-model-to-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major goods carriers Walmart, FedEx, and UPS will move to working 24 hours a day, seven days a week in order to address the global supply chain bottlenecks, the White House announced on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SQUID GAME' becomes NETFLIX biggest-ever launch hit...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/squid-game-becomes-netflixs-biggest-235059497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dystopian South Korean drama "Squid Game" has become Netflix's most popular series launch ever, drawing 111 million fans since its debut less than four weeks ago, the streaming service said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatner set for blast off...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-william-shatner-science-business-lifestyle-09705724072c0ecad2674c8511f0fcab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VAN HORN, Texas (AP) — Actor William Shatner counted down Wednesday to his wildest role yet: riding a rocket into space, courtesy of “Star Trek” fan Jeff Bezos. Best known for his role as Captain Kirk, the 90-year-old Shatner joined three other passengers for the planned launch from West Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request for Tucker Carlson's Performance Review Is 'Intrusive,' Judge Says...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/2020-election/judge-steers-away-from-dominions-intrusive-requests-for-fox-news-hosts-performance-reviews-in-1-6b-defamation-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delaware judge overseeing a $1.6 billion lawsuit against Fox News has steered away from an attempt by Dominion Voting Systems, Inc. to obtain the internal personnel records of high-profile hosts Tucker Carlson, Sean Hannity, Maria Bartiromo, Jeanine Pirro, and former host Lou Dobbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's Balancing Act in China Gets Trickier During Xi's Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-balancing-act-china-gets-160000957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In less than a year, China has upended the world’s largest internet sphere, throwing its biggest players from Alibaba to Tencent into a tailspin with a storm of regulatory measures to loosen their stranglehold over data and content. Yet Apple Inc., the largest of them all and an American icon, has sailed through mostly unscathed.Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Li</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second whistleblower reports 'potential criminal violations' to Feds...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/10/11/tech/facebook-whistleblower-sophie-zhang-congress/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sophie Zhang, who said she felt like she had "blood on her hands" after working at Facebook, is willing to testify before Congress about her former employer, she told CNN Sunday. She said she had also passed on documentation about the company to a US law enforcement agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DEADLINE NEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/biden-s-vaccinate-or-test-mandate-approaches-questions-arise-over-n1281130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Occupational Safety and Health Administration was already a strained agency before the president announced the new requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Nations Have Deadlier Covid Outbreaks With Same Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/why-some-nations-have-deadlier-outbreaks-with-the-same-vaccines/ar-AAPr6Ho</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRLINES REBUFF TEX GOV</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012200659-vbp9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AIRLINES-VACCINE (PIX):Rebuffing Texas governor, American Airlines, Southwest stand by vaccine mandate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to test vax nasal spray...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012185352-0bl3g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-VACCINE (PIX):Russia to test COVID-19 vaccine in form of nasal spray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies scraping for staff ahead of holidays...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-christmas-shopping-holidays-e7e45190fdf6c9fb138aee565e4c9b58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — All employers want for Christmas is some holiday help. But they might not get their wish. Companies that typically hire thousands of seasonal workers are heading into the holidays during one of the tightest job markets in decades, making it unlikely they’ll find all the workers they need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL BATTLE OVER VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-nba-sports-business-aa6c30fa6270b735acafc69e2ce26766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — With the governor of Texas leading the charge, conservative Republicans in several states are moving to block or undercut President Joe Biden’s COVID-19 vaccine mandates for private employers before the regulations are even issued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPERMAN' actor slams gay reveal: 'It isn't bold or brave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/dean-cain-superman-bisexual-1235030248/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Superman actor criticized the DC Comics storyline about Clark Kent's son, who is now Superman of Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% want to make career change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/why-50percent-of-workers-want-to-make-a-career-change-new-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whopping 76% of workers say they want their company to make work permanently flexible in terms of schedule and/or location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Ranch threatened by wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/ronald-reagan-ranch-alisal-fire-santa-barbara-county-1234854834/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are working to protect the ranch once owned by Ronald Reagan amid the rapidly moving Alisal Fire in Santa Barbara County. The 688-ranch, Rancho del Cielo, served as the vacation home for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART Cartel Reporter Dies in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2021/10/11/breitbart-cartel-reporter-dies-in-mexico-authorities-believe-he-drowned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breitbart News Cartel Reporter Gerry Aranda's body was discovered in the Pacific Ocean in Chiapas, Mexico, on October 4, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCS Boot from Ring of Honor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/RapSheet/status/1448043568979927042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwayne Johnson Lets Down His Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/10/dwayne-johnson-speaks-his-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A no-holds-barred talk with the megastar and entrepreneur about his volatile childhood, his heartbreaking relationship with his dad, and Vin Diesel’s “bullshit.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Kristof forms committee for Oregon gov run...</title>
      <link>https://www.opb.org/article/2021/10/12/new-york-times-columnist-nick-kristof-oregon-governor-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday, Kristof officially formed a political action committee, a move that will allow him to raise money and hire staff ahead of a likely official announcement of his candidacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Tyga arrested on domestic violence charge...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/10/12/tyga-arrested-on-felony-domestic-violence-charge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper turned himself in Tuesday after refusing to speak with police Monday at his home following Swanson’s allegations and is being held on $50,000 bail.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
