<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Reality shows sending people to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/05/tech/who-wants-to-be-an-astronaut-space-hero-reality-television-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hottest new reality show isn't set in a house, on an obstacle course, or on the Jersey Shore. Television producers are betting on a new location: the International Space Station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarmed Louisiana Residents Turn to Jabs in 'Darkest Days' of Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/05/alarmed-louisiana-residents-turn-to-vaccines-in-darkest-days-of-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMMOND, La. — Officials in Louisiana have been willing to try just about anything to jolt the state’s lagging Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sturgis bike rally revs back bigger, despite virus variant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-sd-state-wire-71bb16eee8ff6f9a4540405a3c69aba3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — Crowds of bikers are rumbling their way towards South Dakota's Black Hills this week, raising fears that COVID-19 infections will be unleashed among the 700,000 people expected to show up at the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON  MAYOR COMPARES MANDATE TO SLAVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/boston-mayor-janey-compares-vaccine-passports-to-slave-papers-birtherism/37213542#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There's a long history in this country of people needing to show their papers," said Janey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 CASES IN DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-covid-19-cases-hit-six-month-high-over-100000-reuters-tally-2021-08-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States hit a six-month high for new COVID cases with over 100,000 infections reported on Wednesday, according to a Reuters tally, as the Delta variant ravages areas where people did not get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA asks airports to monitor passenger alcohol intake, citing unruly behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/faa-asks-airports-monitor-passengers-alcohol-intake-citing-unruly-behavior-n1276015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Some airport concessionaires have offered alcohol 'to go,' and passengers believe they can carry that alcohol onto their flights," the agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy renouncing American citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wealthy-people-are-renouncing-american-citizenship-67fbada4-e2e4-4699-b106-c986839f209d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasons renouncing citizenship tend to be financial, not political.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Kamala Harris crisis dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/kamala-harris-press-coverage-crisis-dinner-7139cfc7-754b-42aa-a411-95716273dbb0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris has faced a torrent of bad press early in the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carl Lewis slams track team as 'embarrassment'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/05/carl-lewis-slams-us-track-team-as-embarrassment-after-relay-fail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An event that the United States previously dominated is now looking like “a total embarrassment” for Team USA – at least, that’s what one of its greatest legends thinks. Carl Lewis — who won nine g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Crash kills 10 in van carrying migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/ten-killed-12-injured-texas-crash-involving-migrant-worker-van-local-media-2021-08-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A van overloaded with 30 people, many of them believed to be illegal immigrants, crashed in southern Texas on Wednesday, killing 10 occupants and critically injuring many of the others, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE mogul Larry Page allowed into New Zealand despite closed border...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/google-co-founder-larry-page-allowed-into-new-zealand-despite-closed-border-2503055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google co-founder Larry Page was allowed into New Zealand despite its closed border so his son could receive urgent medical attention, the government confirmed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driverless Semi Reaches Milestone in Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/driverless-semi-reaches-milestone-in-test-startup-plus-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Driverless Semi Reaches Milestone in Test, Startup Plus Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How G7 task force helps governments target critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-finance-fatf-consequences-specialrepo/special-report-how-a-little-known-g7-task-force-unwittingly-helps-governments-target-critics-idUSKBN2F616V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late 2020, when Ugandan President Yoweri Museveni faced a fresh challenge to his 35-year rule, a new tool helped to silence his critics: anti-money laundering legislation promoted by the G7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American stars fail to earn stripes in more athletics woe...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210805-usa-stars-fail-to-earn-stripes-in-more-athletics-woe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA stars fail to earn stripes in more athletics woe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police allege HILLSONG CHURCH founder concealed child sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-3418b25401fa5dac98efcfc74c7e6acd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — The founder of the Sydney-based global Hillsong Church, Brian Houston, has been charged with concealing child sex offenses, police said Thursday. Detectives served Houston’s lawyers on Thursday with a notice for him to appear in a Sydney court on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comFire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comFire engulfs Northern California town, leveling businesses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne plunges back into lockdown week after leaving it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/melbourne-plunges-back-into-coronavirus-lockdown-a-week-after-leaving-it/ar-AAMXGLs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mystery cases, suspected to be the delta variant, come as Sydney endures a lengthy shutdown amid a slow vaccine rollout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo logs record 5,042 cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-lifestyle-sports-coronavirus-pandemic-business-0b250f40128b0892863bc55067a4ba39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Tokyo reported 5,042 new daily coronavirus cases on Thursday, hitting a record since the pandemic began as the infections surge in the Japanese capital hosting the Olympics. The additional cases brought the total for Tokyo to 236,138, about a quarter of the national total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC launches its own health passport...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/new-york-city-launches-vaccine-passport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYC Covid Safe app is the new coronavirus vaccination app the city is rolling out for people to use to show they are vaccinated for indoor dining, gyms, and other places that will be forced to check.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic secret to age women start menopause discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/aug/04/genetic-secret-to-age-women-start-menopause-discovered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research could lead to doctors being able to tell women how long they have got left to start a family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes with White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/desantis-white-house-trade-barbs-as-florida-covid-cases-climb/ar-AAMWYGA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Governor Ron DeSantis had a heated exchange with the White House on Wednesday amid a surge of coronavirus hospitalizations and deaths in his state that’s prompted a political clash over mask mandates and vaccine requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to announce vax requirement for active-duty forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/sec-of-defense-austin-to-announce-mandatory-vaccine-policy-for-all-active-duty-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin is expected to announce a mandatory vaccine policy for all active-duty forces in the U.S. military Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some school districts push ahead with mask mandates, defying threat to cut funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Some-Florida-school-districts-push-ahead-with-16364677.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of Florida's largest school districts have announced they will either keep or issue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left wing complicates Pelosi's calculus...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Left-wing-complicates-Pelosi-s-calculus-16364819.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In July 2019, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., had a particularly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  WORSE THAN DELTA COMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fauci-delta-variant-covid-d1c0d550-6624-417d-bde6-33c8f56deaba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People who are not getting vaccinated mistakenly think it’s only about them. But it isn’t."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE FOREIGNERS TO JAB</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-a312ebaf72844c5b75246fb10b0f2ba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is taking the first steps toward requiring nearly all foreign visitors to the U.S. to be vaccinated for the coronavirus, a White House official said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark side of TIKTOK exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3410817/tiktok-star-deaths-timbo-the-redneck-anthony-barajas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIKTOK stars have become the latest set of celebrities but the dark side of the app has seen its rising talent die from suicide, addiction, shootings, and stunts for their account.  Timbo the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Zucker to stay at WARNERMEDIA at least until DISCOVERY deal closes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/04/cnn-president-jeff-zucker-will-stay-at-warnermedia-at-least-until-discovery-deal-closes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Zucker will stay at WarnerMedia at least until the AT&amp;T media unit merges with Discovery, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER linked to rare eye inflammation...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/pfizer-covid-19-vaccine-linked-to-rare-cases-of-eye-inflammation-study-675839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-one people developed anterior uveitis and two developed Multiple Evanescent White Dot Syndrome (MEWDS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Assembly Dems support impeaching...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/majority-of-assembly-democrats-support-impeaching-gov-cuomo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Democrats in the New York State legislature’s lower chamber support impeaching Gov. Andrew Cuomo after a state Attorney General probe that found the governor is a serial sexual harass…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA considers requiring proof at restaurants, gyms, indoor sporting events...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-consider-requiring-vaccine-proof-195454496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. City Council to consider requiring that people show their vaccination status to visit indoor places such as restaurants, stores and gyms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayhem for airline travel as summer turns into 'hot mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/mayhem-airline-passengers-crew-hot-vax-summer-turns-hot-mess-n1275947</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines took aggressive moves to cut overhead costs when the pandemic hit — but experts say they overshot the mark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Alone, Silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-alone-silent-after-ag-report-as-new-york-awaits-next-move/ar-AAMWgaj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo worked in the Executive Mansion in Albany on Wednesday, avoiding news cameras that he used to seek out as Democrats continued to call for his resignation over sexual-misconduct allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE FOREIGNERS TO JAB</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210804202933-qabl9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (EXCLUSIVE, URGENT):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. developing plan to require foreign visitors to be vaccinated -official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Giraffes highly complex social species, misunderstood...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/08/03/Britain-study-giraffes-socially-complex-species/6091628002986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giraffes are as socially complex as elephants, but their communication has been misunderstood, a new study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba Dumping Corpses in Backyards, Losing Bodies in Mass Graves...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2021/08/04/coronavirus-cuba-dumping-corpses-peoples-backyards-losing-bodies-mass-graves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent outlets published videos this week showing Cuban cemetery workers dumping suspected Chinese coronavirus victims in mass graves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Sues U.S. Gun Makers over Cartel Crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2021/08/04/mexican-government-sues-us-gun-makers-over-cartel-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government of Mexico is suing six U.S. makers, claiming "massive damage" created by "unlawful trafficking" of firearms to cartels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Fires Dozens of Employees for Data Misuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gk73/google-fired-dozens-for-data-misuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some allegations potentially center around accessing Google user or employee data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes sues MSNBC after 'spiteful' Maddow allegedly smeared him on air...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/rep-nunes-sues-msnbc-after-rachel-maddow-allegedly-smeared-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devin Nunes, 47, who has had three lawsuits against other outlets thrown out in the last year, filed the defamation lawsuit in Texas on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. comes out of hiding, announces tour dates...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/04/louis-c-k-announces-new-tour-dates-in-bizarre-email/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He will embark on a 24-city nationwide comedy tour, starting with gigs in New York City next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFSPRING drummer dropped from band for refusing vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/offspring-drummer-pete-parada-says-band-cut-him-loose-over-covid-19-vaccine-decision/ar-AAMWsN8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Offspring drummer Pete Parada explains why he decided against a vaccine. 'The hesitant population is not a monolithic group,' he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State spending billions to house homeless in hotels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-california-coronavirus-pandemic-835c2091c63c199d397346a497e7ae49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — When homeless outreach workers first visited her encampment under a Los Angeles highway overpass last fall, Veronica Perez was skeptical of their offer of not just a bed, but a furnished apartment complete with meals, counseling and the promise of some stability in her life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterinarian Pleads Guilty to Making Animal Torture Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78kdv/florida-veterinarian-guilty-plea-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsealed court documents about a Florida vet accused of possession of child porn reveal disturbing details of torture and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases among children, teens jump 84%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/us/covid-19-children-teens/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 72,000 children and teens caught Covid-19 last week -- a "substantial" increase from a week earlier, the American Academy of Pediatrics reported Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned chickens reveal trend is fizzling...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/abandoned-chickens-roosters-city-zoning-pandemic-16361232.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some, raising backyard chickens seemed like a good idea — at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Nurse Breaks Down: 'Worse Now Than Ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/louisiana-icu-nurse-breaks-down-over-skyrocketing-covid-19-cases-68845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Felicia Croft said that two of the patients in her hospital's ICU are the parents of her daughter's friend. "As a nurse, to know that if you can't get these two people home, that their kids will be orphaned," Croft said in a now-viral video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Auto Show Cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/04/new-york-auto-show-cancelled-due-to-covid-19-delta-variant-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers cited "growing incidences of the COVID-19 Delta variant and the increased measures announced recently by state and local officials to stop its spread."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dre's daughter reveals she's homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9857957/Dr-Dres-eldest-daughter-reveals-shes-homeless-living-car.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LaTanya Young, 38, works as a delivery driver for DoorDash and Uber Eats and as an assembler at a warehouse but claims that she can't afford to secure an apartment in California, DailyMail.com can reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Hospitals' Request For Emergency Staff Denied As Hospitalizations Quadruple...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/texas-hospitals-request-emergency-staff-denied-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals in North Texas say they need hundreds of additional staff to deal with a surge of COVID-19 cases, but the state has denied their requests for emergency personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Bill to Require Alcohol Monitors for All New Cars...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/infrastructure-bill-would-require-alcohol-monitors-for-all-new-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bipartisan infrastructure bill includes a provision that would require auto manufacturers to equip "advanced alcohol monitoring systems" in all new cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China seals city as its worst virus outbreak in year grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-china-coronavirus-pandemic-46fd21e9be94b2b3f4ebeb59ec4fa77c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's worst coronavirus outbreak since the start of the pandemic a year and a half ago escalated Wednesday with dozens more cases around the country, the sealing-off of one city and the punishment of its local leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSECUTORS PROBE CUOMO</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/manhattan-and-westchester-prosecutors-seek-materials-about-cuomo-s-conduct-for-possible-criminal-probes/ar-AAMWfel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The request from the district attorneys came a day after the top prosecutor in Albany confirmed his office is conducting a criminal investigation of alleged sexual harassment by the New York governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While they were asleep, their TESLAa burned in garage. It's risk many automakers taking seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/while-they-were-asleep-their-teslas-burned-in-the-garage-it-e2-80-99s-a-risk-many-automakers-are-taking-seriously/ar-AAMVBlV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire inspector cited the thermal management system in one of the Tesla Model S sedans as one of two possible causes in the blaze, which showed what can happen when one electric car ignited another in the garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In drought-plagued northern Mexico, tens of thousands of cows starving to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/latino-life/story/2021-08-02/in-drought-plagued-northern-mexico-cows-are-starving-to-by-the-tens-of-thousands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonora is the cattle capital of Mexico. But prolonged drought is killing off the herds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Torrez entered to Beethoven, bloodied foe's face and can win gold for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/richard-torrez-entered-to-beethoven-bloodied-a-foe-e2-80-99s-face-and-can-win-gold-for-the-us/ar-AAMVwNf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No U.S. man has won boxing gold since 2004. The Super-heavyweight has a chance Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORBES: Rihanna Billionaire...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/maddieberg/2021/08/04/fentys-fortune-rihanna-is-now-officially-a-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the singer became the richest female musician on the planet. Hint: it wasn't performing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cuomo brothers: New spotlight on unique relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/media/andrew-cuomo-chris-cuomo-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albany, Westchester criminal probes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/04/cuomo-allegations-westchester-county-da-seeks-evidence-for-potential-criminal-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DA Mimi Rocah asked NY AG Letitia James to send her materials related to one of the 11 women who in a bombshell report accused Cuomo of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic of hypocrisy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/566257-americas-pandemic-of-covid-hypocrisy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If COVID-19 continues in some variation, the same politicians who fanned its spread will be the first to condemn the Biden administration for not ending it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY vs. Scarlett Johansson: Ton of Lawsuits May Be Next...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/disney-vs-scarlett-johansson-lawsuits-next-1234992368/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Bob Chapek-led regime goes to war with a Marvel star, Hollywood stars and creatives fear the end of massive backend deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Americans believe worst still ahead...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/566256-majority-in-new-polling-believes-worst-in-pandemic-is-still</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Americans say in new polling that the worst of the coronavirus pandemic is still ahead of us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitmen Dressed Up in PPE to Murder Politician...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbv4m/hitmen-dressed-up-in-covid-ppe-to-murder-this-politician</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killers in Honduras often disguise themselves as police or military officers. But this team had a pandemic ruse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: American Obsession With Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/08/the-american-obsession-with-decline/619656/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether economic times are good or bad, the lament for the old days of factories and mills never changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Benefits of Talking to Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/08/why-we-should-talk-strangers-more/619642/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So often we’re raised to see strangers as dangerous and scary. What would happen if we instead saw them as potential sources of comfort and belonging?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Seen to Push Herd Immunity Threshold Above 80%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/delta-seen-to-push-herd-immunity-threshold-above-80/ar-AAMT9bD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spread of the delta coronavirus variant has pushed the threshold for herd immunity to well over 80% and potentially approaching 90%, according to an Infectious Diseases Society of America briefing on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas Gov Admits Mistake on Mask Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/arkansas-republican-governor-admits-mistake-on-mask-mandates-as-cases-soar-i-wish-that-had-not-become-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Covid-19 cases surging in his state, Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR) wishes he could take back the ban on local mask mandates that he signed into law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Facing Dead Heat In Recall Election..</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/update-new-poll-shows-newsom-facing-near-dead-heat-in-recall-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Governor Gavin Newsom could be facing a dead heat in the recall election next month, according to a newly released poll.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
