<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Art or activism? Oscars identity crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/23/art-v-activism-can-the-oscars-survive-its-identity-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s awards will be a battle between political propriety and cinematic excellence. But will medium or message finally triumph?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals filling up again with Covid patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/fl-ne-south-florida-covid-hospitalizations-continue-20210424-jxuqa5zerfc2lfaturmabsbke4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a few weeks in March, South Florida hospital workers took a breath and thought the state was on the right track with coronavirus cases. But in April, the situation shifted again and COVID hospitalizations are increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Family may spend life in prison after 'church' sold bleach as cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/bradenton-family-may-spend-life-in-prison-after-church-sold-bleach-as-covid-19-cure/ar-BB1fZob4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apr. 23—A federal grand jury brought charges against members of a Bradenton family nearly a year after they were arrested for selling bleach that they claimed to be a cure for the COVID-19 virus. Mark Grenon and his three sons — Jonathan, Jordan and Joseph — face several charges for peddling their "Miracle Mineral Solution" to customers even after the Food and Drug Administration refuted those ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police depts struggling with shortage of recruits, surge in retirements...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia-police-recruitment-pennsylvania-nj-jobs-20210423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People don’t want to be police anymore," one local police chief said. "It’s a good job, and good-paying job, but when you look at national news every day, people just don’t want to be officers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions Skipping 2nd Shot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/25/millions-are-skipping-their-second-doses-of-covid-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Americans are not getting the second doses of their Covid-19 vaccines, and their ranks are growing. More than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas creeps higher...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-4dd3acc2293884756aabb11f74f05912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Gas prices have been creeping higher in New Jersey and around the nation, analysts say. AAA Mid-Atlantic says the average price of a gallon of regular gas in New Jersey on Friday was $2.90, up four cents from a week ago. Drivers were paying an average of $2.03 a gallon a year ago at this time. The national average price for a gallon of regular gasoline was $2.88, up two cents from last week. Drivers were paying an average of $1.79 a gallon a year ago at this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump accountant at center of N.Y. probes could bring down empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/us-elections-government/ny-trump-accountant-allen-weisselberg-becomes-key-figure-in-criminal-probe-20210425-4tce7nirrbepje4b3fw6cosk4m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In previously unreported deposition documents obtained by the Daily News, Weisselberg, who has micromanaged the organization’s finances for decades, shrugged off interest in or knowledge of the legalities around Trump's till.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor used bailout to buy TESLA, property...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/dc-pastor-used-ppp-loan-to-buy-tesla-baltimore-property-us-attorney-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A D. C. pastor used loans meant for COVID pandemic relief to buy a Tesla and a property in Baltimore, according to U. S. Attorney's Office for the District of Maryland. Rudolph Brooks Jr. , of Cheltenham, Maryland, known as the pastor at Kingdom Tabernacle of Restoration Ministries, faces a federal charge for wire fraud. Federal authorities have also seized $2. 2 million from his various bank accounts, along with a 2018 Tesla Model 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Pay Remains Stratospheric, Even at Battered Companies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/c-e-o-pay-remains-stratospheric-even-at-companies-battered-by-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing had a historically bad 2020. Its 737 Max was grounded for most of the year after two deadly crashes,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland mayor urges residents to 'unmask' rioters after weeks of violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/portland-mayor-urges-residents-to-unmask-rioters-after-weeks-of-violence/ar-BB1g17Js</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Ted Wheeler asks residents to stand together and “take the city back.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Price Shock Coming to Store Near You...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-grocery-price-shock-is-coming-to-a-store-near-you/ar-BB1fZDaC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key measure of farming commodities has surged in recent days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Blocking Criticism of Government...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/pranavdixit/twitter-blocking-tweets-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 50 tweets are now blocked in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI6 chief believes Moscow's power is waning...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/russia-military-power-ukraine-britain-mi6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MI6 chief believes Moscow’s power is waning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political revival of Ralph Northam: How ostracized gov became liberal champion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/25/politics/ralph-northam-virginia-governor/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam looks back at his tenure, the inflection point between being a run-of-the-mill executive and the progressive leader he has become is a painful one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman charged with felony for unreturned VHS tape...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/04/24/woman-charged-felony-unreturned-vhs-tape-22-years-ago/7366876002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman found out 21 years later that she was charged with felony embezzlement for not returning a VHS tape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany faces lockdown until June as curbs fail to push down cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/germany-faces-lockdown-until-june-curbs-fail-push-down-cases-2021-04-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's coronavirus infection rate rose at the weekend despite stricter restrictions and Finance Minister Olaf Scholz said he did not expect moves to ease curbs before the end of May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor who raped staffer runs town from prison cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-mayor-who-raped-a-junior-staff-member-in-his-office-continues-to-run-the-town-from-his-prison-cell/ar-BB1g1QPi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georges Tron, the mayor of Draveil, outside Paris, was convicted of the rape and sexual assault of a junior staff member in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More parents speak out in growing backlash against 'woke' NYC schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9508667/More-parents-speak-growing-backlash-against-woke-NYC-private-schools.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a series of controversies at some of Manhattan's most expensive public schools, more parents shared their concerns in interviews with the New York Post on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese man arrested after dating 35 women -- to 'get birthday presents'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news/japan-man-arrested-dating-35-152935505.html#click=https://t.co/eu9lQjzFug</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Japanese man has been arrested after reportedly dating more than 35 women at the same time. Takashi Miyagawa, a part-time worker, is being investigated for allegedly defrauding dozens of women by pretending he was serious about each of their relationships and receiving hundreds of pounds worth of gifts from them. He was apparently caught out when the women joined forces to create a victims’ association after discovering his extensive infidelity and reported him to the police, according to local media. Among the claims is that he gave each woman a different date for his birthday, ensuring a constant stream of gifts throughout the year. One 47-year-old woman reportedly thought his birthday was on February 22, another aged 40 was told it was July, while another 35-year-old believed his birthday was in April. In total, he allegedly received around 100,000 yen (£668) worth of gifts from the women, including a £200 suit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Suggests Explosion Was 'Drone Strike' Targeting Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/roger-stone-suggests-gas-explosion-florida-warehouse-was-drone-strike-targeting-him-1586192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In reality, firefighters have explained that highly-flammable Styrofoam in the warehouse caught fire, spreading rapidly and causing propane tanks to explode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Hunt for Ways Around Tax Hikes They Were Warned About...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/rich-americans-who-were-warned-on-taxes-hunt-for-ways-around-them/ar-BB1g0hGQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Joe Biden and state lawmakers target millionaires and billionaires, wealth advisers are trying to help their clients adapt to the new rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. air strikes in Afghanistan may continue -- after drawdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/04/23/us-air-strikes-surveillance-in-afghanistan-may-continue-from-afar-after-drawdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Gen. Frank McKenzie, the head of U.S. Central Command, is drawing up options for keeping counterterrorism forces on call in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New photos show Epstein, Maxwell were VIP guests in Clinton White House...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/25/epstein-and-maxwell-were-vip-guests-in-clintons-white-house-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disgusting duo were invited to the White House in 1993, after Epstein reportedly donated money to have the Oval Office refurbished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Highway 1 along Big Sur reopens after collapse...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/california-highway-1-along-big-sur-reopens-after-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A section of California’s scenic Highway 1 that collapsed during a winter storm reopened to traffic on Friday. Gov. Gavin Newsom and work crews stood on the freshly paved and marked roadway t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Night's Back: UFC thrills sellout Florida crowd...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/sports/2021/04/25/i-dont-think-it-gets-any-better-ufc-thrills-sellout-jacksonville-crowd-plans-to-return/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A packed crowd. Chants of Duval. Even more chants of USA. Stars and celebrities everywhere. A night that Jacksonville waited for was worth every bit of the wait. And it’s just getting started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaniard charged with infecting 22; Coughed on co-workers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-europe-coronavirus-9f9b58ace372e895f2c6d29157a44bdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — A Spanish man with COVID-19 symptoms who coughed on work colleagues and told them “I’m going to give you all the coronavirus” has been charged with intentionally causing injury after allegedly infecting 22 people. Spanish police said their investigation began after a COVID-19 outbreak at the company where the 40-year-old man worked on the Mediterranean island of Mallorca. Days before the outbreak, the man showed COVID-19 symptoms but refused his colleagues’ suggestions to go home and self-isolate, police said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Warns of Mutants as Tougher Curbs Take Effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/merkel-warns-of-virus-mutants-as-tougher-curbs-take-effect/ar-BB1g01Mw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s new lockdown law, which automatically imposes tougher curbs in places where new infections exceed a certain threshold, came into effect on Saturday after both houses of parliament backed Chancellor Angela Merkel’s bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLD CITY UNREST</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9508445/Clashes-Jerusalem-continue-Israeli-Prime-Minister-calls-calm-sides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh clashes broke out later Saturday between Palestinians and police after Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu called for 'calm on all sides' after several nights of unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first 'floating' sky pool...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/14741221/rooftop-swimming-pool-london-nine-elms-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first ‘floating’ sky pool with a glass bottom and views from 115ft above the streets of London is opening next month. The pool, located between two blocks of luxury flats in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Won't Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2765537/caitlyn-jenner-dons-cap-california-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAITLYN Jenner was spotted wearing a “Caitlyn for California” cap just hours after announcing her plans to run for governor. The former Olympian and Keeping Up With the Kardashians star…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCALATION OVER JERUSALEM</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/escalation-over-jerusalem-is-how-wars-start-analysis-666229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is important to understand that this timeline is similar to how tensions grew in 2014 and other cycles that led to tensions in Gaza and Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica hits record infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210424211635-yadcz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/COSTA RICA (PIX):Costa Rica hits new daily record of COVID-19 infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontrunner 'NOMADLAND' Set For Lowest Boxoffice Ever For Best Picture...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/oscars-best-picture-winner-lowest-box-office-record-nomadland-minari-1234742718/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter which film takes home Best Picture Sunday night, that title will be the lowest-grossing in Oscar history. According to Comscore, Kathryn Bigelow’s 2009 title The Hurt Locker stands …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR TREK' Shuts Down After Scare In Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/covid-star-trek-discovery-shutdown-toronto-cbs-studios-1234742843/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: As the coronavirus infections surge in and around Toronto once again, Star Trek Discovery has hit the pause button on production. Months into shooting its fourth season, the Sonequa Mart…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA's exodus overshadowed by migration within its borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-churning-golden-state-on-the-eve-of-new-population-numbers/ar-BB1g0GYe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has seen an out-of-state exodus, but its internal migration is equally profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Won't Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9507317/The-Kardashians-NOT-hit-campaign-trail-Caitlyn-Jenner-announced-bid-Governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not a single member of the Kardashian klan has spoken out about Jenner's run over a day after she formally announced her campaign Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210424-iran-fuel-tanker-attacked-off-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early front-runners like Yang usually win NYC mayoral primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/24/politics/nyc-mayoral-race-analysis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York City Democratic mayoral primary is now less than two months away, on June 22. The polls indicate that businessman and former 2020 presidential candidate Andrew Yang continues to hold a clear lead in the first New York City mayoral election being held under ranked choice voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala skillfully running silent and deep...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/549369-kamala-harris-skillfully-running-silent-and-deep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When immersed in turbulent political waters, experienced politicians know to hold their cards to their chests and consider all obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world isolates. A New Zealand band plays to 50,000 fans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-health-music-sports-arts-and-entertainment-13fbb155e4796d07c239030af7a7c6c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand (AP) — Singer Matiu Walters grinned as he gazed out over 50,000 damp but delirious fans and said those magic words: “So, what’s up Eden Park?” While much of the world remains hunkered down, the band Six60 has been playing to huge crowds in New Zealand, where social distancing isn't required after the nation stamped out the coronavirus. The band’s tour finale on Saturday night was billed as the largest concert in the world since the pandemic began. Equally momentous for a band which met while playing rugby at university was getting to play the first concert ever held at the storied Eden Park rugby stadium. And finding themselves at the apex of world music came as a twist for Six60, which has enjoyed unparalleled success in New Zealand but whose forays abroad have ended without the breakthroughs they sought.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
