<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Vatican jails Italian priest for child porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vatican-jails-italian-priest-child-porn-162753369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Vatican court on Saturday jailed for five years an Italian priest who worked as a diplomat for the Holy See's Washington embassy, for possessing and sharing child pornography. Monsignor Carlo Alberto Capella pleaded guilty on Friday, the opening day of the court hearing, saying he had gone through</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten days after Trump-Kim summit, hard work is yet to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ten-days-trump-kim-summit-hard-yet-begin-012835526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The landmark summit between President Donald Trump and Chairman Kim Jong Un ended with a North Korean pledge of "complete denuclearization," but 10 days on no timetable for action has emerged. After flying back to Washington last week, seemingly giddy with success, the US leader tweeted,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi women driving ban ends!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-women-driving-ban-ends-213714400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia allowed women to drive from Sunday, overturning the world's only ban on female motorists, a historic reform that is expected to usher in a new era of social mobility. The move, which follows a sweeping crackdown on women activists who long opposed the ban, is part of Crown Prince Mohammed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of last blue macaws to be reintroduced to Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dozens-last-blue-macaws-reintroduced-brazil-204525512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - About 50 of the last Spix's macaws, the blue parrot made famous in the hit animation movie "Rio," will be reintroduced to the wild in Brazil from captivity in Europe, officials said Saturday. Brazilian Environment Minister Edson Duarte is due in Brussels on Sunday to sign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jailed for 36 years in killing of Chicago policeman is freed after confession is tossed...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-jackie-wilson-bond-hearing-20180622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge who last week threw out a confession tainted by Burge-era torture allegations ordered accused cop killer Jackie Wilson released after 36 years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Babies separated from parents are in Miami shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article213729394.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz told the Miami Herald that babies and toddlers separated from their parents after crossing the U.S.-Mexico border are being held in two shelters in Miami-Dade County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online sellers consider how to comply with sales tax ruling...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/online-sellers-consider-comply-sales-140124154.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While a Supreme Court ruling on sales taxes will create more obligations and expenses for many small online retailers, owners are already thinking about how they'll comply. The decision allows states to require out-of-state businesses to collect sales tax from customers in other states — for example</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMMIGRATION WORKPLACE RAIDS INTENSIFY...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/far-southwest-children-workplace-raids-await-fate-142039778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORWALK, Ohio (AP) — Two of the largest workplace immigration raids yet under the Trump administration, carried out just weeks apart in Ohio, have upended the lives of hundreds of children caught in the middle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma medical pot question hinges on conservative support...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8cd40ed67d040d7881c1df830f04933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINDSAY, Okla. (AP) — Danny Daniels, an evangelical Christian in the rural Oklahoma town of Lindsay, is reliably conservative on just about every political issue.        Th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ gives Congress new classified docs on Russia probe...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/doj-gives-congress-classified-documents-russia-probe-142052316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department says it has given House Republicans new classified information related to the Russia investigation after lawmakers had threatened to hold officials in contempt of Congress or even impeach them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Little Russian media project' tries to turn America against itself...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article213403299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Russian operator trying to influence American politics, any publicity is good publicity for his website that seeks to drop roots in the soil of a divided U.S. The site's stories portray a near state of chaos in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In India, 'child marriage is like a disease'...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/news/asia/india/in-india-child-marriage-finally-meets-its-match-1.2240578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaigner Kriti Bharti runs a one-woman hotline for underage brides and grooms in northwestern India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real estate booms along Koreas' border...</title>
      <link>http://www.postbulletin.com/news/world/real-estate-booms-along-koreas-border/article_3650bec6-4238-52a2-a4ed-ca9fff79ecd7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TONGIL-CHON, South Korea — In 1993, a land speculator arrived in this remote South Korean village of rice, bean and ginseng farmers, and liked what he saw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Mexican presidential hopeful 'AMLO,' 3rd time a charm?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1dac66baa76d4ea0908c6833d6382015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — While financial markets fret about left-leaning candidate Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador, the man himself is calmly cruising toward what polls say is a likely vict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR: Trump Staffers Hypocrites for Eating at Mexican Restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/npr-trump-admin-members-are-hypocrites-when-eating-at-mexican-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food Police are here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Times MS-13 Gang Members Posed as Minors to Enter USA Illegally...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/06/22/9-times-ms-13-gang-members-posed-as-minors-used-kids-to-enter-u-s-illegally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has repeatedly asked the Republican-controlled Congress to close immigration loopholes in order to end the trafficking and smuggling of children across the border by illegal aliens who hope to be released into the interior of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKERS CHANGE MENU...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/hah-hacker-changes-menu-of-little-liberal-red-hen-restaurant-that-tossed-out-sarah-sanders-and-her-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP PAGE BOMBARDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/sarah-huckabee-sanders-red-hen-owner-dismissal-virginia-restaurant-34b08ce3-7be5-4d52-9fa6-f7d84d7684ed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner granted an interview to The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED HEN BOOTS SANDERS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/red-hen-owner-who-booted-sarah-sanders-speaks-out-would-absolutely-do-it-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy says 'arrogant' France risks becoming 'No.1 enemy' on migration...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italy-says-arrogant-france-risks-becoming-no-1-172859262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy on Saturday said "arrogant" France risked becoming its "No.1 enemy" on migration issues, a day before European leaders convene in Brussels for a hastily arranged meeting on the divisive issue. In answer to comments by French President Emmanuel Macron, who said migration flows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE SPOKESWOMAN KICKED OUT OF RESTAURANT BY TRUMP HATER!</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/23/sarah-huckabee-sanders-restaurant-thrown-out-moral-grounds-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Huckabee Sanders kicked out of a restaurant on moral grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN ON BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/angry-erratic-erdogan-cusp-becoming-080000736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recep Tayyip Erdogan sat in stony silence as he listened to the complaints of his citizens.  During his final drive for votes ahead of Sunday’s elections, the Turkish president agreed to go on a popular radio call in show, where the host nervously played recordings of people who had phoned in with their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV BLACKOUT FOR OPPOSITION...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-23/on-eve-of-vote-only-erdogan-gets-tv-time-campaign-trail-update </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s biggest rival appealed to a massive rally in Istanbul in the campaign’s final hours. You just wouldn’t know it watching state television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushes back against border separation uproar...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5877399/President-Trump-tweets-link-images-Obama-era-family-migrant-holding-centers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An article linked by the news aggregation site contained numerous photos of children pictured in 2014 at Obama-era holding centers for unaccompanied migrants in Texas and Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney making final pitch ahead of Senate primary in Utah...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/romney-making-final-pitch-ahead-senate-primary-utah-152942760--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN FORK, Utah (AP) — Mitt Romney is flashing his familiar smile at city parks and backyards in Utah's mountains and suburbs this week, making his final pitch after being forced into a Republican Senate primary Tuesday against a conservative state lawmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numb to Outrage, Republican Voters Feel Deepening Bond to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/23/us/politics/republican-voters-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the president’s approval rating at 90 percent among Republicans, many supporters say they defend Mr. Trump even with some misgivings because they feel criticism of him is constantly overblown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Beck's Media Empire Implodes. Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/glenn-becks-media-empire-implodes-again </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative mogul’s business woes continue via another round of layoffs and the death of a sale to the billionaires backing fellow right-wing media giant Ben Shapiro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London BLOODBATH: Parents told to count their knives to fight crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/978448/Parents-count-knives-combat-knife-crime-bloodbath</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOME Office Minister Victoria Atkins has said British parents should count their knives to check their children haven’t taken any, in a bid to help combat surging knife crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penske war with neighbors over plan to turn historic church into mega mansion...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5876449/Media-mogul-war-neighbors-plan-turn-historic-local-church-mega-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media mogul and heir to his father's billions, Jay Penske, is at war with his neighbors over plans to replace a historic church in the local black community with a mansion for himself to live in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Sanders kicked out of restaurant because manager didn't want to serve...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5877545/Sarah-Sanders-gets-kicked-Virginia-restaurant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaike Foley-Schultz, a server at the Red Hen in Lexington, said the White House Press Secretary lasted just two minutes in the restaurant until his boss asked her to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major New York-area traffic bottleneck about to get worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/major-york-area-traffic-bottleneck-worse-150112230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH BERGEN, N.J. (AP) — It is the bane of tourists and truckers, theatergoers and weekday 9-to-5ers: the congested, pothole-strewn roadway that bisects the teeming towns overlooking the Hudson River before descending into the Lincoln Tunnel to New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP House Candidate Who Beat Sanford Seriously Hurt in Car Accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gop-house-candidate-who-beat-sanford-seriously-hurt-in-car-accident-1529764753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolina State Rep. Katie Arrington, who defeated U.S. Rep. Mark Sanford in his re-election bid, has undergone surgery after being seriously injured in a car wreck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood reeling over 'career suicide note'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5876211/Why-Hollywoods-reeling-whats-called-Johnny-Depps-career-suicide-note.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp will surely come to regret the narcissistic impulse which led him to ask a Rolling Stone magazine journalist to come and spend a few days with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa lions threatened with extinction by villagers bent on revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/23/revenge-poisonings-using-pesticides-threaten-wipe-africas-lions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poison is supposed to be so fast-working that the locals call it &amp;ldquo;Two Step&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; because &amp;ldquo;you take two steps and drop dead&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; but the lions died slowly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Denies Plan to 'Take Down Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-denies-joining-forces-with-tom-arnold-to-take-down-trump?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s self-proclaimed fixer says he had only a “chance, public encounter” with the comedian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating robotic factory will build satellites and spaceships in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/made-in-space-created-a-robotic-factory-to-build-satellites-in-orbit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Archinaut, a system made of 3-D printers and robotic arms, could be the flying factory humans need to colonize space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING robot submarine back roaming off California coast...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-boeing-echo-voyager-20180623-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co.'s Echo Voyager undersea drone has embarked on its second round of testing in the waters off the Southern California coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who was fired by machine 'out for blood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/at-work/no-human-could-do-anything-the-man-who-was-sacked-by-a-machine-out-for-blood/news-story/1852bfd331a671a5ac153721bf91eb1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOT content with taking our jobs, the machines have already started firing people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space tourists could be struck down by astro-sickness, warns astronaut...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/space-tourists-could-struck-down-120000359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dream of boldly going where only a few have gone before has inspired hundreds of people to sign up with space tourism companies like Virgin Galactic. But Nasa astronaut Anna Fisher, who made history by becoming the first mother in space, has warned many are unprepared for the rigours of spaceflight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Media Firms Pay CEOs More for Less...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/big-media-firms-pay-ceos-more-for-less-1529751600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief executives in the media and telecom industries made twice as much as their peers in the S&amp;P 500 even though the group’s performance came up short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC: Psychopath Capital of America...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/06/23/washington-dc-the-psychopath-capital-of-america-218892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study ranks each state, plus D.C., by their psychopathic tendencies. The race for first? It isn’t even close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Up Getty: Fabled Family Finds Their Showbiz Portrayals 'Demonizing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/23/style/getty-family.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fabled family finds their showbiz portrayals “demonizing,” “disgusting” and unrepresentative of their super-L.G.B.T.Q. values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LYNCH: 'You gotta be selfish. It's a terrible thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jun/23/david-lynch-gotta-be-selfish-twin-peaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Twin Peaks director lives for his work. He talks about his four marriages, why explaining his films is a ‘crime’, and what makes him a happy camper</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
