<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov. candidate Allen West 'livid' after wife arrested for suspicion of DWI...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/news/crime/texas-gov-candidate-allen-west-livid-after-wife-arrested-for-suspicion-of-dwi-denies-she-was-drinking/287-45c46fa3-167b-4a9f-b517-64d628909e26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen West, the former Texas Republican Party chairman, said in an Instagram video Saturday morning that his wife had not been drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 dead, 40 missing after extreme floods rock Middle Tennessee...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/08/21/middle-tennessee-nashville-weather-water-rescues-and-flooding/8227162002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens were missing in Middle Tennessee after floods rocked the area including Humphreys, Dickson, Hickman and Houston counties on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RI in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/story/news/local/2021/08/20/emergency-responders-rhode-island-businesses-gird-another-emergency/8211267002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After investing heavily in a summer of relaxed COVID-19 restrictions, officials and business owners prepared for another potential curveball on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Sees Historic Rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/tropical-storm-henri-to-become-hurricane-as-path-tracks-up-east-coast/3229412/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weakened Tropical Storm Henri made landfall Sunday afternoon along the coast of Rhode Island with maximum sustained winds around 60 mph, though its threats of potentially deadly storm surges and flooding for parts of Long Island and Connecticut remain from over. Henri is expected to slow down and possibly stall near the Connecticut-New York border Sunday night, according to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom could be replaced by candidate with far fewer votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/california-recall-reality-newsom-could-be-replaced-by-candidate-with-far-fewer-votes/ar-AANAV76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal scholars say courts would uphold California's recall law, even if an incumbent were replaced by someone with fewer ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban appear to mock Iwo Jima flag raising in latest propaganda push...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/08/21/taliban-photo-appears-to-mock-iwo-jima-flag-raising-in-latest-propaganda-push/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban’s media wing has wasted little time releasing droves of new propaganda in the wake of its ascension to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racehorse bucks jockey, escapes track, takes run in traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/sports/horses/article253660718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The riderless horse, Bold and Bossy, could be seen running along a major highway in a video shared on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bombs Gaza in response to violent border clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20210822-israel-bombs-gaza-in-response-to-violent-border-clashes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's military bombed Palestinian militant weapons sites in the Gaza Strip early Sunday in response to a violent demonstration on the perimeter fence that left an Israeli police officer critically…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concert to celebrate end of virus cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210822-hurricane-henri-cuts-short-new-york-covid-19-recovery-concert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This time, Barry Manilow didn’t make it through the rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept hit by cyber attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/state-department-hit-with-cyberattack-in-possible-serious-breach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department is the latest to fall victim to a cyberattack and the notification of a possible serious breach was made by the Department of Defense Cyber Command, a source told Fox News Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot by wife's boyfriend who was secretly living in their home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox10tv.com/news/mobile_county/creola-man-shot-by-wifes-boyfriend-who-was-secretly-living-in-their-home-deputies-say/article_5e124dbc-ff7a-11eb-98a1-27937bc0160c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CREOLA, Ala.--On August 15, 2021 at around 9 p.m., Mobile County Sheriff’s Office responded to a shooting that occurred at home on Skidmore Road in Creola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprinter Sha'Carri Richardson finishes last in return from substance ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/olympics/story/_/id/32061927/sprinter-shacarri-richardson-finishes-last-100-meters-return-substance-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sha'Carri Richardson ran the 100 meters in 11.14 seconds to finish last and then withdrew from the 200 meters at the Prefontaine Classic. It was her first race since testing positive for a chemical found in marijuana after a win at the Olympic trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half CT could lose power...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Hurricane-Henri-powers-toward-Connecticut-but-16403608.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest forecast says Tropical Storm Henri could move west throughout the day and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil Reserve Air Fleet activated; Commercial airlines requested to assist airlift...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/22/biden-administration-activates-civil-reserve-air-fleet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon on Sunday said it activated the Civil Reserve Air Fleet, ordering U.S. airlines to provide flights for the Afghanistan evacuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth on escape plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-58297893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman went into labour en route to Ramstein Air Base in Germany and gave birth on the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden grapples with twin crises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/568816-biden-grapples-with-twin-crises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is grappling with an international crisis involving the fall of the Afghan government and a domestic one in the COVID-19 pandemic, testing the resolve and ability of his young presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm surge threat...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/weather/henri-tracking-hurricane-conditions-long-island-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking update: Tropical Storm Henri made landfall in Rhode Island on Sunday, packing heavy winds and drenching rains as it lashed the northeastern U.S. coastline. Original story: NEW YORK —…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets, subways flood...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/22/hurricane-henri-already-flooding-nyc-streets-subways/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers are starting to feel Hurricane Henri’s impact as cars are left stranded and subway stations flooded ahead of the storm’s arrival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trains, flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/21/trains-flights-canceled-as-nyc-braces-for-hurricane-henri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trains were canceled and flights were grounded across the New York City region Saturday as Hurricane Henri made its way up the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside luxurious lives of disgraced, deposed leaders in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/21/inside-the-luxurious-lives-of-disgraced-deposed-leaders-in-dubai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just days after Ashraf Ghani fled his homeland the former Afghan president emerged in his new safe haven: Dubai, a veritable Disneyland for deposed despots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti faces anger and despair week after quake...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210821140809-dooth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Haiti faces anger and despair a week after quake, fanning security fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakens to tropical storm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tropical-storm-henri-hurricanes-35b9448730d64a02ca81da6cbbd6dc18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTERLY, R.I. (AP) — Tropical Storm Henri hit the coast of Rhode Island Sunday afternoon, packing high winds that knocked out power to tens of thousands of homes and bands of rain that led to flash flooding from New Jersey to Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflicts descend into violence, harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-2eba81ebe3bd54b3bcde890b8cf11c70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — The Hawaii lieutenant governor watched in horror as protesters showed up outside his condo, yelled at him through bullhorns and beamed strobe lights into the building to harass him over vaccine requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=41.750:-78.000:33.250:-64.000&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENOUGH IS ENOUGH:  Queen tells top aides to plot legal blitz on Harry &amp; Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15930851/queen-legal-fightback-harry-meghan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has ordered senior Palace aides to plan a legal fightback amid ­hurtful attacks by Harry and Meghan — declaring: “Enough is enough.” The monarchy’s legal team is consulting libel experts …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAIR BLASTS BIDEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/21/tony-blair-western-troops-must-stay-afghanistan-until-eligible-evacuated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former prime minister says abandonment of Afghanistan shows UK is now a second-rate power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/news/coronavirus/jesse-jackson-sr-jacqueline-jackson-test-positive-for-covid-19-currently-hospitalized-at-northwestern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Reverend Jesse Jackson Sr. and his wife, Jacqueline Jackson have both tested positive for COVID-19 and are hospitalized at Northwestern Memorial Hospital, according to a statement from Ra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE LONG ISLAND, HAMPTONS</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2021-08-21-tropical-storm-hurricane-henri-new-york-new-england-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Henri is now a hurricane, and will threaten portions of the Northeast while it is near hurricane strength. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talkshow host Phil Valentine dies after covid battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/conservative-talk-show-host-phil-valentine-dies-after-covid-19-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative radio talk show host Phil Valentine has died after weeks in a Nashville area hospital battling COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa, Marjorie Taylor Greene tests national appeal...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/in-iowa-marjorie-taylor-greene-tests-her-national-appeal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia U.S. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, in her debut political trip to Iowa, is trying to build her nationwide profile as a lawmaker, though her far-right views and past beliefs in the QAnon conspiracy theory have made her a pariah...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA:  'Seriously, y'all. Stop it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article253662138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Food and Drug Administration issued a strong and unusual warning on Saturday: “You are not a horse. You are not a cow. Seriously, y’all. Stop it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 23,000 Atlanta students in quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/over-23000-metro-atlanta-students-quarantine-weeks-into-school-year/6FP3J5IHTBBAJMOTQDBWCGE65U/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those numbers are just a fraction of how many students are likely quarantined: Only a select few districts release quarantine numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi infected who refuse self-isolate face fines, jail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/568868-mississippi-covid-19-patients-who-refuse-to-self-isolate-could-face-fines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state health officer for Mississippi issued a COVID-19 isolation order on Friday, telling people that if they test positive for COVID-19 and refuse to self-isolate, they could face fines or possible ja</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=40.500:-78.500:32.000:-64.500&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeasterners scramble to hunker down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/northeasterners-scramble-to-hunker-down-as-hurricane-henri-takes-aim/ar-AANAcYe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People across coastal New England and Long Island made last-minute preparations ahead of Henri's anticipated landfall Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four weeks in July: Inside Biden struggle to contain delta surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/four-weeks-in-july-inside-the-biden-administration-e2-80-99s-struggle-to-contain-the-delta-surge/ar-AANA8py?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After declaring ‘independence from a deadly virus’ on July Fourth, Biden and his team were caught flat-footed as the delta crisis spiraled out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The vaccinated are worried and scientists don't have answers.</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/the-vaccinated-are-worried-and-scientists-don-t-have-answers/ar-AANzgN7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Anecdotes tell us what the data can’t: Vaccinated people appear to be getting the coronavirus at a surprisingly high rate. But exactly how often isn’t clear, nor is it certain how likely they are to spread the virus to others. And now, there’s growing concern that vaccinated people may be more vulnerable to serious illness than previously thought. There’s a dearth of scientific studies with concrete answers, leaving public policy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people ingesting livestock dewormer after FOXNEWS push...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/fda-horse-dewormer-covid-fox-news-1215168/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You are not a horse. You are not a cow,” the Food and Drug Administration said about using the drug that hosts on Fox News have been pushing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor accused of sacrificing animals for 'Santeria' witchcraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/doctor-accused-sacrificing-animals-apartment-24810434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a tip-off from a neighbour, investigators found at least 22 farm animals in Emilio Otero's three-bedroom apartment in New Jersey including goats, chickens and a dead pigeon</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
