<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Line Up to Be Injected With Illegal 'Homemade' Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyppyy/hundreds-of-people-queue-lubeck-airport-to-receive-unauthorised-winfried-stocker-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The developer of the unauthorised vaccine is believed to be Winfried Stöcker, a German doctor who also owns an airport, and a department store that featured in “The Grand Budapest Hotel.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credible UFO Reports Ignored, Declassified Canadian Govt Docs Reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dggbx/canada-military-rcaf-ufos-sightings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike in the U.S., UFO reports in Canada pretty much get “shit-canned,” declassified files obtained by Motherboard show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch hotel saga raises quarantine questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211129-dutch-covid-hotel-saga-raises-quarantine-questions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the "Hotel Omicron" in the Netherlands, where a couple of quarantine fugitives have just discovered that you can check out any time you like, but you can't leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jesus Christ Superstar' actor, accused Capitol rioter, claimed 'divine' authority...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/january-6-jesus-christ-superstar-sovereign-citizen/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court hearing for a January 6 defendant quickly turned contentious Monday after an actor and Oath Keeper tried to reject the United States' authority over him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delays federal worker mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/federal-workers-vaccine-mandate-holidays/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Office of Management and Budget is telling some agencies they can delay firing federal employees who refuse to get vaccinated until after the holidays, an official confirmed to CNN, as an "education and counseling period" continues in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urges Calm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-urges-calm-in-the-face-of-omicron-variant-a-cause-for-concern-not-a-cause-for-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Monday urged Americans to remain calm as the Omicron variant of Covid-19 threatens to begin a rampage across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nervous Traders Track Gauges...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nervous-traders-track-gauges-markets-164725526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Friday’s stock-market drubbing reignited coronavirus-related fears for traders. Now, many are taking to reading charts for clues to where prices might settle. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransThe two key levels to watch for the S&amp;P 500 are 4,546, which represents the September high before that month’s retreat, and 4,489, which is the redrawn long-term uptrend support</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets face weeks of uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-face-weeks-uncertainty-wait-131238784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The fate of global markets now depends at least in part on laboratories around the world probing the omicron Covid-19 strain, potentially leaving investors with weeks of uncertainty in the wait for answers. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransThe variant detected in Africa is described as highly worrying and international travel bans are proliferating. Scientists are an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kennedy Jr.: Fauci  'Like J. Edgar Hoover'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/11/28/robert_kennedy_jr_on_dr_fauci_like_j_edgar_hoover_carrying_water_for_the_pharmaceutical_industry.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kennedy Jr. talked about his new book, The Real Anthony Fauci: Bill Gates, Big Pharma, and the Global War on Democracy and Public Health on the Theo Von podcast.  "Under his watch chronic disease has gone from impacting 12% of the American population to 54%. We take more pharmaceutical drugs than anybody in the world and we pay the highest prices. He has made this country a pharmaceutical nation," Kenndy said.  "If you're born after 1989, I think it is 1 in 12" with a food allergy, he said. "It is the same with all these chronic diseases that are all listed as side effects... The Moderna vaccine was completely developed by Tony Fauci. he hands it to a private group, and then they put $2 billion in federal money to allow them to develop it, and then Tony Fauci's agency keeps half the profits from the vaccine. It would be like... if EPA made half of its profits selling coal. It is the same thing. These agencies are not independent agencies, they are completely captured." "All of the other institutions of government that should stand between a greedy corporation and vulnerable child have been compromised."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC start of winter surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/new-york-city-may-be-at-start-of-winter-surge-of-covid-19/ar-AARebUc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS BACK ON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/nyc-reinstitutes-covid-mask-advisory-at-all-times-indoors-regardless-of-vaccination-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City has not identified any cases of omicron so far, according to outgoing Mayor Bill de Blasio and Health Commissioner Dr. David Chokshi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover potential cause of Alzheimer's disease...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-11-scientists-potential-alzheimer-disease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prevailing theories posit plaques in the brain cause Alzheimer's disease. New UC Riverside research instead points to cells' slowing ability to clean themselves as the likely cause of unhealthy brain buildup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and West 'one mistake' from nuke conflict, warns admiral...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4165272/russia-nuclear-war-west-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world is “one mistake” from all-out nuclear war thanks to Vladimir Putin’s “dangerous games” in Eastern Europe, warns an ex-Navy chief. Moscow is amassing 100…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters gear up to collect signatures on Michigan petition to decide presidency by popular vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supporters-gear-up-to-collect-signatures-on-petition-to-decide-presidency-by-popular-vote/ar-AARdoC4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames shot hoarding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/27/world/africa/coronavirus-omicron-africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With countries trying to close their doors to the new coronavirus variant, southern African officials note that the West’s hoarding of vaccines helped create their struggle in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When YOU'RE the Investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/what-happens-when-you-e2-80-99re-the-investment/ar-AARfQLY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigating antisemitic fliers left at homes in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/583334-police-investigating-antisemitic-fliers-left-at-homes-in-beverly-hills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating antisemitic fliers that were left at homes in Beverly Hills on Sunday, hours before Hanukkah began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Archaeologists Just Find Evidence of Hanukkah Stories?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/did-archaeologists-just-evidence-hanukkah-085147411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gil Cohen-Magen/AFP via Getty ImagesThis week marks the beginning of Hanukkah, the “festival of lights.” The holiday commemorates an event during the Maccabean revolt in the second century BCE, when the candelabrum in the Jerusalem Temple miraculously burned for eight days despite only having enough oil for one. But Hanukkah isn’t just about energy efficiency; broadly speaking it celebrates the successful struggle for Jewish independence. Now archaeologists have unearthed the charred remains of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems want Biden to start swinging at Republicans. Allies aren't sure he can...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/29/dems-want-biden-to-go-negative-523427</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the White House a debate rages over how hard the president should attack Republicans heading into the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To protest mandates, CA town declares self 'constitutional republic'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/protest-covid-mandates-california-town-130058867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Northern California town of Oroville this month declared itself a "constitutional republic" because of COVID-19. Residents have mixed feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new crop of 'raunchy as hell' Christmas movies shaking up TV...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-crop-raunchy-hell-christmas-130025206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irreverent, diverse and brought to life by big-name talent, VH1's "Naughty or Nice" movie slate aims to break into a crowded field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Divided POLITICO: Playbook Drama, 'Woke Police' Fears, Union Fights...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/28/inside-a-divided-politico-playbook-drama-woke-police-fears-and-union-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politico is known for its wildly popular Playbook newsletter, its vast reporting talent pool, and its success as the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese province targets journalists, foreign students surveillance system...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211129115754-k9r47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-SURVEILLANCE/ (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Chinese province targets journalists, foreign students with planned new surveillance system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says hypersonic missile hit target in latest test...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211129113322-f07sh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-MISSILES/:Russia says Zircon hypersonic missile hit target in latest test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone MS clinic on front line...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211129105748-4z142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/ABORTION-MISSISSIPPI (PIX):Lone Mississippi clinic on front line of U.S. Supreme Court abortion battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic nuns lift veil on abuse in convents...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211129101446-e5spf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Roman Catholic Church pays more attention to the closed world of convents, where women spend much of their time, more episodes of psychological, emotional and physical abuse are coming to light</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food, gas prices pinch families as inflation surges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-business-poland-f559465c6a822d12b2dd513f122d5a31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST, Hungary (AP) — From appliance stores in the United States to food markets in Hungary and gas stations in Poland, rising consumer prices fueled by high energy costs and supply chain disruptions are putting a pinch on households and businesses worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pushes shots, not restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-health-infectious-diseases-anthony-fauci-44fab8b3448ad31f0865aebb26f91741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will urge Americans to get vaccinated and receive a booster shot as he seeks to quell concerns Monday over the new COVID-19 variant omicron , but won't immediately push for more restrictions to stop its spread, his chief medical adviser said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury Confronts Rare Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/maxwell-jury-confronts-rare-case-alleging-female-sexual-predator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell Jury Confronts Rare Case Alleging Female Sexual Predator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt for 'Blood Diamond of Batteries' Impedes Green Energy Push...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/29/hunt-for-the-blood-diamond-of-batteries-impedes-green-energy-push/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KASULO, Democratic Republic of Congo — A man in a pinstripe suit with a red pocket square walked around the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse Troughs, Hot Tubs, Hashtags: Baptism Getting Wild...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/29/horse-troughs-hot-tubs-and-hashtags-baptism-is-getting-wild/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russell Moore’s baptism in 1983 was a decorous occasion, or at least as decorous as possible when the main event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY BOWS TO COMMUNISTS: Omits 'SIMPSONS' Episode With Tiananmen Square Joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/simpsons-china-censorship-1235053711/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2005 episode features the Simpson family visiting Beijing, where they drop by the landmark, finding a placard that reads: “On this site, in 1989, nothing happened.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul launches fresh salvo at Fauci after claimed critics were anti-science...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10252953/Sen-Rand-Paul-launches-fresh-salvo-Fauci-COVID-tsar-claimed-critics-anti-science.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with CBS News, President Biden 's chief medical adviser also dismissed Republican criticism of his work as 'lies' and agreed with the notion that the GOP was using him as a scapegoat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns Omicron variant poses 'very high' risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/who-omicron-covid-variant-poses-very-high-risk-global-spread-likely.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The omicron Covid variant is likely to spread further and poses a "very high" global risk, according to the World Health Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TRAVEL BANS</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/travel-bans-omicron-world-health-organization-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While investigations continue into the Omicron variant, WHO recommends that all countries "take a risk-based and scientific approach and put in place measures which can limit its possible spread."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futurists predict how we'll one day eat, vacation, work...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/29/futurists-predict-how-well-eat-vacation-and-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget about Mark Zuckerberg, Facebook and all the talk about a metaverse. The real future will be a world that is convenient and scary and fantastical — at least according to futurologists. As thi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD SHUTS AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-japan-fumio-kishida-82e53a7a17d1a4c30031065d389bda37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Nations around the world sought Monday to keep the new omicron variant at bay with travel bans and further restrictions, even as it remains unclear what it means for the COVID-19 pandemic .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Afrophobia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Omicron-travel-bans-on-African-countries-are-16659087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of Malawi has described travel bans imposed by several nations - including...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch police arrest couple 'fleeing' Covid hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/dutch-police-arrest-couple-attempting-flee-covid-quarantine-rcna6893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch military police said on Sunday they had arrested a married couple who left a hotel where they were in quarantine after testing positive for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid-positive Czech president swears in new PM from within isolation box...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/covid-positive-czech-president-swears-in-new-prime-minister-from-within-transparent-isolation-box/ar-AARfSCA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Haiti, rise of gangs leads to another horror: Gang rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211129-in-haiti-rise-of-gangs-leads-to-another-horror-gang-rape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the rising power of criminal gangs plunges Haiti deeper into chaos, health care workers are getting overwhelmed by the number of women being raped by these violent groups, and by the sheer horror…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC may be at start of winter surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/new-york-city-may-be-at-start-of-winter-surge-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City May Be at Start of Winter Surge of Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets face weeks of uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/markets-face-weeks-of-uncertainty-in-wait-for-omicron-answers/article_1846844c-b4a7-5915-913c-6d9a2e9b34e2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fate of global markets now depends at least in part on laboratories around the world probing the omicron COVID-19 strain, potentially leaving investors with weeks of uncertainty in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>62% of Swiss back new virus laws...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211128154926-fvqg1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SWISS-VOTE (URGENT):Some 62% of Swiss voters back Swiss COVID-19 law - gov't</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI OPENS DOOR TO LOCKDOWNS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211128141821-cjvtt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FAUCI (URGENT):U.S. should be prepared to do "anything," including lockdowns, to fight Omicron - Fauci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Iran Broaden Cyberwar to Attack Civilian Targets...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/27/israel-and-iran-broaden-cyberwar-to-attack-civilian-targets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of ordinary people in Iran and Israel recently found themselves caught in the crossfire of a cyberwar between their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Austin Became One of LEAST Affordable Cities...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/27/how-austin-became-one-of-the-least-affordable-cities-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Over the last few years, in one of the fastest-growing cities in America, change has come at a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothers to take center stage in Smollett trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-crime-chicago-race-and-ethnicity-9b8decca50a228f67411b0816ad5a88c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Two brothers stand at the center of the case that prosecutors will lay before jurors when the trial of Jussie Smollett begins this week. The former “Empire” actor contends he was the victim of a racist and homophobic assault  in downtown Chicago on a frigid night in January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was battling rare cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/virgil-abloh-has-died-aged-41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgil Abloh, the founder of Off-White and the Men’s Artistic Director of Louis Vuitton, has died, his Instagram account confirmed this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeklong earthquake swarm hits North Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article256176422.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent was reported the morning of Saturday, Nov. 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP FASHION ICON DEAD AT 41...</title>
      <link>https://wwd.com/fashion-news/designer-luxury/virgil-abloh-dies-of-cancer-at-1235004104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wwd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The designer had privately battled the disease for several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Abloh's Drudge Report Inspired Site Says About the State of Design...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dmkobe94/what-virgil-ablohs-drudge-report-inspired-personal-site-says-about-the-state-of-design-58e6d85d7370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This January Virgil Abloh created an archival site highlighting all of his work since his beginnings in Rockford, Illinois to his current…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
