<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Confirms Trump Went WH Shelter During Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/attorney-general-william-barr-house-judiciary-committee/#post-update-4ac45624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr's appearance comes as the Democrat-led panel has been focusing on possible politicization of the Justice Department under his tenure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 78% of survivors have heart damage...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/927908/even-mild-coronavirus-cases-cause-lasting-cardiovascular-damage-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you needed another reason to avoid coronavirus at all costs, here's one. Skeptics of the disease and the necessity of shutting down the economy to stop its spread have focused on the fact that most coronavirus cases have been mild or even asymptomatic, mistakenly comparing COVID-19 to 'just the flu.' But a recent study of 100 recovered coronavirus patients reveals 78 of them now have lasting cardiovascular damage even though a vast majority of them had mild cases of COVID-19 in the first place. The study published Monday in JAMA Cardiology details the results of cardiac MRI exams of 100 recovered coronavirus patients. Twenty-eight of them required oxygen supplementation while fighting the virus, while just two were on ventilators. But 78 of them still had cardiovascular abnormalities after recovery, with 60 of them showing 'ongoing myocardial inflammation,' the study shows. These conditions appeared to be independent of case severity and pre-existing conditions, though JAMA researchers note these findings need a larger study. President Trump and his administration have tried to say America's low coronavirus mortality rate proves the country is beating the virus. But not only is COVID-19's mortality rate not as low as Trump has claimed; this study proves there are far more consequences of catching coronavirus than just dying of it. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Test for Alzheimer's Disease Getting Closer...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2020-07-28/scientists-get-closer-to-blood-test-for-alzheimers-disease</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rice vaults to top of VP heap...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/27/susan-rice-top-biden-vice-president-383026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rivals for the vice presidential nod are growing nervous that the former national security adviser has a powerful edge — her relationship with Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes grows empire with ownership stake in ROYALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/28/patrick-mahomes-takes-ownership-stake-in-kansas-city-royals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Bowl winning quarterback Patrick Mahomes has become the youngest owner in sports history. He has joined the ownership group of the Kansas City Royals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALS vote against traveling to Miami...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/sports/content/nats-vote-against-going-to-miami-after-marlins-covid-19-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Nationals players have voted not to travel to Miami this weekend for a series against the Marlins after players and staff members for the team tested positive for the coronavirus. ESPN's Jeff Passan reports that Major League Baseball will make the ultimate determination on this matter and adds "it's hard to see it going against the will of the players. " RELATED:2 MLB games postponed as Marlins deal with virus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Goof, Accidentally Create New Kind of Fish...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-goofed-accidentally-created-fish-130000234.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an effort to save the Russian sturgeon, scientists accidentally created a fish hybrid while breeding the endangered species in captivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 PATRIOTS opt-out of 2020 season...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29551606/source-patriots-donta-hightower-opt-2020-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots linebacker Dont'a Hightower, a three-time Super Bowl champion and team captain, has decided to opt out of the 2020 season along with safety Patrick Chung, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists revive microbes from 100 million years ago...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-revive-microbes-100-million-years-ago-154439850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have successfully revived microbes that had lain dormant at the bottom of the sea since the age of the dinosaurs, allowing the organisms to eat and even multiply after eons in the deep. A team led by the Japan Agency for Marine-Earth Science and Technology analysed ancient sediment samples</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakest Dollar in History?</title>
      <link>https://www.nysun.com/editorials/is-the-w-mr-trump-wants/91203/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nysun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, it's official. The Trump Dollar is now the weakest in our history. The value of the greenback collapsed over the weekend to less than a 1,940th of an ounce of gold, where, as we write, it lurks. "Gold Rips Up Record Book as $2,000 Test Looms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belarus president who claimed vodka would cure -- tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-president-who-claimed-vodka-22430771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belarus President Alexander Lukashenko today confirmed he has contracted the killer bug, having refused to lockdown the country and continuing to take part in sporting events at the start of the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida hits new record with 186 virus deaths in day, pushing toll past 6,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article244537942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARK KILLS WOMAN IN MAINE...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston25news.com/news/local/woman-dies-following-apparent-shark-attack-harpswell-maine-state-says/KLX2MTVGTNCYPGHBZUA2GERUTQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston25news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman has died following an apparent shark attack in Harpswell, Maine on Monday afternoon, the state’s Department of Marine Resources announced in a release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELLEN' UNDER INVESTIGATION BY WARNERMEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/ellen-degeneres-workplace-investigation-1234717494/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Ellen DeGeneres Show” has become the subject of an internal investigation by WarnerMedia following numerous accounts of workplace problems on the long-running daytime series, Varie…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ABC WORLD NEWS' #1 TV SHOW IN NATION; TOPS ALL CABLE AND BROADCAST... </title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/624897496096866304/1-program-in-us-across-network-and-cable-is</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘World News Tonight’ Is the Top Program in America for the 8th Week in a Row ‘World News Tonight’ Is the #1 Newscast for the Week and Season to Date Across the Board Among Total Viewers, Adults 25-54...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER RESTRICTS DON JR</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/twitter-partially-suspends-donald-trump-jr-for-sharing-hydroxychloroquine-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media giant Twitter suspended the account of Donald Trump Jr. after he shared a video of doctors talking about the controversial anti-malarial drug hydroxychloroquine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Favorite Doctor Believes in Demon Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stella-immanuel-trumps-new-covid-doctor-believes-in-alien-dna-demon-sperm-and-hydroxychloroquine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is pushing the coronavirus theories of a Houston doctor who also says sexual visitations by demons and alien DNA are at the root of Americans’ common health concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King dollar's decline ripples across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-dollar-analysis/king-dollars-decline-ripples-across-the-globe-idUSKCN24T1G5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An accelerating decline in the U.S. dollar is reverberating around the world, adding fuel to a global momentum rally that has boosted prices for everything from technology stocks to gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It looks like downtown Baghdad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8563241/On-Portlands-streets-Anger-fear-fence-divides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officers who are protecting Portland's courthouse under the orders of the Trump administration have revealed that they 'fear for their lives' after the 61 nights of protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Spends 9-in-10 Ad Dollars Defending States He Won...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/trump-spends-9-in-10-advertising-dollars-defending-states-he-won</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise lost: Eviction looms for hermit living alone on Italian island...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/budelli-hermit-eviction-morandi/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 30 years, Mauro Morandi has been the sole inhabitant of Budelli, an Italian island in the Mediterranean Sea. As the global coronavirus crisis unfolds, he now faces eviction from "the safest place on Earth"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer confidence tumbles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f7141aab14400d4fcd7f47a88e3b8e44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. consumer confidence tumbled in July to a reading of 92.6 as coronavirus infections spread in many parts of the country. The Conference Board, a New York research...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President seeks political shot in arm in vax push...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7cc45cdcb3e53515b8ff4304a4ae5c06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s handling of the coronavirus pandemic put his political fate in grave jeopardy. Now he’s hoping to get credit for his administration’s aggressive push for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Merkel and waning global clout of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2020/07/28/trump-merkel-us-waning-global-clout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The image of the U.S. began the new decade in a weaker position globally than at most points in the previous two presidential administrations."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Bob Ross Still So Popular?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/07/why-bob-ross-still-so-popular/614431/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-five years after his death, the painter who gave us “happy little trees” is more ubiquitous than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Of Pleasure: Hedonism Key To Happier Life, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/power-of-pleasure-hedonism-key-to-living-happier-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds people who take the time for hedonism are living happier lives and suffer less depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI REBUKES TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dr-fauci-rebukes-trumps-tweetstorm-against-him-i-have-not-been-misleading-the-american-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci shrugged off Donald Trump's attacks against him in light of the president's new tweetstorm against his medical recommendations regarding the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER 'CURE'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8566907/Donald-Trump-goes-Twitter-binge-retweets-posts-praising-hydroxychloroquine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump retweeted a slew of posts praising controversial drug hydroxychloroquine for treating COVID-19 on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CALL THAT LIVING?' HOCKNEY RIPS BORIS OVER HEALTH PLANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8566333/Artist-David-Hockney-lays-bossy-boots-Boris-Johnsons-anti-obesit-crackdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist David Hockney has branded Boris Johnson and Matt Hancock 'bossy boots' over the government's attempts to crack down on obesity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes high as Depp's libel case against tabloid closes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fade699882c0208520fa3622c4c7f437</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Johnny Depp’s libel case against a British tabloid that accused him of abusing ex-wife Amber Heard was wrapping up Tuesday, with the star's lawyer insisting Depp had never hit a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil rights icon Rep. John Lewis lies in state at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/31d9efec950ba0d69bb17c88fd48ab2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a solemn display of bipartisan unity, congressional leaders praised Democratic Rep. John Lewis as a moral force for the nation in a Capitol Rotunda memorial service rich with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Isaias likely to form in Atlantic, adding to record-breaking season...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-tropical-storm-isaias-tuesday-update-hurricane-center-20200728-43kkadvmavgerkrzbvla4a74je-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A low-pressure system with disorganized showers in the Atlantic could form into the next tropical depression or Tropical Storm Isaias with long-range forecasts bringing it close to Florida, according to the National Hurricane Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE ON MARS? ROVER SET FOR LAUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/space/os-bz-mars-rover-launch-preview-20200728-zztbqp2hbzaklgjofjpsamd3py-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early March, when out of thousands of name ideas for NASA’s new Mars rover 13-year-old Alexander Mather’s suggestion of “Perseverance” was chosen, no one foresaw the prescient message it would carry as the coronavirus pandemic capsized American life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Do We Believe in UFOs? That's Wrong Question...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/28/insider/UFO-reporting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting on the Pentagon program that’s investigating unidentified flying objects is not about belief. It’s about a vigilant search for facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluffy the Human Slayer? FORD Unleashes Robot Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.motortrend.com/news/ford-boston-dynamics-robot-dog-spot-fluffy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motortrend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ford just sourced two of Boston Dynamics' robot dogs to help scan the Blue Oval's Van Dyke transmission plant as it gears up for a retooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape America? 12 Countries Where Can Buy Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/laurabegleybloom/2020/07/28/escape-america-countries-buy-citizenship-second-passport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many countries, you can live the dream and live abroad by buying residency and dual citizenship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mystery seeds from China landing in Americans' mail boxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/seeds-from-china-mysterious-seed-landing-american-mail-boxes-usda-investigating-do-not-plant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USDA is investigating, and state agriculture officials are warning residents not to plant, or even touch the unsolicited seeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamptons Concert With Goldman CEO, CHAINSMOKERS Faces Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/hamptons-concert-with-goldman-ceo-chainsmokers-faces-n-y-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamptons Concert With Goldman CEO, Chainsmokers Faces N.Y. Probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Senator Criticized for Ad Enlarging Jewish Opponent's Nose...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5872563/georgia-senate-race-ad-jewish-nose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is the oldest, most obvious, least original anti-Semitic trope in history,” Democrat Jon Ossoff said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's 1980 -- in reverse...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/509275-its-1980-in-reverse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today, as in 1980, the United States is a profoundly unhappy country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran targets dummy US aircraft carrier in Gulf exercises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-targets-dummy-us-aircraft-carrier-gulf-exercises-114815827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran&amp;#39;s Revolutionary Guards blasted a mock-up of a US aircraft carrier with missiles on Tuesday during military exercises in sensitive Gulf waters, state television said. Footage of the war games broadcast on state television showed the Guards&amp;#39; air and naval forces readying for an attack off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clue to Van Gogh's Final Days Found in His Last Painting...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/28/a-clue-to-van-goghs-final-days-is-found-in-his-last-painting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM — One hundred and thirty years ago, Vincent van Gogh awoke in his room at an inn in Auvers-sur-Oise,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He got $4 million in relief loans. Then bought LAMBORGHINI...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-got-4-million-covid-210256806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the first things David T. Hines bought when he got $4 million in COVID-19 relief loans from the feds for his supposedly ailing South Florida moving business was a super-luxury Lamborghini Huracan Evo, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball players express fear, uncertainty in wake of MARLINS outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/baseball-players-express-fear-and-uncertainty-in-the-wake-of-marlins-coronavirus-outbreak/ar-BB17fyyB?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr plans to mount defiant defense of Trump in showdown with House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/What-to-expect-when-Barr-is-questioned-by-the-15438189.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Attorney General William Barr will tell the House Judiciary Committee on Tuesday that President Donald Trump has not inappropriately intervened in Justice Department business - even though Barr has more than once moved in criminal cases to help the president's allies - and he will defend the administration's response to civil unrest in the country, according to a copy of his opening statement.  Barr, according to the statement, will take a defiant posture as he testifies before the panel for the first time since Democrats took control of it, alleging that they have attempted to "discredit" him since he vowed to investigate the 2016 FBI probe of possible coordination between Russia and the Trump campaign, and that the media has been unfair in covering unrest. He is expected to face critical questioning on his response to anti-police-brutality protests across the nation, his controversial interventions in high-profile cases involving allies of Trump and many other matters.  According to a Democratic committee counsel, lawmakers will ask Barr about his role in dispatching federal agents to respond to police-brutality protests that have at times grown violent - first in the District of Columbia and, more recently in Portland, Ore. Several Democratic leaders - including House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler, N.Y. - have asked the Justice Department and Homeland Security inspectors general to probe the federal government's actions in those cities and raised questions about whether they were legal.  "Citizens are concerned that the Administration has deployed a secret police force, not to investigate crimes but to intimidate individuals it views as political adversaries, and that the use of these tactics will proliferate throughout the country," Nadler and others wrote earlier this month.  Barr will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS SURROUND DHS CHIEF'S HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.alxnow.com/2020/07/27/activists-protest-at-alexandria-home-of-acting-dhs-chief-chad-wolf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.alxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of protestors demonstrated outside the Alexandria home of acting Department of Homeland Security Secretary Chad Wolf on Sunday, and called for him to end actions against protestors throughout the country by federal agents. "We live among the people who are wreaking havoc on this country,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200727140344-dkmrl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-O'BRIEN (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Trump national security adviser O'Brien tests positive for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As virus threatened invasion, 'Red Dawn' team tried to save America...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/coronavirus-threatened-invasion-red-dawn-team-save-america/story?id=72000727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Red Dawn" pandemic experts on early email chain with government officials break their silence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Wealthy Men Twice As Likely To Develop High Blood Pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/wealthy-men-twice-as-likely-to-develop-high-blood-pressure-than-those-with-low-income/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals that men with a higher income have a greater risk of developing high blood pressure versus those with a lower income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More federal agents sent to reinforce courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trump-administration-sending-more-federal-agents-to-reinforce-portland-courthouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Trump administration is sending more federal agents to Portland, Ore., as officials consider pushing back harder and farther against the growing crowds and nightly clashes with protesters, vandals and rioters, The Washington Post has learned. To strengthen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First debate moved to Cleveland amid pandemic concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/27/presidential-debate-moved-to-cleveland-382960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate, which is in just over two months, was originally scheduled to be hosted by the University of Notre Dame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis Lies in State in Capitol Rotunda...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/07/27/895150700/watch-civil-rights-icon-john-lewis-honored-at-capitol-hill-ceremony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late Georgia congressman's body will lie in state in the Capitol Rotunda. A public viewing for the "conscience of the Congress" will be held outside due to the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard major disputes top admin officials over clearing White House protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/27/politics/white-house-protest-church/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top National Guard official will tell Congress that the widely criticized decision to forcefully clear protesters from a park outside the White House last month was made even though demonstrators were acting peacefully, a view at odds with public comments by top Trump administration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym owners who defied gov arrested on contempt charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/27/ian-smith-and-frank-trumbetti-atilis-gym-owners-wh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owners of a New Jersey gym that has repeatedly defied Gov. Phil Murphy’s executive order to remain closed during the COVID-19 pandemic were arrested Monday on contempt charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Seeks Criminal Referral Related To Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/news/veritas-video-heartens-congressman-to-solicit-ag-barr-for-criminal-referral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigating and exposing corruption in both public and private institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists growing miniature human organs to test drugs...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/927696/scientists-are-3d-printing-miniature-human-organs-test-coronavirus-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether the goal is to find a treatment for COVID-19 or another disease, scientists often have to conduct preliminary tests on animals to determine whether the drug is safe or effective in people. It's not always a one-for-one comparison, but The New York Times reports there may be a new way around that step going forward: 3-D printing. For example, Anthony Atala, the director of the Wake Forest Institute for Regenerative Medicine, and his team are using 3-D printers to create tiny replicas of human organs, including miniature lungs and colons, which are particularly affected by the coronavirus. They send them overnight for testing at a biosafety lab at George Mason University. The idea predated the coronavirus â€” Atala said he never thought 'we'd be considering this for a pandemic' â€” but it could come in handy and help expedite the experimental drug process, especially since Atala said his Winston-Salem, North Carolina-based lab can churn out thousands of printed organs per hour. 'The 3-D models can circumvent animal testing and make the pathway stronger from the lab to the clinic,' said Akhilesh Gaharwar, who directs a lab in the biomedical engineering at Texas A&amp;M University. Read more at The New York Times. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark of 'significant size' closes down Long Island beaches...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/27/shark-of-significant-size-closes-down-some-li-beaches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shark of “significant size” was spotted off Hempstead, LI, on Monday — prompting local beach closures, officials said. The town tweeted out an alert in the early afternoon sayin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hermain Cain STILL hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12240930/herman-cain-hospital-coronavirus-president-trump-rally-tulsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HERMAN Cain is at an Atlanta hospital receiving coronavirus treatment, according to a statement posted to his Twitter account. The former 2012 Republican presidential candidate developed symptoms &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to fly helicopter over Mars: 'Wright brothers' moment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-rover-perseverance-helicopter-flight-mars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The helicopter, Ingenuity, will travel to Mars clutching the rover's belly and, a few months after touchdown, attempt to fly solo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Cops Setting Up 'Mask Traps'...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/27/miami-police-setting-up-mask-traps-issuing-100-fines-to-people-wearing-masks-improperly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theoretical case for government mask mandates has to be weighed against the reality of their enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust fever rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/antitrust-fever-rises-big-tech-ceos-set-testify-152450617.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antitrust fever hits a peak in Washington this week with lawmakers set to grill top executives of four of the biggest US technology firms in what promises to be a rare political spectacle for the digital era. The showdown Wednesday in the House of Representatives comes amid rising concerns over Big</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
