<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CDC chief warns of spring break surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/15/cdc-chief-warns-of-another-covid-surge-as-americans-travel-for-spring-break-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said Covid-19 cases "will climb now if we stop taking precautions," even as more Americans are vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's New Invasive Species: 10-Foot Long River Monster...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/15/florida-new-invasive-species-fish-arapaima-river-monster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is already in a battle with dangerous and invasive species like the Burmese python, green iguana and lionfish and now there's a new predator in the state called the arapaima, a fish that can grow up to 10 feet long and weigh hundreds of pounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.8 mag quake shakes buildings in Tokyo... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210315191303-zxin4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Magnitude 4.8 earthquake shakes buildings in Tokyo, no tsunami warning -NHK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to label posts to 'combat misinfo'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-misinformation-coronavirus-pandemic-mark-zuckerberg-55583cb7cee4e6966f49f8604d76a081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Facebook is adding informational labels to posts about vaccines as it expands efforts to counter COVID-19-related misinformation flourishing on its platforms. CEO Mark...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Big 'Hands' Brag Under Fire...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/cuomo-accusers-lawyer-says-the-governor-made-a-point-to-says-he-has-large-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know what they say about men with big hands, and apparently so does New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D). An attorney for Charlotte Bennett said Monday afternoon that her client met on Zoom for four hours with attorneys who were appointed by the New York Attorney General Letitia James to investigate sexual harassment claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Recalls Losing Nearly $200,000 To Bruno Mars Imposter...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/14/north-texas-woman-recalls-losing-nearly-200000-bruno-mars-imposter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Richland Hills woman is speaking out for the first time about the romance scam involving a Bruno Mars imposter that cost her close to $200,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air travel rises to highest levels yet since pandemic hit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-air-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-united-states-1c63502b7bee11a7088ae8ee58f26ce0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the United States, air travel is recovering more quickly from the depths of the pandemic, and it is showing up in longer airport security lines and busier traffic on airline...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom won't 'take recall attempt lying down'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/newsom-wont-recall-attempt-lying-170619786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom had refused to comment on recall efforts, saying his focus was on reducing coronavirus spread and ensuring Californians are vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVING LAS VEGAS:  Strip sees big crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9362265/Las-Vegas-sees-large-crowds-casinos-allowed-50-percent-capacity-Monday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds were seen strolling the Las Vegas Strip on Saturday and guests gathered shoulder-to-shoulder inside casinos as capacity restrictions are expected to ease to 50 percent Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Restrictions Ease, Many Left Dealing With Psychological Effects...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/15/covid-restrictions-texans-psychological-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that Governor Greg Abbott has lifted all statewide COVID restrictions, many Americans are ready to ditch their masks and resume their old lives, but it may not be that easy for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security officials to scale back fencing around US Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-fencing-306c493c5c4bfcdd7cbfacea28068760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Security officials will soon scale back the perimeter fencing surrounding the Capitol in response to guidance from the U.S. Capitol Police that “there does not exist a known,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 dead, others injured when car plows into San Diego pedestrians...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-03-15/police-8-to-10-people-hit-by-car-near-san-diego-city-college</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine people struck when car plows into homeless encampment in tunnel on B Street around 9 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel, Mercers Go Big for 'HILLBILLY ELEGY' Author's Senate Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/03/15/super-pac-supporting-possible-ohio-senate-candidate-j-d-vance-gets-10-m-donation-peter-thiel/4700540001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PayPal co-founder Peter Thiel donated $10 million to a super PAC supporting Hillbilly Elegy author J.D. Vance, a show of support for the possible Ohio Senate contender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OOPS:  WASHPOST Issues Massive Correction to Report on Georgia Call...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/washington-post-corrects-story-about-call-to-georgia-election-officials-misquoted-trumps-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post has issued a correction to an earlier story that had quoted former President Donald Trump as instructing a Georgia election official “find the fraud” in the state, after audio of the phone call was released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAMMYS hit new lows...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/grammy-awards-ratings-2021-1234930898/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 63rd Annual Grammy Awards, hosted by South African comedian Trevor Noah and boasting powerhouse performers Harry Styles, Taylor Swift, Dua Lipa, BTS, Billie Eilish, Post Malone and Megan Thee S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pups dying as pet buyers turn to backyard breeders online in pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2021/03/15/pups-dying-of-parvo-as-pet-buyers-turn-to-backyard-breeders-online-in-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As demand for animal companionship rises during social isolation, new legislation aims to curb death and heartache from fly-by-night breeders. Meanwhile, rescues try to pick up the pieces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny says detention conditions like 'concentration camp'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210315-imprisoned-putin-critic-navalny-says-detention-conditions-comparable-to-concentration-camp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny, who is serving a two-and-half-year jail term in a penal colony outside Moscow, said Monday he was locked up in a “real concentration camp”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nashville bomber driven by 'paranoia,' FBI says...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/crime/2021/03/15/fbi-nashville-bombing-suspect-acted-alone-driven-paranoia/4701670001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say the Christmas Day bombing in Nashville was motivated by Anthony Quinn Warner's intention to kill himself and was not an act of terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duke Orders Quarantine After Fraternities Fuel Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article249925583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students who live on campus will be required to stay in their residence halls and classes will shift to all remote as Duke tries to contain the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 in 5 Manhattan Office Workers Will Not Return Full-Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/roughly-4-in-5-manhattan-office-workers-will-not-return-full-time-survey-says/2943582/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan’s largest employers are starting to plan for the post-COVID future of work, and it seems most of them are giving up on the traditional way of doing things. Just 22 percent of the island’s large employers will require all workers to return to the office full-time when they do eventually go back, according to a Partnership for New York…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest 100s...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/15/miami-beach-dan-gelber-rowdy-spring-breakers-take-money-elsewhere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spring break crowds on South Beach are much larger this year than last year, which was the start of the pandemic. Now, officials are worried the increased visitors will worsen the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin traders rival Wall Street as mania builds...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retail-bitcoin-traders-rival-wall-135353699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The cryptocurrency market’s little guys are going toe-to-toe with the big banks as Bitcoin continues to surge to new highs, data compiled by JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. suggest.Using Square and Paypal data as a proxy, retail investors have purchased over 187,000 Bitcoins so far this quarter, compared to roughly 205,000 last quarter, strategists including Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou wrote in a Friday report. Meanwhile, institutions have bought about 173,000 of the world’s largest cryptocurrency over that time frame -- as gathered by Bitcoin futures, fund flows and company announcements -- after buying nearly 307,000 in the last quarter of 2020.While far from bulletproof, the stats suggest that flows into Bitcoin are becoming more balanced after institutions dominated late last year. Wall Street’s embrace of crypto was cited a key reason for Bitcoin’s run-up in 2020, with banks and asset managers alike unveiling plans in the space. Now, with the Reddit-fueled meme stock craze cooling and novelties such as digital artwork setting records, retail traders -- some now armed with $1,400 stimulus checks -- are taking control.“For many retail cryptocurrency traders, Bitcoin was the bread-and-butter trade of the pandemic. Meme stock trading volatility burnt many, but Bitcoin has maintained an amazingly bullish trend that has made most winners,” said Ed Moya, senior market analyst at Oanda Corp. “Retail traders got reinvigorated with the latest NFT buzz and as the stimulus checks hit their bank accounts.”Bitcoin climbed above $60,000 for the first time this weekend after President Joe Biden signed the $1.9 trillion pandemic-relief bill into law, but dropped below that mark Monday morning. The world’s largest cryptocurrency has surged roughly 990% over the past year.Those staggering gains can become self-fulfilling as individuals on the sidelines want to get in on the action, according to Brian Vendig, president of MJP Wealth Advisors.“When institutions started to get more into the space, that shows market leadership and helps to show validation for something and then individual investors also want to participate,” Vendig said. “As you see something taking off, that creates an impulse where you want to participate -- that balancing act tilting more to the greed side or the fear of missing out, I’m sure that’s a component to it as well.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>32,000 DEAD IN FLORIDA, WAS DESANTIS RIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/florida-covid-response-reopening-ron-desantis-0b432cf6-a6ba-41cf-82c0-0148158581cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death rate is no worse than the national average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Epic storm dumps 50-plus inches in Wyoming; Denver 4th-biggest snow ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/historic-winter-storm-batters-nations-mid-section/915348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This season's largest storm caused power outages, sparked chaos and dumped multiple feet of snow across numerous states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  Third wave sweeps across EU and forces new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-europe-mario-draghi-italy-paris-65f7e53fb48d8719754e0e4b020902ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Tighter restrictions aimed at reining in surging coronavirus infections took hold in much of Italy and parts of Poland on Monday, while in France, Paris risks being slapped with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Who am I to judge?'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2515726/pope-francis-signs-ruling-catholic-church-cannot-bless-gay-marriages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE Francis has ruled priests cannot bless same-sex unions and that such blessings are not valid. The ruling will greatly disappoint gay Catholics who had hoped their Church was becoming more welc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Close Receives Oscar and Razzie Nom -- for Same Role!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/glenn-close-receives-oscar-and-razzie-nomination-for-the-same-role</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glenn Close on Monday received an Academy Award nomination for her work in Hillbilly Elegy. She also received a Razzie nomination for the same role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen proposing global minimum levy on multinationals...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/543208-yellen-proposing-global-minimum-tax-on-multinationals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen is working with other countries on an agreement to update corporate tax rules to establish a global minimum tax as the Biden administration considers raising taxes on businesses in order to finance spending prioriti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany suspends...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-0ab2c4fe13370c96c873e896387eb92f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The German government said Monday that it's suspending the use of AstraZeneca’s coronavirus vaccine over new reports of dangerous blood clots in connection with the shot. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's Greens look to be kingmakers in post-Merkel era...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Germany-s-Greens-look-to-be-kingmakers-in-a-16026526.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - Buoyed by regional election results over the weekend, Germany's Greens are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank God it's Thursday: The four-day workweek some want to bring to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Thank-God-it-s-Thursday-The-four-day-workweek-16026517.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women at the Belgian nonprofit Femma decided quickly how to spend their new free...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN predicts economy will grow 8%...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/goldman-sachs-us-economy-grow-8-per-cent-2021-eb7e1d84-b6fa-483a-9e19-37a7faddadc0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If correct, this would mark the largest economic expansion for the U.S. in generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular boosters are future in battle with virus, top genome expert says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210315130156-tzt2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-PEACOCK (EXCLUSIVE, TV, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Regular booster vaccines are the future in battle with COVID-19 virus, top genome expert says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER to offer background checks on would-be dates...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tinder-background-checks-dates-1cbaf030-b479-4d3a-b691-3fe10c851823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dating service is partnering with a non-profit to report on criminal records of match-ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach police pepper-spray, arrest 100...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-beach-police-pepper-spray-unruly-spring-breakers-arrest-100-as-authorities-fear-covid-19-surge/ar-BB1eBlKa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities worry the Miami Beach melee is a sign of what may come this month as covid-weary spring breakers flock to the beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MANK' LEADS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oscar-2021-nominations-academy-awards-6200c2a90ef434ebd23d1b4685503abf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — David Fincher’s “Mank” led nominations to the 93rd Academy Awards with 10 nods Monday, and for the first time, two women — Chloé Zhao and Emerald Fennell — were nominated for best...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forensic experts question Tiger Woods crash probe after new finding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/15/forensic-experts-question-probe-into-tiger-woods-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LA County Sheriff’s Department made several critical decisions in the investigation of Tiger Woods’ devastating crash that were favorable to the golfing legend — who was given the benefit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: OSCAR NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/2021-oscars-nominations-full-list-of-nominees-1234714432/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 93rd Oscars were revealed Monday morning, with the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences is announcing noms in 23 categories representing the best in cinema over the past …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: OSCAR NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g8HyyDEqhEg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor-producer Priyanka Chopra Jonas (â€œThe White Tigerâ€�) and singer, songwriter and actor Nick Jonas (â€œKingdomâ€�) will announce the 93rd Oscars Nominations in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Sarkozy trial to probe lavish election spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210315-second-sarkozy-trial-to-probe-lavish-election-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second Sarkozy trial to probe lavish election spending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest sandstorm in decade turns Beijing skies yellow...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210315-biggest-sandstorm-in-decade-turns-beijing-skies-yellow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biggest sandstorm in decade turns Beijing skies yellow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison guards refusing jabs despite outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/public-health-ap-top-news-prisons-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-522775575fc815ee2354e97c3428dce0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida correctional officer polled his colleagues earlier this year in a private Facebook group: “Will you take the COVID-19 vaccine if offered?” The answer from more than half: “Hell...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic therapy could 'reset' depressed brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-56373202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful hallucinogen used in shamanic rituals is being trialled as a potential depression cure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramen shop vandalized with racist messages after owner speaks out against TX  reopening...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/local/2021/03/14/ramen-shop-vandalized-with-racist-messages-after-owner-speaks-out-against-texas-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ramen noodle shop on the Northwest Side was vandalized just days after its owner spoke against Governor Greg Abbott’s decision to end the state’s mask mandate in an interview with CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will return on NEWS UK TV?</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/media/rupert-murdoch-opinionated-news-uk-tv-channel-launch-ofcom-approval-779383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murdoch's nightly TV channel is in a race to air with GB News led by Andrew Neil — both believe they can take viewers from the BBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota legislators want to rename highway after Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-legislators-want-to-rename-highway-after-prince/600034298/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the StarTribune for the news, photos and videos from the Twin Cities and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild horse on southern Outer Banks dies at 25, North Carolina group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/life/wildlife-nature/vp-nw-shackleford-wild-horse-dies-outer-banks-20210314-5b3f3itkxjgadcjk7wt2jmmk6i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mare, nicknamed Dusty, died at age 25, the Foundation for Shackleford Horses wrote Saturday on Facebook. She was “one of the grand dames of the wild herd” that lives on the Shackleford Banks, which is the southernmost island on Cape Lookout National Seashore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN:  'I've got the whole world talking about me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/14/business/media/piers-morgan-walks-off-british-tv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British TV executives see opportunity — and money to be made — in bringing American cable-style clashes to their screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 'MAYFLOWER' CREW-LESS CROSSING OF ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9337833/AI-Mayflower-attempt-cross-Atlantic-autonomously-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayflower Autonomous Ship (MAS) will depart from Plymouth, England on April 19. MAS will take the same route as the original Mayflower ship to Massachusetts back in 1620.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
