<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Antifa Blasts List Of ICE Personnel's Photos And Identities...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/antifa-spreads-ice-agents-identities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antifa has been known to get violent ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates vow to dump Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/20/pelosi-democrats-candidates-midterms-655484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of hopefuls say they won’t back her for speaker if Democrats win the House. Pelosi has little margin for error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Global warming,' now brought to you by local TV weathercaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/global-warming-now-brought-you-your-local-tv-weathercaster-n884831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local weathercasters have become one of the primary conduits for news on global warming. One nonprofit helped push the change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Subway Conductor Sucker-Punched Aboard Train...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/19/mta-conductor-attacked-q-train/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim says getting assaulted in broad daylight was something he never thought he'd have to worry about. That is, before this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY: Left-wing violence and extremism on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/germany-left-wing-violence-extremism-rise-113644138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German security officials say left-wing extremists have become more willing to use violence over the past five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Populism not the answer...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-interview/exclusive-pope-criticizes-trump-administration-policy-on-migrant-family-separation-idUSKBN1JG0YC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has criticized the Trump administration's policy of separating migrant families at the Mexican border, saying populism is not the answer to the world's immigration problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR FOX: DISNEY UPS BID...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/20/disney-raises-bid-for-fox-assets-to-38-a-share.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big banks embrace 'pay by voice'...</title>
      <link>http://www.kansas.com/news/business/article213503889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks start to offer banking through virtual assistants like Amazon's Alexa, but security experts express worry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mosquitoes Remember Your Smell -- And Swat...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mosquitoes-remember-human-smells-swats-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might think that bug spray or citronella candles are the best repellants, but a recent study found that swatting at mosquitoes may actually help them learn to stay away from you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops fire rubber bullets, tear gas to disperse crowd at rapper's memorial...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/20/cops-fire-rubber-bullets-tear-gas-to-disperse-crowd-at-xxxtentacion-memorial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20-year-old artist – born Jahseh Dwayne Onfroy – was gunned down in a drive-by shooting Monday night in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bots poised to wreak havoc in midterm elections?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/expert-bots-poised-wreak-havoc-2018-midterm-elections-090048965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Automated bot accounts that spread disinformation and sowed disgust and confusion among voters during the 2016 presidential election are poised to wreak havoc again in this year’s midterm elections, according to Samuel Woolley, a leading expert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu warns of cyber risks that can down fighter jets...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180620105719-jfpys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-CYBER/NETANYAHU (TV, PIX):Israel's Netanyahu warns of cyber risks that can down fighter jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flames sweep through barn killing 5,000 pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.10tv.com/article/5000-pigs-killed-fayette-county-barn-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire started around 1 p.m. at the Straathoff Swine Farm on Old Route 35 in the southeastern part of the county.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant operation against wildlife crime in 92 countries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abb53f5d1921485dae23dde73d40950d/Giant-operation-against-wildlife-crime-in-92-countries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A monthlong global operation against illegal trade in wildlife and timber has resulted in the seizure of thousands of live animals and tons of meat and ivory, interna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another test of loyalty looms over Trump's Minnesota visit...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/another-test-of-loyalty-looms-over-trump-s-minnesota-visit/485995871/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign trip Wednesday to Minnesota could signal whether he'll wade into the GOP's primary for governor between a former two-term governor who once called him "unhinged" and an underdog who is an avowed supporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
SCHWARZENEGGER: Politicians Should Be Held In 'Cages'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5863995/Arnold-Schwarzenegger-speaks-against-Trumps-immigration-policy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger has spoken out against Trump's immigration policies saying that innocent children shouldn't be used as pawns after it emerged they were being held in detention cages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says could get tougher on Gaza after warplanes hit Hamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-says-could-tougher-gaza-warplanes-hit-hamas-093936719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli warplanes pounded Hamas targets in the Gaza Strip early Wednesday in a new flare-up of hostilities that saw dozens of rockets and mortar shells fired from the Palestinian enclave, the army said. A military spokesman said all targets belonged to Hamas's military wing, the Ezzedine al-Qassam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats 'become routine' in toxic Brexit debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/death-threats-become-routine-toxic-brexit-debate-030925681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro-EU lawmakers challenging the government's Brexit strategy have received repeated death threats, and at least one MP recently decided not to rebel on a bill for fear of reprisals. One member of Prime Minister Theresa May's Conservative Party is under such threat that they had to be accompanied</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest U.S. Oil Patch Near Its Limit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-20/shale-giant-says-permian-oil-faces-shut-ins-on-pipeline-shortage </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Permian oil region will have to shut wells within four months because there aren’t enough pipelines to get the oil to customers, the head of one of the industry’s largest producers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Whites Dying Than Being Born in Majority of States...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/20/us/white-minority-population.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pattern first started more than a decade ago. But lagging fertility rates and rising white mortality rates have sped demographic change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA TESTS FOR BORDER KIDS, PARENTS?</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/tony-perkins-sessions-dna-tests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sessions is talking to congressional members and is hoping for a legislative fix'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORRIFYING PHOTOS OF OBAMA'S ILLEGAL ALIEN FACILITIES MEDIA REFUSES TO SHOW...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/photos-obama-immigration-detention-facilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negligent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urgent need to prepare for manmade virus attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jun/19/urgent-need-to-prepare-for-manmade-virus-attacks-says-us-government-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swift progress in our ability to manufacture viruses is making us vulnerable to biological attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdown over extradition...</title>
      <link>https://www.hrw.org/news/2018/06/19/uk-should-reject-extraditing-julian-assange-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hrw.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been six years since Julian Assange, founder of Wikileaks, fled to the Ecuadorean Embassy in London to seek asylum from possible extradition to the United States to face indictment under the US Espionage Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN:  Disability Applications Plunge as Economy Strengthens...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/disability-applications-plunge-as-the-economy-strengthens/17639836/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans seeking Social Security disability benefits is plunging, a startling reversal of a decades-old trend that threatened the program’s solvency. It is the latest evidence of a stronger economy pulling people back into the job market or preventing workers from being sidelined in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguan city chooses to govern self as crisis intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Nicaraguan-city-chooses-to-govern-itself-as-13005485.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANAGUA, NICARAGUA - Amid the deepening political crisis in Nicaragua, opposition leaders from a key city that had once cradled President Daniel Ortega's socialist revolution on Monday announced that they do not recognize Ortega's leadership and that they would create a commission to self-govern the city. The town of Masaya, about 15 miles south of the capital city of Managua, was a bastion of support for Ortega and his Sandinista rebels who overthrew the dictatorship of Anastasio Somoza in 1979. For the past few weeks, Masaya has been controlled by protesters, a warren of citizen-manned roadblocks and barricades, with city hall abandoned and police hunkered down in their barracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas hotel EVACUATED after 'SHARK Reef Aquarium leaks and roof COLLAPSES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/976747/flood-las-vegas-mandaly-bay-hotel-shark-reef-aquarium-leak-roof-collapse </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMERGENCY services are responding to reports of a huge water leak at the Mandalay Bay Hotel in Las Vegas, Nevada with images showing the venue floor covered in gallons of water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film director on hunger strike in Russian prison casts dark cloud over World Cup...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-russia-sentsov-20180619-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revered Ukrainian film writer Oleg Sentsov has been on a hunger strike for 36 days in a Russian prison colony in northern Siberia. Concerns are growing about his fate after he has refused to eat until the Kremlin releases all 64 Ukrainian political prisoners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton 'son' slams former president for showing compassion for immigrant children but 'abandoning his own'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5862413/Bill-Clintons-son-slams-former-president-defending-migrant-children-abandoning-him.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danney Williams, 32, has slammed former president Bill Clinton on Twitter for showing compassion for the immigrant children separated from their families at the border, but abandoning him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS faces backlash from Hollywood creators...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fox-news-channel-faces-backlash-hollywood-creators-213127128--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News Channel faces a growing backlash among Hollywood creators that intensified Tuesday following Laura Ingraham's description of "zero tolerance" detention facilities for children separated from their parents as "essentially summer camps."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Wants Trump to Pay His Attorney Fees...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-wants-trump-to-pay-his-legal-fees-1529447136 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen has hired New York lawyer Guy Petrillo to represent him in a federal investigation into his business dealings, and has told associates he wants President Donald Trump, his former boss, to pay his legal fees, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe obesity rates surging in rural America...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-obesity-rural/severe-obesity-rates-surging-in-rural-america-idUSKBN1JF2ID </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters Health) - Severe obesity rates have been on the rise nationwide since the turn of the century, disproportionately affecting children and adults in rural communities, two U.S. studies suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Freedom city'? Going beyond 'sanctuary,' Austin, Texas, vows to curtail arrests...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-austin-freedom-city-2018-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid concerns over arrests of minorities and immigrants, Austin, Texas has declared itself a 'freedom city.' The term goes a step beyond 'sanctuary city,' requiring officers to avoid discretionary arrests and to inform immigrants of the right to not cooperate with police. Will other cities follow?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS CLOSING 150 STORES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-19/starbucks-pumps-the-brakes-in-its-home-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Schultz exiting, it’s now up to CEO Kevin Johnson to decide where to slow versus grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Organizations Consider Suing SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER over 'extremist' labeling...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/about-60-organizations-are-considering-a-lawsuit-against-the-splc-following-3m-nawaz-settlement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are reviewing all our legal options."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR ON BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/karlazabludovsky/trumps-family-separations-are-leaving-people-waiting-to?utm_term=.rhpGn6RY9A#.loy2VoKdYk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If they take my son from me, I would die,” one woman, who was seeking asylum when she was turned away from the border, told BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Will Harass You Mercilessly if You Try to Quit...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/facebook-will-harass-you-mercilessly-if-you-try-to-break-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're like that bad boyfriend who just can't quit you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok escorted out of FBI, but still employed...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5862743/FBI-lover-Peter-Strzok-escorted-FBI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agent Peter Strzok, who was revealed to have sent a text to his FBI lover saying he would 'stop' Trump, was marched out of the building Friday, following an IG report that criticized his conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Chase Homeland Security Secretary from Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/protesters-harass-chase-dhs-secretary-from-dinner-at-mexican-restaurant-watch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists with the D.C. chapter of the Democratic Socialists of America crashed Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen's dinner Tuesday evening and appeared to chase her from the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL INTERN SCREAMS 'F*CK YOU!' AT PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/audio-congressional-intern-screams-f-you-at-president-trump-at-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW CRIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/rachel-maddow-breaks-down-on-air-delivering-news-of-migrant-babies-being-detained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undocumented kills women in Miami, dumps bodies on street...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article213426999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Honduran national in the U.S. illegally has been charged with the murders of two women, both prostitutes, police said. Juan Carlos Hernandez-Caseres, 37, is suspected of killing the women in Miami and leaving their bodies on the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth of world's millionaires tops $70T!</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2018/06/19/Wealth-of-worlds-millionaires-tops-70-trillion-for-first-time/8231529424130/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The combined wealth of all the world's millionaires rose in 2017 for the sixth straight year, and topped the $70 trillion-mark for the first time on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERAL ELECTRIC Booted From DOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/walgreens-to-replace-ge-in-dow-industrials-1529443336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Electric will drop out of the Dow Jones Industrial Average next week, a milestone in the decline of a firm that once ranked among the mightiest of U.S. blue-chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUDDLE ON CAPITOL HILL...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/393127-trump-vows-to-stand-with-house-gop-1000-percent-on-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump urged House Republicans to get an immigration bill to his desk during a closed-door meeting Tuesday evening, vowing to stand with them “1,000 percent” as they attempt to pass legislation meeting his demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Saudi Moves Ahead With Canal Plan To Make Qatar An Island...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/news/gulf/saudi-arabia/saudi-arabia-moves-ahead-with-salwa-canal-plan-1.2238965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waterway alongside Saudi-Qatari border to be completed within 15 months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'Home' leaks location to hackers?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/06/19/your-google-home-and-chromecast-may-leaking-your-precise-location/716018002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is working on a fix that could plug a Chromecast, Google Home link that could reveal your precise whereabouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alexa' In Hotels Lets AMAZON Spy On Your Vacation...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/alexa-for-hospitality-lets-amazon-follow-you-on-vacatio-1826947384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those averse to talking on the phone, hotel stays can resemble a war of attrition, testing your mettle to see how long you’ll go without calling the front desk and admitting you forgot to pack your toothbrush. But Amazon’s new Alexa for Hospitality service, which puts an Echo device in your hotel room, might let you avoid the conversation altogether, and let you bring a bit of your always-on, always-listening, always-spying smart home with you. So don’t do anything stupid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers Make 'Pride' Merch In Places Where Being Gay Is Illegal, Persecuted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/19/business/gay-pride-merchandise-retailers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pride memorabilia is becoming big business in the United States, but some products are made in countries where it is illegal to be gay or where persecution is commonplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUDDLE ON CAPITOL HILL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/19/trump-capitol-hill-visit-immigration-653545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president will meet with House Republicans this evening, but there’s widespread skepticism that they can trust he’ll stick by what he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest orangutan dead at 62...</title>
      <link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-06-19/oldest-orangutan-in-the-world-dies-at-perth-zoo/9886946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's oldest Sumatran orangutan, a prolific mother who is estimated to have given birth to 10 per cent of the global population of the species in captivity, dies after developing age-related complications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Condoms, Flaming Kites: New Gazan Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/From-flaming-kites-to-explosive-condoms-The-new-battle-with-Gazan-terror-560350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latex condoms and helium balloons with IEDs attached are flying further into Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lincoln's iconic top hat, blood-stained gloves may be auctioned due to debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/abraham-lincoln-museum-artifacts-could-go-to-auction-debt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Somebody's got some explaining to do," says one former board member of the Lincoln Presidential Library and Museum in Illinois</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort put in solitary confinement...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/19/manafort-in-solitary-confinement-to-avoid-attack-by-someone-intent-on-street-cred-trump-ex-lawyer-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort is being held in solitary confinement after his bail was revoked, in an outrageous violation of his civil liberties, former Trump lawyer John Dowd has told Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JURASSIC WORLD' Cuts Lesbian Reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/jurassic-world-2-cut-lesbian-reference-says-daniella-pineda-1121454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Daniella Pineda says that insight into her character was removed for time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhones exempt?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40586845/the-trump-administration-promised-apple-it-would-not-place-tariffs-on-iphones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major tech companies, including Apple, fear the looming trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 states refuse to deploy National Guard to border...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/four-us-states-refuse-deploy-national-guard-border-173545530.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five US states are refusing to deploy National Guard troops to the US-Mexico border amid a growing outcry over a controversial immigration policy of President Donald Trump's administration that has led to migrant children being separated from their parents. The Democratic governors of Colorado,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tube station explosion leaves several injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6575725/southgate-tube-station-explosion-evacuation-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPS have evacuated a tube station in North London after terrified commuters reported an explosion at the height of evening rush-hour. Locals were told to stay inside after emergency services and s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead great white shark selfie causes uproar...</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/article213410339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics say a photo of a woman beside a dead great white shark on an Aptos, Calif., beach disrespects the animal, but marine biologist Giancarlo Thomae, who shot the photo, says his colleague posed beside the shark for scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist groped, kissed during live broadcast at World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/19/journalist-groped-kissed-during-live-broadcast-at-world-cup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gross creep brazenly groped and smooched a TV-journalist as she reported on the World Cup from Russia. Julieth Gonzalez Theran, a reporter for German TV-news channel Deutsche Welle, was broadcast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California moves to restrict police use of force...</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article213452784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California Senate Public Safety Committee on June 19, 2018 approved Assembly Bill 931 that would restrict the circumstances under which California police officers could use deadly force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY FIRES BACK -- AT HILLARY...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/comey-hillary-clinton-still-doesnt-understand-why-she-was-under-fbi-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posting fake positive reviews?</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/2018/06/19/gotti-fake-reviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is more interesting than the movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA Gov Orders National Guard Helicopter Crew to Return from Border...</title>
      <link>http://www.richmond.com/news/plus/northam-orders-virginia-national-guard-helicopter-crew-to-return-from/article_5de9926e-1a62-548c-9813-e14ccffe778b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ralph Northam has ordered a Virginia National Guard helicopter and crew assisting with immigration enforcement at the southern border to return home until President Donald Trump ends his family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outage triggers mass NYC subway delays...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-subway-delays-20180619-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Track power went out on two Manhattan subway corridors, disrupting service on seven lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter CEO Shared Russian Troll's Tweets 17 Times...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russian-trolls-weigh-in-on-roseanne-barr-and-donald-trump-jr-1529425771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With U.S. midterm elections approaching, Russian trolls found ways to remain active on Twitter well into 2018 trying to rile up the American electorate, a Wall Street Journal analysis found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexual servitude alleged at 'orgasmic meditation' center...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/onetaste-orgasmic-meditation-sexual-daedone-nicole-13004804.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former employees of OneTaste say the San Francisco-based wellness company encouraged them to spend thousands of dollars on orgasmic meditation classes and, in some cases, engage in sexual servitude, according to a Bloomberg Businessweek report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private sector warms to U.S. Cyber Command carrying out 'hack backs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberscoop.com/cyber-command-hack-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cyberscoop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government should decide how to retaliate against the worst attacks on the country’s private sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Push for Parents Who Commit Crimes To Get Off Scot-Free...</title>
      <link>http://thefederalist.com/2018/06/19/democrats-border-separation-bill-let-nearly-parents-commit-federal-crimes-get-off-scot-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spraying snake with gas leads to house blaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Spraying-snake-with-gas-leads-to-house-blaze-in-13006714.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) - An improvised method of getting rid of a snake in a garden by spraying it with gasoline kicked off a chain reaction that ended up with a house on fire in southern Finland. Finnish public broadcaster YLE reported Tuesday that some of the flammable liquid spread by an ill-fated homeowner in Siuntio, west of Helsinki, landed on a nearby lawnmower that was warm enough to ignite a fire. Flames spread quickly Monday in extremely dry conditions to the wooden house, reaching the exterior wall and attic. The broadcaster said firefighters extinguished the blaze but damages may reach 15,000 euros ($17,000), although the home's interior was not affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Dozens Of Baby Seagulls Dead On Chicago Sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/06/18/south-loop-dead-baby-seagulls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of baby seagulls were found dead on a sidewalk in the South Loop this weekend, and wildlife experts believe someone -- perhaps even other seagulls -- pushed or threw them off a roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beggar asks for cash on board plane...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5861269/Beggar-asks-cash-board-PASSENGER-PLANE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The middle-aged man held out a plastic pouch and pleaded for help onboard a Qatar Airways flight from Doha to Shiraz, ignoring repeated requests from staff to sit down - reports Daily Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOTTI' fires back at critics: 'Trolls behind keyboard'...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/06/19/gotti-slams-movie-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst reviewed movie of the year is firing back at film critics. The official Twitter feed for Gotti released an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies destroy ISIS drug lab making 'Jihadi Pills'...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/2018/06/18/us-led-coalition-destroys-islamic-state-narcotics-cache-including-300000-so-called-jihadi-pills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international coalition to defeat the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria destroyed a large drug cache on June 12 that was previously controlled by the militant group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Invasion of West...</title>
      <link>https://www.chroniclesmagazine.org/trump-and-the-invasion-of-the-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chroniclesmagazine.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[St]riking down the policy will leave America's immigration crisis still unresolved. Consider. Since 2016, some 110,000 children have entered the U.S. illegally and been released, along with 200,000 Central American families caught sneaking across the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER under fire after mistaking ICE worker tattoo for Nazi symbol...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/19/new-yorker-fact-checker-under-fire-after-mistaking-ice-workers-tattoo-for-nazi-symbol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harvard-educated fact-checker for the New Yorker is being excoriated by the Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency for “baselessly slandering” a Marine veteran — by falsely accusing him…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders consider camps outside bloc to process refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/regional-disembarkation-platforms-eu-leaders-consider-camps-outside-bloc-to-process-refugees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nets Flood Broadcasts With 176 Minutes of Separated Kids Coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/geoffrey-dickens/2018/06/19/six-days-june-nets-flood-broadcasts-176-minutes-separated-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outraged anchors and correspondents at ABC, CBS and NBC attacked the Trump administration for separating children from parents at the border as they overwhelmed their Monday morning and evening news programs with a massive 94 minutes of coverage on the detainment policy. Overall, in just six days of coverage (June 13 through June 18) the nets have flooded their broadcasts with almost three hours (176 minutes) of emotional segments that included pictures of crying children and accompanying anger from correspondents and pundits alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Invasion of The West...</title>
      <link>http://www.unionleader.com/article/20180614/OPINION02/180619646/0/NEWS07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the G-7 summit in Canada, President Donald Trump described America as “the piggy bank that everybody is robbing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DOUBLES DOWN:  Dems want illegals to 'infest our country'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392977-trump-dems-want-illegal-immigrants-to-infest-our-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday restated his support for his administration's policy of separating migrant families at the U.S. border, calling Democrats "the problem."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: DNA Tests Reveal Species Of Mystery Animal Shot In Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dna-test-reveals-identity-of-mysterious-wolf-creature-shot-in-montana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a month after the animal turned up on a Montana ranch, a DNA test has come back with its true identity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE HEATS UP CAMPAIGNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.gjsentinel.com/breaking/border-separations-ripple-through-midterm-campaigns/article_7d7e46da-73c6-11e8-9e4a-03bd699ad789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gjsentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wrenching scenes of migrant children being separated from their parents at the southern border are roiling campaigns ahead of midterm elections, emboldening Democrats on the often-fraught issue of immigration while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS PLANS DRUG DELIVERIES NATIONWIDE...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyjournal.net/2018/06/19/us-cvs-prescription-deliveries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyjournal.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CVS Health is making prescription deliveries nationwide to accommodate the heightened expectations of convenience from consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Trump and the Invasion of The West...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/trump-and-the-invasion-of-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is cruel. It is immoral. And it breaks my heart,” says former first lady Laura Bush of the Trump administration policy of “zero tolerance,” under which the children of illegal migrants are being detained apart from their parents. “Disgraceful,” adds Dr. Franklin Graham. “We need to be … a country that governs with a […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicted own death?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6569196/xxxtentacion-dead-rapper-predicted-own-death-video-miami-shooting-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER XXXTentacion predicted his own death in a chilling Instagram video he filmed before he was fatally shot in Florida yesterday. The 20-year-old was gunned down as he left a motorcycle dealersh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson Broadway Musical Planned...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/19/michael-jackson-broadway-musical-planned-but-its-not-so-easy-as-abc-1-2-3-to-tell-his-life-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Michael Jackson Estate is said to be producing a Broadway musical about the King of Pop. Pulitzer Prize winning playwright Lynn Nottage is writing the book. Tony Award winning choreographer Chr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems rising star admits -- he's a Trump supporter!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/392945-dem-house-candidate-in-west-virginia-voted-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Ojeda backed Donald Trump for president, but the West Virginia state senator is now running as a Democrat for the House as his party seeks to wrest control of Congress from Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk alleges extensive sabotage by employee...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/elon-musk-email-employee-conducted-extensive-and-damaging-sabotage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk sent an e-mail to all employees late on Sunday night alleging a saboteur within the company's ranks had tweaked code on internal products and sent company data out without authorization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderate drinking teaches heart cells how to toughen up...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5860471/How-alcohol-protects-heart-Scientists-discover-moderate-drinking-toughens-heart-cells.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of São Paulo discovered the body's reaction to drinking alcohol is similar to its reaction during a heart attack, so alcohol could help the body learn to protect itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets Begin to Take Threat of Trade War Seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/markets-begin-to-take-threat-of-trade-war-seriously-1529411543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese stocks logged their steepest declines since trade tensions between the U.S. and China began, a turning point in the reaction to an escalating trade war. Dow futures pointed to a more than 300-point decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared meets Jordan's Abdullah about Israeli-Palestinian peace...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180619133252-9t8jz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-JORDAN/ (URGENT):White House says Kushner met Jordan's Abdullah about Israeli-Palestinian peace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Officials Approve Plan to Build Largest Mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/florida-officials-approve-plan-to-build-largest-u-s-mall-1529406001 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when store closures are accelerating and struggling malls pockmark the country, county commissioners in Florida have approved a plan to build what would be the largest mall in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange health fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/976425/julian-assange-health-update-wikileaks-anniversary-ecuador-embassy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULIAN Assange’s lawyers hit out at the UK and the WikiLeaks founder is being forced to make an “impossible choice” between his health and his safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent Fight Caught On Video At Hollywood Homeless Camp; Residents Fed Up...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/18/homeless-camp-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent fight at a homeless camp in Hollywood was caught on camera. Residents say it happens all the time and they are fed up and fighting back. Tom Wait reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
