<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fight about gifts broke out at baby shower. Expectant father shot 3 guests, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-fight-about-gifts-broke-out-at-a-Pennsylvania-16472412.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen friends and family members gathered at Kinloch Fire Department's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats against members of Congress skyrocketing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/threats-against-members-of-congress-are-skyrocketing-its-changing-the-job/ar-AAOD2CJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year that kicked off with the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol, threats against Congress members are soaring: 4,135 in just the first three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian pro-Putin party wins big majority after crackdown; foes cry foul...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210920111424-wtsr1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Russian pro-Putin party wins big majority after crackdown; foes cry foul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surging Fertilizer Costs Risk Making Food Even More Expensive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-fertilizer-costs-risk-making-040100289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most people don’t give fertilizer a second thought -- except maybe when driving through a particularly fragrant agricultural area. But with prices for some synthetic nutrients at their highest levels since the financial crisis, it could mean weaker harvests and bigger grocery bills next year, just as the world’s supply chains start to recover from the pandemic.A perfect storm of events -- from extreme weather and plant shutdowns to new government sanctions -- have hit the chemical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Heart of Nashville, Rolling Parties Rage at Every Stoplight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/19/in-the-heart-of-nashville-rolling-parties-rage-at-every-stoplight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE — The John Deere tractor pulled onto Broadway and rumbled into the madness. On a Friday night in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief warns China, USA to avoid Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-china-climate-united-states-health-f1186707bee7f8376b0be5523496ddca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Warning of a potential new Cold War, the head of the United Nations implored China and the United States to repair their “completely dysfunctional” relationship before problems between the two large and deeply influential countries spill over even further into the rest of the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUDEAU ON BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/20/justin-trudeaus-bid-for-third-term-in-balance-as-canada-goes-to-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post-vaccination election gamble may not win over a fractured electorate, but result is not expected quickly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash and burn: Intense and fleeting romances of Covid era...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/sep/20/covid-pandemic-dating-relationships-breakups </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/thousands-flee-lava-spewing-volcano-spains-la-palma-island-destroys-houses-2021-09-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canary Islands' first volcanic eruption in 50 years has forced the evacuation of about 5,000 people, including around 500 tourists, and destroyed about 100 houses, officials said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris to Tell Bezos AMAZON Must Pay Fair Share of Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/uk-e2-80-99s-johnson-to-tell-bezos-amazon-must-pay-fair-share-of-taxes/ar-AAOCbik</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson said he will tell Jeff Bezos that Amazon.com Inc. must pay its fair share of taxes in the country when the two meet on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, UK attempt to smooth tensions as France calls sub snub 'crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/us-and-uk-try-to-ease-tensions-with-france-over-submarine-deal-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and the United Kingdom are looking to ease tensions with France after a deal with Australia that Paris described as a "stab in the back."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul sets record for most Emmys by Black artist...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/572960-rupaul-sets-record-for-most-emmys-by-a-black-artist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RuPaul is striking a pose in the history books, setting a record for the most Emmy Award wins by a Black artist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID US death toll on verge of surpassing 1918-19 Spanish Flu pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-us-death-toll-024500236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States' known death toll from COVID-19 will surpass the number of dead from the Spanish Flu within the next day or two, according to the side-by-side numbers — though a direct comparison between the raw numbers doesn’t give the whole story, medical experts and statisticians say. What is clear is that the sheer numbers, given the modern-day tools that combat such illnesses, are a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big gap between PFIZER, MODERNA for preventing hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-gap-between-pfizer-moderna-034719881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna's COVID-19 vaccine does a significantly better job of preventing COVID-19 hospitalizations compared with Pfizer's shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi on Center Stage With Biden's $4 Trillion Agenda at Risk...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/pelosi-on-center-stage-with-bidens-4-trillion-agenda-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earnings Alarm Bells Ringing; Signs of Fatigue...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earnings-alarm-bells-ringing-market-200000936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An alarming number of companies have warned that profits won’t meet expectations when they report in a month. The group, including PP Industries Inc. and Sherwin-Williams Co., are primarily materials producers that have struggled amid supply-chain disruptions. While just a small part of the S&amp;P 500, their earnings have historically been the most correlated to the index’s of all sectors, a study by Bank of America Corp. found.The profit warnings come as economic growth is slowing,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Haven't Been This Down on Housing Since 1982!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-haven-t-down-housing-174212114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The last time Americans were this turned off by the U.S. housing market, borrowing costs were over five times the current rate. The share of people who think now is a good time to buy a home fell in September to 29%, extending the plunge from March when the proportion was more than twice as high, data from the University of Michigan consumer sentiment survey showed Friday. It’s also the smallest chunk of respondents since 1982.Back then, the average for a 30-year fixed rate mortga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents of Del Rio Feel Impact of Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/20/not-the-same-residents-of-del-rio-feel-the-impact-of-the-migrant-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — On Friday afternoon, Jose Rodriguez stood near a fence that was steps away from the Rio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Supreme Court, Plea to Reveal Secret Surveillance Rulings...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/20/at-the-supreme-court-a-plea-to-reveal-secret-surveillance-rulings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Last year, six months before he was nominated to be attorney general, Judge Merrick B. Garland wrote a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Determined migrants unfazed as deportations begin from Texas border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/determined-migrants-unfazed-as-deportations-begin-from-texas-border/ar-AAOCbZg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasons they come are complicated and varied. The routes they traverse are dangerous and unpredictable. But what thousands of migrants found on the other side of the Rio Grande was beyond anything they expected when reaching the United States.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW FUTURES TUMBLE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/19/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors fear a contagion sweeping financial markets from the troubled China property market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL MARKETS ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-worry-builds-key-week-060121984.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA PROPERTY FEARS</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hong-kong-stocks-sink-evergrande-023055601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Growing investor angst about China’s real estate crackdown rippled through markets on Monday, adding pressure on Xi Jinping’s government to prevent financial contagion from destabilizing the world’s second-largest economy.Hong Kong real estate giants including Henderson Land Development Co. suffered the biggest selloff in more than a year as traders speculated China will extend its property clampdown to the financial hub. Intensifying concerns about China Evergrande Group’s debt c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax NFL star offers to buy tickets for UNVACCINATED fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3690546/cole-beasley-buffalo-bills-nfl-unvaccinated-fans-tickets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star and anti-vaxxer Cole Beasley has offered to buy unvaccinated fans tickets to Bills games away from home. Wide receiver Beasley, 32, along with side’s long snapper Reid Ferguson, 27, made t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy satellites could be targeted with giant high-powered lasers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3687396/us-spy-satellites-targeted-lasers-officials-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US intelligence satellites could be targeted with giant high-powered LASERS fired from the sea, officials have claimed. Leading military personnel believe that new technology, developed by foreign …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brass close ranks around embattled general who warned of 'unstable' Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/19/milley-china-contacts-trump-mullen-512752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Having communications with counterparts around the world is routine,” Michael Mullen said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mossad assassinated Iran's chief nuke scientist with remote AI gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iran-denies-new-york-times-assassination-report-679800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times published a report detailing the assassination of Iran's leading nuclear scientist by a Mossad-operated AI machine gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano blows on Spain's Canary Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10006123/Spanish-island-braces-possible-earthquakes-eruption.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The explosion took place in an area known as Cabeza de Vaca on the western slope of the volcano and comes after the island registered up to 1,000 earthquakes in the past five days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO PLANS TX COMEBACK: RUNNING FOR GOV...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-beto-plans-texas-comeback-governors-race-33a3ae1a-4c58-4e7a-9e44-26342d3128c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'Rourke's entry would give Dems a high-profile candidate with a national fundraising network to challenge Greg Abbott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Attendants Tell All About Flying Super-Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/private-jet-attendants-tell-all-about-flying-the-super-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires in tighty-whities, pot-bellied pigs, massive tips, and mile-high escapades. Private air hosts have seen it all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Biden Bet It All on Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/09/biden-vaccine-mandates/620103/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s decision could cost Democrats in 2022 and 2024. He doesn’t care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Accounting Giants Craft Favorable Rules From Inside Govt...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/19/how-accounting-giants-craft-favorable-tax-rules-from-inside-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For six years, Audrey Ellis and Adam Feuerstein worked together at PwC, the giant accounting firm, helping the world’s biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25,000 employees sue DISNEY for better pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/disneyland/article/Amid-reports-of-homelessness-and-food-insecurity-16461950.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Every time we get to the end of the month, I have to choose what bills to pay.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong holds first 'patriots only' vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hong-kong-holds-patriots-only-elections-b97edf47-8b90-4d1c-b80d-b55da3423a85.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;0.6% of Hong Kong's 7.5 million population is voting to choose the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Kicked Out Of Restaurant -- For Wearing Masks!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/09/18/rowlett-restaurant-owner-explains-no-mask-policy-after-asking-family-to-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have spent my money on the business, my blood sweat and tears in this business, and I don’t want masks in here,” the owner said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milwaukee in grip of worst violence in modern history...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/front-lines-u-homicide-epidemic-120006986.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homicides have skyrocketed across the country during the COVID-19 pandemic. Milwaukee has seen one of the largest spikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Rioter Rally Draws 'Dozens' of Attendees, 'Hundreds' of Cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-pro-rioter-justice-for-j6-rally-draws-dozens-of-attendees-hundreds-of-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early reports and videos emerging from the pro-Capitol-rioter "Justice for J6" rally indicate that the event has drawn "a few dozen" attendees, and many times that number of press and police. On Saturday afternoon, videos began trickling out on social media showing the early stages of the event, organized to show support for those imprisoned […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milwaukee in grip of worst violence in modern history...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2021-09-19/la-na-homicides-america-milwaukee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homicides have skyrocketed across the country during the COVID-19 pandemic. Milwaukee has seen one of the largest spikes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
