<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FOURTH Texas Republican Congressman Plans to Retire in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/08/05/kenny-marchant-becomes-fourth-texas-congressman-retire-gop-exodus-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight-term Rep. Kenny Marchant, who narrowly won reelection last November, is now the fourth Texas Republican congressman to pick retirement over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW SET FOR WILD RIDE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/us-futures-amid-trade-turmoil-between-beijing-and-washington.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures fell sharply as a trade war between the world's largest economies intensified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hit list, 'rape list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/83e222c2be834d1fb3b472f9f77aabb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment? Town halls may decide next steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/434ead07f1d64a24aa467291602b7717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Scraps Kashmir's Long-Held Autonomy, Escalating Tensions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pakistan-leader-warns-crisis-india-023503550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- India has revoked the special constitutional status of Kashmir in a move that’s drawn protests in parliament and risks worsening its already fraught security relationship with rival Pakistan in the disputed region.It took Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s government just a couple of hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes, travel chaos in Hong Kong as leader warns city on brink...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-leader-says-city-brink-protesters-unleash-043109190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong riot police clashed Monday with pro-democracy protesters for a third straight day, as the city's leader warned the global financial hub was nearing a "very dangerous situation" and a rare strike caused transport chaos. Clouds of tear gas billowed across multiple locations on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Not Even Dollars Can Save Venezuelans From Inflation Wrath...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/not-even-dollars-save-venezuelans-090000480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Carmen Rojas used to be one of the fortunate Venezuelans who lived off a steady flow of money from relatives abroad, with $150 from her two sons providing enough cash to last a month. Today, she’s lucky if that amount gets her through the week.Luxuries like trips to restaurants and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'Chernobyl on ice' as Moscow prepares floating nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/04/russia-floating-nuclear-power-station-chernobyl-on-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scepticism and safety concerns persist before vessel begins 4,000-mile Arctic journey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia ready to defy Putin?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/04/moscow-protests-police-crackdown-putin-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discontent and a push for political reforms have led to the largest protests in Moscow in almost a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE: UFO sightings over Cincinnati as mystery lights filmed vanishing from sight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/796262/Cincinnati-UFOs-flood-Twitter-video-lights-vanishing-across-US</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans immortal -- 20 years? </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/794107/immortality-human-futurism-transhumanist-fountain-of-youth-science</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lets yuan break key 7 level for first time in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/chinese-yuan-moves-against-the-dollar-amid-us-china-trade-turmoil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese yuan crossed a closely watched 7 barrier against the dollar on Monday following a recent reescalation in the trade war between Beijing and Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protest, strike brings city to standstill...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/hong-kong-protest-and-strike-brings-city-to-a-standstill-11777774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam says the ongoing protests are pushing the city to the "verge of a very dangerous situation".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion: Biden offers sympathy for 'tragic events in Houston and Michigan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/confusion-biden-offers-sympathy-for-the-tragic-events-in-houston-today-and-also-in-michigan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden misstated the locations of mass shootings in El Paso, Texas, and Dayton, Ohio, while speaking to donors at a high-dollar fundraiser in San Diego on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND MASS SHOOTING IN 12 HOURS...!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9650601/el-paso-walmart-shooting-dayton-ohio-mass-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT least 29 people have died in two US mass shootings in just 12 hours. Twisted gunman Patrick Crusius used an AK47-type weapon to gun down parents and kids in a packed Walmart in El Paso, Texas, o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County sheriff: 'This Anglo man came here to kill Hispanics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article233512672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI faces skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/FBI-faces-skepticism-over-its-anti-domestic-14279800.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI insists it is fully engaged in combating the threat of violence from white supremacists, but some former federal officials charge that the government is still coming up short in the face of a strain of American terrorism that now seems resurgent.  The weekend massacre at a Walmart in El Paso has focused public debate once again on the issue, after federal prosecutors called it an act of domestic terrorism.  In recent congressional testimony, senior FBI officials said they were conducting about 850 domestic terrorism investigations - a decrease from a year earlier, when there were roughly 1,000. The category covers more than just racist-motivated violence, but officials say such motivations are a large part of their domestic terrorism caseload.  Yet by other measures, the threat of white nationalist violence appears to be rising. Between October and June, there were about 100 arrests of domestic terrorism suspects - and if that trend continues, the total for 2019 would outpace the prior year, when there were about 120 such cases. The year before that, about 150 domestic terrorism suspects were arrested.  "Our focus is on the violence," FBI Director Christopher Wray insisted at a congressional hearing two weeks ago. "We, the FBI, don't investigate ideology, no matter how repugnant. . . . When it turns to violence, we're all over it."  That poses particular challenges in the world of white supremacists, who often do not belong to specific groups but find congregations of similar-minded people online, and feed each other's anger and hate.  That general lack of centralized groups or leaders among many white supremacists presents legal challenges to investigators, according to law enforcement officials. And in some cases, it shortens the time period from which a person may adopt extremist views and then...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8chan loses network provider...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/network-provider-cloudflare-drop-8chan-after-el-paso-shooting-n1039151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloudflare CEO Matthew Prince said the anonymous internet forum's "lawlessness" caused "multiple tragic deaths."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico vows to take legal action against USA after El Paso shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/mexico-vows-take-legal-action-against-u-s-wake-deadly-n1039096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least six of the 20 dead in Saturday's attack, described by Mexico's foreign minister as an "act of barbarism," are Mexican nationals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  DRUDGE critics wrong. Publishing killer manifesto right thing to do...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/08/el-paso-shootings-free-speech-curbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People can decide for themselves what to make of hateful words, whether in Mein Kampf or a murderer’s manifesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RHETORIC GOT TOO HOT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/critics-say-trump-foments-white-supremacy-aide-says-dont-blame-him-in-el-paso-shooting/ar-AAFkluq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE:  Anti-immigrant rhetoric looms over El Paso massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/spotlight/how-do-you-stop-these-people-trumps-anti-immigrant-rhetoric-looms-over-el-paso-massacre/ar-AAFkCYL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend of mass killing reflects how violence goes viral... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Weekend-of-mass-killing-reflects-how-American-14279885.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In El Paso, Dayton and Chicago, a weekend of horrific gun violence seemed on the surface to be another spasm of disconnected mayhem, people taking the lives of others almost at random. But on closer examination, the attacks served to illustrate how America's lone wolf shooters aren't really alone.  Whether the proximate cause was political or personal, whether it grew out of ideological indoctrination, mental illness or some toxic blend of factors that left shooters isolated and damaged, each attack demonstrated a troubling disorder festering in modern America.  The 21-year-old man who allegedly killed 20 people doing their Saturday shopping in El Paso, Texas, appears to have taken pains to post a manifesto that leaned heavily on the virulently anti-immigrant rhetoric that inspired recent mass shootings in New Zealand and California, authorities said - though they were still working to confirm its authenticity.  The suspect, Patrick Crusius, did not appear to be part of any organized group, but the four-page screed posted minutes before he opened fire parroted the extreme white supremacist ideology known as "the great replacement" - the idea that newcomers are taking the jobs of white Christians in America and other Western nations.  The alleged killer of nine people in Dayton, Ohio, Connor Betts, was a 24-year-old Chipotle worker and community college student driven by personal grievance rather than political ideology, authorities said. Betts, who was killed by police, shot his own sister among his victims.  Showing up outside a popular bar around 1 a.m. wearing body armor and carrying a high-capacity rifle and extra magazines, the Dayton shooter instantly joined the ranks of gunmen who have learned online, in video games and in countless movies and TV shows how to escalate personal beefs into community-shattering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA ROUNDUP...</title>
      <link>https://us11.campaign-archive.com/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=b3f55c7aa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF ARMS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/04/the-post-says-ban-assault-weapons-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mass shootings within 24 hours in El Paso and Dayton, days after the Garlic Festival killings. Three months after Virginia Beach, six months after Aurora, nine months after Thousand Oaks, 10 mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters look to shut down city with strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-protesters-look-shut-211614255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hong Kong leader Carrie Lam warned of a “very dangerous situation” as protesters moved to shut down the Asian financial hub with a general strike and commute disruptions on Monday, after a ninth straight weekend of unrest in opposition to China’s tightening grip.Demonstrators hampered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAME GAME</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec74c3c86d1f44c0afc40ba2c6c81702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After pair of mass shootings, Trump remains out of sight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d324c661d5f4a748c0990c8444efdb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in public-shooting-era America: 'You can't just not go'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c485bb8f6124280821ce0c9ee5adb7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian gang leader dresses as teen daughter in bizarre prison-break...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9654376/brazil-gang-leader-caught-dressed-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the bizarre moment a Brazilian gang leader is caught trying to escape a high-security prison – dressed as his teenage daughter. Clauvino da Silva, 42, tried to bust out of Rio’s Geric…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent mass shootings: A timeline...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/recent-mass-shootings-in-the-us-a-timeline/ar-AAFkzcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gilroy shooter left little impression on classmates, community...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/08/04/gilroy-shooter-left-little-impression-on-classmates-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santino Legan was the youngest member of a well-known Gilroy family. Why he carried out a massacre at his hometown’s famed festival remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Star Quits Hit Show, Claims Race and Sex Discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/rookie-star-quits-claims-she-faced-sexual-harassment-racial-discrimination-1229109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afton Williamson announced she would not be returning to the ABC drama starring Nathan Fillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitch McConnell breaks shoulder...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mitch-mcconnell-fractures-shoulder-kentucky-f22f5892-8a00-4158-93f5-c1aa1c4dfc21.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The injury comes as lawmakers are urging McConnell to cancel the Senate recess to address gun control legilsation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Military-Style Surveillance Technology Being Tested in American Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/08/military-style-surveillance-air-often-legal/595063/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the eyes of the law, there’s no difference between a photo taken by a smartphone through an airplane window and one taken by an ultrapowerful camera in a helicopter hovering over your backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20% of millennials have no friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-millenials-no-friends-yougov-poll-20190804-ek5odkrxmvbfhex7ytvp2p6rwy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20% of millennials surveyed in a YouGov poll released Tuesday claimed that they don’t have a singe friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed, burned out and exhausted: Inside world's worst traffic jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/traffic-stress-lagos-nigeria/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lagos, Nigeria, is an African boom city, no doubt. But traffic is so 'hellish' and gridlocked that it's taking a terrible toll on workers who grapple with commutes that last for hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China: Will not 'sit idly by'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests-arrests/thousands-resume-hong-kong-protests-china-media-warns-beijing-wont-sit-idly-by-idUSKCN1UU00X?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired tear gas to disperse hundreds of anti-government protesters in Hong...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland woman allegedly beat police officer with his own baton...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2019/08/portland-woman-allegedly-beat-police-officer-with-his-own-baton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have charged a 38-year-old woman with assaulting a public safety officer and unlawful use of a weapon after she allegedly attacked an officer who was trying to assist her after a motorcycle crash with his own baton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.2 mag quake jolts Japan, off the coast of Fukushima...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7319443/Quake-hits-northeast-Japan-officials-say-no-tsunami-danger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strong earthquake has struck 50 kilometres off the coast of Japan, shaking the region of Fukushima and Miyagi. Nuclear power plants in the area have not suffered damage in the quake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors HALT menopause: Revolutionary procedure delays process by 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7318435/Doctors-halt-menopause-Revolutionary-procedure-delays-process-20-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dixie-Louise Dexter (pictured), 33, is among those to undergo the procedure and described the ovarian transplant surgery to delay her menopause as 'life-changing'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama library brings fear of displacement...</title>
      <link>https://www.baynews9.com/fl/tampa/ap-top-news/2019/08/04/obama-library-brings-elation-but-also-fear-of-displacement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baynews9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago residents living near the Obama Presidential Center&amp;#39;s proposed site say the prospect of a gleaming center honoring the president they supported excites them, but they also fear neighborhood revitalization might push them out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope encourages priests disheartened by sex abuse fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc4.com/news/international/pope-encourages-priests-disheartened-by-sex-abuse-fallout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis on Sunday sent a new letter to priests worldwide offering encouragement in light of the global sex abuse scandal that has shaken the Roman Catholic Church. In a nea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters hurl objects at police station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8be2dd4b7cf24e61b3e8da365045ad88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France ponders giving lesbians, single women access to IVF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48ff2014b3fe4f17b1c41d947cd5a0ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
