<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WALMART apologizes for sweater featuring Santa with cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/08/walmart-apologizes-for-sweater-featuring-santa-with-cocaine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ho, ho, no! Walmart has apologized for an adults-only Christmas sweater that appeared to depict Santa with cocaine on its Canadian website, according to a report. The retailer pulled the holiday ou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Becomes First Studio Ever to Hit $10 Billion at Box Office in Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-becomes-first-ever-studio-with-10-billion-at-global-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's record-breaking 2019 continued this weekend, as it became the first studio ever to gross $10 billion at the global box office in a single year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' Named Best Picture By LA Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/la-film-critics-association-awards-winners-list-1260643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Driver, Jennifer Lopez, Antonio Banderas won the acting prizes in the vote, which took place Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING ORDERS REMOVAL OF FOREIGN COMPUTERS AND SOFTWARE...</title>
      <link>https://www.forexcrunch.com/beijing-orders-state-offices-to-replace-foreign-pcs-and-software-ft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forexcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RIPS 'PATHETIC' FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/473591-trump-claims-fox-news-panders-to-democrats-by-having-liberal-guests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Sunday renewed his criticism of Fox News, claiming that the network was pandering to the Democratic Party by repeatedly hosting liberal lawmakers to discuss the impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI presumes terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8aef6b09fe84ba7f5ee1d0b00e7d1b0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. (AP) — The Saudi gunman who killed three people at the Pensacola naval base had apparently gone on Twitter shortly before the shooting to blast U.S. support of Israel and accuse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global financial watchdogs take aim at Big Tech's data dominance...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208223020-qyfcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECH-REGULATOR/:Global financial watchdogs take aim at Big Tech's data dominance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos of Lindsey Graham are coming back to bite him. But will voters care?</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article237674979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Finland prime minister is 34!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/new-finland-prime-minister-sanna-21053251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanna Marin - a minister for the country's Social Democrats - will become the youngest leader in the world when he takes control of the country next week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE THAN 7 MILLION JOBS CREATED SINCE TRUMP WON ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/08/exclusive-treasurys-monica-crowley-on-the-explosive-trump-economy-success-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Crowley told Breitbart News that President Donald Trump’s “economic freedom agenda” has led to the lowest unemployment in 50 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrelenting chaos as French strike bites...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frances-macron-hold-meeting-pensions-strike-bites-060132547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron, Prime Minister Edouard Philippe and senior cabinet ministers met late Sunday to discuss the government's proposed pensions reforms as public transport in France was crippled for a fourth day running in protest. The country's powerful labour unions, who claim</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi military training in US under scrutiny after base attack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/calls-halt-saudi-military-training-us-attack-175752458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key US lawmakers called Sunday for a halt to a Saudi military training program after a shooting rampage at a naval base in Florida in which a Saudi officer killed three American sailors. US Defense Secretary Mark Esper said he has ordered a review of vetting procedures while defending the training program</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even worse travel woes; Govt seeks answers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f875ff134f42b8c3ab6d654498eb5b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France braced for even worse transportation woes when the new work week begins Monday due to nationwide strikes over the government's redesign of the national retirement system....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Blundering Brilliance of Boris...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/12/boris-johnson-brexit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brexit has given the U.K’s self-seeking Prime Minister the opportunity to show he actually knows what he’s doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  VOTE POSSIBLE THIS WEEK</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208184944-iu3fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Democrats zoom in on Trump impeachment charges this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Underground introduces First Class Carriages -- With A Bar!</title>
      <link>https://www.suffolkgazette.com/news/london-underground-introduces-first-class-carriages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.suffolkgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Underground is introducing luxurious first-class carriages so well-heeled commuters do not need to mix with common riff-raff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wailing, white light and angel wings: 'Possessed' man's terrifying exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/wailing-white-light-angel-wings-21024749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian found himself being the subject of an exorcism after visiting a throat specialist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan arrested over 'racist gesture' at soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7768919/Manchester-City-fan-accused-making-monkey-sounds-United-star-Fred-family-man-40.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Anthony Burke, 41, (pictured) from Manchester appeared to make racist gestures and monkey noises at United midfielder Fred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems embrace exact surveillance tactics they used to warn about...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/07/democrats-have-embraced-the-exact-surveillance-tactics-they-used-to-warn-about/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Democrats have been warning Americans about the dangers of law enforcement metadata collections. They cautioned that communication giants were working in cahoots with law enforcement to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheelchair thief in reindeer slippers stopped in his tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article238168529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am Jesus Christ' lets gamers play through being crucified; Fight Satan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/i-am-jesus-christ-lets-21051487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial game allowing people to play through key moments from the Bible is due to be released on Steam for PC - but Christians have argued it is blasphemous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Ronstadt Needles Secretary of State Pompeo to his face for 'Enabling Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/linda-ronstadt-needles-secretary-of-state-mike-pompeo-for-enabling-trump-to-his-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exchange happened during a State Department dinner for Kennedy Center Honors recipients on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires warning shot at Kim Jong-un...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10508799/trump-warning-shot-north-korea-nuke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump today warned trigger-happy North Korea it has “too much to lose” hours after its latest controversial “missile” test. The tough-talking US president took to Twi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  VOTE POSSIBLE THIS WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/08/politics/jerry-nadler-donald-trump-impeachment-obstruction-of-justice/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With sources telling CNN a vote in the Judiciary Committee to impeach President Donald Trump is expected as soon as this week, House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler said Sunday that he sees the Ukraine evidence as part of "a pattern" of conduct by the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  Vote possible THIS week...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/8/jerrold-nadler-impeachment-vote-possible-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler said there could be a vote as early as this week on articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Typo' overvalued Utah home by $1B -- now county residents have to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/Typo-may-have-overvalued-Utah-home-at-nearly-1B-14888778.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) - Utah officials say a possible dropped phone resulted in a typo that overvalued a home for almost $1 billion.  And taxpayers may have to pay for the mistake.  The Deseret News reports a house built in 1978 in an unincorporated area of the county was recorded in 2019 tax rolls with a value of more than $987 million. That's an overestimate of about $543 million in taxable value.  Wasatch County Assessor Maureen "Buff" Griffiths told officials last month a staff member may have dropped a phone on a keyboard. Griffiths said the accident has resulted in a countywide overvaluation of more than $6 million.  Griffiths added that the blunder also produced revenue shortfalls in five taxing entities.  Wasatch County officials say residents will likely see an increased tax rate over the next three years to make up for the lower amount collected in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Moonves, 'toxic' culture remains in CBS TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-12-08/cbs-tv-stations-toxic-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Times investigation uncovers claims of discrimination, retaliation and other forms of mistreatment at CBS-owned TV stations, including L.A. outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cool Kids of the Left Turned...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/08/elizabeth-warren-jacobin-socialist-left-072693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The socialists of Jacobin magazine used to treat her like a promising alternative to Bernie Sanders. Now they write as if she’s almost as bad as Joe Biden. What gives?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number of African migrants at U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/story/2019-12-08/record-number-of-african-migrants-at-u-s-mexico-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of migrants from African countries in Mexico who have had contact with Mexican immigration officials has increased from 460 in 2007 to more than 5,800 in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan arrested over 'racist gesture' at soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/man-arrested-over-racist-gesture-manchester-derby-135444971--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British police on Sunday arrested a 41-year-old man after a video posted on social media showed a supporter apparently making racist gestures during Saturday&amp;#39;s Manchester derby. &amp;quot;Police were called to a report of a supporter making alleged racist gestures and sounds towards players during the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough or threat? Research on genetics of same-sex behavior ignites ethical debate...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/breakthrough-or-a-threat-research-on-genetics-of-same-sex-behaviour-ignites-ethical-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Were we to avoid studying sexual preference or other such topics … we would be leaving these important aspects of human diversity in the dark’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson promises lower immigration if he wins election...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208075449-7amri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/ (PIX):UK PM Johnson promises lower immigration if he wins election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Go after your enemies': Trump's 21-year-old playbook...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/08/trump-impeachment-playbook-clinton-077717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump shared his real-time thoughts about the Clinton impeachment two decades ago. Those same views are echoing through the president’s fight today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicare chief asked taxpayers to cover stolen jewelry...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/07/medicare-chief-asked-taxpayers-to-cover-stolen-jewelry-077761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seema Verma requested $47,000 for items taken from an SUV that took her to a speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Pentagon: 'We are the good guys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/07/bezos-says-country-in-trouble-if-big-tech-turns-its-back-on-the-pentagon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Silicon Valley courts a closer relationship with the Pentagon, tech firms have faced backlash for pursuing lucrative Defense Department contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservationist attacked by her own tigers at animal sanctuary...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/conservationist-attacked-tigers-animal-sanctuary/story?id=67575571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildlife conservationist was attacked an injured by several of her own tigers during an event at a wildlife sanctuary in southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Mysterious Case of Babies Buried With Helmets of Other Children's Skulls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-mysterious-case-of-babies-buried-with-helmets-of-other-childrens-skulls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papers around the world have sensationalized the discovery of babies buried with the skulls of other children around their heads. But what’s really going on here?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wacky, big-money world of pet influencers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wacky-big-money-world-pet-influencers-082651201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grumpy Cat, Lil Bub, Boo the Pomeranian and Doug the Pug are just some of the internet's star animals, who do everything from support worthy causes to promote major brands. The death this week of Lil Bub, a cat whose tongue was always hanging out due to genetic anomalies, inspired a wave of emotion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kongers mark half year of protest with mammoth rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-democracy-protesters-aim-massive-turnout-rare-210115805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast crowds of democracy protesters thronged Hong Kong's streets on Sunday in a forceful display of support for the movement as it marks six months with organisers warning the city's pro-Beijing leaders they had a "last chance" to end the political crisis. Authorities have repeatedly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Turns to God to Win Over Black Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mayor-pete-turns-to-god-to-win-over-black-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“All candidates should prioritize achieving greater understanding of issues that impact African Americans and other minority groups,” Rep. André Carson (D-IN) said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Chief Won't Call 'Terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-shooting-pentagon-idUSKBN1YB0LH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Mark Esper said on Saturday that he was not prepared at t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts 'important test' at once-dismantled site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/771a2235054d115a526ee8dcc2bd6295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Sunday that it carried out a “very important test” at its long-range rocket launch site that it reportedly rebuilt after having partially dismantled it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 more detained...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10504744/saudi-airmans-colleagues-us-naval-base-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Saudi air force pilot in the US for training who killed at least three people when he opened fire at a military base in Florida was filmed by his colleagues as he went on his killing spree. Moh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation broadens...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Investigation-broadens-in-shooting-at-Naval-Air-14890151.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. - FBI officials broadened their probe Saturday into the deadly shooting rampage at a Navy flight school here amid reports that several of the alleged gunman's Saudi compatriots took video footage as the killing spree was underway.  The shooting at the Naval Air Station Pensacola was labeled an act of terrorism by congressional officials, even as investigators continued to explore why a Saudi military student blasted his way through a classroom building early Friday, killing three people and wounding eight. The gunman, identified as Ahmed Mohammed al-Shamrani, was shot dead by a sheriff's deputy.  Law enforcement officials combed through the suspect's belongings and social media accounts on Saturday while questioning six other Saudi nationals, at least some of them fellow students in the same Navy flight training program. Three of the Saudis were said to have taken cellphone video at the scene, according to a U.S. official familiar with investigation. The official spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss an ongoing criminal probe.  The FBI declined to ascribe a motive for the attack, and it was unclear Saturday whether any of the Saudis questioned had prior knowledge of the gunman's plans. Officials said they were investigating claims, first reported by the Associated Press, that al-Shamrani showed videos of previous mass shootings at a dinner party he hosted in the days before the attack.  There also was no official confirmation of a possible link between al-Shamrani and a Twitter account that surfaced Friday bearing the same name and containing a note in English criticizing U.S. support for Israel and accusing Washington of "funding crimes against Muslims."  The account, which was suspended by Twitter on Friday, did not express an allegiance to any particular extremist group. Law enforcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI HUNTS MISSING SAUDIS IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7768107/FBI-hunt-missing-Saudi-soldiers-Pensacola-Naval-base-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Mohammed Saeed al-Shamrani, 21, killed three and wounded 12 others in the attack before he was shot dead by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi airman radicalized before U.S. Navy base attack...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191207213105-2bnc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORIDA-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Saudi airman may have become radicalized before U.S. Navy base attack</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
