<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>IOWA: Pete gets ovation in most conservative county...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jan/18/pete-buttigieg-iowa-conservative-election-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His campaign feared hostility in Iowa’s most conservative county. But the local response told a different story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MILITARY TO JAM GPS SIGNALS ACROSS EAST COAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/breaking-military-to-jam-gps-signals-across-east-coast-through-jan-24th/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI asserting eminent domain to seize night vision devices from distributors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show of force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/55b76221825a01f47f80f8ceade7e54d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Police are scouring the internet for clues about plans for mayhem, workers are putting up chain link holding pens around Virginia's picturesque Capitol Square, and one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Drives Into Path Of Oncoming Vehicle To Test Faith; Waiting For 'Calling From God'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/17/police-pennsylvania-woman-drives-into-path-of-oncoming-vehicle-while-waiting-for-calling-from-god/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The online court docket indicated her $50,000 bail was revoked Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial to Open With Questions Unanswered on Ukraine 'Favor'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-trial-open-questions-unanswered-110002915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- “Read the transcript!”That’s the rallying cry of President Donald Trump and supporters who say he did nothing wrong in the Ukraine impeachment saga.Democrats countered that the White House readout of Trump’s call with Ukraine’s president offers strong evidence of his guilt. The key line</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron evacuated from theater as protesters block exits over pension reforms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-evacuated-paris-theatre-protesters-113311111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel Macron’s Friday night theatre outing came to a disagreeable end when police had to rescue the president and his wife from dozens of protesters furious over his pension reforms. Demonstrators besieged the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord, where the company led by Peter Brook, the British director,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of tinder box rally, Trump says Constitution under attack...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200118102620-lzn6k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-GUNS/RALLY (PIX):Ahead of tinder box Virginia gun rally, Trump says Constitution under attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People have less sex after Pope visits...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10766384/less-sex-after-pope-visits-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE have less sex after the Pope visits a town, a study suggests. Abortion rates usually fall by a fifth for up to 14 months after a papal visit but the birth rate stays the same. So either coup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump impeachment, starring Bill Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/18/trump-clinton-impeachment-100691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is the one fighting to keep his job, but it can feel like the entire country is reliving the last presidential impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure grows to call Rudy associate as witness...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478883-parnas-pressure-grows-on-senate-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure is growing on Senate Republicans to call Lev Parnas, an associate of President Trump’s personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani, to testify in the impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secretive Company That Might End Privacy as We Know It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/18/the-secretive-company-that-might-end-privacy-as-we-know-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until recently, Hoan Ton-That’s greatest hits included an obscure iPhone game and an app that let people put Donald Trump’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'DOLITTLE' A DUD... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/bad-boys-for-life-dolittle-1917-weekend-box-office-1202833726/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, SATURDAY AM: w/chart When it comes to releasing a long-delayed sequel, or rebooting an old popular franchise, it’s risky business. Yes, sometimes, there’s slam dunks like Juras…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaf man sues porn site over lack of closed captioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/01/16/pornhub-sued-class-action-deaf-demand-closed-captioning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub just got sued because it lacks closed captioning in videos, making it hard to watch for the deaf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff takes on Trump, calling him 'erratic hothead.' Now he's feeling the heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/adam-schiff-takes-on-trump-calling-him-an-erratic-hothead-now-hes-feeling-the-heat/ar-BBZ3GVd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury brings back the 20-year bond to pay for the ballooning deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/treasury-brings-back-the-20-year-bond-to-pay-for-the-ballooning-deficit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury Department is issuing a 20-year bond for the first time in 34 years to help pay for the ballooning $1 trillion dollar budget deficit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's shortest man dies at 27...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worlds-shortest-man-dies-nepal-27-172725938.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's shortest man who could walk, as verified by Guinness World Records, died Friday at a hospital in Nepal, his family said. Khagendra Thapa Magar, who measured 67.08 centimetres (2 feet 2.41 inches), died of pneumonia at a hospital in Pokhara, 200 kilometres from Kathmandu, where he lived</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 more linked to neo-Nazi group arrested in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be1f537775593d49415a008f2639f39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three men linked to a violent white supremacist group known as The Base were charged with conspiring to kill members of a militant anti-fascist group, police in Georgia announced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein jury seated after prosecutors accuse defense of excluding white women...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200117210846-qqnzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-HARVEY WEINSTEIN/JURY (PIX):Weinstein jury seated after prosecutors accuse defense of excluding white women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother and daughter 'psychics' get prison time in fraud case...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/crime/fl-ne-broward-pysching-sentenced-for-million-dollar-fraud-20200117-zj7edl5yoveotog5qmigyxcgee-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They claimed they were “white squaw Cherokee Indian” spiritual healers, and used eggs filled with snake embryos to convince their victims that they were cursed, authorities say. But on Friday, the mother and daughter pair of Annie Marie Vwanawick, 74, and April Miller, 44, both of Broward, were sentenced to prison for defrauding two victims with their spiritual scams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon continues training Saudis on military bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/extreme-vetting-trump-administration-continue-training-saudis-military-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to screen airline passengers from China for new illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e42ddf6414d214a8d86a8ba153d82a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Three U.S. airports will screen passengers arriving from central China for a new virus that has sickened dozens, killed two and prompted worries about an international outbreak,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DREAM TEAM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a0f6c7518ce72e63374ddc9e01eeb18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has assembled a made-for-TV legal team for his Senate trial that includes household names like Ken Starr, the prosecutor whose investigation two decades...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Manhattan's Skyscrapers Are Empty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/01/american-housing-has-gone-insane/605005/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately half of the luxury-condo units that have come onto the market in the past five years are still unsold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Violence Surging In Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/17/794510796/why-gun-violence-is-surging-in-toronto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, more than 760 people were shot. Canada has tighter gun laws than in the U.S., and officials and gun control advocates are trying to figure out why the surge is happening and how to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg assembling fundraising experts to recruit wealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/bloomberg-makes-push-to-recruit-wealthy-donors-but-not-to-take-their-money.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of the Bloomberg team's targets are backing other candidates, but the effort could potentially put pressure on the donors to withhold funds from other contenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New software flaw could further delay BOEING MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/new-software-flaw-could-further-delay-boeings-737-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Boeing Co. has identified a new software flaw in the grounded 737 Max that will require additional work, possibly further delaying the plane's return to service. The company alerted the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration and is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Considers Changes to Law Banning Overseas Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-considers-changes-to-law-banning-overseas-bribes/ar-BBZ46FI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President regrets wading into 'that f***ing vaping thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-hhs-azar-vaping-policy-14475d0f-07db-4e33-ac25-b512562ab419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's one of Trump's few health care accomplishments heading into 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style legend Jean-Paul Gaultier retires from fashion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jean-paul-gaultier-retire-fashion-designer-185054835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French designer Jean-Paul Gaultier shocked the fashion world Friday by saying his next Paris haute couture show will be his last. "Rest assured, haute couture will continue with a new concept," said the designer, who made pop history by putting Madonna in a conical bra, invented the "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two iPhones or the privacy of billions: Why APPLE vs. FBI matters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/two-iphones-or-privacy-billions-why-apple-vs-fbi-matters-n1118001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI's efforts to push Apple to unlock phones have caused alarm among technology industry veterans and academics who see a broader effort to reduce privacy and introduce digital back doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rolls back Michelle Obama lunch program on her birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/policy/article239402203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dems go to war with FACEBOOK, Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/tech/democrats-facebook-war/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few years ago, then President Barack Obama was appearing at dinner and on stage with Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg, and Nancy Pelosi was heaping praise on COO Sheryl Sandberg for "inspiring women across the world to believe in themselves."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes to consider faithless electors, ahead of 2020 vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6f415b0b39decbd05f58ec5a08195e79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Friday it will decide ahead of the 2020 election whether presidential electors are bound to support the popular vote winner in their states or can opt for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX name dropped...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/entertainment/ct-ent-disney-fox-rename-20200117-ytbvfutodrdd3jc3ww5uk7ax2q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20th Century Fox film studio will become 20th Century Studios, and Fox Searchlight Pictures will become simply Searchlight Pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/new-virus-prompts-u-s-health-officials-begin-airport-screenings-n1117911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screening will only take place at the airports with direct or indirect flights from Wuhan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avalanche Reported Near Lake Tahoe; Several Missing...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/17/alpine-meadows-placer-county-avalanche-people-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several people are unaccounted for after an avalanche at Alpine Meadows on Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why SKoreans flipping out over US ambassador's mustache...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/harry-harris-mustache-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might just be the most bizarre criticism of a US ambassador in recent memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Census kicks off in remote Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be84b23d6c8fd94e6fb935bd4fecb257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — The 2020 Census kicks off Tuesday in remote Alaska. U.S. Census Bureau Director Steven Dillingham will be there to conduct the first count in the Bering Sea community of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2020/01/17/coronavirus-us-airports-screening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new virus has sickened dozens in China, and two people have died. Cases have spread to Thailand and Japan. There are no known cases in the U.S., but health experts are concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure building on vulnerable senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/impeachment-trial-resolution-mcconnell-susan-collins/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It had been weeks since the House of Representatives passed articles of impeachment, and back home senators were getting pushed on what they believed a fair impeachment trial would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Considers Changes to Law Banning Overseas Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-17/white-house-considers-changes-to-law-banning-overseas-bribes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China birthrate hits lowest level since country was founded...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/china-birthrate-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's birthrate in 2019 hit its lowest level since the founding of the People's Republic in 1949, according to official statistics released by Beijing Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorite or Volcano? New Clues to Dinosaurs' Demise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meteorite-or-volcano-new-clues-to-the-dinosaurs-demise/ar-BBZ1Q3o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Starr Bashed Trump During Hearings, Praised Witnesses Against Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trumps-new-lawyer-panned-presidents-poor-judgement-on-impeachment-said-testimony-against-him-doesnt-look-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's new lawyer, former independent counsel Ken Starr, served as an analyst for Fox News during the House impeachment proceedings against the president. And in that role, he h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEWINKSY:  Are you f---ing kidding me?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/monica-lewinsky-ken-starr-senate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement that former independent counsel Ken Starr is joining President Donald Trump's impeachment defense team surprised many on Friday, but one person, apparently, had an especially notable reaction to the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem compares self to Manchester Arena bomber on new track...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/jan/17/eminem-manchester-arena-bomb-attack-salman-ramadan-abedi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relatives hit back at ‘disrespectful’ rapper over lyrics referring to terror attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>560-POUND ISIS fanatic dubbed 'Jabba the Jihadi ' is arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/268806/monstrous-40-stone-isis-jihadi-dubbed-jabba-the-hutt-is-arrested-sparking-stream-of-internet-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASSIVE 40-stone jihadi dubbed “Jabba the Jihadi” has been nicked by Iraqi forces— sparking a stream of hilarious internet memes. Hate preacher Abu Abdul Bari had to be loaded onto a flatbed truc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Woman burned in random bleach attack in NYC subway station...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/woman-becomes-target-of-unprovoked-bleach-attack-in-nyc-subway-station-police/2261025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 37-year-old woman was the victim of an unprovoked attack when another woman threw bleach at her face in a Manhattan subway station Thursday afternoon, police said. The woman was standing near the subway booth at 7th Avenue and West 14th Street when a 30-year-old woman threw liquid at her, police said. The victim suffered minor burns, according to the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can cast tie-breaking vote?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/history-shows-chief-justice-john-roberts-could-cast-tie-breaking-n1117506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief justice has offered no clues about how he would approach the question of witnesses, but judges typically rule in favor of allowing relevant testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline forces woman to take pregnancy test to stop 'birth tourism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article239389563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaf man sues porn site over lack of closed captioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/report-deaf-man-sues-pornhub-over-lack-of-closed-captioning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An adult video website is reportedly the target of a lawsuit over an alleged lack of closed captioning for its videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City struggles to keep street lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlantic-city-going-in-wrong-direction-hard-rock-ceo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hard Rock CEO Jim Allen said the company is willing to be part of the solution in Atlantic City but is not encouraged by recent developments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Might Ban Face Recognition From ALL Public Places...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453208/the-eu-might-ban-facial-recognition-tech-for-five-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasoning is that facial recognition tech is so new, yet rolling out so quickly, we simply can’t know all the risks and drawbacks associated with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Heiress Backs Bill That Would Tax DISNEY Over CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453156/abigail-disneys-new-crusade-fixing-the-ceo-to-worker-pay-gap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under California’s proposed tax rules, companies that make over $10 million in taxable income in the state would be liable for higher tax rates based on the pay disparity between the company’s regular employees and its CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Drone Swarms Over Colorado: Mysterious Objects Secret Military Craft?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/usaf-intelligence-expert-claims-drones-21287021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Mike Turber has suggested the mysterious drone swarms seen over Colorado and Nebraska may not be drones at all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW RATINGS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2020/01/16/rachel-maddow-ratings-largest-audience-ever-lev-parnas-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow’s exclusive sit-down with the controversial Lev Parnas delivered her eponymous MSNBC program’s largest audience ever on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's culture minister sparks outrage by echoing Goebbels...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-51149224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The minister uses parts of a speech by Nazi Germany's propaganda boss but calls it a coincidence.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
