<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell admitted Epstein DID have tapes of Trump, Clintons...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9270769/Ghislaine-Maxwell-admitted-Jeffrey-Epstein-DID-tapes-Donald-Trump-Clintons-2016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell appeared to admit Jeffrey Epstein was taping his famous friends, including Donald Trump and the Clintons, during a 2016 meeting with former CBS producer Ira Rosen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mr. Kitty' goes virtually to Washington...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-social-media-fee89914ac530675c0017a485b6aa8ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media movement that made a beloved icon of GameStop enthusiast Keith Gill continued to rally behind the YouTube personality known as Roaring Kitty as he testified to Congress on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands reportedly attempt to obtain easily forged vaccinated certificate...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/thousands-reportedly-attempt-to-obtain-easily-forged-vaccinated-certificate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Green Pass' uses a simple QR code to store inoculation status and personal information; Health Ministry says it will fine those with fake documents, issue more secure ones soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC guidance would keep 90% of schools at least partially closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/18/cdcs-classroom-guidance-would-keep-90percent-of-schools-at-least-partially-closed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new guidance would keep more than 90% of schools, including in almost all of the 50 largest counties in the country, from fully reopening, doctors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones' natural gas company 'hits jackpot'...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/02/17/texas-freeze-allows-jerry-jones-natural-gas-company-to-hit-jackpot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 4 million Texans have had no power during the historic winter weather experienced by the state this week. As of Wednesday night, 7 million in the state had water issues with either boil notices or no water at all. Fingers are pointing. Pipes are bursting. Homes are flooding. Grocery store shelves are [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax at Vatican? You might lose your job...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/italy-coronavirus-pandemic-rome-pope-francis-europe-f3214bfe787e783f8779d3f0fa9edfe8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican is taking Pope Francis’ pro-vaccine stance very seriously: Any Vatican employee who refuses to get a coronavirus shot without a valid medical reason risks being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames his kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/18/ted-cruz-cancun-power-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First spotted at an airport by a social media user who posted his photo, there was an immediate outcry overnight that a U.S. senator would travel out of the state amid the worst storm in many Texans' lifetimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Dems scramble to fight Newsom recall, close ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/18/california-democrats-newsom-recall-469795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But it may already be too late to convince the disorderly Democratic ranks to put aside their political differences and stand in unity with their embattled governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER In Standoff With India Over Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/17/968641246/twitter-in-standoff-with-indias-government-over-free-speech-and-local-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter blocked hundreds of accounts the Indian government said were inciting violence. Then it unblocked them. Now it's stuck between Indian law and defending free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolly Parton asks TN not to put her statue at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dolly-parton-tennessee-no-statue-capitol-ee80ab68ca93f29d5f600b99008fadfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Dolly Parton is asking Tennessee lawmakers to withdraw a bill that would erect a statue of her on the Capitol grounds in Nashville. “Given all that is going on in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka WILL NOT challenge Rubio for Senate seat in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/539407-ivanka-trump-wont-challenge-rubio-for-his-senate-seat-in-2022-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump will not challenge Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Fla.) for his Senate seat in 2022, a source familiar with the matter confirmed to The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Earth its quietest in decades as lockdowns reduce seismic noise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218132810-5xify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambient noise generated by human activity such as travel and machinery dropped by 50% last year, researchers find</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFINING BATTLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218154054-m3g6j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIA-MEDIA/FACEBOOK-PUBLISHERS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Time to get tough with 'bully' Facebook, UK lawmaker and publishers say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans told to ration power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218150220-2du16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/MEXICO-LNG (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-'Switch off lightbulbs:' president asks Mexicans to ration power as Texas limits fuel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA COVID TOLL NEARS 500,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218142847-768v9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TEXAS-FUNERAL HOME (PIX, TV):WIDER IMAGE-'I just ask God to help me': Texas funeral home crushed by death as U.S. COVID toll nears 500,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/did-you-bring-home-covid-spouse-sues-company-for-infection/ar-BB1dNsvg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge is weighing what she called a first-of-its-kind lawsuit that would hold an employer responsible for a worker’s spouse getting sick with Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Ten May Have to Switch Occupations Post Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/one-of-ten-in-us-may-have-to-switch-occupations-post-pandemic/ar-BB1dNyqj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- One out of every ten U.S. workers -- about 17 million, all told -- will likely be forced to leave their jobs and take up new occupations by 2030 as Covid-19’s after-effects destroy huge swathes of low-paying positions in a labor market that was primed for disruption before the pandemic. Women, minorities, the young and the less educated will probably be the hardest hit by what consultant firm McKinsey &amp; Co. foresees in a new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky city's plan to build church with public money raises objections...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/counties/woodford-county/article249279410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Versailles plans to use public funds to build a worship center for a local church that would double as an emergency shelter, sparking objections from a national atheist group and concern among local farmland preservationists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE MOVES ON TO 6G!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-hiring-engineers-develop-6g-110000382.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. launched its first iPhones with 5G wireless speeds a few months ago. Now it’s looking to start work on sixth-generation cellular connectivity, or 6G, indicating it wants to be a leader in the technology rather than relying on other companies.The Cupertino, California-based company this week posted job ads seeking wireless system research engineers for current and next-generation networks. The listings are for positions at Apple’s offices in Silicon Valley and San Diego, where the company works on wireless technology development and chip design.“You will have the unique and rewarding opportunity to craft next generation wireless technology that will have deep impact on future Apple products,“ according to the job announcement. “In this role you will be at the center of a cutting-edge research group responsible for creating next generation disruptive radio access technologies over the next decade.”People hired for the positions will “research and design next generation (6G) wireless communication systems for radio access networks” and “participate in industry/academic forums passionate about 6G technology.” Industry watchers don’t expect 6G to roll out until about 2030, but the job listings indicate Apple wants to be involved at the earliest stages in the development of the new technology. A company spokeswoman declined to comment.Read more: Apple Starts Work on Its Own Cellular Modem, Chip Chief SaysApple’s current swath of iPhones use 5G modems designed by Qualcomm Inc. While the company launched its first 5G devices at an opportune time, several phone makers beat it to market and Apple relied heavily on Qualcomm for connection to the new wireless network, which dramatically improves the amount and speed of data that consumers can download. In order to get 5G into the latest iPhones, Apple settled a contentious lawsuit with the San Diego-based chipmaker. Apple’s early involvement in 6G research and design indicates it won’t wait around for the next major advancement.Late last year, Apple joined an alliance of companies working on standards for 6G and other next-generation cellular technologies. The standards and timing for 6G are still loosely defined, but some analysts say the technology could enable speeds more than 100 times faster than 5G.The job listings are another signal of Apple’s continued push into developing more technology in-house. The company has designed main processors for the iPhone and iPad and last year expanded that effort to the Mac. It has also ramped up work on its own custom screens and camera technologies, in addition to wireless chips for AirPods, Apple Watch and precise location data.Apple last year started developing its first custom modem, the chip that allows phones to connect to wireless networks. In a town hall meeting with employees in December, Johny Srouji, Apple’s custom technology and chip head, said that “long-term strategic investments like these are a critical part of enabling our products and making sure we have a rich pipeline of innovative technologies for our future.”Though Apple is laying the groundwork to be a key player in 6G, it has much work ahead to take full advantage of 5G, a technology in its infancy. The company hasn’t expanded 5G to other devices like the Apple Watch and iPad, and it sells multiple iPhones that use older 4G technology. It’s likely that Apple’s first modem will be for 5G connectivity.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Flees to Cancun Amid Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ted-cruz-airport-power-crisis-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz flew to Cancun, Mexico, with his family this week as Texas dealt with a winter storm that left millions without power, a Republican source confirmed to Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dole reveals he has stage 4 lung cancer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/former-sen-bob-dole-reveals-he-has-stage-4-lung-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, the 97-year-old former Republican senator and 1996 presidential candidate, announced Thursday that he is battling lung cancer. “Recently, I was diagnosed with stage four lung cancer. My f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas congresswoman leads renewed push to study slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/texas-congresswoman-leads-renewed-push-to-study-slavery-reparations/article_ca9c3143-32d6-51b5-af1e-a2aa24905b76.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — U.S. Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee of Texas is renewing a 30-year congressional push to establish a commission that would study the impact of slavery and possible reparations for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Caffeine Changes Brain Structure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/caffeine-brain-structure-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings reveal that even consuming caffeine for a short period of time can change the volume of gray matter in the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans may be BANNED from entering UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9273329/UK-add-red-list-countries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers arriving from the US could soon be added to the UK's 'red list' of countries as officials consider the risk of new variants from the two countries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lopez Obrador says Mexico will not retaliate over gas export ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218135213-636a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/MEXICO-DIPLOMACY (URGENT):Lopez Obrador says Mexico will not retaliate over Texas's gas export ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Flees to Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/02/18/barbs-fly-at-ted-cruz-for-heading-to-cancun-as-millions-in-texas-freeze-without-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – With 3 million Texans shivering in the dark, Sen. Ted Cruz jetted off to Cancun with his family, outed instantly by fellow vacationers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singer Luke Combs apologizes for past use of Confederate flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/entertainment/luke-combs-apology-confederate-flag-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luke Combs has issued an apology for past use of the Confederate flag in his performances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Delete'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/ex-australian-facebook-ceo-urges-users-to-delete-the-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former chief executive of Facebook’s Australian business urged users to delete the social network’s app in response to Mark Zuckerberg’s “sad” decision to block ne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/photos-of-ted-cruz-allegedly-fleeing-to-cancun-during-texas-arctic-blast-disaster-spark-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of Ted Cruz emerged on Twitter that claim to show the Texas Senator flying to Cancun, Mexico to escape the brutal and dangerous cold spell causing blackouts in his home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/did-you-bring-home-covid-spouse-sues-company-for-infection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/17/texas-food-supply-power-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texans running low on food are finding empty grocery store shelves. Food pantries are running out of supplies. And the freeze has wiped out substantial portions of the state's citrus and vegetable crops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA rover hurtles toward historic landing attempt on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/perseverance-mars-rover-landing-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perseverance's landing caps a decade of preparation by Mars teams worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House announces sweeping immigration bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/politics/biden-immigration-legislation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House announced a sweeping immigration bill Thursday that would create an eight-year path to citizenship for millions of immigrants already in the country and provide a faster track for undocumented immigrants brought to the US as children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers facing off with GAMESTOP saga's key players...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maxine-waters-financial-services-media-social-media-36042603229c758b74008bb69dcaafca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawmakers in Washington are digging into the GameStop saga at a congressional hearing. The episode has been portrayed as a victory of the little guy over Wall Street...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNERS-LEE: Could render internet unworkable...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/australia-internet-law-tim-berners-lee-b1803988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning comes amid rising tensions between Australian law makers, news publishers and tech giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irregular sleep schedules connected to bad moods...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-irregular-bad-moods-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An irregular sleep schedule can increase a person's risk of depression over the long term as much as getting fewer hours of sleep overall, or staying up late most nights, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Flees to Cancun?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ted-cruz-accused-flying-cancun-texas-power-outages-photo-goes-viral-1570118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not yet clear if the Republican has left the country as some photos on social media have suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE PAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/in-the-fight-for-tech-giants-to-pay-for-news-google-relented-facebook-didn-e2-80-99t/ar-BB1dLRh5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The search giant struck a deal with Rupert Murdoch's media empire to pay for some of its content, including paywalled stories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALENT ON LOAN FROM GOD</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/rush-limbaugh-dead-talk-radio-conservative-icon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rush Limbaugh, the monumentally influential media icon who transformed talk radio and politics in his decades behind the microphone, helping shape the modern-day Republican Party, died Wednesday morning at the age of 70 after a battle with lung cancer, his family announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI PROBING...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/cuomo-investigation-fbi-covid-nursing-homes-15957401.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation by the FBI and the U.S. attorney's office is examining, at least in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90% of NYC restaurants can't make rent payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/report-nine-out-of-ten-of-nyc-restaurants-could-not-afford-rent-in-december</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers have only worsened since June 2020, when 80 percent of restaurants could not pay rent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  FACEBOOK blocks users from viewing and sharing news in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/facebook-blocks-australians-news-access-8557e9b4890b002921aa4f0738b13ea7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Facebook announced Thursday it has blocked Australians from viewing and sharing news on the platform because of proposed laws in the country to make digital giants pay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outages linger for millions as another icy storm looms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/100-million-americans-more-ice-snow-404012f8d8885259968b8d37b13899d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Millions of Americans endured another frigid day without electricity or heat in the aftermath of a deadly winter storm as utility crews raced to restore power before another...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin hospital without water, heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/story/news/2021/02/17/winter-weather-texas-st-davids-medical-center-austin-without-water-heat/6791735002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. David's South Austin Medical Center is suffering from a loss of water pressure and heat, officials said Wednesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSH DEAD IN PALM BEACH...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2021/02/17/rush-limbaugh-conservative-radio-host-has-died-lung-cancer-70/5998621002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rush Limbaugh, talk titan and Republican kingmaker, died at age 70 of lung cancer at his Palm Beach County home in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Singular figure in American media...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/02/17/business/media/rush-limbaugh-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a following of 15 million and a divisive style of mockery, grievance and denigrating language, he was a force in reshaping American conservatism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL REVIEW:  Voice Like No Other...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/02/farewell-rush-limbaugh-a-voice-like-no-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His death is a powerful loss to conservatism. His life was an inspiration and a lighthouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICA'S REAL ANCHORMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9271027/Rush-Limbaugh-dies-aged-70-lung-cancer-battle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rush Limbaugh, the radio icon and 'voice of American conservatism', died on Wednesday, aged 70, following his year-long battle with lung cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk radio pioneer dominated decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rush-limbaugh-talk-radio-radio-conservatism-us-news-5ee31846669381b16696c5c1306dc7de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rush Limbaugh called himself a truth detector, doctor of democracy, lover of mankind, all-around good guy and harmless fuzz ball, titles his legions of followers embraced as he boomed from their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo nursing home problem getting worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/andrew-cuomo-s-nursing-home-problem-is-getting-worse/ar-BB1dLXZN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York governor’s threat against a Queens Democrat wasn’t his worst move on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White UK govt worker sues over black female's higher salary...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/17/uk-man-sues-over-black-female-colleague-getting-higher-pay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior civil servant is suing the British government for sex and race discrimination because a black female colleague is paid $72,000 a year more than him, according to reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water supply at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/17/texas-water-boil-notices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After enduring multiple days of freezing temperatures, dripping faucets to prevent frozen pipes from bursting, cities across the state warned residents on Wednesday that water levels are dangerously low and may be unsafe to drink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politics Seeping Into Daily Life -- and Ruining Everything...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/17/politics-is-seeping-into-our-daily-life-and-ruining-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are choosing jobs, brands, and friends for partisan reasons, say researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis threatens to pull vax from communities that criticize...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-ron-desantis-vaccine-politics-20210217-cgew27q23fhknh7rpr3h4sf5dy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;I wouldn’t be complaining,&amp;quot; Gov. Ron DeSantis said Wednesday to officials in Manatee County who criticized him for providing special access to COVID-19 vaccines to two wealthy ZIP codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many top NBA players hesitant to promote...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/30918396/sources-many-nba-players-hesitant-promote-coronavirus-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many top NBA players are hesitant to promote coronavirus vaccines, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYTONA 500 least viewed in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/17/nascars-2021-daytona-500-was-the-least-viewed-race-in-its-history-following-rain-delay.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nearly six-hour rain delay impacted Sunday's Daytona 500 which resulted in the lowest viewed event in the race's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals at primate sanctuary freeze to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/animals-at-texas-primate-sanctuary-freeze-to-death-amid-catastrophic-power-outages/ar-BB1dLUD0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A chimpanzee, several monkeys, lemurs and other animals have died after a Texas primate sanctuary lost power amid a brutal winter storm pounding the southern U.S. this week. Staff and volunteers at Primarily Primates were trying to evacuate the facility when they found about a dozen dead animals, the San Antonio-area nonprofit said Wednesday. One of them was 58-year-old Violet, the sanctuary’s oldest chimp.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
