<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch's SUN, UK's Biggest Paper for Decades, Now Worth Zero...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/murdoch-s-sun-u-k-s-biggest-paper-for-decades-now-worth-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp. wrote down the value of its once high-flying Sun title to zero, underscoring the dramatic decline in Britain’s newspaper industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400,000 without power in Puerto Rico after fire, cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/557957-400000-without-power-in-puerto-rico-after-fire-cyberattack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were at least 400,000 people without power in Puerto Rico on Thursday night as the company that took over the island’s power transmissions has been faced with fire and cyberattack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details of torture, cover-ups in China internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/new-details-torture-cover-ups-china-s-internment-camps-revealed-n1270014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese officials spent days burning documents after government information leaked to global media exposed conditions in the camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motor neurone disease linked to 'vigorous exercise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-57431412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular and strenuous exercise can increase the risk of MND in people who are vulnerable, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden wants world to know America back. But has everyone moved on?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/g-7-summit-biden-looks-reassert-american-leadership-wary-weary-n1270278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's election has seen "a dramatic shift in America's international image," Pew said, with public opinion rebounding in a dozen key countries since he became president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-thirds of millennials have homebuyer regrets, new survey says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2021/06/11/millennials-facing-financial-and-physical-regrets-after-buying-homes/7594826002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent Bankrate survey found that 64% of millennials are facing regrets after buying a home, with the main factors being financial and physical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Op-eds in Chinese state tabloid slammed U.S. policy. Author works at Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/op-eds-in-a-chinese-state-tabloid-slammed-us-policy-the-author-works-at-the-pentagon/ar-AAKWfp2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Franz Gayl, a celebrated whistleblower and former Marine, is being investigated after attacking American policy on Taiwan in a Chinese government mouthpiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC to hold 'emergency meeting' on heart inflammation after vax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/557944-cdc-to-hold-emergency-meeting-on-heart-inflammation-after-covid-19-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An advisory panel of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention will hold an emergency meeting on June 18 to discuss rare reports of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of delta variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611100743-8vhsc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SWEDEN-VACCINE:Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of COVID delta variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowout Year for CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/11/behold-the-highest-paid-c-e-o-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to get the DealBook newsletter in your inbox each day? Sign up here. Paying (a lot) for performance Six</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 inmates escape federal lockups in 18 months; Half not caught...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-prisons-prison-breaks-business-c1979d6ad6e7b3531968dab0e61eb22d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Over the past 18 months, 29 prisoners have escaped from federal lockups across the U.S. — and nearly half still have not been caught. At some of the institutions, doors are left unlocked, security cameras are broken and officials sometimes don't notice an inmate is missing for hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars to Cans Getting Pricey as Aluminum Costs Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/cars-to-cans-risk-getting-pricey-as-japan-s-aluminum-costs-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything from a can of beer to an electric vehicle is likely to get pricier with negotiations over aluminum fees in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At El Salvador Bitcoin Beach, glimpse of crypto economy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-el-salvador-bitcoin-lifestyle-technology-d30c52b39e16ef49e4b6342fdc885c92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL ZONTE, El Salvador (AP) — After El Salvador’s congress made the bitcoin legal tender this week, eyes turned to this rural fishing village on the Pacific coast. Known to surfers for its pounding waves, El Zonte has had the cryptocurrency in its economy for the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: LAMBORGHINI Sells Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/lamborghini-is-almost-sold-out-this-year-as-pandemic-gloom-lifts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lamborghini said it’s almost sold out for the year as an easing pandemic unleashes a free-spending attitude among consumers confined to their homes for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer Young Men in Labor Force. More Living at Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/fewer-young-men-are-in-the-labor-force-more-are-living-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 25- to 34-year-olds, the two trends add up to a failure to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law enforcement struggles to recruit since killing of Floyd...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-george-floyd-racial-injustice-only-on-ap-coronavirus-pandemic-d434cc8023875ddb996abb7df0a7bc44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement agencies across the country experienced a wave of retirements and departures and are struggling to recruit the next generation of police officers in the year since George Floyd was killed by a cop .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records of aides and family members also shared...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-donald-trump-politics-ap-top-news-ca-state-wire-5b6f6bf0daf8bccf106a90d2ff52686c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department under former President Donald Trump seized data from the accounts of at least two members of the House Intelligence Committee in 2018 as part of an aggressive crackdown on leaks related to the Russia investigation and other national security matters, according to a committee official and two people familiar with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidenomics not working?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/latest-economic-figures-shows-bidenomics-is-not-working/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden Administration keeps insisting inflation is “transient,” but there are now real signs inflation is here and possibly for the long haul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas will build its own border barriers, governor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/10/greg-abbott-texas-will-build-its-own-border-barrie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If President Biden won’t build a border wall, then Texas will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of his era draws near...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-israel-middle-east-government-and-politics-9785d2410bf55bce06b893b19b3e6234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — In what appear to be the final days of his historic 12-year rule, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is not leaving the political stage quietly. The longtime leader is accusing his opponents of betraying their voters, and some have needed special security protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Bitcoin Gathering Was Hot Spot, Attendees Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/miami-bitcoin-gathering-was-a-covid-hot-spot-attendees-say/ar-AAKVjQ3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency podcaster Luke Martin said he caught Covid-19 during the Bitcoin 2021 conference in Miami last week, one of the biggest events to take place in the U.S. since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Richest Face Squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/worlds-richest-face-tax-squeeze-after-40percent-run-up-in-fortunes/ar-AAKTlik</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos has the resources to launch himself into space. Elon Musk does, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rates of anxiety and depression among college students soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Rates-of-anxiety-and-depression-among-college-16239104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College students are feeling more anxious and depressed as they sleep less and spend more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER GIVES SECOND CHANCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-toobin-returns-to-cnn-gets-grilled-about-masturbating-on-zoom-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Toobin’s had been aggressively lobbying CNN boss Jeff Zucker to allow the legal analyst back on-air, two people familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  Two passengers on first 100% vaccinated cruise in North America test positivefor Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3057850/celebrity-millennium-passengers-vaccinated-america-covid-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO passengers onboard the first fully-vaccinated cruise ship in North America have tested positive for coronavirus. The passengers, who shared a room on the Celebrity Millennium, tested positive d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Ford, 78, begins filming fifth 'INDIANA JONES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3043909/harrison-ford-indiana-jones-films-fifth-blockbuster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISON Ford has still got it as Indiana Jones aged 78 — as he begins filming the fifth blockbuster in the series. He wore the familiar fedora and leather jacket on set in Grosmont, North Yorks. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos rocket mocked for looking like giant penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3043422/amazon-jeff-bezos-space-mission-todger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON billionaire Jeff Bezos’ space mission was met with ridicule yesterday — because people think his rocket is shaped like a giant todger. Online jokers poked fun at the Blue Origin New Shepard …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man going to prison for beheading bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-gets-prison-sentence-for-beheading-bear-on-reservation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has sentenced a man to 15 months in prison for killing and then beheading a 700-pound black bear on an Indian reservation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans picking your nose...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-bans-nose-picking-spanking-24279936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hugely popular Chinese social media platform WeChat, which is heavily regulated by state authorities, has published a list of more than 70 "common violations" and "indecency," including nose picking and "spanking games"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD Federal Taxes, Spending and Deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-spending-and-deficit-all-set-records-through-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set new records in the taxes it collected, the spending it engaged in and the deficit it ran through the first eight months of fiscal 2021 (October through May), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida city bans gambling amid prospects of casino...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/557824-florida-city-bans-gambling-amid-prospects-of-trump-owned-casino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Doral in Florida’s Miami-Dade County voted unanimously on Wednesday to officially ban gambling and casinos in the city, potentially putting in jeopardy reported plans for former President Trump's Do</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL OR ARMS?</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/06/10/iranian-warship-could-be-bringing-millions-of-gallons-of-oil-to-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former oil-tanker the Iranian Navy converted into a warship could be carrying millions of gallons of fuel to Venezuela in a ploy to get around U.S. sanctions, according to photos that emerged on Persian social media. On Thursday, undated photos of IRIN Makran show the ship, designed to carry around 3 million of gallons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Giant IHEART: 'We Are Looking at Only Diverse Hires'...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/business/rob-shimshock/media-giant-iheart-we-are-looking-only-diverse-hires-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An executive producer at America's largest owner of radio stations advertised a job Thursday by stating "we are looking at only diverse hires at this time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah's Ark replica faces dilemma of biblical proportions...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/noahs-ark-replica-faces-costly-dilemma-of-biblical-proportions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This ark might need a miracle to get back home. A replica of Noah’s Ark has been stranded in the United Kingdom for a year and a half and his facing $700-a-day fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms 1st Muslim American federal judge in US history...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-confirms-1st-muslim-american-federal-judge-us/story?id=78206834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zahid Quraish is the first Muslim American federal judge to be confirmed by the United States Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Detects Suicidal Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/app-suicide-risk-sound-of-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Carol Espy-Wilson says the coordination of someone's speech gestures reflects their mental health status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNGER GAMES:  Zuckerberg goes wild boar hunting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9674091/Zuckerberg-seen-camo-carrying-bow-arrows-Hawaii-danger-hike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg and his wife Priscilla own property in Hawaii and have plans to expand on it to create a compound-like home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd FDA expert resigns over controversial Alzheimer's drug decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/10/third-member-of-fda-expert-committee-resigns-over-controversial-alzheimers-therapy-decision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kesselheim wrote that the approval of Biogen’s Aduhelm “was probably the worst drug approval decision in recent U.S. history.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unanswered 'JEOPARDY!' question: Who's the new host?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-b15ea28c004f905a24c0a8936f7797df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — “Jeopardy!” needed a host, and Lucille Ball had an enthusiastic suggestion for creator Merv Griffin: The smooth-voiced, debonair emcee of the “High Rollers” game show. That was 1984.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory water rules hit Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Santa-Clara-Bay-Area-water-restrictions-drought-16235537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is sinking into a drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt for current year hits record $2.1 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-00d83a1898855edb9abcde733b97c158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. budget deficit hit a record $2.06 trillion through the first eight months of this budget year as coronavirus relief programs drove spending to all-time highs. The shortfall this year is 9.7% higher than the $1.88 trillion deficit run up over the same period a year ago, the Treasury Department said Thursday in its monthly budget report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toobin Returns to CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-jeffrey-toobin-returns-to-cnn-to-break-silence-on-moronic-and-indefensible-zoom-masturbation-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief legal analyst Jeffrey Toobin has returned to the network following a 8-month absence after being caught masturbating during a Zoom call with his colleagues from the New Yorker. In his return segment to the network, Toobin was confronted by CNN Newsroom anchor Alisyn Camerota — who summarized the events that led to his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has been 'miserable in therapy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9674023/Jeffrey-Toobin-CNN-months-exposing-Zoom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Toobin was fired from his longtime writing gig at the New Yorker magazine last October after he exposed himself to colleagues during the video call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College linebacker accused of beating man to death over TINDER catfishing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/virginia-tech-linebacker-isimemen-etute-accused-of-fatally-beating-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman Virginia Tech linebacker charged with murder told cops he fatally beat a man – breaking every bone in his face – for catfishing him on Tinder, prosecutors said. Isimemen David Etute, 18,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, CLIVE! GELDOF PLANS COVID LIVE AID CONCERT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/live-aid-set-comeback-battle-24293459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE Global gig Live Aid could be set to make a huge comeback to help combat coronavirus, as Sir Bob Geldof has dropped a huge hint that he is making plans for its return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA breached -- game source code, tools stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/10/tech/electronic-arts-hack/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers have broken into the systems of Electronic Arts, one of the world's biggest video game publishers, and stolen source code used in company games, a spokesperson confirmed to CNN Business on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penthouse sales sky-high in NYC again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/gimme-we-hear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gotham penthouse sky pads are having a moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More kids go down 'deep, dark tunnel.' Docs still can't predict who is at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/10/as-more-kids-get-long-covid-doctors-still-cant-predict-who-is-at-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More children and adolescents are experiencing chronic symptoms after Covid-19 even as the pandemic ebbs in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How primates aid fight against Covid in Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610155949-ic1vp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PRIMATES (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-How primates are aiding the fight against COVID-19 in Louisiana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pursued wives of franchisees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/subways-cofounder-pursued-franchisees-wives-appeared-in-a-shirtless-calendar-and-had-a-secret-adopted-child/ar-AAKUSa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway's current problems are inextricable from the strategies co-founder Fred DeLuca used to build the chain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu pledges 'peaceful transition of power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/netanyahu-trump-transition-power-election-fraud-1cd7e7c6-6f25-4a26-98d0-f1e0f182e905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says he's facing "the fraud of the century."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pursued wives of franchisees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/subways-cofounder-pursued-franchisees-wives-appeared-in-a-shirtless-calendar-and-had-a-secret-adopted-child/ar-AAKUSa8?ocid=BingNewsSearch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway's current problems are inextricable from the strategies co-founder Fred DeLuca used to build the chain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid outbreak among staff at St Ives hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cornwalllive.com/news/cornwall-news/covid-outbreak-among-staff-st-5508053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cornwalllive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just around the corner, preparations are being made for world leaders to arrive in Cornwall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. general: China hiking military capability at 'very serious rate'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610125434-y5oef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/PENTAGON (URGENT):U.S. general: China hiking military capability at "very serious and sustained rate"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Explains Why So Little on $152 Billion Fortune!</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/06/elon-musk-react-propublica-billionaire-federal-income-tax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He responded to an initial ProPublica query with a lone punctuation mark: “?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON IN DANGER:  Mueller prosecutor says Manhattan DA may have 'insider' in Trump criminal case...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mueller-prosecutor-manhattan-district-attorney-insider-trump-criminal-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan prosecutors may have found their "insider" as a grand jury considers whether charges are warranted against former President Donald Trump, according to a top prosecutor in Robert Mueller's special counsel investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughing Gas Quickly Relieves Depression?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/laughing-gas-treat-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say small doses of laughing gas rapidly improve symptoms of depression in a single session for patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP, UP AND AWAY:  Inflation Fastest Since '08...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/prices-rose-5-percent-in-may-over-the-past-year-as-recovery-continues/ar-AAKUgFq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent crop of inflation figures are unlikely to rattle the Biden administration or Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading candidate for NYC mayor --  accused of living in NJ!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/emotional-eric-adams-says-he-lives-in-brooklyn-despite-owning-a-condo-in-fort-lee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams acknowledges that he must cross a bridge to get to City Hall from his primary residence, but it's the Brooklyn Bridge, not the George Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK issues dire economic warning for America...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/557743-deutsche-bank-issues-dire-economic-warning-for-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the U.S. economy descends into an inflation spiral like that experienced after World War II, we could be on the brink of excruciating economic pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians find new unity in struggle against Israel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/palestinians-unity-struggle-against-israel-220512358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israel-Hamas war has helped catalyze a newfound sense of Palestinian solidarity that could mark a new moment in the Middle East, activists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House antitrust panel introducing five anti-Big Tech bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house-antitrust-panel-expected-introduce-5-anti-big-tech-bills-monopoly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic chairman of the House antitrust panel is expected to introduce five bipartisan bills to rein in Big Tech platforms such as Amazon, Facebook, and Google through new anti-monopoly legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked ISIS gunman went from 'bed to bed' executing workers at Prince Harry's landmine charity...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3053851/gunman-execute-landmine-workers-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARKED ISIS gunman reportedly went “bed to bed” executing workers during the bloody attack on a British landmine charity backed by Prince Harry. Ten people were killed and 16 others wer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Castle where leaders are staying...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/travel/3053553/cornwall-g7-summit-tregenna-castle-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD leaders have headed to Cornwall this week for the G7 Summit, being hosted in the tiny village of Carbis Bay. Leaders from Canada, France, Germany, Italy, Japan, the UK and the US are to discu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fentanyl seizures skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fentanyl-seizures-texas-mexico-border-immigration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year, fentanyl seizures have jumped 800% in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming heat wave could push Phoenix, Vegas temps to 115&amp;#8457;...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/looming-heat-wave-could-push-phoenix-vegas-temps-to-115-f/960027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say temperatures will routinely reach well into the triple digits, with one desert location poised to make a run at 125 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Harris gets tough reviews over border on first foreign trip...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/politics/kamala-harris-biden-border-2024/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first six-ish months of Kamala Harris' time as vice president have, generally speaking, gone according to her plan. She's been a consistent messenger for President Joe Biden while learning the possibilities (and limitations) that come with being second-in-command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crosssings continue to soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/u-apprehensions-migrants-crossing-border-100038933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released data show that migrants were stopped 180,034 times across the southern border in May, nearly eight times the total a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing mask may go from symbol of responsibility to vulnerability...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wearing-mask-could-sign-caution-120034163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With California's full economic reopening days away, there remains one question in many people's minds: To mask, or not to mask?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
