<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Masked burglars steal $1M in jewelry from Lori Loughlin's LA home...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/15/lori-loughlin-mossimo-giannulli-home-burglary-robbed-1million-jewelry-stolen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lori Loughlin And Mossimo's Home Robbed, $1million In Jewelry Stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Size, growth rate of tumors weighed to determine care...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hospitals-postponing-thousands-of-surgeries-amid-onslaught-of-covid-and-other-patients/ar-AASNuA5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ raises stakes with rarely used sedition charges for Oath Keepers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/589831-justice-department-faces-challenges-with-oathkeepers-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seditious conspiracy charges brought by the Justice Department Thursday against the leader of the Oath Keepers and other members of the right-wing group signals the government is prepared to take on an ambitious fight to show that they joined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WTF' Crypto Coin Launch Immediately Devolves Into Chaos, Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93bqap/viral-wtf-crypto-coin-launch-immediately-devolves-into-chaos-pain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bots, volatility, and a referral system decried as a "Ponzi" marred the viral launch of a token called WTF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch royals to temporarily halt Golden Coach, following colonial criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/dutch-royal-family-golden-carriage-colonialism-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King Willem-Alexander has said the Dutch royal family will temporarily stop using the Golden Coach until "the Netherlands is ready," following criticism of colonial ties to the horse-drawn carriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's unvaccinated falling out of society...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/16/europe/europe-covid-unvaccinated-society-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The increasingly vast divide between Europe's two populations means that "underground communities" of unvaccinated people have taken root.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-year-old dies after fentanyl overdose at school...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/16/connecticut-student-dies-after-fentanyl-overdose-at-sports-and-medical-science-academy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seventh-grader had been listed in “grave condition” at a hospital after he collapsed in the gymnasium at the Sports and Medical Science Academy in Hartford on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu negotiating plea deal in corruption trial...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/netanyahu-negotiating-plea-deal-corruption-trial-82293466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is negotiating a plea deal in his corruption case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing reports 1st omicron case ahead of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-winter-olympics-sports-health-beijing-f9fb6ea315985b81223697fc0760c401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Beijing has reported its first local omicron infection, according to state media, weeks before the Winter Olympic Games are due to start. The infected person lives and works in the city’s northwestern district of Haidian and had no travel history outside of Beijing for the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJOKOVIC DEPORTED...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/sport/tennis/australian-open/live-novak-djokovic-court-hearing-updates-result-of-visa-cancellation/news-story/5f941dd26abe1171e4a7f2e63644b05b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Novak Djokovic is understood to be boarding his flight and is set to leave Australia after the 20-time grand slam champion’s legal team failed to overturn Immigration Minister Alex Hawke’s decision to cancel his visa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLS embarrass Belichick, pitch 'perfect' game...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/bills-become-the-first-team-in-nfl-history-to-pitch-a-perfect-offensive-game-in-playoff-win-over-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bills didn't punt, kick a field goal, nor turn the ball over in the blowout win</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta transit CEO kills himself, steps in front of train...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/16/atlanta-transit-leader-marta-ceo-jeffrey-parker-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for the Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority (MARTA) said that Jeffrey Parker killed himself when he was struck by a train.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPECT KILLED, EVERYONE FREED</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/news/local/hostage-synagogue-colleyville-texas-congregation-beth-israel-situation/287-38eb82cd-993c-486a-996f-7e5e278190bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation began around 11 a.m. Saturday and lasted nearly 12 hours at Congregation Beth Israel in the Dallas suburb of Colleyville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Sheriff Seizes 144 Horses in Major Cruelty Case...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2022/01/14/severely-malnourished-horses-seized-grand-county-snow-mountain-stables-ymca-rockies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large number of injured and emaciated horses were removed by authorities from the Snow Mountain Stables near Granby during a two-day, multi-jurisdiction operation that concluded Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celine Dion cancels remaining tour dates due to 'persistent' medical issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/15/whats-wrong-with-celine-dion-singer-cancels-balance-of-us-2022-dates-after-earlier-scrapping-dozens-of-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psych evaluation ordered for doctor accused of misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article257335847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maine doctor’s license is suspended for 30 days after being accused of spreading COVID-19 misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE Ripped for Cover Making Black Models Look 'Tragic'...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2022/01/14/vogue-magazine-slammed-cover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's being sold as a Vogue magazine cover celebrating African beauty is being criticized for making Black women look "tragic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deranged man pushes Asian woman to death at Times Square subway station...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/15/woman-pushed-to-her-death-at-times-square-subway-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deranged man fatally pushed an Asian woman in front of an oncoming subway train Saturday morning in Times Square, police and sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California schools under intense strain, fighting to stay open...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-schools-under-intense-strain-130059166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging coronavirus cases among students and staff due to the Omicron variant have put schools under intense strain, exhausting teachers and increasing student anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK CUTS LIVESTREAM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-texas-fort-worth-70bf98670cb880156cf5e1f1e4e08dcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEYVILLE, Texas (AP) — Police say one hostage has been released uninjured from a Texas synagogue where a man had been holding four people. The Colleyville Police Department said the man was released shortly after 5 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden team regroups...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-us-supreme-court-business-health-7bae2b5d394a875395f0f4f700d38e87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Concerned but not giving up, President Joe Biden is anxiously pushing ahead to prod people to get COVID-19 shots after the Supreme Court put a halt to the administration's sweeping vaccinate-or-test plan for large employers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSTAGE DRAMA AT TX SYNAGOGUE</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article257360862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All residents in the immediate area of Congregation Beth Israel were evacuated, and people are asked to avoid the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BACKPACK OF BOMBS'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10406409/Officials-negotiating-man-reportedly-holding-people-hostage-Texas-synagogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is negotiating with a Texas man who is claiming his sister is 'Lady Al Qaeda' Asfia Siddiqui. He has taken three people and the rabbi as hostages inside the Congregation Beth Israel synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTV loss could cripple rightwing ONE AMERICA NEWS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220115163735-pzh6l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AT&amp;T/OAN:DirecTV loss could cripple rightwing One America News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Covid death toll could be 17,000% higher than admitted..</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4470802/chinas-virus-death-toll-higher-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S coronavirus death toll could actually be a staggering 17,000 per cent higher than admitted in a shocking cover-up, an analyst has claimed. It’s feared the country’s true C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The story of how Doomsday Clock began ticking 75 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/story-doomsday-clock-began-ticking-144100844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Martyl Langsdorf designed just one magazine cover, but it has had considerable staying power. A prolific painter of abstract and figurative canvases, she was commissioned 75 years ago by the scientists who built the atomic bomb that ended World War II. By 1947 the Cold War was on, and they wanted to alert Americans to the danger of a nuclear confrontation with the Soviet Union. They ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celine Dion cancels remaining tour dates due to 'persistent' medical issues...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/celine-dion-cancels-remaining-north-american-tour-dates-due-to-health-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celine Dion has canceled her remaining North American tour dates due to 'persistent' medical issues that prevent her from performing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift away from daily case counts has begun...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2022/01/15/news/nation/a-shift-away-from-daily-covid-case-counts-has-begun-joam40zk0w/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epidemiologists caution that the numbers should be relied on only as broad indicators of the velocity and direction of the disease’s transmission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As nations decide to live with virus, experts warn of surrendering too soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-nations-decide-to-live-with-the-virus-some-16778094.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nations around the planet are making a subtle but consequential pivot in their war...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin sworn into office...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/glenn-youngkin-first-republican-to-win-statewide-in-virginia-since-2009-sworn-into-office/ar-AASOgaW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT restaurant opening in New York will serve up status with side of seafood...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/an-nft-restaurant-opening-in-new-york-will-serve-up-status-with-a-side-of-seafood/ar-AASOGzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew accuser seeks testimony from British nightclub witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220115-prince-andrew-accuser-seeks-testimony-from-british-nightclub-witness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Prince Andrew's sexual assault accuser want to question a woman who they say saw him in a London nightclub with a "young girl," US court documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE Blasts Le Pen Video as French Presidential Race Heats Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/louvre-blasts-le-pen-video-as-french-presidential-race-heats-up-1.1708074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s crowded presidential campaign is getting more heated ahead of the April elections, and now even the Louvre, one of the country’s most recognizable symbols, is caught in the fray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrants set off in Honduras in first caravan of '22...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220115161035-eytnw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CENTAM:Hundreds of U.S.-bound migrants set off in Honduras in first caravan of 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safer gun?: 'Smart' pistols debut...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-01-safer-gun-smart-pistols.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Smart" pistols designed to limit who can shoot them are poised to hit the booming US firearm market this year, taking aim at spiking gun deaths as federal lawmakers remain deadlocked on any new restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Trials in Cuba Deepen Harshest Crackdown in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/14/mass-trials-in-cuba-deepen-its-harshest-crackdown-in-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detained protesters in Cuba could get up to 30 years in prison as they face the largest and most punitive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did We Get So 'Cringe'?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2022/01/cringe-culture-everywhere/621272/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early cringe culture was about empathy and secondhand embarrassment. Today, being “cringe” is a serious infraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there second act ahead?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-Biden-ends-his-first-year-amid-many-16778070.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Nearing the first anniversary of his swearing in, President Joe Biden has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decaying 122-year-old San Fran home sells for $2m at auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/14/san-francisco-victorian-home-2-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price tag on the roughly 2,000 sq ft Victorian, called ‘the worst house on the best block’, was the outcome of overbidding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music catalogs fetching huge deals. Are they overvalued?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/music-catalogs-fetching-huge-deals-140011619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songwriters like Bruce Springsteen, John Legend and Bob Dylan are cashing in on the growing demand for popular songwriting catalogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA BEACHES CLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/tsunami-warning-issued-for-california-coast-beaches-closed-waves-expected/ar-AASOpSX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST COAST TSUNAMI THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10405333/Tongans-flee-lives-tsunami-smashes-island-nation-underwater-volcano-erupts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia is the fifth nation to issue a tsunami warning after an undersea volcano in the Pacific Ocean caused havoc in Tonga, with the dangerous waves due to affect Australia from 9.45pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAVES IN HAWAII...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/15/asia/tsunami-warning-tonga-volcano-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tsunami has hit Tonga's largest island, Tongatapu, and reportedly sent waves flooding into the capital after an underwater volcano in the South Pacific exploded in a violent eruption on Saturday, sending a cloud of ash and gas steam into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONGA TAKES HIT...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2022-01-15-tsunami-hawaii-california-alaska-tonga-fiji-volcano-eruption</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story. Please check back for updates. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How diplomats commit crazy crimes living abroad -- and get away with it...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/15/how-diplomatic-immunity-lets-envoys-get-away-with-crazy-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are around 100,000 foreign diplomats, including their dependents, currently living in the US — and some have broken local laws and faced zero consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Gay Cruise Keep 5,500 People Safe Amid Covid?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/14/can-a-gay-cruise-keep-5500-people-safe-amid-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Omicron variant of the coronavirus continues to surge onboard cruise ships, forcing several cruise lines to cancel and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEVER-ENDING: Expect more worrisome variants, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-dc99bc9f769dd6d7cb669e3d185c6261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready to learn more Greek letters. Scientists warn that omicron’s whirlwind advance practically ensures it won’t be the last version of the coronavirus to worry the world. Every infection provides a chance for the virus to mutate, and omicron has an edge over its predecessors: It spreads way faster despite emerging on a planet with a stronger patchwork of immunity from vaccines and prior illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal risks in sedition conspiracy case against Oath Keepers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-riots-conspiracy-indictments-b846daef24d854ed267c509e758164db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seditious conspiracy case against members and associates of the far-right Oath Keepers militia group marks the boldest attempt so far by the government to prosecute those who attacked the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican midterm dilemma: How closely to align with him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-donald-trump-campaigns-presidential-elections-elections-be1c94516de16d480870ea8f46e0f35b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Donald Trump is stepping up his election-year effort to dominate the Republican Party with a Saturday rally in Arizona in which he plans to castigate anyone who dares to question his lie that the 2020 presidential election was stolen, likely including the state’s GOP governor, Doug Ducey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Vienna against mandatory vaccination...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220115151003-w4ya8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRIA (PIX):Thousands protest in Vienna against mandatory vaccination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Politics Making Americans Sick, Literally...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/american-politics-feel-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 in 20 even say thinking about and discussing politics leaves them feeling suicidal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brought to Brink by Vengeful Aide He Crossed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/boris-johnson-brought-to-brink-by-the-vengeful-aide-he-crossed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson Brought to Brink by the Vengeful Aide He Crossed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers stuck at sea after NORWEGIAN cancels cruise mid-voyage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/ports-waterways/589881-passengers-stuck-at-sea-after-norwegian-cancels-cruise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers aboard a Norwegian cruise ship are stuck at sea this week after the cruise line decided to cancel the cruise mid-voyage due to COVID-19 concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Enthusiasts Meet Their Match: Angry Gamers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/15/crypto-enthusiasts-meet-their-match-angry-gamers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — For years, Christian Lantz has played S.T.A.L.K.E.R., a first-person shooter game set in a post-apocalyptic Ukraine that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTV drops OAN in blow to conservative channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mystery-surrounds-decision-directv-drop-one-america-news-network-its-lineup-1669743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OANN has positioned itself as rightward of Fox News. However, the network has been accused of running "disinformation campaigns."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French fashion brand under fire for photo shoot involving indigenous women in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-fashion-brand-under-fire-191846818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - A production team from the popular French fashion label Sézane landed in Oaxaca earlier this month to photograph their new collection, drawing on the vibrant colors and patterns created by local artisans in southern Mexico. But a video from one of those shoots, involving an indigenous Mexican woman, has drawn widespread criticism, including from the Mexican government, which has launched an investigation into the incident.Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano erupts in Pacific, West Coast under tsunami advisory...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-environment-and-nature-new-zealand-tonga-d434936e25079859df8261780976def8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — An undersea volcano erupted in spectacular fashion near the Pacific nation of Tonga on Saturday, sending large tsunami waves crashing across the shore and people rushing to higher ground.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
