<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Reverses course on healthcare for illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/joe-biden-reverses-his-position-on-government-healthcare-for-illegal-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is now doing what Democrats always do when asked to defend their stance on immigration: He's pretending he doesn't support the thing he just advocated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico murder rate reaches all-time high;  94 killings every day...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9446065/mexico-murder-rate-highest-ever-94-killings-each-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO is experiencing its worst ever murder rate with 94 killings each day amid a massive surge in violence between cartels. The number of homicides has rocketed over the past four years with more…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson found guilty of illegally filming criminal trial for social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9443759/tommy-robinson-guilty-contempt-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOMMY Robinson fans have clashed with cops after he was found in contempt of court at a hearing at the Old Bailey today. The former English Defence League leader was met by calls of “Oh Tommy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage shatters all-time high temp record as Alaska swelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/sweltering-heat-wave-produces-all-time-record-high-in-anchorage-on-independence-day/70008741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BACKFIRE: Russia Meddling Wouldn't Have Happened 'on My Watch and Barack's Watch'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-russia-election-interference-wouldnt-have-happened-my</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘But I promise you it wouldn’t have, and it didn’t’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS KEEP SHAKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/07/05/hundreds-aftershocks-follow-california-earthquake/1654878001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fourth of July California earthquake was followed by hundreds of aftershocks rumbling near Ridgecrest, the epicenter for the magnitude 6.4 quake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House faces court deadline to reveal census citizenship plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-census/white-house-faces-court-deadline-to-reveal-u-s-census-citizenship-plan-idUSKCN1U01LG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House faces a Friday afternoon court deadline to reveal whether it int...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARVEL first openly trans actor calls for more portrayals...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9589b8f66e4e4038a808d1e7851bcd1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70-year-old marathon runner accused of cheating found dead in river...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/05/marathoner-frank-meza-found-dead-in-river-after-being-disqualified-for-cheating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 70-year-old retired physician who was accused of cheating in the Los Angeles Marathon was found dead in a river, police and relatives said. The body of Frank Meza, who was disqualified Monday aft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police break up large 'modern day slavery' ring in UK....</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/jul/05/charity-and-police-break-up-uks-largest-modern-slavery-ring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courts jail eight people from gang that exploited vulnerable people trafficked from Poland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Hollywood franchise fatigue drives down global ticket sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/jul/05/hollywood-film-franchise-fatigue-drives-down-global-ticket-sales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cinemagoers spent almost $19bn in first six months of the year, down from $20.2bn in 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens British shipping in retaliation for tanker seizure...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-iran-tanker-idUSKCN1U00S5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian Revolutionary Guards commander threatened on Friday to seize a Britis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNUSUAL NUMBER OF AFTERSHOCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/07/05/california-earthquake-map-shows-unusual-number-of-aftershocks/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 159 aftershocks of magnitude 2.5 or greater were recorded after the earthquake, according to USGS Seismologist Robert Graves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA finds name of rural road in distasteful, asks for change...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/northwest/idaho/article232238047.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd secret FACEBOOK group for border agents shows mocking images...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/05/politics/cbp-second-facebook-group-images/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one other social media group with an apparent nexus to Customs and Border Protection has been discovered to contain vulgar and sexually explicit posts, according to screenshots shared with two sources familiar with the Facebook pages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China faces another discontent challenge as planned garbage plant stirs protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/china-faces-another-discontent-challenge-as-planned-garbage-plant-stirs/article_6107ce4e-8801-5f67-8c84-2444f4f59a2b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — On suffocating summer nights in Wuhan city, China, the smell of burning garbage drifts through the air, so acrid that people close their windows and complain that they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich father-in-law has helped, complicated O'Rourke's career...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/84ca432974f04a699e4b2f7eaf0c74a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictions Of 'Tiny Crowd' Proven Spectacularly Wrong...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2019/07/05/media-predictions-of-tiny-crowd-for-trump-july-4-speech-proven-spectacularly-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More fake news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden attacks Trump as he tries to pivot from busing debate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-attacks-trump-tries-pivot-110445824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden said he wasn’t prepared for the friendly fire he’s taken from Democrats over busing, and instead tried to refocus his message on differences with President Donald Trump.In an interview with CNN, the former vice president said his decades-old comments on school desegregation were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Spacey accuser drops lawsuit against actor...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/07/05/kevin-spacey-accuser-drops-lawsuit-accusing-actor-of-groping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young man who says Kevin Spacey groped him in a Nantucket bar in 2016 has dropped his lawsuit against the Oscar-winning actor. Mitchell Garabedian, an attorney for the man, announced in an email Friday that the suit filed June 26 in Nantucket Superior Court has been voluntarily dismissed. No reason was provided either by Garabedian or in the court filing. Garabedian said he would have no further comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Short Bouts Of Exercise Make Smarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/short-spurts-exercise-improve-brain-function-may-make-you-smarter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much has been written about the great mental health benefits that come with regular exercise. Now a new study shows that hitting the treadmill every morning -- even for a short period of time -- offers another brain benefit: it may make you smarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. dream pulls African migrants in record numbers across Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-africa/u-s-dream-pulls-african-migrants-in-record-numbers-across-latin-america-idUSKCN1U01A4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marilyne Tatang, 23, crossed nine borders in two months to reach Mexico from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: STRONGER QUAKES WITHIN DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7216129/California-face-BIGGER-quake-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geologists say yesterday's 6.4-magnitude quake in California is likely to produce a forceful 5.5-strength aftershock and a series of smaller tremors - and could even prompt a larger one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 157,005,000 EMPLOYED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/susan-jones/157005000-employed-june-19th-record-trump-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Photo by Tasos Katopodis/Getty Images) (CNSNews.com) - After the Fourth of July fireworks, the fifth of July brings another reason for Americans to celebrate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUNE JOBS BOOM!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/05/jobs-report-june-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Payroll growth rebounded sharply in June as the U.S. economy added 224,000 jobs and the unemployment rate rose to 3.7%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 MAG RATTLES SOCAL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/902d275ef9084156ade446454e580ece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek election: Voters crave return to mainstream politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3f6cb9737cda457282ede8e9e43417ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-scooters: Transport 'tsunami' flooding cities worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-07-e-scooters-tsunami-cities-worldwide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They appeared in June last year as Paris was waking up from its annual all-night Festival of Music: hundreds of green-and-black electric scooters dotting the pavements of the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATE CUT OFF?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-jobs-top-forecast-224-123001521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. hiring rebounded in June and topped all estimates of economists, a sign of labor-market strength that may ease calls for a Federal Reserve interest-rate cut. Stock futures fell while Treasury yields and the dollar advanced.Payrolls climbed 224,000 after a downwardly revised 72,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran to paint over George Washington mural...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9f3037c7ec9d48a286059ac8f9975afe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.4 MAG JOLTS...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/54-magnitude-earthquake-hits-ridgecrest-1-day-after-64-temblor/5379870/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 5.4 earthquake hit near Searles Valley Friday morning, one day after a powerful 6.4 quake hit the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran fumes as Britain seizes Iranian oil tanker...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-iran-tanker/tehran-fumes-as-britain-seizes-iranian-oil-tanker-over-syria-sanctions-idUSKCN1TZ0GN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Royal Marines seized a giant Iranian oil tanker in Gibraltar on Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Coal Baron Dies in Copter Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/billionaire-us-coal-baron-chris-cline-dies-in-helicopter-crash/ar-AADSarC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland moves to exempt young workers from income tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190705-poland-moves-exempt-young-workers-income-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland moves to exempt young workers from income tax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden: I wasn't ready for Kamala to attack me that way...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/05/politics/joe-biden-cnn-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden said in an exclusive interview with CNN airing Friday that he wasn't prepared for California Sen. Kamala Harris to confront him on issues of race the way she did at the first Democratic primary debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Is this big one?'</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/04/california-earthquake-temblor-rocks-state/1650441001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary magnitude 6.4 earthquake rocked Southern California on Thursday, shaking an area for hundreds of miles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100,000 pickup suddenly within reach...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/07/05/luxury-pickup-trucks-chevrolet-ford-gm-ram-tesla-rivian/1620574001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll need some serious towing capacity to afford the increasingly luxurious pickupsÂ hitting dealerships from Chevrolet, Ford, Ram and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common cold virus 'could cure cancer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/07/04/common-cold-virus-could-cure-cancer-pioneering-trial-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The common cold virus could cure cancer, scientists say, as a &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; treatment was found to eradicate the disease in a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seismograph in PA picked up...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/earthquake-SoCal-felt-in-Bay-Area-14072030.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 6.6 magnitude earthquake that struck near Ridgecrest, Calif. was picked up by a seismograph in the San Francisco Bay Area - and much further beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAKEALERT fails to send warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/california-earthquake-la-shakealert-warning-14072013.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of earthquake preparedness on the West Coast is supposed to be ShakeAlert, an app that warns residents a significant earthquake is about to start shaking. But many Southern California residents were disappointed that they never received an alert before or during the 6.4-magnitude earthquake that rattled Searles Valley in San Bernardino County Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Curious Mystical Text Behind Marianne Williamson's Presidential Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/05/nyregion/marianne-williamson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Age author was drawn to an esoteric kind of bible as an aimless young woman in the 1970s. It has made her a self-help megastar. And now it has entered the political mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWARM OF AFTERSHOCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Preliminary-Magnitude-66-Earthquake-Rattles-Southern-California-512225192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude-6.4 earthquake rattled Southern California Thursday morning, with residents reporting feeling it from the high desert to the coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARGEST IN DECADES...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-earthquake-california-shake-quake-20190704-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earthquake rattles Southern California. The 10:33 a.m. quake was centered in the Searles Valley, a remote area of Kern County about 100 miles from L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRES, MEDICAL EMERGENCIES...</title>
      <link>https://wlos.com/news/nation-world/64-magnitude-earthquake-in-southern-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wlos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) &amp;mdash; The strongest earthquake in 20 years shook a large swath of Southern California and parts of Nevada on Thursday, rattling nerves on the July 4th holiday and causing some injuries and damage in a town near the epicenter, followed by a swarm of ongoing aftershocks. The 6. 4 magnitude quake struck at 10:33 a. m. in the Mojave Desert, about 150 miles (240 kilometers) northeast of Los Angeles, near the town of Ridgecrest, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like Turntable'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/04/6-6m-quake-strikes-near-ridgecrest-in-kern-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It struck in in the remote Kern County community of Searles Valley Thursday morning, about 160 miles northeast of Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FELT LA TO VEGAS...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/07/04/6-6-earthquake-jolts-southern-california-on-4th-of-july/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A state of emergency has been declared in Ridgecrest after a magnitude 6.4 earthquake rocked the Mojave Desert and was widely felt around Southern California Thursday morning, the Fourth of July. The quake struck at 10:33 a.m. and centered about 7 miles southwest Searles Valley, roughly 11 miles east-northeast of Ridgecrest, 109 miles north of San Bernardino and 121 miles north-northeast of Los Angeles, according to the U.S. Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITAL EVACUATED...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/us/live-news/earthquake-california-july-2019/h_127677cc4848a97e61a28bc922743fe3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ridgecrest Regional Hospital is being evacuated following today's 6.4 magnitude earthquake, the Kern County Fire Department tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 MAG QUAKE RATTLES SOCAL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/60fe39042bb64733ab283abab8b228f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump celebrates US might, avoids politics in rousing speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-producer-president-makes-july-4th-own-show-200916773.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump sang the praises of the US military and American heroes of the past two and a half centuries Thursday as he skirted politics in a rousing Independence Day speech in Washington. As combat aircraft, including the rarely seen B2 stealth bomber flew overhead, Trump scrolled through</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FUTURE BELONGS TO THE BRAVE'</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-4th-july-address-future-belongs-brave</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We are one people chasing one dream and one magnificent destiny’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French lawmakers approve 3% tax on online giants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd16a5f8db154b48ab5de53c62617826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidents on July 4: Some chill, some get in your face...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8960643f2cd64ba7989ed807f37f74bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel unveils ancient road 'where Jesus walked' to temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/israel-road-jesus-temple-ancient-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel officially opened a stairway, known as "Pilgrim's Road," that Jesus is believed to have walked on in ancient Jerusalem as another place for Judeo-Christian visitors to see in the Holy Land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France moves to make companies block 'hate speech' online...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/89dd24221b5043fd848ee974cc6d98fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson fans sue 'LEAVING NEVERLAND' accusers...</title>
      <link>https://spectrumnews1.com/oh/toledo/ap-top-news/2019/07/04/french-michael-jackson-fans-sue-leaving-neverland-accusers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectrumnews1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Michael Jackson fan clubs in France are suing two men who accused the singer of sexual abuse in the HBO documentary &amp;#34;Leaving Neverland.&amp;#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans shooting off more fireworks than ever...</title>
      <link>https://expo.oregonlive.com/news/g66l-2019/07/82de1a29083345/its-not-your-imagination-americans-are-shooting-off-more-fireworks-than-ever.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;expo.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genes, yes, but obesity pandemic mostly down to diet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190704-genes-yes-but-obesity-pandemic-mostly-down-diet-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Genes, yes, but obesity pandemic mostly down to diet: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Sub That Caught Fire Linked to Underwater Drone Program...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/damaged-russian-sub-linked-to-underwater-drone-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire aboard a secret Russian nuclear research vessel that killed 14 Russians may have been involved in underwater drone operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest defrocked for abusing Scouts in landmark case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afe37f5391db4046a56f46123d34ac1b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nuclear reactor safe'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/083b233940e843fba89b34680dc24848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player has arm amputated after crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/sports/miami-dolphins/fl-sp-dolphins-kedrick-norton-20190704-4xdzokmlnzdabmjelkh7yh26ii-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Dolphins defensive lineman Kendrick Norton, a former University of Miami standout, was involved in a serious car accident that likely will end his playing career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.4 MILES DEEP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci38443183/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Jewish Europeans face more abuse than their parents...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190704162747-1syiy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU-ANTISEMITISM/ (PIX):Young Jewish Europeans face more abuse than their parents -study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese studios ban American actors...</title>
      <link>https://t.co/w6lycj8wDG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;t.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR MIFFED:  Time for her to ditch victim act...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/entertainment/opinion/2019/07/03/scooter-braun-feud-is-part-of-taylor-swifts-instinct-for-victimhood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive order on citizenship?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-trump-considers-executive-order-on-citizenship-question-5c9dfdb5-facd-46ed-b1fd-fdda7eb2aa15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We didn’t come this far just to throw in the towel."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#ArrestAntiPakjournalists tops TWITTER trends in Pakistan... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/arrestantipakjournalists-tops-twitter-trends-pakistan-145643885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hashtag calling for the arrest of journalists briefly became the top Twitter trend in Pakistan Thursday, deepening concern over a shrinking space for dissent in the country. Many users accompanied it with a composite photograph of prominent journalists and TV anchors, some of whom regularly criticise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day filled with concerts, parades and politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/417337aca3eb4282b926c0eb7d03fe3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
