<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thieves Hit on New Scam: Synthetic Identity Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/04/07/thieves-hit-on-a-new-scam-synthetic-identity-fraud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Your wallet and your purse could be a crime scene any day of the week.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Orban be wedge Vlad drives between Western allies?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/will-hungarys-orban-be-the-wedge-putin-drives-between-western-allies/ar-AAW23gH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-LGBTQ Proposals Flooding State Legislatures at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-lgbtq-proposals-are-flooding-us-state-legislatures-at-a-record-pace/ar-AAW0kr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge appears likely to allow Jan 6-related candidacy challenge against Greene...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/08/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-candidacy-challenge-lawsuit/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge signaled Friday that she'll likely allow a group of Georgia voters to move forward with their constitutional challenge against GOP Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, which claims she can't run for reelection because she aided the January 6 insurrectionists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakeholder Musk tweets 'Is Twitter dying?'</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-twitter-stakeholder-elon-musk-tweets-is-twitter-dying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter's newest board member and largest stakeholder Elon Musk tweeted Saturday to ask if the social media network was "dying" and to call out users such as singer Justin Bieber, who are highly foll…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sour and angry America poised to punish Dems this fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/09/angry-voters-biden-inflation-midterms-00024218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and his top advisers know that the window to change the economic narrative through executive action is rapidly closing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we witnessing beginning of de-dollarization?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/3262514-are-we-witnessing-the-beginning-of-de-dollarization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hegemony of the U.S. dollar was reliant on America’s hegemonic status in the world. With the world moving toward multipolarity and with the U.S. no longer the world’s largest trading nation (it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In outcome of Whitmer case, some see freedom, others danger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whitmer-kidnap-plot-trial-adam-fox-gretchen-whitmer-presidential-elections-violence-e2f805952538cdbef69c3dca82ddbfd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside the Michigan courthouse where a jury did not convict any of the four men charged with planning to kidnap Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEELERS QB Haskins Dies After Hit By Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/5088876/dwayne-haskins-dead-steelers-nfl-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star Dwayne Haskins has died after being hit by a vehicle while training with the Steelers just weeks after signing a new contract with the team, according to reports. Football fans mourn the f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stop the Steal' Rally Organizer Agrees to Cooperate with Jan. 6 Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-trump-stop-the-steal-rally-organizer-agrees-to-cooperate-with-jan-6-criminal-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activist and Trump rally organizer Ali Alexander has agreed to cooperate with the committee investigating the January 6 attack on the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson surprise meeting with Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/boris-johnson-ukraine-zelensky-2283122f-3d5a-487a-91df-95eb62d81f5b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Right now Boris Johnson's visit to Kiev began with a tet-a-tet meeting with President Zelensky," a Ukrainian official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loses his NINTH colonel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10702421/Ukraine-war-Putin-loses-NINTH-colonel-tank-commander-latest-Russian-officer-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A funeral was held for Colonel Alexander Bespalov on Friday in the closed Russian city of Ozersk, according to a local announcement, which said he was killed during 'special operation'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE TURNS RIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220409-france-prepares-for-first-round-of-tight-macron-re-election-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France on Saturday prepared for the first round of presidential elections projected to produce a run-off rematch between President Emmanuel Macron and far-right leader Marine Le Pen that will be far…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow First Default in Century Looks All But Inevitable Now...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-first-default-century-looks-073000013.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Sanctions Against Putin’s Daughters, IMF AccountNations Eye Modern Arms for Ukraine as Soviet-Era Stocks DwindleFinland Hit by Cyber Attack, Airspace Breach as NATO Bid WeighedDHL Jet Skids Off Runway, Breaks Up After Emergency LandingShanghai, Guangzhou Plan More Mass Tests as Covid Cases RiseRussia’s first external default in a century now looks all but inevitable after another brutal week for the country’s finances.First, the Treasury hal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson, COVID and retirement show Congress' partisan path...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-ketanji-brown-jackson-us-supreme-court-covid-business-f5a7b68b0a4e0c17792de15412c87e8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A milestone Supreme Court confirmation that endured a flawed process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpses Of Afterlife? 'Near-Death Experiences' Aren't Hallucinations, Scientists Conclude...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/08/near-death-brain-activity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A review of research exploring what people experience when they’re close to death reveals “that near-death experiences” are a real thing, even if we can’t explain them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal referrals of former Trump officials pose thorny questions for DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/3262936-criminal-referrals-of-former-trump-officials-pose-thorny-questions-for-doj/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tough decisions are piling up at the Justice Department (DOJ), which is now weighing three criminal referrals from Congress directed at former Trump White House officials.   The referrals…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians Turn on One Another Over War...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/09/spurred-by-putin-russians-turn-on-one-another-over-the-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marina Dubrova, an English teacher on the Russian island of Sakhalin in the Pacific, showed an uplifting YouTube video to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president offers voters chance to kick him out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mexico-e2-80-99s-president-offers-voters-the-chance-to-kick-him-out/ar-AAW1sGm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lachlan Murdoch, once ambivalent FOX heir, makes his views clear...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lachlan-murdoch-once-the-ambivalent-fox-heir-expresses-his-views/ar-AAW2c9B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Haitian migration routes change, compassion tested in Florida Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-haitian-migration-routes-change-compassion-is-tested-in-florida-keys/ar-AAW24Gz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask, no mask: Biden pandemic practices vary as covid risks grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mask-no-mask-biden-e2-80-99s-pandemic-practices-vary-as-covid-risks-grow/ar-AAW0L6M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 dead in train station attack as Russian troops regroup in east...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/50-dead-in-train-station-attack-as-Russian-troops-17068393.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KRAMATORSK, Ukraine -- At least 50 people were killed and 98 injured in what Ukrainian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissatisfied With Party, Wealthy Republican Donors Form Secret Coalitions...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/06/dissatisfied-with-their-party-wealthy-republican-donors-form-secret-coalitions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coalition of wealthy conservative benefactors that says it aims to “disrupt but advance the Republican agenda” gathered this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food prices soar to record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-health-europe-united-nations-fe2cc912195478f0dd861e6252c8f3b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Prices for food commodities like grains and vegetable oils reached their highest levels ever last month largely because of Russia's war in Ukraine and the “massive supply disruptions” it is causing , threatening millions of people in Africa, the Middle East and elsewhere with hunger and malnourishment, the United Nations said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACADEMY SLAPS BACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/will-smith-oscars-ban-664346ac2d2441939764f35be2d8026b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The motion picture academy on Friday banned Will Smith from attending the Oscars or any other academy event for 10 years following his slap of Chris Rock at the Academy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia or die:  These Ukrainians were given only one way out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/07/europe/ukraine-mariupol-russia-deportation-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Russian forces and allied separatist soldiers arrived offering a path to safety, it felt like a sick twist of fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Theft Rings Stealing Fuel Across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/gas-theft-rings-have-now-stolen-more-140k-worth-fuel-across-us-1696543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of gallons of gas have allegedly been stolen around the country as prices have soared in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest speaks out against war despite threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-priest-speaks-out-against-war-in-ukraine-despite-threats/ar-AAW0Dc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreaks give taste of living with virus: 'Get used to it'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-living-with-virus-outbreaks-26ce89a748b27b3a47730d29a947237a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is getting a first glimpse of what it’s like to experience COVID-19 outbreaks during this new phase of living with the virus, and the roster of the newly infected is studded with stars. Cabinet members, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, Broadway actors and the governors of New Jersey and Connecticut have all tested positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department: WH gift records for Trump, Pence missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ab704b1bb2945bc04a31c12a81248e56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The State Department says it is unable to compile a complete and accurate accounting of gifts presented to former President Donald Trump and other U.S. officials by foreign governments during Trump's final year in office, citing missing data from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: 6 human skulls found at mail facility on way to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5083967/human-skulls-chicago-iowa-netherlands-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A K-9 dog has discovered six human skulls going through the US mailing system. The human skulls were shipped from the Netherlands and en route to Iowa before being taken away at O’Hare’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Braces for President Getting Covid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3262454-white-house-acknowledges-biden-could-get-covid-stresses-hes-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Friday acknowledged President Biden could get COVID-19 amid an uptick in positive cases surrounding the president but stressed he has taken steps to protect himself. “We take eve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DANCING WITH THE STARS' Moving To DISNEY+; Stunning Move After 16 Years On ABC...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/dancing-with-the-stars-leaving-abc-disney-plus-season-31-1234996886/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Hold on to your Danskins: Dancing with the Stars is relocating to Disney+ in a groundbreaking arrangement. DWTS has received a two-year pickup — for Seasons 31 and 32 — and w…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
