<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Was hospitalized less than two weeks after attending MAGA rally in Tulsa...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/30/herman-cain-dead-dies-74-sick-covid-19-attending-trump-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herman Cain, once a GOP presidential hopeful, died after battling COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Vaccine distribution will be 'joint venture' between CDC, Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/30/coronavirus-vaccine-distribution-388904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan breaks with the longstanding precedent that CDC distributes vaccines during major outbreaks through a centralized ordering system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Secrets, From Sex to Pets to Celeb Bad Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/eight-shocking-secrets-i-learned-while-working-on-private-jets/ar-BB17lXlV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worth even more the day after Congressional grilling!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/a-day-after-congress-grilling-big-tech-stocks-add-250-billion/ar-BB17o6e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP PLUNGES RECORD 32.9%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/economy-suffers-titanic-329-plunge-in-2nd-quarter-gdp-shows-and-points-to-drawn-out-recovery-2020-07-30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An economy badly battered by the coronavirus shrank at a record 32.9% pace in the second quarter, underscoring just how big a hole the U.S. finds itself in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix to break record for its hottest month!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Phoenix-to-break-record-for-its-hottest-month-15447006.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unforgiving heat has baked Phoenix this month, not only scorching the afternoons but staying hot at night, more often than not above 90 degrees round the clock. Such unforgiving heat poses public health risks and could be a sign of things to come as climate change leads to a hotter, drier Southwest.  Thursday's low temperature stayed above 90 degrees in Phoenix for the 15th time this month. The count of exceptionally hot nights has obliterated the previous July record of 11 set in 2006. Assuming that the temperature does not drop below 90 before midnight Thursday, the count will match the most such hot nights in Phoenix for any year on record, with much summer heat still to come.  Low temperatures this month have been the warmest recorded for the city, where weather data began in the 1800s. The July average temperature for Phoenix of 98.6 degrees is also the hottest on record for any month.  With an excessive heat warning in effect through Saturday, and temperatures expected to top 110 into the middle of next week, the city probably will see its hottest recorded month.  The heat is in large part due to a strong area of high pressure, also referred to as a heat dome, parked over the region for much of the month.  The hottest major city in the country, Phoenix averages about 175 days at or above 90 degrees and 110 days at or above 100, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA).  But it's a dry heat; such an arid atmosphere tends to allow temperatures to cool off at night. Until recently.  Ninety-degree lows were almost unheard of in Phoenix before the 1970s, but then the city started seeing about one to two a year in the 1980s and '90s. Since 2000, such occurrences have increased in frequency.  In the early 2000s the 30-year average was still...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA FORECAST: HURRICANE?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-isaias-to-eye-florida-us-east-coast/785580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA THURSDAY:  1,529 COVID DEATHS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1288970515344842753?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sales soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730202918-jcjn9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON.COM-RESULTS/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Amazon posts biggest profit ever at height of pandemic in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS REJECT</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730180310-sef8v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/DELAY (UPDATE 8, PIX):UPDATE 8-Trump floats election delay, congressional Republicans reject idea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court lets Michael Cohen publish book while sentenced at home...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730174309-vif6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/COHEN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. lets ex-Trump lawyer Michael Cohen publish book while serving sentence at home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for third straight day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f69d7f7b08fb036647880ae4874a5dc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Florida tallied on Thursday a new record high in daily confirmed COVID-19 deaths for the third straight day as the state faces pressure to outline new measures to combat the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd virus surge hits plateau?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3081a60a6abf62effa2e6030556ee30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — While deaths from the coronavirus in the U.S. are mounting rapidly, public health experts are seeing a flicker of good news: The second surge of confirmed cases appears to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FLOATS ELECTION DELAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d203eaa406dc5e7362dfa9e33522195e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump, lagging in the polls and grappling with deepening economic and public health crises, on Thursday floated the startling idea of delaying the Nov. 3...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS SPIKE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1878e580f5acd2c0305e5236c4e3197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The coronavirus pandemic sent the U.S. economy plunging by a record-shattering 32.9% annual rate last quarter and is still inflicting damage across the country, squeezing already...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERMAN CAIN DEAD FROM COVID...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8173fe14f7cf7095ced3b55fdc65581e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Herman Cain, former Republican presidential candidate and former CEO of a major pizza chain who went on to become an ardent supporter of President Donald Trump, has died of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Music Lessons Don't Make Children Smarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/music-lessons-dont-make-children-smarter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors declare that “teaching music with the sole intent of enhancing a child’s cognitive or academic skills may be pointless.” LONDON — Parents who think guitar or piano lessons will help their child’s academic performance may end up singing the blues themselves, according to a surprising new study. Researchers from both Japan and England conclude…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deleted Biden video sets off crisis at VOICE OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/30/deleted-biden-video-sets-off-a-crisis-at-voice-of-america-388571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The taxpayer-funded outlet is grappling with the fallout from a video post deemed too favorable to the former vice president, setting off recriminations and suspicion amid a shakeup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA FORECAST: HURRICANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/302054.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen DeGeneres Addresses 'Toxic Work Culture' Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ellen-degeneres-addresses-workplace-allegations-changes-forthcoming-staff-letter-1305189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the steps to change a workplace environment under fire, two sources tell The Hollywood Reporter that producer Ed Glavin will soon be out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will she be canceled?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/30/will-ellen-degeneres-become-a-canceled-celebrity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s faced major backlash in recent months, and her show is under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton ripped for remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theroot.com/will-someone-come-get-bill-clinton-he-just-shaded-stok-1844561440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theroot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how on beat they seem during the “Electric Slide” or how good their blaccent may be, there is a reason not every white person can come to the proverbial Black cookout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Why Trump Might Quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/30/why-trump-might-quit-387681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is logic behind saying to hell with reelection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court lets Michael Cohen publish book while sentenced at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/court-lets-ex-trump-lawyer-cohen-publish-book-while-sentenced-at-home-636989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK reports massive revenue growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/facebook-fb-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has seen an increase in user engagement as a result of the coronavirus, but has also endured an ad boycott that may crimp revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE blowout; Sales up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/apple-aapl-earnings-q3-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple reported a historically strong quarter for the company on Thursday, including $59.7 billion in revenue and double-digit growth in its products and services segments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sales soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/amazon-amzn-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company beat on both the top and bottom lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study finds higher viral load in young children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/30/health/children-coronavirus-viral-load-transmission-study-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children younger than 5 have between 10 and 100 times more genetic material from the novel coronavirus in their noses compared to older children and to adults, according to a small study published Thursday in the journal JAMA Pediatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: 92-Year-Old Woman With Dementia Sexually Assaulted In Home...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/stockton-woman-92-assaulted-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Joaquin County Sheriff deputies arrested James Lee Coose Wednesday for the attack a day earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama delivers eulogy at funeral with Presidents Bush, Clinton in attendance...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/30/barack-obama-delivers-eulogy-at-rep-john-lewis-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama is delivering the eulogy at civil rights icon Rep. John Lewis’ funeral Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY authorities break up alleged sex party...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/york-authorities-break-alleged-sex-party-crackdown-large/story?id=71948681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheriff's deputies in New York City recently broke up a sex party in Midtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese AI Creating Axis of Autocracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2020/09/china-ai-surveillance/614197/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Xi Jinping is using artificial intelligence to enhance his government’s totalitarian control—and he’s exporting this technology to regimes around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Gene-Altered Squid Thrills Biologists...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2020/07/30/895733739/the-first-gene-altered-squid-has-thrilled-biologists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have modified the genes of a squid, and genetically-altered octopuses could be coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HW Bush aircraft sailors test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2020/07/30/a-small-number-of-carrier-george-hw-bush-sailors-test-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials declined to say how many sailors had been infected, but called it a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis protester who sparked fire is Hells Angels member...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/minneapolis-umbrella-man-autozone-fire-hells-angels-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicknamed “Umbrella Man” for his all-black getup that included hood, gas mask and black umbrella, police say the man’s actions led to an arson fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian jet fighter buzzes two US spy planes over Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/russian-jet-fighter-buzzes-two-us-spy-planes-over-black-sea-636958</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAs backed by Soros join fray in clash with police...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/da-soros-justice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for drastic criminal justice and police reforms have swept the country since the death of George Floyd, but local prosecutors already are making waves on that front -- in a sign that under-the-radar political investments made by progressive groups in recent years are paying off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative journalist stabbed in back by Portland protester...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8574813/Conservative-journalist-stabbed-Portland-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking video captured the moment Andrew Duncomb, 25, was stabbed while he was out filming footage of protests by Portland's Mark O Hatfield federal courthouse early Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police ratchet up shark response after uptick in sightings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/30/long-island-maine-police-monitoring-sharks-after-fatal-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have deployed helicopters and boats to track sharks on the coastlines of Long Island and Maine after a New York City woman was fatally attacked by a great white this week — and several other…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>None will satisfy all sections of party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joe-bidens-running-mate-none-080012215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris? Val Demings? Democrats speculate but no single candidate will be able to satisfy all the interest groups and sectors of the partyIt doesn’t matter who Joe Biden picks as his running mate – somebody will be disappointed.The former vice-president and de facto Democratic presidential nominee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil reopens to foreigners...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/07/30/brazil-reopens-tourists-despite-reporting-record-numbers-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People arriving by air will be allowed entry for the first time in four months, though those travelling by land or sea will still be barred</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash piles up in Philly during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/philadelphia-trash-piles-up-as-coronavirus-pandemic-stymies-its-removal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia is struggling to overcome a surge in garbage caused by the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP, PUMP, PUMP:  Fed sticks to whatever it takes with no signs of virus easing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-leaves-rates-near-zero-180000544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Federal Reserve left interest rates near zero and vowed to use all its tools to support the recovery from an economic downturn that Chair Jerome Powell called the most severe “in our lifetime.”“The path forward for the economy is extraordinarily uncertain, and will depend in large</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask Fatigue: Workers Claim Headaches, Shortness Of Breath, Anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/mask-fatigue-texas-workers-headaches-shortness-breath-anxiety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether the elastic is too tight or the cloth is too thick, there are a lot of reasons for mask fatigue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence's Motorcade Involved In Crash With Dump Truck...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/07/30/vice-president-mike-pence-bus-crash-greensburg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists in VP Pence's motorcade are reporting separate accidents with a minor crash involving a bus in the motorcade, and later, an accident involving two motorbike escorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami-Dade ICUs Hit 146% Capacity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-dade-ic-us-at-146-percent-capacity-with-coronavirus-patients-151222876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals in the Miami area have been so overwhelmed by coronavirus patients that intensive care units are now operating well beyond full capacity, according to a federal pandemic update obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins Doc Says End Of 2021 Realistic Timeline For 'Wide Distribution' Of Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/johns-hopkins-press-conference-coronavirus-pandemic-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johns Hopkins public health experts laid out challenges in distributing and administering coronavirus vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis issues call to action in posthumous op-ed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76a63a9d89f53018f9347206b98ae9a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — John Lewis was mourned, revered and celebrated on Thursday at Atlanta's Ebenezer Baptist Church, a sacred place for many of those who helped to shape civil rights history. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West couple jailed for violating quarantine orders...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/couple-jailed-violating-quarantine-730259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 30--A Florida couple was arrested yesterday for defying quarantine orders issued after they each tested positive for COVID-19, police report. Cops last night busted Yohana Gonzalez, 26, and Jose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift Fans Doxx and Harass Music Critic Over Review...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/taylor-swift-remains-silent-as-fans-doxx-and-harass-music-critic-over-folkore-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans tweeted a Pitchfork editor’s address and phone numbers—and even photos of her and her home—all over a review some zealous Swifties decided was not positive enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Tech Companies Already Won...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2020/07/antitrust-hearing-tech-pandemic-inescapable/614749/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antitrust could break up the big players. It wouldn’t change everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*ck' and 'sorry': New sounds of baseball season...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/30/astros-josh-reddick-screams-f-k-after-popup-against-dodgers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This won’t be the last “f–k” of the baseball season. Astros outfielder Josh Reddick screamed the curse in anger after popping out during his team’s 4-2, 13-inning loss…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA SINGLE DAY RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730134919-dqydg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (URGENT):Florida reports record increase in COVID-19 deaths for third day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nazi Hunter Taking On Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-nazi-hunter-taking-on-mark-zuckerberg-and-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serge Klarsfeld has spent his life pursuing Nazis. Now, he’s teamed up with a number of other Holocaust activists and survivors to combat Facebook’s support of Holocaust denialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW GOVTS USE GEOLOCATION DATA TO IDENTIFY EVERYONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/how-government-entities-use-geolocation-data-to-identify-everyone_07302020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA is 'Satan,' Israel 'Chained Dog' --  But TWITTER Gives Ayatollah Pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/international/patrick-goodenough/us-satan-israel-its-chained-dog-twitter-gives-ayatollahs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s supreme leader, in a tweet Wednesday that was not flagged, restricted, or blocked by Twitter, called the United States “Satan,” labeled Israel America’s “chained dog,” drawing fresh attention to questions about the platform’s content policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Catches UBER EATS Driver -- Eating Her Chicken Wings! </title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/its-called-uber-eats-not-uber-eats-my-food-austin-neighborhood-man-catches-delivery-driver-eating-his-wing-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Austin neighborhood resident said his Uber Eats delivery driver liked his food so much that the driver ate some of it himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordics brush off mouth covers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-country-face-masks-nordics-brush-off-mouth-095007454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As most of the world either orders or recommends the use of face masks, with even US president Donald Trump seen wearing one, Nordic nations are the remaining holdouts. In supermarkets, on buses, and along the streets of capitals -- such as Stockholm, Copenhagen, Oslo, Helsinki and Reykjavik -- face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci39322287/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launches to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fcc3d442fe0cb4e640b0eae05d3e71c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The biggest, most sophisticated Mars rover ever built — a car-size vehicle bristling with cameras, microphones, drills and lasers — blasted off for the red planet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis issues call to action in posthumous op-ed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/30/opinion/john-lewis-civil-rights-america.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though I may not be here with you, I urge you to answer the highest calling of your heart and stand up for what you truly believe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Secrets, From Sex to Pets to Celeb Bad Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/private-jet-secrets-from-sex-to-pets-to-celebrity-bad-behavior</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight Shocking Secrets I Learned While Working on Private Jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TOO...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/texas-reports-single-day-record-coronavirus-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas passed the 6,000 deaths mark the same day the U.S. passed 150,000 deaths, the most of any country in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launches to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df83e06ae963e63a1ec3b525df4ae50e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The summer’s third and final mission to Mars — featuring NASA's most elaborate life-hunting rover — is on the verge of liftoff. The rover Perseverance will follow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP: 4.2 MAG QUAKE SHAKES SOCAL...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/preliminary-45-quake-hits-near-san-fernando-area/6342317/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 4.2-magnitude earthquake hit the Pacoima area early Thursday morning, according to the U.S. Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Mysterious Drone Swarm Descended On Palo Verde Nuke Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/34800/the-night-a-drone-swarm-descended-on-palo-verde-nuclear-power-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious case of mass drone incursions over America's most powerful nuclear power plant that only resulted in more questions and no changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Unleashes on Trump Privately as He Raises $24 Million for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/30/obama-unleashes-on-trump-privately-as-he-raises-24-million-for-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At fund-raising events where he has pulled in more than $24 million for Joseph R. Biden Jr.’s campaign in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Could Free 20% of Prisoners to Avoid Infection...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/30/about-20-of-n-j-prisoners-could-be-freed-to-avoid-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey lawmakers seemed close to supporting legislation on Thursday that could free more than 3,000 prisoners — about 20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First dog to test positive in USA dies...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/first-dog-with-covid-pets-coronavirus-buddy-german-shepherd/6341615/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mahoneys say, Buddy, their 6-year-old German Shepherd, started having trouble breathing in mid-April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors' approval ratings drop as cases mount...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/509722-governors-approval-ratings-drop-as-covid-19-cases-mount</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters growing weary after months of the coronavirus pandemic are increasingly critical of their governors, especially in states where those governors raced to reopen the economy and are now suffering a surge in new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama to deliver eulogy at John Lewis funeral where Presidents Bush and Clinton will attend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1223604/obama-eulogy-john-lewiss-funeral-bush-clinton-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARACK Obama is reportedly going to deliver the eulogy at Rep. John Lewis’ funeral. Former US Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton will also be at the Thursday funeral – but Trump will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico's power grid fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/puerto-ricos-power-grid-fails-hours-ahead-of-potential-arrival-of-tropical-storm/ar-BB17l0tN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA'S DEADLIEST DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-reports-217-more-people-have-died-from-covid-19-the-highest-of-pandemic/ar-BB17l3VS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fires gun in Miami hotel because people weren't social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/man-fires-gun-in-miami-hotel-because-people-weren-t-social-distancing-police-say/ar-BB17lylv?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 30 Million in USA Didn't Have Enough to Eat Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/almost-30-million-in-us-didn-e2-80-99t-have-enough-to-eat-last-week/ar-BB17ldBN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born-again fiscal conservatives are sign of Trump's weakening hand in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Born-again-fiscal-conservatives-are-sign-of-15443923.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A growing number of Senate conservatives have provided the latest sign of President Donald Trump's weakening hand on Capitol Hill.  From the presidentially ambitious Sens. Ted Cruz, R-Tex., and Josh Hawley, R-Mo., to onetime deficit hawks like Sen. Patrick J. Toomey, R-Pa., conservatives are abandoning the president as his top aides struggle with negotiations on a pandemic relief bill that is Trump's last, best chance to pass legislation that could help his floundering reelection bid.  Ignoring their own record of support for adding trillions of dollars to the national debt, these conservatives have signaled that they think, in a post-Trump Republican Party, that deficits will return to the forefront just as they did in the first years of the Obama administration.  "We can't just waste money. So I'm very concerned about the amount of money we're talking about," Sen. Rick Scott, R-Fla., told reporters Tuesday after leaving a GOP huddle with White House Chief of Staff Mark Meadows and Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin.  Those Trump advisers negotiated with Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., for a week until they rolled out proposals that totaled $1 trillion, a figure that left Scott stumped.  "A lot of money," he said.  Others washed their hands of the negotiations and said that Trump's advisers would negotiate an even larger compromise with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., whose initial offering two months ago cost $3 trillion.  "It's a mess. I can't figure out what this bill's about," Hawley said leaving the same meeting Tuesday. "This is not going to be the bill. They're going to go negotiate with Pelosi. We have no idea what the final bill will be, and we'll be the last to know."  And Sen. Ben Sasse, R-Neb., fresh off winning his primary, with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baghdad soars to 125&amp;#8457;, its highest recorded temp... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/temperature-soars-124-ancient-desert-204217413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high temperatures will continue to be challenged across the Middle East this week as blistering heat and dry conditions remain over the region.The week got off to a blazing start in Baghdad, Iraq, with a temperature reading of 50.6 C (123.1 F) on Monday. But on Tuesday, the temperature climbed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE A MINUTE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730001802-03zgs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CASUALTIES (UPDATE 2, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-U.S. records a coronavirus death every minute as total surpasses 150,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona leads multi-state probe into older iPhones slowing, shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200729181342-8fnch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE-PROBE/ (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Arizona leads multi-state probe into older iPhones slowing, shutting down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci suggests wearing goggles or eye shields... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/dr-fauci-wear-goggles-eye-shields-prevent-spread/story?id=72059055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Fauci says in order to best prevent spreading or catching COVID-19, you should consider using goggles or a face shield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump TWITTER doc says Jesus will destroy FACEBOOK if doesn't put vid back...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1223386/doctor-says-jesus-will-destroy-facebook-over-covid-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HOUSTON doctor who went viral because of a now-deleted video where she touted hydroxychloroquine as a “cure” for COVID-19 has said Jesus Christ will destroy Facebook’s servers if the footage is n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to Unveil Ugliest GDP Report Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-is-about-to-unveil-the-ugliest-gdp-report-ever-recorded/ar-BB17jsXO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil reopens to foreigners...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/brazil-lifts-four-month-ban-on-foreigners-arriving-by-air-despite-virus-surge-decree-jhb-ch-01596075904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil reopened Wednesday to foreign visitors arriving by plane, hoping to revive its lockdown-devastated tourism industry despite the rapid spread of the new coronavirus in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST DEATHS SINCE MAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1288603954985578498?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top exec sees $200 million windfall...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/29/kodaks-top-exec-sees-200-million-windfall-on-stock-frenzy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The net worth of Kodak’s top executive has skyrocketed on the company’s transformation from an ailing camera maker to cutting-edge pharmaceutical start-up — thanks in part to some timely share purc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg  undergoes bile duct procedure in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-supreme-court-justice-ginsburg-000443552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is resting comfortably after undergoing a non-surgical medical procedure on a bile duct stent on Wednesday at a New York City hospital, the court said. Ginsburg, at 87 the oldest member of the Supreme Court and its senior liberal justice, expects to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Consider PAYING Infected To Self-Quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/la-los-angeles-covid-city-council-positive-test-pay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles City Council is considering plans to pay Angelenos who test positive for COVID-19 to stay home.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
