<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Gold shines as virus surge unnerves...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets/gold-shines-as-coronavirus-surge-unnerves-investors-idUSKBN23U3J0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold prices surged to their highest in nearly eight years on Wednesday, while global shares cooled as signs of an acceleration in coronavirus cases kept investors on edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Known Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/06/24/882683463/the-computer-got-it-wrong-how-facial-recognition-led-to-a-false-arrest-in-michig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Williams says his driver's license photo was incorrectly matched with a wanted suspect. He says he was arrested and detained. Though the case was dropped, Williams says its effect is lasting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin state senator attacked as demonstrations turn violent...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/national-international/crowds-tear-down-statues-attack-wisconsin-state-senator/2394552/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds outside the Wisconsin State Capitol tore down two statues and attacked a state senator amid protests following the arrest of a Black man who was at a restaurant with a megaphone and a baseball bat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia holds massive show of military might in Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/24/russia-victory-day-parade-2020-why-it-matters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is holding its annual Victory Day parade in Moscow on Wednesday, but the event is more than a historic commemoration to Putin and the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of selling about to hit stock market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/23/theres-a-wave-of-selling-estimated-to-be-in-the-billions-thats-about-to-hit-the-stock-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the stock market's sharp gains this quarter, traders are expecting more volatility as investors take gains from equities and move them into bonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turns focus to Wisconsin with battle-tested hires...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joe-biden-turns-focus-wisconsin-093227111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden is turning to a quartet of experienced Wisconsin political operatives to lead his campaign in a state that helped deliver President Donald Trump an Electoral College majority four years ago. Wisconsin, where Trump won by fewer than 23,000 votes in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals Counting Beds Again...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/coronavirus/hospitals-are-counting-beds-again-with-virus-cases-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As several U.S. states see a rising swell of Covid-19 patients, hospitals are trying to avoid a scenario where they face more sick patients than they have beds to hold them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog celebrates 20th birthday; Named oldest golden retriever in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsls.com/news/2020/06/24/tenneessee-dog-turns-20-sets-record-for-oldest-living-golden-retriever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsls.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tennessee dog is proving that age is just a number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Herd immunity music festival' set for July...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/herd-immunity-festival-music-coronavirus-wisconsin-a9583016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY: Longtime congressman falls behind insurgent left-wing challenger...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/eliot-engel-falls-behind-early-in-ny-primary-as-dems-progressive-wing-appears-insurgent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime U.S. Rep. Eliot Engel of New York, who was first elected in 1988 and rose to become one of the most powerful Democrats in the House, was substantially trailing middle school principal Jamaal Bowman in Tuesday's primary -- which could mark the second major upset of a veteran New York City Democratic congressman in just two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charleston removes slavery advocate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/john-c-calhoun-statue-charleston-removing-staunch-slavery-advocate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for removal of monument to early 19th century U.S. vice president and U.S. senator have long been controversial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Escapism: Isolationist Travel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/24/the-new-escapism-isolationist-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From taking cooking classes in the home of a local to learning traditional crafts from Indigenous people, much of travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden Takes Dominant Lead as Voters Reject Trump on Virus and Race...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/24/biden-takes-dominant-lead-as-voters-reject-trump-on-virus-and-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph R. Biden Jr. has taken a commanding lead over President Trump in the 2020 race, building a wide advantage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDOFF IN HIMALAYAS: India deploys more forces as China holds ground...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-reinforces-flashpoint-area-china-holds-ground-sources-094904239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian fighter jets roared over a flashpoint Himalayan region Wednesday as part of a show of strength following what military sources say has been a Chinese takeover of contested territory. Chinese forces have held onto a chunk of land covering several square kilometres (miles) at the mouth of the Galwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't open the door!: Haunted house goes drive-in...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dont-open-door-japan-haunted-house-goes-drive-064751860.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside a car, guests can scream as loudly as they like, with no mask required, as hideous creatures daubed in blood swarm towards them. In fact, the new format might even be scarier than a traditional haunted house, producer Kenta Iwana, 25, told AFP. "At the drive-in haunted house, guests are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Desperate' Fiji eyes tourism bubble...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/desperate-fiji-eyes-virus-free-tourism-bubble-033720066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourism-reliant Fiji has proposed a "travel bubble" to welcome visitors from virus-free countries, as the South Pacific holiday hotspot desperately tries to revive its stalled economy. Without streams of international travellers flocking to their palm-fringed shores, tens of thousands of Fijians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER SPIKE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/32cb14de009bfff91bc76a967323c621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — New coronavirus cases in the U.S. have surged to their highest level in two months and are now back to where they were at the peak of the outbreak. The U.S. on Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A generational time bomb going off'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/the-fighter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Gen Zer Madison Cawthorn battles to replace Mark Meadows in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President cut robocall for defeated candidate...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/jmartNYT/status/1275601875325333505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President drives immigration message amid pandemic and civil unrest... </title>
      <link>https://www.westport-news.com/news/article/Trump-visits-border-wall-to-drive-immigration-15361294.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.westport-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LUIS, Ariz. - President Donald Trump toured a border fence along the U.S.-Mexico divide here Tuesday, seeking to tout what he views as a key reelection accomplishment in a critical state as his bid for a second term has been upended by a resurgent pandemic, an economic crisis and racial unrest.  Trump, who has increasingly focused on immigration amid the coronavirus crisis, said he was marking the 200th mile of border wall erected since his election and reviving one of the most contentious issues of a first term now defined by more pressing challenges.  "It's never mentioned anymore - the wall is never mentioned anymore," Trump said during a roundtable in Yuma, Ariz. "The reason it's not mentioned - it's not that we won the battle. It's that it's such a compelling thing to have done. Because you see the number, and where that wall is going, as you're seeing, it's like magic."  While visiting the border, Trump put his signature on a plaque attached to the barrier.  The trip - more than three hours on Air Force One to a state dealing with a record-high spike in coronavirus cases - was itself controversial because Trump and his aides continued to flout public health guidelines at the same time that top administration officials were testifying before Congress about the growing threat of the coronavirus, which causes the disease covid-19.  Neither Trump nor his aides wore masks during the visit to Arizona, which included the border wall tour and a speech to a crowded group of young supporters in Phoenix. Public health officials have argued against unnecessary travel and several testified Tuesday about the need to maintain social distancing and other preventive measures.  Calling the coronavirus pandemic the "greatest public health crisis" that the United States has faced in more than a century, Centers for Disease Control...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REOPENINGS IN DISARRAY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/virus-surges-across-us-throwing-reopenings-into-disarray/ar-BB15SSck?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida 17-year-old is youngest ine state to die...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-17-year-old-is-the-youngest-in-the-state-to-die-from-coronavirus-records-show/ar-BB15SETI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS RESIDENTS URGED TO STAY INSIDE</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/public-health/2020/06/23/spread-is-so-rampant-texas-hits-all-time-high-of-more-than-5k-new-covid-19-cases-gov-greg-abbott-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Gov. Greg Abbott sternly warned Texans of “rampant” spread of coronavirus that took the state to a new high Tuesday of more than 5,000 new cases...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhode Island may change official name...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rhode-island-moves-to-change-states-official-name-due-to-slavery-connotations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current official state name is "The State of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate committee aims to regulate UFO information...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-senate-committee-aims-regulate-ufo-information-235837761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Senate intelligence committee is aiming to regulate a Pentagon UFO program so that the public is better informed of its activities and the country's intelligence branches can more easily share information. The panel said that it "supports the efforts of the Unidentified Aerial Phenomenon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILD THAT WALL? Only three new miles have been constructed in locations where 'no border barriers previously existed'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-campaigns-border-wall-progress-230002232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's visit to a refurbished section of border wall in Yuma highlighted his difficulty finding achievements he can run on in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA CASES HIT NEW HIGH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/record-high-coronavirus-cases-reported-194105184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the state, the positivity rate among those tested for coronavirus has risen from 4.5% to 4.8%, and the number of hospitalizations is up 16%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ POPS 77% IN WEEK</title>
      <link>https://azbigmedia.com/business/covid-19-cases-in-arizona-increase-by-single-day-record-of-3591/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;azbigmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state passed a tough milestone on Monday as the number of confirms COVID-19 cases in Arizona topped 1,000 for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump family seeks to block book by president's niece that calls him 'world's most dangerous man'... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-family-seeks-to-block-book-by-president-s-15361378.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's brother on Tuesday petitioned a New York court to block the publication of a book by Mary Trump that describes her uncle President Donald Trump as the "world's most dangerous man."  Presales of the book, scheduled for publication on July 28, have soared to the top of best-seller lists on the basis of a description from publisher Simon &amp; Schuster that it will reveal decades of family secrets, including a "nightmare of traumas" that explain the psychology of the man who is now president.  President Trump told the Axios news service earlier this week that Mary Trump is "not allowed" to write the book because she signed a non-disclosure agreement in 2001 that settled her suit against Donald Trump and his siblings regarding her inheritance from her grandfather Fred Trump Sr., Donald Trump's father. President Trump said the agreement was a "very powerful one" that "covers everything."  In the petition to stop publication, President Trump's brother Robert Trump said Mary Trump had agreed as part of a settlement related to the inheritance fight that she "would not publish any account" of her relationship with Donald Trump or his siblings.  The terms of the agreement, which were disclosed as part of the petition to stop the book, required that Mary Trump not "directly or indirectly publish" any account of her relationship with the Trump family unless she had permission from Donald Trump and his siblings. The terms of that agreement had not previously been made public.  The petition was filed in Queens County Surrogate's Court in New York.  Mary Trump's lawyer Theodore Boutrous said in a statement that the family's effort to restrain publication should be tossed out.  "President Trump and his siblings seek to suppress a book that will discuss matters of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON SAYS PRESIDENT MAY NOT LEAVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/bolton-asked-whether-trump-will-leave-the-white-house-peacefully-if-he-loses-says-i-certainly-hope-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton continued his media tour Tuesday with Washington Post reporter Robert Costa, who asked him directly if he thinks the president would respect the peaceful transfer of power if he loses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's best restaurant serves food in phase with moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200623-world-s-best-restaurant-serves-food-in-phase-with-the-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World's best restaurant serves food in phase with the moon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Rushmore Doomed?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/06/23/nolte-mount-rushmore-is-doomed-to-the-1619-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no way Mount Rushmore can survive the insurgency of left-wing domestic terrorism currently unfolding in our country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toppled, beheaded, daubed: Controversial statues...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/toppled-beheaded-daubed-controversial-statues-01592936104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests in the wake of African American George Floyd's killing by white police officers in the United States have led to the toppling and vandalism of statues of controversial historical and political figures, often linked to slavery or colonisation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's long, hot bloody summer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/23/video-shows-calm-nyc-man-with-knife-sticking-out-of-his-head/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It looks like a scene out of a freaking movie,” one witness said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU TO BAN AMERICAN TRAVELERS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eu-may-bar-american-travelers-185057247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS -- European Union countries rushing to revive their economies and reopen their borders after months of coronavirus restrictions are prepared to block Americans from entering because the United States has failed to control the scourge, according to draft lists of acceptable travelers seen by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bonds Top Monthly Sales Record!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/junk-bonds-topple-monthly-sales-214812312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Companies shoring up cash to survive the global pandemic raised funds in the U.S. high-yield market at the fastest monthly pace ever.Junk issuers have already sold $46.7 billion of bonds in June, surpassing the prior monthly record of $46.4 billion in September 2013, according to data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  7.4. MAG QUAKE MEXICO...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c64d518478e4f17ed88a58ba3f315023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — A powerful earthquake centered near the southern Mexico resort of Huatulco killed at least five people, swayed buildings in Mexico City and sent thousands fleeing into the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor: Trump ally Roger Stone was 'treated differently'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b60e1e1050d5142b06c5df3f1da4ea87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal prosecutor is prepared to tell Congress on Wednesday that Roger Stone, a close ally of President Donald Trump, was given special treatment ahead of his sentencing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR rallies around Wallace in poignant moment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/477e25d986ac0539ea2e64d436d4d0cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no escaping it: NASCAR is a white-dominated sport with a predominantly white fan base and a longstanding reputation as being far from inclusive. Its evolution, such as it is, has been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charleston votes to remove slavery advocate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3e3d4a9cf077ae2cb45f2fa1dc517d5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) — Officials in the historic South Carolina city of Charleston voted unanimously Tuesday to remove a statue of former vice president and slavery advocate John C....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural Missouri pastor: Virus 'just started to sprout up'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3baea7b87a0ba98dc6b011bd7cf2f3d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'FALLON, Mo. (AP) — Pastor Joshua Manning is waiting for test results, but he can tell by the persistent fever and body aches that he probably has the coronavirus. His wife and three kids have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No charges in NASCAR noose incident involving Black driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/No-charges-in-NASCAR-noose-incident-involving-15361098.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The noose found hanging in Bubba Wallace's garage stall at Talladega Superspeedway had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Today is day 93': Symptoms lasting months...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/today-is-day-93-people-report-experiencing-covid-19-symptoms-that-last-for-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the first reported cases of the novel coronavirus, several support groups have emerged on Facebook consisting of thousands of members calling themselves “long haul survivors,” reporting COVID-19 symptoms that they say have lasted for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buildings collapsed, residents evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/23/weather/mexico-earthquake-southern-coast-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two people have died after a 7.4 magnitude earthquake hit Mexico's southern coastline on Tuesday, collapsing buildings and prompting evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors making biggest bet against stock market in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/23/some-investors-are-making-the-biggest-bet-against-the-stock-market-in-nine-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are making the biggest bet in the futures market since 2011 that the stock market is going to sell off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestor charges NBC Andrea Mitchell, DC Congresswoman...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/henryrodgersdc/status/1275506187400863746</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First US airline pilot with diabetes captains commercial flight...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/first-commercial-pilot-diabetes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an aviation milestone, Captain Bob Halicky becomes the first US commercial pilot with insulin-treated diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Tops 5,000 New Cases In 1 Day For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/06/23/texas-surpasses-5k-new-cases-coronavirus-spreading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes days after Texas eclipsed 4,000 new cases for the first time just last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin considers ending coronavirus emergency, even as cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-administration-has-considered-ending-coronavirus-emergency-even-as-cases-surge/ar-BB15SX8D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Putting Off Marriage, Kids For Financial Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-replacing-traditional-goals-like-marriage-having-kids-with-financial-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A poll of 2,000 Americans finds that most adults are putting off traditional life milestones like marriage, starting a family, and saving for retirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggers local Pacific tsunami...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-quake-idUSKBN23U2KD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful earthquake of magnitude 7.4 struck the coast of southern Mexico on Tuesday, killing at least one person, buckling paved roads, and setting off a tsunami in nearby Pacific coastal areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  TEXAS THISCLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://progresstexas.org/blog/new-poll-shows-biden-within-striking-distance-trump-texas-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;progresstexas.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is still the biggest battleground state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Thing That Would Stop Sports Now: Player's Death...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/06/the-only-thing-that-would-stop-sports-now.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A player dying from the coronavirus is an unlikely but real possibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Sentencing Was Politicized, Ex-Prosecutor Plans to Testify...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/23/roger-stone-sentencing-was-politicized-ex-prosecutor-plans-to-testify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior law enforcement officials intervened to seek a more lenient prison sentence for President Trump’s friend and ally Roger J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RON JEREMY CHARGED WITH RAPING 3 WOMEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/adult-film-star-ron-jeremy-charged-with-raping-3-women-sexually-assaulting-another/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult film star Ron Jeremy has been charged with "forcibly raping three women and sexually assaulting another in separate incidents dating back to 2014."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic after giant mushroom-shaped cloud fills sky near Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/panic-after-giant-mushroom-shaped-22233303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge cloud was spotted in Kiev, Ukraine, just 60 miles away from Chernobyl, which was the site of the worlds worst nuclear disaster in 1986, but officials told residents not to panic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Preps for Blue Wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/23/wall-street-firm-tells-clients-senate-will-flip-to-democrats-as-biden-surges.html?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial advisory firm Signum Global Advisors is telling clients that it now believes the U.S. Senate is going to flip blue as Joe Biden continues surge past President Donald Trump in the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Attacked Journalist. Then Police Handcuffed Her...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/06/23/dc-protesters-black-house-autonomous-zone-shelby-talcott-park-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dispatch from the Black House Autonomous Zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FELONY COMPLAINT...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/los-angeles/ron-jeremy-charged-275893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn star Ron Jeremy was charged today with raping three women and sexually assaulting a fourth female victim in attacks dating back to 2014, according to California prosecutors. Jeremy (real name:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx Contradicts, Privately Tells Govs to Keep Going...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dr-birx-contradicts-trump-privately-tells-govs-to-increase-covid-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her encouragement comes as governors concede to the feds that people are not abiding by their phased down public health guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence falls while boarding Air Force 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pence-falls-while-boarding-air-force-2-signals-he-is-okay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence took a spill while he was climbing the stairs to board Air Force Two on Tuesday morning but appeared to be just fine, recovering and indicating that nothing was wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock Decision: Cosby Granted Appeal In Sex Assault Conviction...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/06/23/bill-cosby-granted-appeal-in-pennsylvania-sex-assault-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Bill Cosby has won the right to fight his 2018 sexual assault conviction before the Pennsylvania Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea reportedly threatens 'new round of Korean War' to end USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/23/north-korea-threatens-new-round-of-the-korean-war-to-end-us-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea's embassy in Moscow has threatened to use its nation's nuclear weapons against the United States in what they claim would be “a particularly sensational event.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.4. MAG QUAKE MEXICO...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/powerful-quake-strikes-southern-mexico-tsunami-warning-issued-170245507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful 7.4 magnitude earthquake struck southern Mexico on Tuesday, triggering a tsunami warning along Central America's Pacific coast and as far south as Ecuador. The epicenter was near Crucecita, in the southeastern state of Oaxaca, but the shock wave was felt as far away as Mexico City, some</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU TO BAN AMERICAN TRAVELERS</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/23/eu-may-ban-travel-from-us-as-it-reopens-borders-citing-coronavirus-failures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS — European Union countries rushing to revive their economies and reopen their borders after months of coronavirus restrictions are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President 'strategically stretches truth to manipulate media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-strategically-stretches-truth-to-manipulate-media-former-adviser-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump routinely strategically exaggerates his achievements and stretches the truth to manipulate the media, according to a former adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will bring 'worst air pollution in 50 years'... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1026862/godzilla-saharan-dust-caribbean-america-atlantic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ENORMOUS plume of Saharan dust, nicknamed ‘Godzilla’, is heading for the U.S. bringing the “worst air pollution in 50 years”. The Saharan Air Layer (SAL) first appeared o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swimmer catches  8-foot SHARK with his bare hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1026443/man-catches-shark-poses-pictures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN swimming at a Cape Henlopen State Park beach in Delaware over the weekend caught a large shark with his bare hands and posed for photos, a video obtained by TMZ shows. The man in knee-deep wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY:  Three in 10 have defied coronavirus quarantine rules to have sex!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1026186/coronavirus-americans-quarantine-rules-sex-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THREE in 10 Americans have flouted coronavirus lockdown rules to sleep with someone, according to a new study. Research conducted by British sexual health company MysteryVibe found that although 58…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland Security' Expands Internal Surveillance Operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2020/06/dhs-insider-threat-program-expanding-anyone-who-accesses-agency-info/166325/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MORE testing, not LESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/fauci-says-u-s-will-expand-testing-not-slow-it-n1231877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump told a crowd of his supporters Saturday at his first campaign rally in months that he wanted to slow down testing for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS PLUNGING, BUT CAN'T COUNT HIM OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-polls-are-plunging-but-it-e2-80-99s-too-early-to-count-him-out/ar-BB15REKL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replace torn-down monuments with Trump statues, Don Jr. says!</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article243730972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAGGER:  'He was such a kind and generous friend'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8449383/Kangaroo-Jack-writer-Steve-Bing-55-jumps-death-27th-floor-LA-apartment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Hurley said she is 'saddened beyond belief' after Steve Bing, a millionaire real estate heir who she dated in the early 2000s and who fathered her son Damian, killed himself Monday, aged 55.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Sahara desert dust plume drifting toward United States...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/saharan-dust-plume-drifting-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dust plume appears to be one of the most extreme in recent memory, and it's heading for the southeastern U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TORCHES FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/DavidBrodyCBN/status/1275407463693590528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE SATELLITE SHOWS THE DIRT...</title>
      <link>https://rammb-slider.cira.colostate.edu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rammb-slider.cira.colostate.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.4. MAG QUAKE MEXICO</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623151437-eljxn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Strong quake hits southern Mexico, people run into streets in capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Message Urges Chicago Officers To Call In Sick, Limit Arrests...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/text-message-urges-chicago-police-officers-to-call-in-sick-limit-arrests-in-a-blue-flu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Along with a spike in violence in Chicago this past weekend comes with a new push by members of the police union to get officers on the street to stand down – and even stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Pro Sports Really Return In 2020?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/coronavirus-cases-questions-increasing-can-sports-return-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does it look like sports leagues have a workable set of protocols in place to ensure that games can actually be played safely? After the developments from recent weeks -- and particularly last Friday -- it's awfully difficult to have any level of confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Few Weeks Critical...</title>
      <link>https://bestlifeonline.com/fauci-most-disturbing-trend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bestlifeonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci, M.D., expressed grave concern over the recent rise in coronavirus cases in a number of U.S. states that reopened earlier than other states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winona Ryder Accuses Mel Gibson of Making Anti-Semitic and Homophobic Remarks...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/winona-ryder-mel-gibson-oven-dodger-1234646288/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winona Ryder has accused Mel Gibson of making anti-semitic and anti-gay comments in an interview with The Sunday Times. The “Stranger Things” star was asked by a reporter if she has exp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican former U.S. national security officials to back...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623150306-v5ank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/BIDEN-REPUBLICANS (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Republican former U.S. national security officials to back Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.4. MAG QUAKE MEXICO</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us6000ah9t/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans actually drinking less during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/life/drinks/2020/06/23/Americans-drinking-less-pandemic-alcohol-wine-sales/stories/202006230055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the coronavirus pandemic, people are drinking less. (Yes, you read that correctly.) While the masses are buying more booze from grocers and liquor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE STIMULUS</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Trump-tells-aides-he-supports-second-round-of-15359525.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has told aides he is largely supportive of sending Americans another round of stimulus checks, believing the payments will boost the economy and help his chances at reelection in November, according to three people aware of internal administration deliberations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER: NASDAQ NEW RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/22/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overnight, stock futures turned negative after White House trade advisor Peter Navarro told Fox News in a Monday interview that the trade deal with China was "over."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro ordered to wear mask in public...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-53154890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brazilian leader has belittled the risk posed by coronavirus and attended anti-lockdown rallies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT RIPS VIRUS 'CONFESSION'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/504038-lincoln-project-hits-trump-on-testing-confession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lincoln Project, an anti-Trump Republican super PAC, slammed President Trump in a new ad on Tuesday after he quipped that he encouraged administration officials to slow down coronavirus testing and blamed it for increased cases in the U.S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN: Russia to raise taxes on high earners after coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://rtvi.com/news_en/putin-announces-tax-hike-on-top-earners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rtvi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin proposed to raise the country's income tax rate from 13% to 15% for people earning over 5 million roubles (over $72,800) a year in a nationally televised address on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-covid-19-cases-surge-111157223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-five U.S. states reported more new cases last week than the previous week, including 10 states that saw weekly new infections rise more than 50%, and 12 states that posted new records, according to the analysis of data from The COVID Tracking Project, a volunteer-run effort to track the outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Trump to issue order on monuments, threatens force against DC protesters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623133258-dobya</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS-POLICE/STATUES-TRUMP (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Trump to issue order on U.S. monuments, threatens force against D.C. protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Reopening Party Season Already Fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-coronavirus-outlook-veers-toward-disaster-as-young-people-lean-into-reopening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strip clubs. Bars. Pools and golf clubs. Pro sports. As one doctor put it, “There’s active community spread. If you’re young, you’re old, it doesn’t matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to face McConnell hurtles toward unpredictable finish...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/22/booker-mcgrath-kentucky-senate-334617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Charles Booker is still considered the underdog in Tuesday’s primary against Amy McGrath, the party favorite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS: TEXAS CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL ADMITTING ADULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/health/coronavirus/texas-childrens-hospital-admitting-adult-patients-as-covid-19-cases-continue-to-rise/285-5aa0a132-a318-4a41-81b3-6659086c2ef7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One pediatrician tweeted that she is up for the challenge, but she also asked the public to wear a mask and stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/23/us/us-coronavirus-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With half of US states reporting a rise in new cases, one expert warns of 'danger signs' in some parts of the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clash near White House prompts Secret Service to tell press to leave grounds in unusual move...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/22/politics/white-house-secret-service-press/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A confrontation between protesters and police in the park across the street from the White House on Monday evening led the US Secret Service to take the unusual step of ordering members of the White House press corps to immediately leave the grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton on Trump second term: Be afraid...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bolton-trump-second-term-b16f9ec9-1d0a-4749-8753-567ae06af00a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two subjects the former national security wouldn't discuss: his legal situation and note-taking practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore restaurant denies service to Black woman, son...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/baltimore/2020/06/restaurant-apologizes-after-black-woman-son-denied-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore restaurant issued an apology after video showed a Black woman and her son being denied service because of the boy’s clothes while a white child dressed a similar way had been served.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's #1 tennis player Djokovic positive after hosting tournament!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/504032-worlds-1-tennis-player-novak-djokovic-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's top-ranked tennis player, Novak Djokovic, said on Tuesday that he tested positive for the novel coronavirus after participating in an exhibition series he organized in Serbia and Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AMAZON Delivery Driver Dumps Packages Into Sewer...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/amazon-delivery-drive-packages-thrown-in-sewer-maryland-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after an Amazon delivery driver was caught on camera allegedly throwing packages down a sewer in Parkville, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jun/23/first-thing-covid-19-cases-surging-us-states-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infections have risen in 29 states, with several breaking their daily records. Plus, how a botched assassination plot exposed the rot in Russia’s spy services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-Church Set to Host Rally Falsely Claim Air Filter Zaps COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/arizona-mega-church-set-to-host-trump-rally-falsely-claim-its-air-filter-zaps-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dream City Church’s claim that it has technology to kill the coronavirus and protect rallygoers “is absurd,” says one epidemiologist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENNIS STAR DJOKOVIC POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennis.com/pro-game/2020/06/world-no-1-novak-djokovic-tests-positive-coronavirus/89329/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Serb has come under tremendous criticism since Grigor Dimitrov&amp;#39;s positive test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC SCAPEGOAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/23/trump-cdc-overhaul-coronavirus-335039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Trump under fire for his handling of the outbreak, his advisers are eyeing the federal bureaucracy for other culprits ahead of the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky meat plant cited, penalized after cow shot in the head 4 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/state/kentucky/article243711552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS PLUNGING...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-s-polls-are-plunging-but-it-s-too-early-to-count-him-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every recent poll shows President Donald Trump headed to defeat in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI TESTIFIES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a36ac8c2b3edf7f9c41f850e945c32e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With coronavirus cases rising in about half the states and political polarization competing for attention with public health recommendations, Dr. Anthony Fauci returns to Capitol...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
