<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>France investigates secret restaurants for Paris elite...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-france-931e731b1d0485ef938a4911944cc5b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Champagne, lobster and no masks: That's what a French TV documentary says is on the menu at one of multiple high-end “clandestine restaurants” catering to the Paris elite, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  GLOBAL TAX!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/janet-yellen-minimum-global-corporate-income-tax-0a839a4705566a8b9f8bd5411bfe62d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Monday urged the adoption of a minimum global corporate income tax, an effort to at least partially offset any disadvantages that might...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Absolutely' Violated Policy, Minneapolis Police Chief Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/derek-chauvin-absolutely-violated-policy-minneapolis-police-chief-says/ar-BB1fksxA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief of the Minneapolis Police Department testified on Monday that Derek Chauvin had “absolutely” violated department policies when he knelt on George Floyd for more than nine minutes in May, saying Mr. Chauvin “should have stopped” when Mr. Floyd was calling out for help. Chief Medaria Arradondo said in court that Mr. Chauvin, who has been charged with murder, had failed to follow department policies on use-of-force, de-escalation, and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO: Full House As 40K Fans Fill Seats For RANGERS Opening Day!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/with-100-capacity-allowed-rangers-see-packed-stands-for-home-opener-at-globe-life-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 40,000 fans were inside Globe Life Field in Arlington Monday afternoon for the Texas Rangers' home opener.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOURTH Stimulus Check In The Works?</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/stimulus-check-update-fourth-relief-payment-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the latest round of stimulus checks already distributed to most eligible Americans, many wonder if additional aid is forthcoming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER halts vax shipments to Israel after country fails to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/banana-republic-pfizer-outraged-israel-failed-to-pay-for-covid-vaccines-664140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shipment of 700,000 doses was expected to arrive in Israel on Sunday but was halted until further notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU, Privacy Champion, Sharing Personal Info with FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/aclu-data-shares-facebook-4f1d21f4-d432-4998-8c67-364500015c28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even organizations that don't like Facebook still find it an effective way to reach people online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS Not Following Guidance on PFIZER Spacing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/walgreens-not-following-u-s-guidance-on-pfizer-vaccine-spacing/ar-BB1fjIqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens has inoculated hundreds of thousands of Americans against Covid-19 this year using the vaccine developed by Pfizer and Germany’s BioNTech. But the pharmacy chain has not been following guidance from federal health officials about the timing of second doses. People are supposed to get two doses, three weeks apart. Walgreens, however, separated them by four weeks because that made it faster and simpler for the company to schedule...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid rule-breaker 'dies after exercise punishment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56641398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was allegedly forced to do exercises after buying water during a curfew in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi to allow only 'immunised' pilgrims to Mecca...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210405-saudi-to-allow-only-immunised-pilgrims-to-mecca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi to allow only 'immunised' pilgrims to Mecca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible second breach at toxic wastewater reservoir in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/possible-second-breach-toxic-wastewater-reservoir-florida-officials-say-n1263064</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone spotted the potential additional leak at about 2 a.m., forcing a brief evacuation of engineers at the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov Abbott Declines Invitation To Throw First Pitch At RANGERS Opening Game...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/texas-governor-mlb-false-narrative-voter-integrity-laws-1st-pitch-rangers-opener/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Greg Abbott declined to throw out the ceremonial first pitch at the opening game of the Texas Rangers because of his displeasure with Major League Baseball's decision to move this summer's All-Star game after sweeping changes to voting laws in Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Pilot Accused Of Exposing Genitals During Flight...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/southwest-pilot-michael-haak-accused-of-exposing-genitals-in-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities say pilot Michael Haak exposed his genitals in acts that began, continued and ended while flight 6607 on Aug. 10 was in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol arrests terror suspects in CA amid migrant surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/5/border-patrol-arrests-two-terrorist-suspects-calif/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol announced Monday that agents arrested two Yemeni men who were on the FBI’s terrorist watch list over the past two months, confirming Republican lawmakers’ reports that terrorism suspects were attempting to sneak into the country as part of the migrant surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Video Of Clandestine Luxury Dinner In Paris Prompts Police Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2021/04/05/984409984/undercover-video-of-clandestine-luxury-restaurants-in-paris-prompts-police-inqui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Once you pass through the door, there's no more COVID," a man told a visitor to one exclusive pop-up dining spot. The high-priced menu included Champagne and foie gras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White People Keep Posing As People of Color for Clout...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3vpn4/white-people-keep-posing-as-people-of-color-for-clout-identity-theft-racial-appropriation-v28n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For generations, people of color have had to pass for survival. Now white people are wearing the experiences of racialized people like a costume—and getting called out for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END THE HYGIENE THEATER, CDC SAYS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/end-the-hygiene-theater-cdc-says-173440864.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time to unplug the sanitizing robots and put away the bottles of Clorox that seem to line the entrance to every school, restaurant and supermarket wanting to advertise its safety protocols. While such protocols may be reassuring to an anxious populace, they are not necessary, revised guidance issued on Monday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skepticism runs deep among white evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-baptist-coronavirus-pandemic-southern-baptist-convention-32898166bbb673ad87842af24c8daefb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of the Southern Baptist Convention, America’s largest evangelical denomination, posted a photo on Facebook last week of him getting the COVID-19 vaccine. It drew more than 1,100...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Travel on Hold for UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/johnson-eases-lockdown-but-foreign-travel-on-hold-for-u-k/ar-BB1fkfNb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson confirmed restaurants, pubs and shops will open again as England’s lockdown is eased next week, but the ban on foreign travel may remain for longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Fed took control of economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/economy-federal-reserve-fed-control-2cc60f7f-4cde-43c7-9b83-5fa01d025b4a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with this control, the Fed has by its own admission failed to fully reach its goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Dead In TX Home In Suspected Murder-Suicide 'Pact'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/allen-murder-suicide-pact-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said there's a social media post by one of the victims saying he made a pact with his brother to kill his family and commit suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says trial is attempt at 'judicial coup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/netanyahu-says-trial-is-a-witch-hunt-against-him-and-his-family-664185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  How evangelicals made Donald the new Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/161888/matt-labash-eric-metaxas-debate-trump-evangelicalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In which journalist Matt Labash (a Never Trumper) and radio host Eric Metaxas (a Trump supporter) agree to disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida bar owner didn't get in trouble for banning masks. But strip show landed him in jail!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-Florida-bar-owner-didn-t-get-in-trouble-for-16077074.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, Gary Kirby has banned masks and social distancing at his bar on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some patients get second shot at life thanks to lung transplants...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/some-covid-19-patients-get-second-shot-at-life-thanks-to-lung-transplants/article_476c942a-e96d-57e6-a658-7e25881161f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio — Greg Borden knew that COVID-19 would wreak havoc on his body if he caught it, but he never expected it would take his lungs in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of stabbing family member to death after bible study...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-used-samurai-knife-to-kill-elderly-family-member-in-bellwood-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is accused of stabbing an elderly family member dozens of times using a "samurai knife," killing her inside her Bellwood home before leaving with a phone and envelopes of cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules for GOOGLE in closely watched copyright case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/05/supreme-court-rules-in-googles-favor-in-copyright-dispute-with-oracle-over-android-software.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday sided with Google against Oracle in a long-running copyright dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLARENCE THOMAS: TREAT FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER LIKE UTILITIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/thomas-scotus-twitter-trump-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last fall, Justice Clarence Thomas argued that it was time to rein in Section 230 immunity. Now, Justice Thomas is laying out an argument for why companies like Facebook, Twitter and Google should be regulated as utilities. On Monday, the Supreme Court vacated a lower court ruling in finding that Pr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX, DRUGS AND MAGA?  Republicans Dumping Gaetz...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/mediaites-colby-hall-says-conservatives-are-dumping-matt-gaetz-crickets-coming-from-the-gop-caucus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite Founding Editor Colby Hall weighed in on the Department of Justice's investigation into Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL) during a Monday morning appearance on Newsmax -- pointing to the complete lack of support the congressman has received from his own party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  USA WILL NOT MANDATE VACCINE PASSPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-vaccine-passports-fauci-federal-government-ece3e53c-82a1-4a14-8e0a-a92b547fe68b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea of requiring immunization credentials has become a point of contention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican digs illegal tunnel to 'exhume King David's DNA and bring Messiah back to life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/vatican-digs-illegal-tunnel-exhume-23855934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rabbi has alleged there's a sinister plot behind the illegal construction of a passage beneath a church in Jerusalem as groups demand legal action against the tunnel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Stock Hits Record High...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/FB?qsearchterm=facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Facebook (FB:NASDAQ) real-time stock quotes, news, price and financial information from CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like Hypersonic Missile': Black Triangular Object Spotted in California Skies...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/viral/202104051082546678-like-a-hypersonic-missile-enigmatic-black-triangular-object-spotted-in-california-skies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the blogger mused about the alleged extraterrestrial nature of the phenomenon in question, some social media users suggested that it could've been a balloon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin signs law allowing him to run for two more terms in Kremlin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-putin-idUSKBN2BS18W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin signed a law allowing him to run for two more terms in the Kremlin once his current term ends in 2024, a document posted on a government website showed on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking photos of bodies strewn on ground capture horror of ISIS massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9436585/Shocking-photos-capture-horror-ISIS-Mozambique-massacre-left-one-Brit-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of innocent people were killed when Islamist insurgents launched a raid the northern town of Palma on March 24, including Briton Philip Mawer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Double mutant' strain emerges in California...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/05/double-mutant-covid-19-strain-emerges-in-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new “double mutant” variant of the coronavirus has been discovered in California — as scientists worry the strain could be more infectious. The Stanford Clinical Virology Lab id…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Worst COVID Death Rate Sends Czechs Back Into Cold War Misery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-worst-covid-death-rate-081311848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyLITOMĚŘICE, Czech Republic—A blue light flashing across bedroom windows has become a feature of the nights. This is Litoměřice, a town in the north of the Czech Republic. The light is from yet another ambulance climbing the access road that leads from the dark, deserted town to a hospital perched on a hill. On board, there is likely to be another COVID-19 patient. This is the country with the highest COVID death rate on Earth, and it’s experiencing another surge of infections.Kateřina Steinbachová, a doctor, lives next door to the Litoměřice hospital in a medical residence. A year ago, this hospital was selected to be one of the special COVID units for the northern part of the country. Ironically, the ambulance traffic is the only sign of life during these desperate nights of the pandemic.“My parents told me that the outside world looks like evenings during the communist dictatorship,” the 31-year-old doctor says.Back in the communist era, businesses would close early, there were no neon signs blinking into the night and people would rather keep to themselves at home than wander around. Boredom, anxiety and feelings of abandonment suffocated towns back then. This past year, the string of restrictions, bans, curfews and lockdowns has brought back these unhappy memories for many Czechs.“Many of my older patients have fallen into a depression, saying the surroundings now remind them of the times of the ‘Communist normalization.’ They feel like they’re being swallowed by grayness,” says psychotherapist Tomáš Rektor.He’s referring to the 1970s following the so-called Prague Spring when the Soviet tanks sent from Moscow brutally crushed the Czechoslovakian rebellion against Communist rule. The bloodshed put the Communist hardliners back in charge. They subsequently governed the country with a mixture of bureaucratic overreach and violent repression.Apart from the similarity in how things look, it is the Communist social legacy that has come into sharp relief these days. The mindset of many Czechs was formed during the dictatorship, which ended in 1989 after 42 years, when the current generation of Czech people over 50 were in the prime of their lives. This has significantly contributed to the current health crisis, analysts say.The Czech Republic’s COVID-related death rate per 100,000 remains the highest in the European Union, and so is the daily number of infected people. Dozens of hospitals are on verge of collapse, many unable to receive gravely ill patients for the lack of ICU beds and medical personnel.Dozens of hospitals in the Czech Republic have declared a “mass casualty event,” meaning that ICU beds might not be available for patients who need them. It’s gotten so critical that the Czech government has asked Germany, Switzerland and Poland to take in dozens of patients to help these overwhelmed hospitals.The current crisis here is particularly mind-blowing because the Czech Republic successfully smashed the virus during the first wave in the spring of 2020. Czechs watched in horror as Italy, their favorite vacation destination, was ravaged by the coronavirus. While hundreds of Italians were dying each day, in the Czech Republic the daily death toll in the first three months of pandemic never surpassed 10. There were even days when no one died.The COVID-19 pandemic has served as a big test for this young democracy and many believe that after the initial triumph against the virus, Czechs failed big-time. There is still a sense that people expect the government to solve their problems rather that taking personal responsibility. “Since the fall of communism, we have yet to learn how to live in freedom. We have not developed a sense of self responsibility. We prefer to delegate it onto somebody else. In this case onto the government,” said sociologist Jiřina Šiklová, who was a close ally of late President Václav Havel. She came from the same dissident circle as Havel, and she was good friends with the first freely elected head of the state after the totalitarian regime had ended.In times of crisis like the COVID pandemic, this buck-passing attitude is unlikely to serve you well if the government turns out to be incompetent. And the Czech government, under the leadership of the current, controversial prime minister, Andrej Babiš, has a long record of failed decisions and botched strategies in dealing with the COVID threat.Babiš, a former member of the Communist secret service police, acknowledged some blunders in a recent speech. Specifically, he said it was a bad decision to allow businesses to reopen for the Christmas season and that the summer relaxation of the masks wearing mandate was wrong. He also admitted that his government underestimated the British variant of the virus.The local hospital in Litoměřicre is on the receiving end of these missteps and errors. It has been overflowing with COVID patients who got infected with the dangerous British mutation.“My colleagues at the COVID units are exhausted. They have been in it for a year and, in the last few months, have had to endure war-like situations,” says Dr. Steinbachová.Many hospitals are so short of staff that they desperately keep asking for voluntary workers with little or no experience. Some even employ soldiers and firefighters. On top of these extreme circumstances, many doctors and nurses have been infected and, according to the government figures, are among the hardest hit professionals in terms of COVID contagion.And it is far from over. At the end of February this year, Prime Minister Babiš said that the month of March would be hellish. The statistics proved him right. The rate of hospitalization, the number of gravely ill and currently infected are at record levels. And this country of 10.7 million is rapidly approaching 27,000 COVID-19 related deaths. Globally, the Czech Republic sits in first place when it comes to deaths per 100,000.Pavel Žáček, a former director of the Institute for the Study of Totalitarian Regimes, said the Czech population was being forced into a period of self-examination as the required pandemic response offered echoes of their autocratic past.Developed democracies at the beginning of the pandemic could not blunt the spread of the virus because their people were not used to being told what to do and many defied restrictions, said Žáček. The autocratic regimes were more successful at enforcing rules but took advantage of the situation to go after dissenters.“The Czech Republic falls somewhere in between those two systems,” he notes, saying that on one hand many deeply distrust Babiš’s government’s handling of the pandemic, while on the other there are still large swaths of the population who demand more intervention.Žáček fears people are forgetting what they’ve learnt since the end of the Cold War.“I am worried that in the post-COVID era, a good enough number of Czechs will want the government to keep helping them,” said Žáček, “and the country will shift towards socialism again.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Loses 31% of Market Share in Year as Rivals Gain Ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/netflix-lost-31-market-share-130058085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year in which streaming became even more important to millions of Americans, thanks to the coronavirus pandemic, Netflix still dominates the streaming universe in the U.S. But new data shared by Ampere Analysis with TheWrap shows that while Netflix holds 20% of the U.S. streaming market, its dominance over the rest of the streaming landscape has shrunk from 29% — a drop of nearly one third– as more services enter the market. Here’s a snapshot of the top streaming services in the U.S. and how their market share stacks up compared to the same time last year: Also Read: Inside Hollywood's Rush to Cash in on NFTs A few points worth mentioning: • Netflix’s U.S. market share has taken a hit in the last year — even as it added a company-record 36.58 million new accounts globally in 2020. Netflix’s U.S. market share has been sliced from 29% to 20% since the start of 2020; that’s a 31% drop in the last year. • In January, Netflix reported that it had 73.94 million subscribers in both the U.S. and Canada (Netflix always reports the two markets together); an estimated 7 million of those subscribers come from north of the border, meaning Netflix has about 67 million active subscriptions in the U.S. alone. • Netflix’s slice of the overall streaming pie in the U.S. has gotten smaller as new services like HBO Max and NBCUniversal’s Peacock emerged in 2020. • The same can be said for Amazon Prime Video. A year ago, Amazon Prime Video claimed 21% of the U.S. streaming market, but that’s now down to 16% — a drop of nearly 24%. • Amazon Prime Video is a bit trickier for streaming analysts to project. For one thing, anyone who pays for an Amazon Prime subscription gets access to Prime Video, but that doesn’t necessarily mean every Prime subscriber is watching “The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel” or “Jack Ryan.” (Some may sign up for free shipping on goods.) Amazon hasn’t given an update on its total Prime memberships since early 2020, when it announced it had passed 150 million paying customers; Ampere’s data indicates nearly 54 million of Prime members use their Prime Video app in the U.S. • Disney-owned Hulu takes the bronze medal here, but that includes both its Hulu streaming service and its live TV streaming service. • This may be the most surprising aspect of Ampere’s data: Disney+ is sitting in fifth place in the U.S. streaming field, and even finds itself narrowly behind HBO despite the uneven rollout of HBO Max last year. While Disney+ reported 94 million subscribers by the end of 2020, the service has a strong presence outside the U.S., and as The Information recently reported, a hair less than 40 million of its subscribers are American. • HBO’s numbers are impressive. In January, parent company AT&amp;T boasted that HBO Max had topped 41 million American subscribers, edging past Disney+ domestically — but that tally includes some chicanery: About 17.2 million of those subscribers are “activated,” as AT&amp;T put it, meaning they’ve downloaded the HBO Max app. (Remember, HBO already had existing streaming customers across both its HBO Go and HBO Now services prior to HBO Max.) • The biggest gainers, in terms of market share, were Peacock, which went from 0% of the market to 5% of the market by the end of 2020, and HBO, which only claimed 3% of the streaming pie at the same time last year; that slice has now quadrupled in size, as HBO has looked to propel its linchpin service, HBO Max, into the upper echelon of streaming services. Most notably, in an effort to win over new subscribers, Warner Bros. decided to release all 17 of its 2021 films — including “Godzilla vs. Kong” and Keanu Reeves’ “Matrix 4” — on HBO Max at the same time they hit theaters this year. For another angle, here’s how the current streaming hierarchy shakes out in the U.S., a few weeks before Netflix and other streamers are set to report their Q1 subscriber gains (or losses): Also Read: Inside FuboTV's Push Into Sports Betting and Pandemic Streaming Trends The battle for third place in the U.S. streaming hierarchy looks to be the key battleground in 2021. Ampere Research Manager Toby Holleran said he expects HBO Max to enjoy “a fair bit of success this year” and credited Warner Bros.’ plan to release all of its theatrical releases on the service the same they hit theaters. However, he predicted, that one-year gambit “will not quite catch up with Hulu.” On top of that, Holleran said he expects “Disney+ to overtake both HBO Max and Hulu” within the first half of 2021, and “finish the year as the third largest streaming service in the U.S., with Hulu taking the fourth spot, and HBO Max taking fifth.” Other streaming competitors — including Apple TV+, NBCUniversal’s Peacock and ViacomCBS’ Paramount+ (here listed by its pre-rebrand name, CBS All Access) — trail far behind the leaders in the category. “Bridgerton” (Netflix) Ampere’s data comes as the average American household is now spending $40 per month on streaming services, as TheWrap reported earlier this year. That’s up 17% from the $34 Americans were spending each month in early 2020, and up 33% from Q1 2019, when Americans were spending $30 per month on average. That’s also likely to push higher in 2021, as services like Disney+ bump up their monthly fees. Holleran added Netflix’s place atop the streaming hierarchy is “seemingly cemented,” even with its slice of the American pie shrinking in the last year, at least for the near future. But despite its first-mover advantage and array of big-name original shows, from “Stranger Things” to “Bridgerton,” Netflix’s no.1 status isn’t guaranteed forever. For one thing, Holleran noted that Disney’s overall streaming business, including both Hulu and ESPN+, surpassed Netflix’s U.S. subscriber base more than a year ago, “and is on track to overtake it worldwide by 2024.” In other words: Don’t be shocked if Disney+ continues to narrow the gap with Netflix, both in the States and abroad. Read original story Netflix Lost 31% of Market Share in the Last Year as Streaming Rivals Gained Ground | Charts At TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defendant No. 1 or Next PM? Netanyahu Divides Nation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/05/defendant-no-1-or-next-prime-minister-netanyahu-divides-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu appeared in a Jerusalem court on Monday for the opening of the key, evidentiary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Most Can't Tell Difference Between Screams Of Joy, Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/screams-of-joy-screams-of-terror/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say screams of happiness are often interpreted as screams of fear because both have similar acoustic features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Rangers of the Loneliest Road in America...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dark-rangers-loneliest-road-america-080755337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TashkaIn July 1986, Life magazine described U.S. Route 50 as the “Lone­liest Road in America.”Underneath a single depressing photo, the magazine featured this description of the two-lane highway:“It’s totally empty,” says an AAA counselor. “There are no points of interest. We don’t recommend it.” The 287-mile stretch of U.S. 50, running from Ely to Fernley, Nev., passes nine towns, two abandoned mining camps, a few gas pumps and an occasional coy­ote. “We warn all motorists not to drive there,” says the AAA rep, “unless they’re confident of their survival skills.”It was a colossal diss, but Nevada tourism officials couldn’t have been happier. All of a sudden, Life’s non-endorsement of their de­pressing little highway had given it a brand, and in so doing man­aged to popularize the road among a certain set of gloomy travelers. The state put up signs advertising the new name—HWY 50, THE LONELIEST ROAD IN AMERICA.Just three months after that article was published, U.S. 50 got an attraction that even the most jaded AAA counselor would have agreed at least counted as a point of interest. Set back a few miles from the highway, a 76,000-acre plot of land was given a branding upgrade of its own. In October 1986, Congress passed a law establishing Great Basin National Park.The park was intended to serve as a representative sample of the entire Great Basin region—a massive watershed spanning five states, including almost all of Nevada. All the water found in the Great Basin drains or evaporates internally, never making its way to the Pacific Ocean or the Gulf of Mexico. Put another way, what happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.The park itself is less than 300 miles from the Las Vegas Strip, the brightest spot on our entire planet when viewed from space. But the country’s loneliest road doesn’t see many head­lights. The closest town to Great Basin—Baker, Nevada—is home to just 68 people.“We’re pretty rare,” ranger Annie Gilliland told me when I met her near the visitor center. “This is one of the—if not the darkest place in the Lower 48.”Annie is a “Dark Ranger,” part of an elite squad of park staff who lead regular astronomy presentations.“I love it,” she told me, smiling. “It makes me sound like a superhero.”The Dark Rangers are real-life guardians of the galaxy, tasked with ensuring that the lighting inside the park stays low so that visitors aren’t distracted from the sky up above. At Great Basin, the stars are the star attraction.Before my meeting with Annie, I had spent the day hiking a few short trails and drove up the park’s Wheeler Peak Scenic Drive. The scenery I’d seen was pleasant enough, but most of it, to my eye at least, was the same type of pinyon-juniper woodland that can be found all throughout the Great Basin region.If one were to go home when the sun goes down, then Great Basin might merely seem as “Great” as the Great Plains. That’s why rangers like Annie encourage visitors to stick around. Here, they have a saying…Half the park… is after dark.I’d heard about Great Basin’s skies, and I’d timed my visit so that I would arrive on the night of a new moon—the darkest pos­sible night. It was also a weekend night, which meant Annie would be hosting one of her popular astronomy talks. As the sun set, a small crowd began to form in the parking lot. Flashlights were forbidden—Annie wanted our eyes to adjust naturally.When the stars finally made their debut, the canopy shining overhead did not strike me as something that should be referred to as a “dark sky.” Wind Cave was dark. This was the brightest sky I had ever seen.Rising up from the east, the Milky Way slowly streaked across Great Basin’s horizon—it looked like the heavens had been ripped apart. This wasn’t some faint constellation where you have to struggle to connect the dots just to see a shape that vaguely re­sembles a bear chasing after twin crabs. This was an unmissable interstellar Grand Canyon, a massive band of light so brilliant it cast shadows on the ground.I was transfixed. It was hard to comprehend that all of these thousands of stars had all been up there all along, hiding in plain sight. I realized that all other supposedly beautiful starry nights of my life had been symphonies with notes missing. At Great Basin, I was finally able to appreciate the full composition.An astronomer would tell you that I was still only seeing a tiny fraction of the universe. The human eye, under the best of condi­tions, can see fewer than 5,000 of the billions of stars that shine in our galaxy alone. As I tried to take them all in, I wondered if the limiting factor was not the eye, but the human brain. Throw in even a few dozen more bright-white pinpricks and it felt like my head would explode.When I occasionally lowered my gaze to rest my neck for a few minutes, I could see the heads of a hundred other tourists craned skyward, their eyes wide with wonder. Annie had set up telescopes in the parking lot for anyone who wanted to take a closer look. When I walked over to one to peer at Jupiter, I met a troop of Boy Scouts from Farmington, New Mexico, who had come to the park to earn their astronomy merit badges. I asked one of the Scouts if the sky was different than what he was used to seeing back home.“I can’t see any of this back home,” he said. “It makes me think, our world is so small, and the galaxy out there is so big.”At an age when most kids think they’re the center of the uni­verse, the stars of Great Basin helped remind this kid that he wasn’t. That none of us is.For most Americans, this kind of cosmic insight is increas­ingly hard to come by. More than two-thirds of the country lives in areas where the Milky Way can’t be seen from their backyards. While today we know far more about the cosmos than any genera­tion in history, we see far less of it.When the International Dark-Sky Association announced in 2016 that it was recognizing Great Basin as a “Dark Sky Park,” program manager John Barentine told the Las Vegas Review-Journal that Great Basin was “as close as you can get to what the night sky might have looked like before the invention of electric light.”It’s easy to forget that the era he was referring to wasn’t actually that long ago. Lights have only been obscuring our view of the sky for a century and a half—Thomas Edison’s company didn’t start selling bulbs until the 1880s, and it took a long time for cities to turn into the glistening metropolises we know today. But our world keeps getting brighter and brighter. The direst predictions esti­mate that, by 2025, there may be no dark skies left in the Lower 48.Before it could be certified as a Dark Sky Park, Great Basin first had to adjust its lighting fixtures to all point downward. The bulbs around the visitor center were retrofitted to use low-wattage red lights, a color that allows our eyes to stay better adjusted to the dark. (That’s why everything from the numbers on digital alarm clocks to the insides of submarine control rooms is illuminated red.)Most important, the park strove never to use more light than necessary. When something wasn’t in use, it was switched off. That’s how easy it can be to address light pollution. It literally can go away with the flick of a switch. Light pollution is reversible.Parks, with their charge to preserve, “unimpaired,” our natural resources, have an ecological responsibility to consider the impact of light. Artificial light sources can cause massive disruptions to the circadian rhythms of animals in the parks and impact the rela­tionship between nocturnal predators and their prey. Lights can also disorient species that rely on the moon and stars for naviga­tional cues.Every year in Florida, millions of sea turtle hatchlings die when they waddle off in the direction of artificial light sources along the beach, mistaking the glow of condos for the light of the moon. Frogs, which croak at night to find a mate, may never realize it’s night if it’s too bright outside. If the males can’t get in the mood to make their baby-makin’ music, then the females don’t mate, and the frog population dies out.Beyond the environmental impact of light pollution, seeing the stars at Great Basin reminded me that the night sky itself is a re­source worth preserving. The view of what lies beyond our world can be just as powerful and transformative as any of the scenery found on its surface. Unfortunately, protecting that view is beyond the power of a few Dark Rangers. The view of what lies beyond our world can be just as powerful and transformative as any of the scenery found on its surface. Leave Only Footprints: My Acadia-to-Zion Journey Through Every National Park Penguin Random House LLC. Excerpted from Leave Only Footprints by Conor Knighton Copyright © 2020 by Conor Knighton. Excerpted by permission of Crown, an imprint of Random House, a division of Penguin Random House LLC.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casey Affleck Mounting Comeback Despite Sex-Harassment Claims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/casey-affleck-mounting-comeback-despite-075908607.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marilla Sicilia/GettyCasey Affleck’s slow and steady ascent to household name, much like his older brother Ben, seemed as though it was about to finally take hold in 2016, with his critically lauded film Manchester by the Sea. Eyes fixed on a shiny golden Oscar, Affleck hit the awards press circuit hard, appearing on almost every red carpet, doing interviews with major publications, and roping in big bro and longtime family friend Matt Damon to ultimately nab the Academy Award for Best Actor.Yet as Affleck attempted to dazzle his way onto the Hollywood A-list, disturbing sexual-harassment allegations against him resurfaced. Affleck, now 45, had settled two civil lawsuits in 2010 from women who worked on his mockumentary I’m Still Here, starring his then brother-in-law Joaquin Phoenix.The women, cinematographer Magdalena Gorka and producer Amanda White, sued Affleck for $2.25 million and $2 million, respectively. Gorka claimed in her suit that the treatment she endured while working under Affleck was “by far the most traumatizing of her career.” Almost “immediately” after joining the project in 2008, Gorka claimed in court papers that “Affleck and other members of the production team made lewd comments, they discussed in engaging in sexual activity with [Gorka] and they suggested that she have sex with the camera assistant.”Comedian Jamie Kennedy on How He Ended Up in an Anti-Abortion Propaganda FilmOne of the final straws for Gorka, she claimed, occurred in mid-December of 2008 after the crew traveled to New York for the film and were put up in Phoenix and Affleck’s apartment. Gorka was given Phoenix’s private bedroom to rest, but claims she awoke in the middle of the night to Affleck “curled up next to her in the bed wearing only his underwear and a T-shirt,” her suit stated. “He had his arm around her, was caressing her back, his face within inches of hers and his breath reeked of alcohol.” When Gorka demanded that he get out of the bed, Affleck allegedly asked why, and if she “was sure,” angrily slamming the door on his way out when she rebuffed his advances.Gorka said she resigned over the incident, but rejoined the film in January 2009 when White convinced her to return, believing the environment would be safer with another woman now working on the film. However, Gorka claimed the harassment continued, and that she was “subjected to a near daily barrage of sexual comments, innuendo and unwelcome sexual advances by crew members, within the presence and with the active encouragement of Affleck.” She also claimed she was berated and verbally attacked by Affleck after she refused his alleged sexual advances.She said she left the film for the final time due to the “harassment and abuse.” She claimed in her suit that Affleck retaliated against her, refusing to honor the terms of their agreement, including payment and crediting her as “director of photography” on the film.Just days before Gorka filed suit, White filed her own complaint, going into greater detail about the comments and conduct that Affleck and the crew allegedly inflicted upon the women. She claimed that Affleck once “grabbed in a hostile manner in an effort to intimidate her into complying” after she refused to stay a night in a hotel room with the married actor.On another occasion, “Affleck instructed a crew member to take off his pants in order to show [White] his penis, even after [White] objected,” her complaint claimed. She claimed Affleck remarked “isn’t it about time you get pregnant?” when he learned of her age, as well as allegedly referred to women as “cows” and discussed his and other celebrities’ sexual exploits.At the time of the suits, Affleck denied any wrongdoing, characterizing it as a contract dispute gone awry, and his powerhouse lawyer Marty Singer threatened the women with a countersuit. Both women settled out of court for an undisclosed sum.The Daily Beast reached out to Gorka and White for comment. But when the allegations resurfaced in 2016, while Affleck was vying for his Oscar, they were ignored by much of the entertainment press, who conducted softball interviews with the actor. He alluded to the suits briefly in glowing profiles, telling Variety that “people say whatever they want. Sometimes it doesn’t matter how you respond… I guess people think if you’re well-known, it’s perfectly fine to say anything you want.” Affleck went on to win Best Actor, gracing the Oscar stage in February of 2017 to give an acceptance speech (much to presenter Brie Larson’s chagrin).Months later, the #MeToo movement ripped through Hollywood, gaining worldwide attention due to damning exposes about mega-producer Harvey Weinstein, who was accused of sexual assault and harassment by dozens of women.Affleck retreated from public view (even bowing out of presenting the award for Best Actress at the next Oscars, a tradition for the previous year’s Best Actor). In his first interview after the #MeToo movement in August 2018, Affleck apologized and admitted he “behaved in a way and allowed others to behave in a way that was really unprofessional.”“First of all, that I was ever involved in a conflict that resulted in a lawsuit is something that I really regret,” he said. “I wish I had found a way to resolve things in a different way. I hate that. I had never had any complaints like that made about me before in my life and it was really embarrassing and I didn’t know how to handle it and I didn’t agree with everything, the way I was being described, and the things that were said about me, but I wanted to try to make it right, so we made it right in the way that was asked at the time. And we all agreed to just try to put it behind us and move on with our lives, which I think we deserve to do, and I want to respect them as they’ve respected me and my privacy.”Of course, Affleck revealed his real motivation for doing the interview earlier on during the conversation. “If I’m not promoting a movie, I’m not going to do any press, so that’s why you haven’t heard from me,” he said. Casey Affleck poses at the Light of My Life photocall during the 69th Berlinale International Film Festival Berlin at Grand Hyatt Hotel on Feb. 8, 2019, in Berlin, Germany. Pascal LeSegretain/Getty The following year, while on a press campaign for his feature directorial debut, Light of My Life, Affleck offered a different take on why he didn’t speak out sooner in support of #MeToo, saying he figured “the best thing to do was to just be quiet so I didn’t seem to be in opposition to something that I really wanted to champion.”“Who would not be supportive of the #MeToo movement,” he asked. “That there are some people saying we do not believe in equality and we think the workplace should be a dangerous place for certain people and not for others. That’s preposterous.”It’s now 2021, more than a decade since the civil suits were settled, and it seems Affleck has rebounded from the claims against him. He has a new movie out, Every Breath You Take; recently starred in Our Friend alongside Dakota Johnson and Jason Segel; and produced and starred in The World to Come, a critically acclaimed drama opposite Academy Award nominee Vanessa Kirby. He also has a number of other projects in various stages of production, including his sophomore effort behind the camera.Why Casey Affleck’s #MeToo ‘Apology’ Falls ShortThe allegations have been almost completely sidestepped in recent interviews with the actor. One publication referenced how he skipped the Oscars in 2018, yet breezed by why, while another asked him to reflect on his choices over the course of his 25-year career, prompting Affleck to discuss wanting to direct more.By largely ignoring the previous claims, Affleck has been allowed to come across as an insightful, brooding artist on a journey of self-discovery and on the precipice of reclaiming his delayed stardom. And while it can be argued that the settled lawsuits are more than a decade old and that Affleck has acknowledged them, there hasn’t been a true examination of his efforts to right his wrongs, or an in-depth interview with Affleck probing the allegations. .It’s really only his side that the public gets to hear, too. It’s impossible to truly know if either Magdalena Gorka or Amanda White agree with Affleck’s previous characterization of everyone just wanting “to move on” out of respect for their privacy, as neither has ever spoken out about their experiences since signing confidentiality agreements back in 2010.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flurry Of Quakes Rattle LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/3-3m-earthquake-shakes-south-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquake occurred at 4:44 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Arizona's water one-percenters...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/apr/05/arizona-water-one-percenters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the deserts of Phoenix, two cities are emerging: one is water-rich, the other water-poor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver therapists secretly use magic mushrooms to help patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/denver-dabbles-magic-mushrooms-using-100033474.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denver decriminalized magic mushrooms in 2019. Now advocates are pushing to legalize psilocybin — the active ingredient — as a treatment for various mental health problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Half of Republicans believe false accounts of deadly Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-disinformation/half-of-republicans-believe-false-accounts-of-deadly-u-s-capitol-riot-reuters-ipsos-poll-idUSKBN2BS0RZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the deadly Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol, former President Donald Trump and his Republican allies have pushed false and misleading accounts to downplay the event that left five dead and scores of others wounded. His supporters appear to have listened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran arrests 'Israeli spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iran-arrested-israeli-spy-in-eastern-azerbaijan-report-664169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge Of The Winklevii...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeldelcastillo/2021/04/05/revenge-of-the-winklevii-facebook-winklevoss-bitcoin-nft-billionaire-revenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After losing an epic battle with Mark Zuckerberg over ownership of Facebook and being shunned in Silicon Valley, CAMERON and TYLER WINKLEVOSS are back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMC newly-unveiled HUMMER EV SUV is 830HP of electric 'supertruck'...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/gmcs-newly-unveiled-hummer-ev-suv-is-830-hp-of-electric-supertruck-220323684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hummer EV pickup won't be the only "supertruck" in GMC's fleet after the automaker unveiled its Hummer EV SUV variant on Saturday. It's slated for release in spring 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.0 mag quake rattles LA...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/california/los-angeles/earthquakes-rattles-los-angeles-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.0 quake was the largest of three small earthquakes that rattled Los Angeles out of bed Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force continues to pound ISIS targets in Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/04/03/air-force-continues-to-pound-isis-targets-in-iraq/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attacks destroyed two ISIS camps and two caves, killing at least two ISIS fighters, Iraqi officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid mutants multiply as scientists race to decode variations...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/science/health/covid-mutants-multiply-as-scientists-race-to-decode-variations-11617616553045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the virus continues to evolve in the short term, one of the most hopeful scenarios is that it may run out of big moves it can make to evade antibodies that make the current vaccines work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen to call for global minimum tax rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/janet-yellen-global-minimum-tax-rate-51c7395b-e46a-4a5c-b18b-bdcf5d8bd352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speech to the Chicago Council on Global Affairs also will touch on vaccine access and climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan reports new incursion into defense zone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210405094224-34eiu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/DEFENCE (PIX):Taiwan reports new incursion by Chinese jets into defence zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in Israel's Brave New Post-Pandemic Future...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/05/my-life-in-israels-brave-new-post-pandemic-future/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Green Pass allows us, the vaccinated, to go to concerts, restaurants and sporting events. But Israel’s real-time experiment in</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
