<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VICTIMS...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/victims-of-the-borderline-bar-mass-shooting-have-been-identified/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Losing, Dem Politicians Now Say They Can Be Truthful...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/losing-dem-politicians-now-say-can-truthful/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Losing Democratic politicians say they can finally tell the truth now that they are "freed from the constraints" of needing support of their constituents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wearing 'I Love Jesus' hat breaks into church, rips Bibles...</title>
      <link>https://wtvr.com/2018/11/07/man-wearing-i-%E2%9D%A4%EF%B8%8F-jesus-hat-broke-into-chesterfield-church-ripped-bibles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chesterfield Reverend is in disbelief after someone broke into his church, ripped Bibles, spray-painted walls, and smashed a glass window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After losing, Texas judge frees juvenile defendants, skips court...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/11/07/texas-juvenile-judge-frees-defendantsafter-losing-re-election-democrat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas judge ousted in the midterm elections spent the next morning releasing nearly all of the juvenile offenders who came before him.Harris...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple sues NETFLIX for using demon god statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/08/the-satanic-temple-sues-netflix-warner-bros-for-150-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Satanic Church is not happy with "The Chilling Adventures of Sabrina" for depicting satanists as evil and featuring a statue similar to its monument to Baphomet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Niece of Ex-FOXNEWS Correspondent Killed...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/tamera-mowrys-niece-among-dead-in-thousand-oaks-shooting/4647510/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Sister Sister" actress Tamera Mowry-Housley and her husband released a statement confirming that their niece, Alaina Housley, was among the 12 killed in a mass shooting in Thousand Oaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US crude enters bear market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/08/oil-markets-opec-global-crude-production-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. crude prices dropped for a ninth consecutive session on Thursday, falling into a bear market, on further signs of growing supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie considered to replace Sessions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/chris-christie-being-considered-for-replacing-sessions-as-attorney-general/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former New Jersey governor is under consideration to replace Jeff Sessions, two sources tell CBS News' Major Garrett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant breastfeeds stranger's baby on flight...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/08/flight-attendant-breastfeeds-strangers-baby-on-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coffee, tea, breast milk? A flight attendant went above and beyond to help a mom who ran out of formula for her infant Tuesday during a domestic Philippine Airlines flight. Patrisha Organ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Hawking's wheelchair sells for $393,000...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/84bc4ae43f774792a42a0eee110a424e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A wheelchair used by physicist Stephen Hawking has sold at auction for almost 300,000 pounds ($393,000), while a copy of his doctoral thesis fetched almost 585,000 pounds ($767,000), auctioneer Christie's said Thursday. The motorized chair, used by Hawking after he was paralyzed with motor neuron disease, raised 296,750 pounds in a Christie's online auction. It had been expected to fetch up to 15,000 pounds. Proceeds from the chair's sale will go to two charities, the Stephen Hawking Foundation and the Motor Neurone Disease Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Niece of Ex-FOXNEWS Correspondent Missing...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/08/tamera-mowry-niece-missing-thousand-oaks-bar-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a heart-rending exchange, Alaina Housley's roommate said she has already been in contact with Alaina’s uncle, former Fox News correspondent Adam Housley, but that there is no news yet about her whereabouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousand Oaks was third-safest city in USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-was-third-safest-city-in-us-before-mass-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousand Oaks, California — where a gunman killed 12 people inside a packed bar Wednesday — was ranked the third-safest city to live in in the United States this year. There are an average of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise, CA wildfire spreads; Thousands evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/california-wildfires/article/Evacuations-ordered-across-Butte-County-as-Camp-13374840.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people were ordered to evacuate several Sierra foothills towns near Chico on Thursday as a wildfire raged out of control, growing rapidly to more than 5,000 acres. The blaze, dubbed the Camp Fire, started in the area of Camp Creek Road and Pulga Road near Highway 70 in the Feather River Canyon, said officials with the California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection, or Cal Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne Husband Rips Interim AG Pick As 'Illegal'...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/kellyanne-conways-husband-writes-scathing-op-ed-saying-trumps-interim-ag-pick-is-illegal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exec Killed By Company Bus On GOOGLE Campus...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/07/mountain-view-pedestrian-struck-google-bus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young woman crossing a street on Google's Mountain View campus was fatally struck by a tech company bus Monday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigarette smoking rate declines to new low...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-cigarette-smoking-rate-declines-low-180824900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cigarette smoking is losing popularity in the United States, where health officials Thursday announced just 14 percent of the population now smokes, the lowest level ever recorded in the country. The current rate marks a 67 percent decline since 1965, the year the National Health Interview Survey (NHIS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies El Chapo-wife embrace, deems too risky...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/judge-denies-el-chapo-wife-embrace-deems-too-174359500.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US judge overseeing the New York trial of Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman ruled Thursday that the notorious drug baron could not hug his beauty queen wife, as requested, just before opening statements are to begin. Guzman has been held in solitary confinement since he was extradited to the United</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YVES SAINT LAURENT launches controversial penis jewelry...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/7689563/yves-saint-laurent-ysl-penis-jewellery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THEY’RE not what we’d choose to wear for Sunday lunch with our gran but if you’re a fan of jewellery that’s a little bit different – look no further. Designer brand Yv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for ripping wigs off Jewish women...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/08/man-arrested-for-ripping-wigs-off-orthodox-jewish-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was busted this week for ripping wigs off the heads of three unsuspecting Orthodox Jewish women in California, according to local police. The first two incidents occurred in September on Yom …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitey Bulger Funeral Held in South Boston...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/Whitey-Bulger-Funeral-South-Boston-500047692.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcboston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A funeral mass for James 'Whitey' Bulger was held Thursday morning at a church in South Boston, the Archdiocese of Boston confirms. Among those spotted at notorious Boston gangster's funeral, which took...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-foot emu and feisty donkey fall in love...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article221276505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A boy donkey and girl emu have apparently fallen in love, and their relationship has created a problem for one of Charlotte’s best known animal shelters. The odd pair refuse to leave each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested for Allegedly Making 40 Harassing, Death Threat Calls to CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/man-arrested-allegedly-making-death-threats-cnn-1159479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect was booked on numerous charges, including multiple counts of felony terroristic threatening and multiple counts of misdemeanor harassing communications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People concerned offering their ribs and organs!</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/article221343550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is in the hospital after falling and fracturing three ribs. People on social media are offering the 85-year-old judge their own ribs and wishing her a fast recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH DRAMA AT HIGH COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6367831/Ginsburg-85-hospitalized-fracturing-3-ribs-fall.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was hospitalized after a fall in her office that led her to fracture three of her ribs. She was treated at George Washington Hospital in Washington D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Has Begun Writing Final Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/08/politics/trump-reviewing-answers-mueller/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he was preparing to remove Jeff Sessions as attorney general, President Donald Trump had already begun reviewing with his lawyers the written answers to questions from special counsel Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Ginsburg hospitalized after fracturing 3 ribs in fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/08/supreme-court-justice-ruth-bader-ginsburg-85-has-broken-her-ribs-in-a-fall.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 85, fell in her office at the court and fractured three ribs, the court says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gunman identified as Ian Long, 28...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2018/11/08/police-respond-to-reported-mass-shooting-in-thousand-oaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen people are dead after a gunman — who has been identified — opened fire on a crowd at a country dance bar holding a weekly “college night” Wednesday in Southern California, send…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC's Maddow Organizing Street Marches...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-msnbcs-maddow-organizing-street-marches-protest-sessions-fir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is a "break the glass in case of emergency" moment'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KCBS LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/video/channel/322-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live Streaming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Horrific scene'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d2737a3853bc4aea8a27c957c75c88ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSAND OAKS, Calif. (AP) — Using a smoke bomb and a handgun, a hooded former Marine dressed all in black opened fire during college night at a country music bar in Southern California, killing 12 people and sending hundreds fleeing in panic before apparently taking his own life, authorities said Thursday. Authorities said the motive for the attack Wednesday night was under investigation. The killer was identified as Ian David Long, a 28-year-old veteran who authorities said had an episode of erratic behavior last spring that was thought to be post-traumatic stress disorder because of his military background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KABC LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/thousand-oaks-mass-shooting-13-dead-including-gunman/4644573/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mass shooting at a Thousand Oaks nightclub left 13 people dead, including a Ventura County sheriff's sergeant and the gunman, authorities said Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV-infected man accused of raping scores of teens...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hiv-infected-thai-man-accused-raping-scores-teenagers-143501877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Police in Thailand say they have arrested an HIV-infected soldier who allegedly blackmailed and raped more than 70 teenage boys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneiderman Will Not Face Criminal Charges in Abuse Complaints...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/08/nyregion/eric-schneiderman-abuse-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four women said the former New York State attorney general assaulted them, but the Nassau County district attorney determined there were “legal impediments” to charging him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon town elects 18-year-old as mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.kezi.com/content/news/Yoncalla-elects-18-year-old-as-new-mayor--499994951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kezi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Simons received 41 percent of the vote election night, beating out two other candidates and becoming the town's youngest mayor in its history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University considers minorities-only gym...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/ohio-university-considers-minorities-only-gym-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proposal would transform underused space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First AI newsreader...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1042682/China-AI-newsreader-video-Sogou-robotics-robots-Xinhua-News-Oxford-University</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IN a world first, a Chinese state news agency has created a virtual newsreader that works 24/7 and says whatever it is told to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gunman identified as Ian Long, 29...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/08/gunman-who-murdered-12-people-in-student-bar-identified-as-ian-long-29-8118604/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;xLong 29, drove his mother's car to the bar in Thousand Oaks, California, before opening fire on customers attending a student night aimed at 18-21 year-old partygoers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama event ticket on sale for $90K!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2018/nov/08/michelle-obama-event-ticket-touted-for-70k-viagogo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tickets for former first lady’s London talk on sale for hundreds of times face value on secondary ticketing site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope denounces governments that use media to defame critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-denounces-governments-media-defame-critics-135703483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis is denouncing the way some governments seek to discredit their critics through "whisper" campaigns, using the media to defame anyone who represents a threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry King Slams Network: 'Stopped Doing News Long Time Ago'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/415669-larry-king-hits-cnn-stopped-doing-news-to-focus-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-CNN host Larry King on Wednesday mocked his former employer declaring that the network “stopped doing news a long time ago” by opting to primarily cover President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White South Africans barred from registering on govt jobs site...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-07/white-south-africans-barred-government-jobs-website-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows broken with stools to escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-bar-shooting-people-broke-windows-stools-escape/1928031002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a gunman opened fire at Borderline country-western dance barÂ in Thousand Oaks, Calif.,Â Matt Wennerstrom said he and his friends starting pushing people under a pool table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon to Senate: 2020 Dem brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/08/2020-democrats-senate-965522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least a half-dozen senators are likely to run, a dynamic that Mitch McConnell jokingly said will be &amp;quot;fun to watch.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Gunman Threw Smoke Bombs Into Bar Before Opening Fire...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-shooting-borderline-bar-and-grill-13-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a dozen people have been injured, including a deputy, in a shooting at a bar filled with college students in Thousand Oaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He died a hero': Ventura County Sheriff Sgt. among killed...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/08/ron-helus-ventura-county-sheriff-sergeant-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen people were killed in a shooting at the Borderline Bar &amp; Grill in Thousand Oaks, including the shooter and Ventura County sheriff’s Sgt. Ron Helus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 17-foot python caught in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/record-setting-17-foot-burmese-python-caught-south/story?id=59043768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snake weighed in at 120 pounds, according to the South Florida Water Management District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He died a hero': Ventura County Sheriff Sgt. among killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/11/08/thousand-oaks-shooting-slain-sheriff-ron-helus/1927917002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ventura County Sheriff's Office said sergeant Ron Helus 'died a hero' after entering the scene of a reported shooting inside a bar in Thousand Oaks, Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horses slaughtered for meat across Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/article221337725.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students at Venezuela's top veterinary school stood around a pile of skin and bones sobbing one recent morning, finding nothing more left of their beloved bay-colored mare nicknamed Miss Congeniality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: Kamala, Booker won't defeat Trump; Nominate Michelle Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/michael-moore-says-kamala-harris-cory-booker-wont-defeat-trump-urges-dems-to-nominate-michelle-obama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial documentary filmmaker Michael Moore on Wednesday said Democratic Sens. Kamala Harris and Cory Booker would lose against President Trump in the 2020 election, suggesting the party should nominate “beloved American” like Michelle Obama..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies disappear in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.tbo.com/news/environment/wildlife/Florida-study-finds-monarch-butterflies-declined-80-percent-since-2005_173359609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tbo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every year thousands of monarch butterflies dance through the air over North Florida, migrating between their breeding ground in Mexico and their regular homes along the U.S. Atlantic coastline.Every</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga, meditation on rise...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/08/health/yoga-meditation-rising-cdc-report/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The use of complementary health practices such as yoga and meditation is increasing among children and adults, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA WEATHER CONTROL: Move clouds, make rain with satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7682561/china-weather-control-plan-satellites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA is launching a bizarre bid to control Earth’s weather so it can shift rain clouds thousands of miles from its soaking south to its parched north. Six satellites will form a ring to spot water…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating apps use artificial intelligence to help search for love...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181108-dating-apps-use-artificial-intelligence-help-search-love</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions suspected in drowning of 400 buffaloes in Botswana...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/lions-suspected-drowning-400-buffaloes-botswana-doc-1ao0a51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farrakhan, in Iran, warns Trump Mideast war possible...</title>
      <link>http://www.arabnews.com/node/1401396/middle-east</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, UAE: Minister Louis Farrakhan, the leader of the Nation of Islam, is warning President Donald Trump not to pull “the trigger of war in the Middle East . at the insistence of Israel.”His remarks came during a visit to Iran where Farrakhan spoke to journalists in Tehran on Thursday.The 85-year-old Farrakhan, long known for provocative comments widely considered anti-Semitic, criticized the economic sanctions leveled by Trump against Iran after he pulled America from the nuclear deal between Tehran and world powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underperforming Chinese workers made to drink urine, eat bugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/underperforming-chinese-workers-made-to-drink-urine--eat-bugs-10908822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot virginity for sale at creepy new brothel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/sex-robot-virginity-sale-creepy-13554426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brothel claims to be focused on robot rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three asteroids will fly dangerously close to Earth this weekend, NASA warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/three-huge-asteroids-fly-dangerously-13554507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest of the three is predicted to be up to 30 metres wide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym-obsessed men at 'significantly' higher risk of depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/gym-obsessed-men-significantly-higher-13555235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Striving for a muscular body can take its toll on men's mental health</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters feud with White House poised to reach new heights...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/415642-maxine-waters-will-soon-wield-gavel-in-feud-with-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public feud between Rep. Maxine Waters and President Trump is poised to reach new heights when the California Democrat is granted subpoena power as head of a powerful congressional committee overseeing the financial sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California shooting: Country fans inside bar 'Vegas massacre survivors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/california-shooting-country-fans-inside-13554551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman dressed in black opened fire at the Borderline Bar &amp; Grill in Thousand Oaks, west of Los Angeles in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/Breaking911/status/1060329164367167488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“WATCH: Activists ring doorbell, gather outside of Fox News Personality Tucker Carlson’s home. “Tucker Carlson, we will fight! We know where you sleep at night!”  https://t.co/TLGZSWOlmj”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa Publishes Addresses of Coulter, Hannity, MORE... </title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/dc-antifa-publishes-home-addresses-of-tucker-carlson-and-his-brother-as-well-as-ann-coulter-neil-patel-and-sean-hannity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESSIONS OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46132348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Trump had publicly humiliated the top law official over the Russia probe dogging his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service agent blocks his entry...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6365549/CNNs-Jim-Acosta-BANNED-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Secret Service agent denied Acosta entry to the White House grounds on Wednesday evening, and revoked his 'hard pass', the long-term press pass issued to the White House press corps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO WOULD BE KING...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/prince-charles-at-70-i-wont-be-a-meddling-monarch-11547731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a documentary to mark the Prince of Wales' 70th birthday his family describe the man the public does not see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DAY AFTER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49f4e16c0e674a1391525a6f7d7db43b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Suddenly facing life under divided government, President Donald Trump and congressional leaders talked bipartisanship Wednesday but then bluntly previewed the fault lines to come. Trump threatened to go after House Democrats who try to investigate him, while Rep. Nancy Pelosi said her party would be "a check and balance" against the White House. The day after midterm elections reset Washington, Trump took a victory lap at a raucous news conference, celebrating Republican Senate wins but distancing himself from the GOP's loss of the House. He said he was interested in working with House Democrats but was ready to respond if he felt he was being ill-treated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital footprint 'starts in womb'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/08/emb-thurs-children-have-1000-pictures-posted-online-turn-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children have more than 1,000 pictures of themselves posted online before they turn 13, the Children's Commissioner has warned, as she backed the Telegraph&amp;rsquo;s Duty of Care campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Suicides spike on Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/07/suicides-spike-monday-mornings-according-new-study-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Japanese study has found suicide rates among middle-aged male office workers often peak on Monday mornings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World leaders demand answers from Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1042277/facebook-news-mark-zuckerberg-fake-news-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK boss Mark Zuckerberg faced new demands yesterday to submit to a grilling by an international panel of MPs on his role in spreading fake news and protecting users' personal information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny robots swim through eyeball to deliver medicine...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/11/watch-tiny-robots-swim-through-eyeball-deliver-medicine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientist use magnetic field to drive spiral nanobots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acting Attorney General to take over probe oversight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/07/trump-says-attorney-general-jeff-sessions-resigns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sessions departs after the president repeatedly hammered him about his decision last year to recuse himself from the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election and whether the Trump campaign colluded with the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. oil output new record...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/energy/article/Inventories-rise-with-oil-at-lowest-price-since-13371181.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. stockpile of commercial crude oil continued to rise with the country's record oil production estimated at 11.6 million barrels a day, and domestic oil prices are now down to their lowest levels since March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER PROBE AT RISK?</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-mueller-russia-investigation-20181107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the midterms now over, the special counsel faces key decision points in his 18-month-old investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE MODE</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/nation-world/ct-trump-midterms-reaction-20181106-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump reveled in his party's Senate victories and mocked members of his own party who lost after not seeking his support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Kubrick Script Set for Auction...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/stanley-kubrick-script-burning-secret-up-for-auction-would-film-companies-bite-1202496235/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-lost Stanley Kubrick script Burning Secret is up for auction at Bonhams New York on 20 November. The original manuscript is expected to fetch in the region of $20,000. The script, which has be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE SUSPENDS CNN ACOSTA PRESS PASS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/jim-acosta-press-credential-pulled-donald-trump-white-house-1202498131/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after a harsh on-air confrontation between the President of the United States and Jim Acosta, the CNN reporter has been “suspended” from the White House “until further notic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOB OUTSIDE HOME OF TUCKER CARLSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/protesters-chant-outside-tucker-carlson-home-fox-news-host/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smash Racism D.C., a self-described “anti-fascist” group, posted a video of their members scremaing obscenities at Carlson’s house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zucker to Staff: 'We Have Your Backs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cnns-jeff-zucker-tells-employees-trump-attack-we-have-your-backs-1159281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The work that you do is important," Zucker wrote in a memo. "And that is why we are so vigilantly protective of our role as journalists."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams Refuses To Concede in GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/trailing-but-close-abrams-pushes-keep-campaign-alive/7BVThq0RDAfyh2C9oUShmJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early Wednesday, trailing but tantalizingly close in the race for governor, Stacey Abrams exhorted h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Chinese  Rapper's iTunes Sales Acquired 'Fraudulently' and Won't Count Toward Charts...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/music/news/kris-wus-massive-itunes-u-s-sales-were-acquired-fraudulently-and-will-not-count-towards-charts-1203022049/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strange thing happened on the iTunes U.S. store on Monday (Nov. 5) when Kris Wu, a Chinese-Canadian actor and artist, practically swept the Top 10 songs chart. For much of the day and into the ni…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cockatoos create, manipulate novel tools...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-goffin-cockatoos-tools.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goffin's cockatoos can tear cardboard into long strips as tools to reach food—but fail to adjust strip width to fit through narrow openings, according to a study published November 7, 2018 in the open-access journal PLOS ONE by A.M.I. Auersperg from the Medical University of Vienna, Austria, and colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drowning cow saved by 'mermaid' on 200-mile swim...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-gloucestershire-46122547</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Cole is swimming 200 miles along the River Thames wearing a tail as part of a single-use plastic campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force tests missile, says 'not related to real world events'...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2018/11/07/air-force-test-launches-missile-from-vandenberg-afb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force has conducted a test launch of an unarmed Minuteman 3 intercontinental ballistic missile from Vandenberg Air Force Base, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brightest kids recruited to develop 'killer bots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2172141/chinas-brightest-children-are-being-recruited-develop-ai-killer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing Institute of Technology recruits 31 ‘patriotic’ youngsters for new AI weapons development programmeExpert in international science policy describes course as ‘extremely powerful and troubling’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX House member wins re-election from jail cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxan.com/news/investigations/tx-house-member-wins-re-election-from-a-jail-cell/1577793977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Houston-area Democrat member of the Texas House of Representatives coasted to a win in Tuesday's elections — while sitting in a county jail cell. Rep. Ron Reynolds keeps his seat for another four-year term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen-Elect Mitt Romney first warning shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2018/11/07/sen-elect-romney-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington • Senator-elect Mitt Romney said Wednesday that President Donald Trump’s firing of Attorney General Jeff Sessions should not affect the special counsel’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESSIONS OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Attorney-General-Jeff-Sessions-resigns-at-Trump-s-13371798.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Attorney General Jeff Sessions resigned on Wednesday at President Donald Trump's request, ending the tenure of a beleaguered loyalist whose relationship with the president was ruined when Sessions recused himself from control of the investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 presidential campaign. In a letter to Trump, Sessions wrote he had been "honored to serve as Attorney General" and had "worked to implement the law enforcement agenda based on the rule of law that formed a central part of your campaign for the presidency." Trump tweeted that Sessions would be replaced on an acting basis by Matthew Whitaker, who had been serving as Sessions' chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: VICE to shrink workforce as growth stalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/vice-media-to-shrink-workforce-by-as-much-as-15-as-growth-stalls-1541632597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice Media plans to shrink its workforce by as much as 15% and cut its selection of digital sites by at least half, according to people familiar with the matter, the result of stalling growth at the onetime new-media darling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord cutting accelerates; TV largest-ever quarterly loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/11/07/cord-cutting-accelerates-1-m-customers-dropped-pay-tv-last-quarter/1919471002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay-TV providers lost more than 1 million customers from July to September, the worst-ever decline â€“ a sign that cord cutting is accelerating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto Allies already thinking about Act 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/latest-news/article221185175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are already pointing to a list of changes O’Rourke needs to make if he wants to be a major player in the party — ones the candidate and his close-knit team have resisted for fear of losing the support that lifted him into the spotlight in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem rebels warn Pelosi: We ran on 'change'...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-pelosi-speaker-20181107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi faces a potentially cantankerous battle to regain the House speaker's gavel in the wake of Democratic wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President opens door on 'Russia' doc declassifying...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/07/trump-declassify-russia-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump 'very seriously' considering declassification</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems loosen Republican state legislature grip...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-win-some-state-legislatures-but-gop-maintains-majority-1541618643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats won control of six more state legislative chambers in Tuesday’s election and loosened Republicans’ grip on some others, but they didn’t significantly shift a balance of power that still heavily favors the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-driving cars to function as moving brothels?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/07/brothels-could-move-self-driving-cars-academics-predict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brothels could move into self-driving cars, British academics predict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000-year-old art discovered in remote cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/11/news-oldest-animal-drawing-borneo-cave-art-human-origins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Southeast Asian island of Borneo joins a growing number of sites boasting early cave art innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sues for legal age change to help meet women on TINDER...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/07/man-69-wants-to-legally-change-age-to-49-to-help-him-pull-women-on-tinder-8115524/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘When I'm on Tinder and it says I'm 69, I don't get an answer. When I'm 49, with the face I have, I will be in a luxurious position.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former allies unload on 'selfish' Paul Ryan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/07/us/politics/democrats-republicans-house.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite warnings from within the GOP, Republicans lost their unity and grip on messaging, allowing the Democrats to gain a majority of congressional seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says he cannot save Brazil alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/far-bolsonaro-says-cannot-save-brazil-alone-184802795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - Brazil's President-elect Jair Bolsonaro said Wednesday that he alone cannot rescue the country from economic hardship and spiraling violent crime, as he met with outgoing head of state Michel Temer and the country's Supreme Court chief. Bolsonaro won an election run-off 10 days</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
