<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biggest snubs, surprises...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/golden-globes/2018/12/06/golden-globes-nominations-snubs-4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2019 Golden Globes nominations are out. Let's first hit some surprises, because there were some rather huge ones on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6467875/Elizabeth-Warrens-advisers-want-APOLOGIZE-DNA-stunt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats blasted the liberal Massachusetts senator in October for drawing attention to her biggest political liability in the middle of a tense midterm election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval rating crashes to 18%...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7915541/emmanuel-macron-predicts-violence-france-weekend-approval-rating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL Macron’s approval rating has crashed below 20 per cent today as he predicts more “major violence” across France this weekend. The beleaguered head of state is locked in a law and order cri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY, ZUCKER, DRUDGE NAMED 'MOST INFLUENTIAL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/mediaites-most-influential-in-news-media-2018/8/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES CHAOS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d47620b3896e4f47b82aac1ec5069554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Adam McKay's Dick Cheney biopic "Vice" seized control of the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards with a leading six nominations, narrowly edging Bradley Cooper's tear-jerking revival "A Star Is Born," the interracial road-trip drama "Green Book" and the period romp "The Favourite." "Vice" topped all contenders Thursday, in nominations announced at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California, including best picture, comedy and best actor nominations for Christian Bale's nearly unrecognizable performance as the former vice president. It also earned nominations for Amy Adams' Lynne Cheney, Sam Rockwell's George W. Bush and both the screenplay and direction by McKay, the veteran comedy filmmaker who once skewered politicians as a "Saturday Night Live" writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amal Clooney accuses Trump of 'giving green light' to autocratic regimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/amal-clooney-accuses-trump-giving-green-light-autocratic-regimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amal Clooney has claimed Donald Trump gives the &amp;quot;green light&amp;quot; to autocratic regimes during a speech in which she warned against the US president's attacks on the press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/elizabeth-warren-stands-by-dna-test-but-around-her-worries-abound-/18043961/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The plan was straightforward: After years of being challenged by President Donald Trump and others about a decades-old claim of Native American ancestry, Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., would take a DNA test to prove her stated family origins in the Cherokee and Delaware tribes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student protests intensify alongside tax revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181206-french-student-protests-intensify-alongside-yellow-vest-revolt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French student protests intensify alongside 'yellow vest' revolt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Spoilers?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/811016/5-republicans-who-could-challenge-trump-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of them can win. But they could play spoiler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatters Diversity Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-shatters-diversity-record-4-10-best-picture-nominees-non-white-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Crazy Rich Asians," "BlacKkKlansman," "Black Panther" and "If Beale Street Could Talk" all break into the top categories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The College Guys Trying to Ban Porn on Campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-college-guys-are-trying-to-ban-porn-on-campus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movement started at Notre Dame but has quickly spread to other universities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stair test may predict risk of dying of heart disease, cancer, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/how-live-longer-stair-test-may-predict-longevity-death-risk-t144556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you can do this simple test, it's a good sign of your exercise capacity. If not, you may need to exercise more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Generation Xanax...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/generation-xanax-doubling-children-treated-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New figures reveal the rise of &amp;ldquo;generation Xanax&amp;rdquo; - with a doubling in young people being treated for addiction to anti-anxiety drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon grilled by Senate Intel Committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/senate-intelligence-committee-grilled-steve-bannon-about-cambridge-analytica </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notorious “psychographic” data firm remains of interest to Senate investigators—as does the former Trump strategist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Watch can now detect irregular heart rhythms, other problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/apple-watch-ecg-sensor-review.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We tried out the new ECG app and irregular heart rate notification for Apple Watch ahead of its release on Thursday. Here's how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Claims Chased U.S. Destroyer Out Of Territorial Waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-06/russia-claims-it-chased-us-destroyer-out-its-territorial-waters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Cheney Takedown 'VICE Tops With 6 Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2019-golden-globes-nominations-full-list-1165090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ceremony is set for Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz passes cyber snooping laws with global implications...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/australia-passes-cyber-snooping-laws-global-implications-103222310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia Thursday passed controversial laws allowing spies and police to snoop on the encrypted communications of suspected terrorists and criminals, as experts warned the "unprecedented powers" had far-reaching implications for global cybersecurity. There has been extensive debate about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's slow-motion staff 'shakeup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/06/trumps-slow-motion-staff-shakeup-stunts-2019-planning-1046414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has left top officials in a state of limbo and top jobs without permanent occupants, creating &amp;quot;a sense of chaos.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Gap Widens to 10-Year High...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-trade-deficit-climbs-to-10-year-high-despite-tariffs-tough-trump-stance-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trade deficit rose 1.7% in October to a 10-year high amid a record shortfall with China, keeping the U.S. on pace to record the largest gap in a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 9,000 counterfeit NIKES seized in New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/us/counterfeit-nikes-seized-new-york-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you spot a fake?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payroll growth slows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/payroll-growth-slows-in-november-as-labor-market-tightens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls increased by 179,000, below the 195,000 growth expected by a Refinitiv survey of economists. The number also was a drop from the 225,000 in October and below the 203,000 prior monthly average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/golden-globe-nominations-2019-1203082075/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards will be announced Thursday morning show live from the Beverly Hilton Hotel. Actors Terry Crews, Danai Gurira, Leslie Mann and Christian Slate are…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Tanzania, Crackdown Sends LGBT People Into Hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/behind-the-curtain-in-tanzania-a-crackdown-sends-lgbt-people-into-hiding-1544101201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crackdown on LGBT rights in Tanzania has forced people into hiding and sparked an international backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro athletes say they will lose fortune under tax law...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-pro-athletes-may-lose-a-fortune-because-of-the-new-tax-law-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPAs who work with athletes say they can no longer get full deductions for state and local taxes — or for itemizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS</title>
      <link>https://www.goldenglobes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goldenglobes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood awards season kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/how-to-watch-the-golden-globe-nominations-nbc-live-facebook-instagram-1202514901/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nominees for the 76th Annual Golden Globe Awards will be announced Thursday, Dec. 6 by Terry Crews, Danai Gurira, Leslie Mann, and Christian Slater. In addition to the nominees, the Hollywood F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of underground LSD guides...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/06/lsd-guides-psychedelic-assisted-psychotherapy </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Americans searching for alternative paths to healing have turned to psychedelics. But how does one forge a career as a guide when the substances are illegal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment/la-et-2019-golden-globe-nominations-how-to-watch-the-golden-globe-1544036969-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything you need to know about how to livestream Thursday's Golden Globe nominations announcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1055152/Macron-news-france-crisis-protests-end-of-macron-no-confidence-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL Macron’s leadership is hanging by a thread as left-wing groups within the French parliament discuss launching a no confidence vote against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honduran woman in migrant caravan gives birth in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3ca21d8faf414f639693f07fbf4bc7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — A Honduran woman affiliated with a caravan of Central American migrants gave birth on U.S. soil shortly after entering the country illegally amid growing frustration about a bottleneck to claim asylum at official border crossings. Border Patrol agents arrested the woman Nov. 26 after she entered the country illegally near Imperial Beach, California, across the border from Tijuana, Mexico, Customs and Border Protection said Wednesday. She was arrested with her 20-year-old husband and 2-year-old son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Workers Get Just 1.25 Cents for Each DISNEY Doll Produced...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/dec/06/revealed-disney-ariel-doll-earns-chinese-worker-1p </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Undercover investigation exposes illegally long working hours and low wages for staff at factory producing toys for Disney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first bee vaccine seeks to save dying pollinators...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/World-s-first-honey-bee-vaccine-seeks-to-save-13446663.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of honey bees die each year due to pesticides, vanishing habitats, poor nutrition and climate change, with potentially disastrous consequences for agriculture and natural diversity. Now, scientists at the University of Helsinki have developed the first edible vaccine against microbial infections, hoping to save at least some of the pollinators. "We might be right now at a tipping point, without even realizing it," Dalial Freitak, the lead scientist on the project, said in an interview on Wednesday. "We've been taking the pollination services for granted for so long. These insects are not there, they are disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chavez Bleak Legacy Keeps Venezuela Broken 20 Years After Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/on-the-road-venezuela-20-years-after-hugo-chavez-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Guardian travels across the nation the late Hugo Chávez dreamed of transforming, to understand its collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/politics/elizabeth-warren-dna-test-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since releasing the results in October, the ancestry issue clouding her possible presidential campaign has only intensified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots will feel love, suffer pain when dumped...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7908769/sex-robots-will-soon-feel-love-and-suffer-devastating-pain-after-we-dump-them-expert-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX robots will soon feel love and suffer pain after being dumped, according to an expert. Professor Robin Mackenzie, director of Law and Medical Ethics and Kent Law School, claimed robotics will b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Deli Customer Attacks Worker for Wait Time Over Bagel Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Angry-Deli-Customer-Attacks-Worker-Bacon-Egg-Cheese-Cinnamon-Raisin-Bagel-Brooklyn-502035522.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An irate deli customer is wanted for his violent tantrum in which he attacked a worker when he was told his wait time for a bacon, egg and cheese sandwich would take at least five minutes, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes noms... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181206-hollywood-awards-season-kicks-off-with-golden-globes-noms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes noms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging STDs pose serious public health threats...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/std-sexually-transmitted-diseases-partner/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although gonorrhea, chlamydia and syphilis grab most of the headlines, public health officials are warily watching the emergence of other bacterial sexually transmitted infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK May urged to POSTPONE Brexit Commons vote; Leave date can be moved beyond March...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911547/theresa-may-brexit-postpone-eu-leaders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May has been urged to POSTPONE next week’s crucial Brexit vote, with Cabinet ministers warning defeat could collapse the Government. It comes as EU leaders suggest the leave date coul…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pig hearts for humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/12/05/pig-hearts-could-soon-tested-humans-scientists-pass-important/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pig hearts could soon be tested in humans after scientists passed an important milestone when transplanting the organs into primates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'GREEN BOOK' became polarizing awards contender...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/How-Green-Book-became-this-year-s-polarizing-13445211.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon after we meet Tony Vallelonga in "Green Book," the Italian-American man tosses out a pair of water glasses because black repairmen drank out of them. His wife fishes them out of the trash can. But by the end of the movie, which follows Tony as he chauffeurs acclaimed jazz pianist Dr. Don Shirley through the Jim Crow South for a two-month concert tour, Tony is the one inviting the black man into his home. This shouldn't come as much of a spoiler. "Green Book," based on a true story and co-written by Tony's son, Nick, has been promoted as a healing tale of how the two men, played by Viggo Mortensen and Mahershala Ali, overcome their differences and form an unlikely friendship in the early 1960s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Unable to Speak, Walk, See, Breathe Days After Getting Flu Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/man-unable-to-speak-walk-see-or-breathe-days-after-getting-flu-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It’s the last time anyone in my family will ever get one'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of poor in Brazil grows by two million...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181205-number-poor-brazil-grows-two-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of poor in Brazil grows by two million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing scale of personal data harvested....</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6465037/Shocking-extent-big-firms-harvest-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis by the Mail found that Marriott International, Facebook, Asda, Paypal, BT and Tesco engaged in hidden data harvesting and sharing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Hudson book reveals secrets closeted star tried to hide...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6464365/Book-reveals-Rock-Hudson-sent-letters-lovers-diagnosed-AIDS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In new biography All That Heaven Allows, author Mark Griffin reveals how Rock Hudson struggled to balance his secret life as a gay man and his Hollywood heartthrob persona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Ranger dog Maiko died in Afghanistan saving soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/419837-army-ranger-dog-named-maiko-died-in-afghanistan-saving-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent clash in Afghanistan resulted in the death of a U.S. soldier and an Army Ranger dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: 2020 Election Will Be Most Violent In American History...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-05/martin-armstrong-2020-presidential-election-will-be-most-violent-american-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Navy to Challenge Moscow in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2018-12-05/us-navy-prepares-to-challenge-russia-in-black-sea-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market sell-off set to continue as Dow futures get hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/05/market-sell-off-set-to-continue-as-dow-futures-get-hit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lingering concerns about an economic slowdown plagued stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gets last laugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/trump-has-last-laugh-on-america-first-after-macron-yellow-vest-u-turn-2018-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron's rebuke of Trump was widely seen as a slap in the face. But it fell on deaf ears among the "Yellow Vests" to whom he has now yielded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Begins Evicting  Homeless From Streets...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/homeless-man-evited-in-nyc-department-of-homeless-services/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city's homeless crisis is apparently so bad that officials are now serving eviction notices before tearing down homeless encampments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER plans self-driving car relaunch... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-uber-selfdriving-test/uber-plans-smaller-more-cautious-self-driving-car-launch-idUSKBN1O502L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber Technologies Inc's is plotting the return of its self-driving cars, bu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot companions for elderly...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/robot-carer-elderly-people-loneliness-ageing-population-care-homes-a8659801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convulsions shake candidate lineup...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/05/democrats-2020-election-1046056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one 24-hour period, a glimpse of the primary election to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. destroyer challenges Moscow claims in Sea of Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-destroyer-challenges-russian-claims-sea-japan-n944566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy sent the USS McCampbell near Peter the Great Bay as the United States and Russia are clashing over a variety of issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California becomes first state mandating solar power for new homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2018/12/05/california-officially-adopts-solar-requirement-for-new-homes-built-in-2020-or-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California became the first state in the U.S. mandating new homes have rooftop solar panels or get power from solar farms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors ramp up foreign lobbying investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/756f95038fd14fa580ea43283f68dfcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Spinning off from the special counsel's Russia probe, prosecutors are ramping up their investigation into foreign lobbying by two major Washington firms that did work for former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort, according to people familiar with the matter. The investigation had been quiet for months since special counsel Robert Mueller referred it to authorities in Manhattan because it fell outside his mandate of determining whether the Trump campaign coordinated with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Flynn Case Winds Down, Probe of Turkish Lobbying Persists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/05/us/politics/michael-flynn-turkey-investigation-virginia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel, Robert S. Mueller III, has referred back to prosecutors in Virginia a case that once ensnared President Trump’s former national security adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power plant steam making snow in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2018-12-04-industrial-plants-snow-monday-nebraska-and-minnesota</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cold air was a contributing factor to this localized snowfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hickenlooper staffs up...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d9a96f2ecbf744c5bcdcbb3d4eb745db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper and his allies are taking new steps toward launching a presidential campaign, including interviews with dozens of potential staffers and hiring a pollster and national fundraiser, according to a person close to the Democrat. He's already launched a political action committee that allows him to raise money nationally and hired his 2014 campaign manager, Brad Komar, to run it. Since the PAC was formed in September, Komar has done 80 interviews with possible campaign staffers, the person said. Of those, Hickenlooper has conducted or participated in 30 interviews. The operation has hired Democratic veteran Anna Greenberg as its pollster and FK &amp;amp; Co. as national fundraisers; it raises money for Democratic senators including Minority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing readies dark side of the Moon mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/china-moon-dark-side-change-4-launch-time-lunar-lander-nasa-a8666181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Luxembourg makes all public transport free...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/luxembourg-to-become-first-country-to-make-all-public-transport-free</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government seeks to prioritise environment and end some of world’s worst traffic congestion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven Marines missing after planes crash off Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/seven-marines-missing-after-planes-crash-off-japan-during-mid-air-refueling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search and rescue operations were underway late Wednesday after two U.S. Marine Corps aircraft crashed while refueling in mid-air during a regularly scheduled training exercise off the coast of Japan, the Marines said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI email chain may provide damning FISA abuse evidence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/419901-fbi-email-chain-may-provide-most-damning-evidence-of-fisa-abuses-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI emails suggest that agency had doubts about Christopher Steele's anti-Trump dossier before citing it in warrant application to FISA court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Intensifies Church Attacks: 'Kill Those Useless Bishops'...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/philippines-duterte-kill-useless-catholic-bishops-181205132220894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provocative president intensifies attack on the Catholic Church, which opposes his deadly war on drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine Corps Aircraft Crash Off Japan...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/marine-aircraft-crash-off-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GORBACHEV: Peace In Jeopardy...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5471437/mikhail-gorbachev-george-hw-bush-war-peace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A remembrance by the only President of the USSR</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly brain-dead woman survives after being removed from life support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/nearly-brain-dead-woman-survives-after-being-removed-life-support-n944276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michele De Leeuw, of Sterling Heights, Michigan, has almost fully recovered after open heart surgery, speech and physical therapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Heading To SUNDANCE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/sundance-2019-new-frontiers-lineup-eminem-arthur-ashe-movies-1202514594/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No word yet if Eminem will be showing up in Park City for one of those late night concerts that only happen at Sundance but the Oscar winning 8 Mile star is certainly part of the New Frontier slate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not enough to contain public anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c692e0741894b4cb8b7c120382bf4db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on mass protests in France (all times local): 9:20 p.m. French protesters are welcoming President Emmanuel Macron's decision to scrap a fuel tax rise planned for next year — but say it may not be enough to contain public anger. Jacline Mouraud, one of the group's self-proclaimed spokespeople, told The Associated Press "I think it comes much too late." She said each of the disparate protesting groups will decide what to do next, but many will probably keep protesting. She says Macron's move on Wednesday night "is on the right path but in my opinion it will not fundamentally change the movement." She urged protesters to seize on the French government's weakness to push other demands such as a rise in the minimum wage. The anti-government protests started last month over the fuel tax but have grown to encompass a broad range of grievances and anger at Macron. More protests are planned Saturday in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg, 25 years after 'SCHINDLER'S LIST,' warns against collective hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nightly-news/spielberg-25-years-after-schindler-s-list-warns-against-collective-n944416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When collective hate organizes and gets industrialized, then genocide follows," the legendary director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board Backs Sandberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-board-backs-sheryl-sandbergs-handling-of-research-into-investor-george-soros-1544038662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s board said it backs Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg’s handling of research into George Soros, calling her request to probe whether the investor shorted the company’s stock “entirely appropriate.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC radio host found dead after walking out during show...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/bbc-radio-presenter-found-dead-walking-mid-way-radio-show-inquest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BBC radio presenter found dead at her home hours after leaving work mid-way through her radio show intended to take her own life, a coroner has ruled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRAZY RICH ASIANS' flops in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-isnt-crazy-at-all-about-crazy-rich-asians-1544031975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hit U.S. movie has turned out to be a flop in the world’s largest population of Asians, where it plays to empty theaters; “Americans just don’t understand us.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Caves...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/latest-leading-protest-activist-macron-speak-59624047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on mass protests in France (all times local): 8:55 p.m. French President Emmanuel Macron has scrapped a fuel tax rise amid fears of new violence, after weeks of nationwide protests and the worst rioting in Paris in decades. An official with the Elysee palace told The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Launches 20th Rocket Of Year, But Can't Stick Landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/05/spacex-launches-its-20th-rocket-of-the-year-but-doesnt-quite-make-the-landing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX has successfully launched its 20th rocket of the year, a mission to the International Space Station (ISS) to take food and supplies, after a problem with some mice food on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES columnist hit by bus awarded $85M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/05/new-york-times-columnist-hit-by-sightseeing-bus-awarded-85m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “Vows” columnist for the New York Times who was run over by a double-decker sightseeing bus won a whopping $85 million award from a Manhattan jury late Tuesday. Devan Sipher, who desc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest 84 in European crackdown on Italian mob...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a6b91b27ea7404c9b29c77212e85f5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — In an investigation that underscored an Italian crime syndicate's role as a leading player in international cocaine trafficking, police in four countries arrested at least 84 suspected mobsters Wednesday in a series of carefully coordinated raids. Those detained allegedly work for the Italian 'ndrangheta criminal network that traffics in cocaine on a global scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New satellite images reveal activity at unidentified NKorea missile base...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/north-korea-satellite-images-missile-base/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New satellite images obtained exclusively by CNN reveal North Korea has significantly expanded a key long-range missile base located in the mountainous interior of the country, offering yet another reminder that diplomatic talks with the US have done little to prevent Kim Jong Un from pursuing his promise to mass produce and deploy the existing types of nuclear warheads in his arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug dealer released from prison carjacks woman in parking lot...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/local/westmoreland/14371705-74/police-youngwood-carjacking-suspect-attacked-woman-outside-westmoreland-county-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Philadelphia man's freedom from the Westmoreland County Prison on Tuesday was short-lived. Moments after Thomas Lee Williams, 36, was released from the Hempfield jail at about 6:15 p.m., police said he attacked a West Leechburg woman in the parking lot, took her sport-utility vehicle and fled with her 1-year-old ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY tower suggested as source of Legionnaires disease...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8cca373502854283815c8a9bb4dd067f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A cooling tower that provides mist to make Disneyland visitors comfortable was the likely source for 22 cases in a Legionnaires' disease outbreak last year near the theme park, a health official testified this week. Most of those who got sick visited the park in the fall of 2017. Disneyland has denied it was the source, pointing to three infected people who had been in the city of Anaheim where Disneyland is located, but not at the park itself. One of them died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops, medics called on mob after CHEESECAKE FACTORY offers free slices...</title>
      <link>https://www.arlnow.com/2018/12/05/developing-large-crowd-reported-at-clarendon-cheesecake-factory-amid-free-cheesecake-promotion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arlnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Updated at 2:15 p.m.) Arlington County police and medics have responded to Clarendon after a promotion for free cheesecake got out of control. Police were called to the area of the Cheesecake Factory at 2900 Clarendon Blvd earlier today for a report of a large crowd and heavy traffic in the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Employees Have Difficulty Breathing After Being Exposed To Animal Repellent...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/firefighters-respond-to-amazon-warehouse-in-robbinsville-after-reports-of-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are looking into "fumes" that reportedly caused the employees to have difficulty breathing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students Caught On Video Having Sex In High School Hallway...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/lawrence-high-school-video-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Public Schools are investigating a video of two students engaged in a sexual act on the high school campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old horse being led to slaughter saves self with great escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article222657875.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alachua County Sheriff’s Office announced a happy ending for the horse that was injured after falling from a trailer on a Florida highway last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W:  The Brightest of  Thousand Points of Light'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-w-bush-eulogizes-his-father-the-brightest-of-a-thousand-points-of-light/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 VISION:  Michael Bloomberg heads to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/bloomberg-iowa-alesci-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg says now that Democrats have won the House, they have to "do something."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY MAG deletes story calling Priyanka Chopra 'scam artist'...</title>
      <link>https://scroll.in/reel/904658/us-website-takes-down-offensive-article-calling-priyanka-chopra-a-global-scam-artist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scroll.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Upon further editorial review, we found this story did not meet our standards,’ said a note on the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Republican Lawmakers Pass Bills to Restrict New Dem Governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wisconsin-gop-lawmakers-pass-bills-to-restrict-new-democratic-governor-1544027159</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin’s Republican-led legislature on Wednesday passed bills that would strip some powers of the incoming Democratic governor, Tony Evers, and curb early voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Cuomo Becomes Most-Watched Anchor on CNN...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/chris-cuomo-ratings-cnn-cable-news-1203080856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has learned that there’s nothing wrong with a little attitude. In just six months, the network’s new 9 p.m. program, “Cuomo Prime Time,” has become the most-watched show on the AT&amp;T-owned c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Dems really do love Republicans  --  when they're dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/04/democrats-really-do-love-republicans-when-theyre-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was a patriot, a hero, a ­genial gentleman and a great American. You can’t pick up a newspaper or go near a television without hearing leftists gush with praise for the late President George H.W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEACHEM: Bush 'A 20th Century Founding Father'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/historian-jon-meacham-delivers-stirring-eulogy-at-george-h-w-bushs-funeral-a-20th-century-founding-father/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Moonves Destroyed Evidence, Misled Investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/les-moonves-obstructed-investigation-into-misconduct-claims-report-says/ar-BBQvr67?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL TOGETHER FOR AN HOUR!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0e443c78c337423db71b9270303888c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The nation's capital is bidding its final farewell to former President George H.W. Bush on Wednesday in a service of prayer and praise that has drawn together world envoys, Americans of high office and many others who were touched by Bush's life in office and afterward. A military band played "Hail to the Chief" as the casket of the 41st president was carried down the U.S. Capitol steps in a solemn procession, with members of the Bush family watching and a cannon salute. His son, former President George W. Bush, placed his hand over his heart. Military pallbearers carried the casket up the steps to the cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clintons snub Trumps?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/bitter-clintons-snub-trumps-at-bush-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton is still bitter. The failed presidential candidate snubbed President Donald and First Lady Melania Trump as the entered former President George H.W. Bush’s funeral today. Watch: ﻿ “President Trump shaking the hands of the Obamas. The Clintons did not acknowledge President Trump,” the CBSN anchor noted. Hillary stared forward as Trump acknowledged the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Is This It?  A Trump-Hater's Guide to Mueller Skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/a-trump-haters-guide-to-mueller-skepticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel is going to put together one hell of a report. But even the president’s foes should ask themselves: was it worth it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEACE IN OUR TIME!  No Trump-slamming at  ceremony 'after deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7903860/george-hw-bush-funeral-no-trump-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE HW’s funeral won’t feature any criticism of Donald Trump after the president “cut a deal with the Bush family” to ensure he wouldn’t be targeted. The US President was disin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC REMEMBERS BUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6463597/George-H-W-Bush-funeral-Final-salute-41st-President.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president died on Friday at his home in Houston, Texas, aged 94 on Friday. His death has silenced political disputes and has brought the country to a standstill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY JEER IN WISCONSIN:  Scott Walker shouted down over Republican attempt to weaken his successor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d95d1190247b4bc6a611c053214cf77e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Demonstrators booed outgoing Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker on Tuesday during a Christmas tree-lighting ceremony, a sign of tumult as Republicans in the Legislature met to push through measures to gut the powers of his Democratic successor. The Legislature met deep into the night Tuesday to pass a series of bills, first unveiled Friday, that would weaken the governor's office and transfer power away from the Democratic-elect attorney general and give it to the Legislature. The Legislature wasn't expected to complete its work until early Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
