<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Too Much Chocolate Can Lead to Death in Middle Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sweet-tooth-heart-disease-midlife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find sugary drinks and eating too much chocolate increases the risk of cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Hawaii visitors cruising around in U-Hauls? Blame the pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/04/22/why-are-visitors-cruising-around-u-hauls-blame-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U-Haul marketing president said Hawaii U-Haul facilities are the busiest they’ve been in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad inventory sells out despite awards show ratings declines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/22/oscars-sells-out-ad-inventory-despite-awards-show-ratings-declines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ratings for awards shows had been slipping even before the pandemic. Viewership for last year's Oscars dropped 20% to a new low, according to Nielsen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Reaches New Heights: Mount Everest...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-19-mount-everest-climbers-superspreader-0852f6ea-f19c-4867-a92b-5771e39dd456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medical experts recently confirmed the first coronavirus cases among climbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon sex therapist ousted from church...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/religion/2021/04/21/lds-sex-therapist-natasha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Latter-day Saint sex therapist who has publicly and repeatedly opposed the church’s doctrines, policies and leaders on sexuality issues has had her membership from the faith withdrawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans push half trillion dollar infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422190717-1qral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/INFRASTRUCTURE-REPUBLICANS (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Republicans unveil $568 bln infrastructure package to counter Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes capital gains hike to 43.4%; for NY could be 52.2%, CA 56.7%!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/22/biden-eyes-capital-gains-hike-to-43-4-for-ny-could-be-52-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will reportedly be proposing new capital gains tax rates that will be quite the raise for some New Yorkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jake Paul Promised Them Fame. Was It Worth Price?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/22/jake-paul-promised-them-fame-was-it-worth-the-price/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the vast world of YouTube villains, there may be none as famous as Jake Paul. The 24-year-old Vine star</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet neighbor releases security camera footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9500075/MaKhia-Bryants-neighbor-says-security-camera-footage-shows-cop-no-choice-shoot-her.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home security footage taken from a garage across the street has captured a new angle of the police shooting of Ma'Khia Bryant in Columbus, Ohio, Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambassador sorry after wife slaps SKorea shop worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56848548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Lescouhier says his wife's reaction to being suspected of shoplifting was unacceptable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Honey Radioactive From Decades of Nuke Bomb Testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dbzan/american-honey-is-radioactive-from-decades-of-nuclear-bomb-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that bees have been harvesting elevated levels of irradiated pollen for decades</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggering Mystery Illnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/22/troops-directed-energy-attacks-484246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DoD briefers identified Russia as a likely culprit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W. Bush Cautions McConaughey Over Possible Gov Run...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/549773-bush-mcconaughey-would-need-to-tune-out-his-critics-if-he-runs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President George W. Bush says Matthew McConaughey could have a shot at being Texas's next governor, if he has "the principles" to tune out his critics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global press freedom deteriorates...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/global-press-freedom-deteriorates-amid-pandemic-55bbfb25-0cb4-4e07-bd03-f14d1ea53103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway is first, the U.S. is 44th and China is near the bottom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>43.4% for Wealthy!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-eyeing-capital-gains-tax-171528499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden will propose almost doubling the capital gains tax rate for wealthy individuals to 39.6%, which, coupled with an existing surtax on investment income, means that federal tax rates for investors could be as high as 43.4%, according to people familiar with the proposal.The plan would boost the capital gains rate to 39.6% for those earning $1 million or more, an increase from the current base rate of 20%, the people said on the condition of anonymity because the plan is not yet public. A 3.8% tax on investment income that funds Obamacare would be kept in place, pushing the tax rate on returns on financial assets higher than the top rate on wage and salary income, they said.Stocks slid on news about the plan, with the S&amp;P 500 Index down 0.7% as of 1:43 p.m. after climbing 0.2% earlier. The Nasdaq Composite fell 0.6% after rising as much as 0.5%. Ten-year Treasury yields erased gains.The proposal could reverse a long-standing provision of the tax code that taxes returns on investment lower than on labor. Biden campaigned on equalizing the capital gains and income tax rates for wealthy individuals, saying it’s unfair that many of them pay lower rates than middle-class workers.QuickTake: How Capital Gains Are Taxed and What Biden Might DoThe White House didn’t immediately respond to a request for comment, and the Treasury Department declined to comment. Biden is expected to release the proposal next week as part of the tax increases to fund social spending in the forthcoming “American Families Plan.”That proposal, expected at around $1 trillion, will come as Congress debates how to proceed on Biden’s separate $2.25 trillion infrastructure-focused package known as the American Jobs Plan, which would be funded by tax increases on corporations. It also follows the $1.9 trillion coronavirus-relief bill passed in March.The families plan is set to include a wave of new spending on children and education, including a temporary extension of an expanded child tax credit that would give parents up to $300 a month for young children or $250 for those six and older.The capital gains increase would raise $370 billion over a decade, according to an estimate from the Urban-Brookings Tax Policy Center based on Biden’s campaign platform.State LeviesFor $1 million earners in high-tax states, rates on capital gains could be above 50%. For New Yorkers, the combined state and federal capital gains rate could be as high as 52.22%. For Californians, it could be 56.7%.Democrats have said current capital gains rates largely help top earners who get their income through investments rather than in the form of wages, resulting in lower tax rates for wealthy people than those they employ. Republicans argue that the current framework encourages saving and promote future economic growth.Capital gains taxes are paid when an asset is sold, and are applied to the amount of appreciation on the asset from when it was bought to when it is sold.Congressional Democrats have separately proposed a series of changes to capital-gains taxation, including imposing the levies annually instead of when they are sold.(Updates with background on plan starting in seventh paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXCONN Finally Admits It Won't Create 13,000 Jobs in Wisconsin...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/04/21/foxconn-finally-admits-it-wont-create-13000-jobs-in-wisconsin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It now plans to employ just 1,454 people after bulldozing dozens of homes to make room for a factory Donald Trump once touted as the "eighth wonder of the world."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario premier's apologizes after retracting restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-canada-ontario-coronavirus-b2a24a77e803c60ea6b3ea701282670d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Ontario Premier Doug Ford apologized Thursday for a failed attempt to ban playgrounds and allow police to stop and question people who were not in their homes — measures that created a backlash from police forces, health officials and the public. The leader of Canada’s most populous province, in his first public appearance since announcing the restrictions, said his government had moved too fast with the measures. "They left a lot of people angry and upset. I know we got it wrong. I know we made a mistake and for that I’m sorry and sincerely apologize,” said Ford, who appeared to choke back tears at one point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd Square sign gives list of special orders for white visitors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/22/sign-at-george-floyd-square-has-list-of-orders-for-white-visitors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The square where George Floyd was murdered by ex-Minnesota cop Derek Chauvin now has a sign with special rules for white people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burnt out: Exhausting cult of productivity finally over?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2021/apr/22/burnt-out-is-the-exhausting-cult-of-productivity-finally-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the last decade, employees have been encouraged to see work and life as interchangeable, and to hustle ever harder. But the pandemic has brought a new reckoning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58% Will Look For New Job If Forced To Return To Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/remote-work-full-time-after-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 11 percent said not being allowed to work at home anymore wouldn't bother them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 in 10 healthcare workers consider leaving profession...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Burned-out-by-the-pandemic-3-in-10-health-care-16120843.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor's bag now sits in his closet gathering dust. He lost his stethoscope somewhere...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC 51ST STATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dc-statehood-bill-house-vote-51st/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the bill passed in the House, it's likely to fail in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Leave us alone!': Australian beach town taking on NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/netflix-faces-byron-bay-backlash-australian-beach-town-fights-reality-n1264901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Byron Bay, known for its relaxed lifestyle, is fighting back in an effort to stop the show — and what some see as a "vacuous, vapid, inaccurate depiction" of their hometown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired Sheriff, Longtime K9 Partner Pass Away Hours Apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/retired-ohio-sheriff-and-his-k9-partner-the-worlds-smallest-police-dog-die-on-same-day-66368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Midge, a rat terrier Chihuahua, was by Geauga County Sheriff Dan McClelland's side for 16 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamptons summer RENTAL for $2 million!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/22/a-house-just-rented-in-the-hamptons-for-2-million-for-the-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A home in the Hamptons rented for $2 million for the summer, as demand far outstrips a record low supply of homes for sale and for rent, according to brokers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters descend on Manchin's houseboat...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/978885/joe-manchin-lives-boat-washington--protesters-are-reportedly-headed-there</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters evidently want all hands on deck in the push to make Washington, D.C. a state, and they're now headed to Sen. Joe Manchin's (D-W.Va.) nautical home. Advocates for D.C. statehood are planning a protest on Thursday, Politico reported, and they'll be gathering at Manchin's house ... boat. 'Yes,' Politico writes for those unfamiliar, '[Manchin] lives on a boat docked in the harbor when he's in Washington.' Indeed, the boat, Almost Heaven, is 'anchored 8 miles south of the Capitol,' a Time story described in 2014, going on to note that Manchin 'routinely invites senators from both parties out for evening cruises.' 'I wasn't crazy on buying any real estate in Washington, not at all,' Manchin told Time. The Washingtonian may have summed it up by writing, 'Manchin lives on a boat because he doesn't like living here.' In fact, this ended up sparking a Republican attack ad against Manchin in 2018, which slammed him for his '$700,000 D.C. luxury yacht.' That's an assertion PolitiFact gave a 'half-true' rating, writing that the boat's '40-foot length would generally qualify it as a yacht, but since Manchin lives there when he is in town, it could be just as easily described as a houseboat' — though he apparently purchased it for $220,000.  Either way, it seems Manchin is one lawmaker who at any given moment — including, perhaps, as protesters gather — is always ready to sail away into the sunset. Brendan Morrow Today I learned from @politico playbook that Joe Manchin’s DC residence is a house boat... pic.twitter.com/oXIzR02irY — Andrew Solender (@AndrewSolender) April 22, 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bugs Allowed Hackers to Dox All JOHN DEERE Owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avy8j/bugs-allowed-hackers-to-dox-all-john-deere-owners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A security researcher found two bugs that allowed him to find all customers who had purchased John Deere tractors or equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Tourists Flock to Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/latin-american-vaccine-tourists-flock-to-texas-for-coveted-covid-jabs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Vaccine tourists” from Mexico and other Latin American countries are booking trips to Texas to get their jabs as rollouts in their home countries stall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desanti$ gives sports betting to Seminole Tribe...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article250847709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of all states now allow some form of legal sports betting, and if a proposal which has been agreed to in principle between the Seminole Tribe of Florida and the state gets approved by the Legislature in the next week, Florida could be added to that list and at least $500 million in annual revenue could be added to the budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Set to Raise Taxes on Rich to Fund Child Care and Education...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/22/business/biden-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s American Family Plan, which remains in flux, does not currently include an effort to expand health coverage, as administration officials had previously planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope announces 'marathon' month of prayer to end pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9500115/Pope-announces-marathon-month-prayer-end-Covid-19-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pope has encouraged Catholics around the world to dedicate next month to praying for the end of the virus which has seen more than three million people die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Britain opening up but many bathrooms closed, outdoor excrement serious problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/With-Britain-opening-up-but-many-bathrooms-still-16120510.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - With Britain slowly easing its way out of its third nationwide lockdown, people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president suggests U.S. citizenship for tree planting program...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422132321-s6mv8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-CLIMATE/SUMMIT-MEXICO (URGENT, PIX):Mexico president suggests U.S. citizenship for tree planting program</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commercial Airline Pilots Keep Reporting UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xewj/air-canada-westjet-porter-pilots-ufo-sightings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICE World News has uncovered dozens of recent UFO reports from Air Canada, WestJet, Porter, and other airlines in a government aviation incident database.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOLE FOODS:  PAY WITH YOUR PALM</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-let-whole-foods-shoppers-pay-with-swipe-their-palm-2021-04-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutally Honest Oscar Ballot: 'MANK' Boring, 'CHICAGO 7' Mediocre, 'MINARI' Excruciatingly Slow...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/oscars-2021-brutally-honest-ballot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A male member of the Academy’s producers branch explains how one of his favorite directors (Fincher) and his favorite writer (Sorkin) disappointed him and why this year’s Oscars deserves an asterisk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin downplays pro-Navalny rallies after nearly 1,800 detained...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210422-kremlin-downplays-pro-navalny-rallies-after-nearly-1-800-detained</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin downplays pro-Navalny rallies after nearly 1,800 detained</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boehner Autobiography Debuts at No. 1 on NYT Best Sellers List...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/boehner-nyt-best-sellers-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker John Boehner's autobiography topped the New York Times bestsellers list in its first week on the market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Beg, borrow, steal': Fight for oxygen...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422123646-2g876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/INDIA-OXYGEN (PIX, TV):'Beg, borrow, steal': the fight for oxygen among New Delhi's hospitals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Tops All Networks for Verdict Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/chauvin-verdict-ratings-cnn-tops-cable-broadcast-networks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ratings are in for Tuesday's conviction of former police officer Derek Chauvin and CNN led the way, beating broadcast and cable competitors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body language expert analyzes George Floyd's killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9496979/Body-language-expert-analyzes-Derek-Chauvins-behavior-George-Floyd-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Body language expert Patti Wood spoke to DailyMail.com about key points in Derek Chauvin's trial that shed light on what he was thinking and feeling with all eyes on him in Hennepin County court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI unlocks ancient Dead Sea Scrolls mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-56842712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Cutting edge technology" reveals how scribes foiled modern scholars with one of the Biblical texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service running 'covert operation' to monitor social posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/the-postal-service-is-running-a-running-a-covert-operations-program-that-monitors-americans-social-media-posts-160022919.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law enforcement arm of the U.S. Postal Service has been quietly running a program that tracks and collects Americans’ social media posts, including those about planned protests, according to a document obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Working From Home Makes MORE Productive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theedgemarkets.com/article/yes-working-home-makes-you-more-productive-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theedgemarkets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(April 22): The great work-from-home experiment occasioned by the pandemic has divided opinion in the corporate suite and sparked endless debates about whether employees work as effectively from the kitchen table as they do from the office.A new study finds that, in fact, remote work does indeed make us more productive.The work-from-home boom will lift productivity in the U.S. economy by 5%, mostly because of savings in commuting time, the study says. The findings suggest the rapid adoption of new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Automated Checkout Coming to Full-Size Supermarkets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/amazon-e2-80-99s-automated-checkout-is-coming-to-full-size-supermarkets/ar-BB1fVAhL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Widespread adoption could fuel charges the company aims to eliminate cashiers. Amazon denies that, saying it created thousands of grocery jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,700 detained at pro-Navalny rallies across Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210422-over-1-700-detained-at-pro-navalny-rallies-across-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 1,700 detained at pro-Navalny rallies across Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Faces Backlash Over Warning To Ohio Officer Who Shot Black Teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/lebron-james-faces-backlash-over-youre-next-tweet-about-ohio-police-officer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns West of harsh response if crosses 'red lines'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/21/putin-warns-against-crossing-russias-red-lines-talks-up-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his annual State of the Nation speech, Russian President Vladimir Putin warned against provoking his country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden opening summit with ambitious climate pledge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-climate-climate-change-summits-d27b869add251860acc82f58e2750fd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will open a global climate summit with a pledge to cut at least in half the climate-wrecking coal and petroleum fumes that the U.S. pumps out, a commitment he hopes will spur China and other big polluters to speed up efforts of their own. Biden is offering Americans and the world a vision of a prosperous, clean-energy United States where factories churn out cutting-edge batteries for export, line workers re-lay an efficient national electrical grid and crews cap abandoned oil and gas rigs and coal mines. His commitment to cut U.S. fossil fuel emissions up to 52% by 2030 — similar to pledges from allies — will come at the launch Thursday of an all-virtual climate summit for 40 world leaders, marking a return by the U.S. to global climate efforts after four years of withdrawal under President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Citizenship Renunciation To Rise Dramatically?</title>
      <link>https://www.wealthbriefing.com/html/article.php?id=190932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wealthbriefing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA extracts breathable oxygen from Martian air...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/nasa-extracts-breathable-oxygen-thin-martian-air-2021-04-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air defense system fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/alarms-sound-in-south-of-israel-665953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SA-5 flies from Syria all the way to Negev in longest-range attack by Syria. Patriot missile activated in response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes targets in Syria after missile lands near nuke reactor...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20210422-israel-strikes-targets-in-syria-after-missile-lands-near-nuclear-reactor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Syrian surface-to-air missile exploded in southern Israel on Thursday, the Israeli military said, in an incident that triggered warning sirens in an area near the secretive Dimona nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Sales Surging. When Does Music Stop?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/22/u-s-home-sales-are-surging-when-does-the-music-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As housing omens go, beware the trending Google search. In the first week of April, U.S. search interest in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom launches effort to deal with drought; Emergencies declared...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2021-04-21/california-drought-newsom-mendocino-sonoma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Newsom has declared a drought emergency in Mendocino and Sonoma counties but said he was not prepared to issue statewide water-use restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California case rate now lowest in USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-case-rate-now-184916537.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's latest seven-day new case rate — 40.3 per 100,000 people — is dramatically lower than the nationwide rate of 135.3 over that same time period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah's life coach on how to be much happier:   'Let yourself be quirky'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2021/apr/21/oprah-winfrey-life-coach-martha-beck-how-be-happier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martha Beck survived abuse, went to Harvard, left her husband – then began working with the world’s biggest TV star. She discusses self-help, nonconformity and the power of truth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Republicans running for Virginia governor wary of vote-counting software...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/three-republicans-running-for-virginia-governor-wary-of-vote-counting-software/ar-BB1fUkRd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rivals teamed up on a letter to the state GOP calling for a hand count of ballots at the party’s nominating convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 55% of Republicans agree with guilty decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/04/21/chauvin-verdict-poll-majority-approve-guilty-finding/7316788002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hours a verdict was announced in the Derek Chauvin murder trial, a USA TODAY/Ipsos snap poll found 71% of Americans agreed Chauvin was guilty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US spy planes keep unusually close eye on China amid live-fire military exercises...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3130500/us-spy-planes-keep-close-eye-china-amid-live-fire-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American aircraft goes unusually near naval base on east coast, think tank says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin awarded firm $1.3 billion to make syringes. Where are they?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-care/trump-administration-awarded-firm-1-3-billion-make-covid-vaccine-n1263872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Covid vaccines are here, but the ApiJect syringe is not yet approved by federal regulators and a new factory in North Carolina is not yet built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT ESCAPE:  Demand may soon exceed supply says CEO of biggest hotel groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/demand-may-exceed-supply-as-ceo-of-one-of-the-worlds-biggest-hotel-groups-sees-surge-in-bookings-11618999201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotel and airline industry will begin to bounce back by second half of 2021, according to the chief executive of InterContinental Hotels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett new PM?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/likud-attacks-bennett-again-665867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says he'd be opposition leader, won't seek presidency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH TIMES:  Entrepreneurs becoming marijuana moguls...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/marijuana-moguls-grow-in-ranks-as-states-legalize-cannabis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the movement to legalize marijuana for medicinal and recreational use sweeps the country the cannabis industry is creating new jobs and raking in millions of dollars in legal profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEENS RUNNING FROM INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90627938/nike-and-chick-fil-a-are-winning-the-hearts-of-american-teens-instagram-is-losing-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snapchat is king. Beyond Meat is tasty. A new report from Piper Sandler offers insight into the hearts, minds, and wallets of generation Z.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's deadliest cartel uses drones to drop bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mexicos-violent-jalisco-new-generation-23955985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's powerful Jalisco New Generation Cartel is run by El Mencho who reportedly ramped up attacks on police following the extradition of his son Rubén Oseguera González to the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Lost on Mountain Follows Hikers to 10,000-ft Summit for Company, Comfort...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/pets/cat-lost-on-swiss-mountain-joins-hikers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lost cat followed two hikers to the top of Mt. Britsen in Switzerland before eventually getting the help she need to reunite with her family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU MOVES TO REGULATE AI</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-government-and-politics-artificial-intelligence-data-privacy-5226382bb316f8aad4cbc5637f03a44c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Risky uses of artificial intelligence that threaten people’s safety or rights such as live facial scanning should be banned or tightly controlled, European Union officials said Wednesday as they outlined an ambitious package of proposed regulations to rein in the rapidly expanding technology. The draft regulations from the EU's executive commission include rules for applications deemed high risk such as AI systems to filter out school, job or loan applicants. They would also ban artificial intelligence outright in a few cases considered too risky, such as government “social scoring” systems that judge people based on their behavior. The proposals are the 27-nation bloc’s latest move to maintain its role as the world’s standard-bearer for technology regulation, as it tries to keep up with the world's two big tech superpowers, the U.S. and China. EU officials say they are taking a four-level “risk-based approach” that seeks to balance important rights such as privacy against the need to encourage innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 arrested at Navalny rallies in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-180-reported-arrest-alexei-navalny-demonstrations-b0fd8e696c86792b5cb1a291fb6338e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Police arrested nearly 1,500 people Wednesday during a day of demonstrations throughout Russia calling for freedom for imprisoned opposition leader Alexei Navalny, whose health reportedly is in severe decline after three weeks of hunger striking, according to a group that monitors political detentions. The largest of the protests took place in Moscow, where thousands marched through the center city. Some of the people arrested were seized before the protests even began, including to top Navalny associates in Moscow. Navalny’s team called for the unsanctioned demonstrations after weekend reports that his health is deteriorating and his life was in danger.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
