<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Collectible Prices Skyrocket, to Dismay of Hobbyists...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2021-09-03/collectible-prices-skyrocket-to-the-dismay-of-hobbyists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have become obsessed with collectibles, bidding up prices for trading cards, video games and other mementos of their youth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ Gov Who Backed Bolsonaro Now Wants Brazil's Top Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/lgbtq-governor-who-backed-bolsonaro-now-wants-brazils-top-job/ar-AAO3EbV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eduardo Leite is young, investor-friendly and vying for the Brazilian presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dearth of Employees Risks Even Higher Food Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2021-09-03/supply-lines-latest-dearth-of-workers-risks-even-higher-food-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milkshakes are missing from U.K.’s McDonald’s branches, tomatoes are rotting on Italian farms, and soldiers mingle with farmers on Vietnam’s rice paddies. All because of shortage of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Uses More Electricity Than Many Countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/09/03/climate/bitcoin-carbon-footprint-electricity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most popular cryptocurrency wastes energy by design. Why is that, and could it ever be greener?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Sparks Political Controversy With Taiwan Films Name Change...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/venice-film-fest-political-controversy-taiwan-movies-name-change-1235007855/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Festival organizers have rankled Taiwanese officials by listing two films in its lineup as being from "Chinese Taipei."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jab snob' travelers flock to Guam for sun, sea, shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Vaccine-snob-travelers-flock-to-Guam-for-sun-16433041.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUMON, Guam - Passport: check. Coronavirus test: negative. Temperature: normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no tourist handouts, hungry Bali monkeys raid homes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-monkeys-da48c1eda07af577f5ffe38ae397179f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANGEH, Indonesia (AP) — Deprived of their preferred food source — the bananas, peanuts and other goodies brought in by tourists now kept away by the coronavirus — hungry monkeys on the resort island of Bali have taken to raiding villagers’ homes in their search for something tasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS-inspired extremist stabs six in New Zealand terror attack...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/zealand-police-shoot-dead-isis-inspired-extremist-stabs/story?id=79808759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand is reeling from a knife-wielding rampage at a supermarket that left six fighting for their lives and the assailant dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats coming down with diseases caused by stress of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9952167/Cats-falling-ill-life-threatening-STRESS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus took hold early last year and the government told people to stay home for work and school, our pets started to get more attention than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most NYC victims were trapped in basement apartments...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/nyc-flooding-kills-several-residents-of-basement-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flooding from the remnants of Ida proved fatal for several New Yorkers living in a particularly vulnerable type of abode: the basement apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban feel 'angry and betrayed' after troops destroyed aircraft before fleeing Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/taliban-feel-angry-betrayed-troops-24899396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Government has been heavily criticised after leaving millions of dollars worth of sophisticated weaponry and aircraft in the hands of the terror group in Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Approval of Labor Unions at Highest Point Since 1965...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/354455/approval-labor-unions-highest-point-1965.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-thirds of Americans approve of labor unions, marking the highest reading since 1965. Union membership among U.S. adults is steady, at 9%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of  Small Businesses Have Unfilled Positions...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/half-u-small-businesses-unfilled-173237603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.A record share of U.S. small-business owners said they had vacant positions in August, and an unprecedented number boosted wages to lure workers, the National Federation of Independent Business said Thursday.Fifty percent of firms had job openings they could not fill last month, up 1 percentage point from July and the largest share in monthly data back to 1986, according to the NFIB dat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to roll out its own TV...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-roll-own-tv-u-001236974.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc is planning to launch its Amazon-branded TV in the United States as soon as October, Business Insider reported on Thursday. The launch, involving teams from Amazon Devices and Lab126, has been in the works for almost two years, the report https://bit.ly/3t9bzrZ said, citing people familiar with the matter. The TVs, which will be powered by voice assistant Alexa, are currently designed and manufactured by third parties, one of which is TCL, the report added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow Returns to ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/tim-tebow-espn-first-take-stephen-a-smith-sparring-partner-1234826748/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow was announced today by ESPN as one of the initial debate partners on Stephen A. Smith’s First Take. Tebow, who was cut from the NFL’s Jacksonville Jaguars in his latest pro spots co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of 'Shadow Docket' Fuels Criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/texas-abortion-ruling-renews-criticism-173730197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of lawmakers in both parties have questioned how the Supreme Court handles emergency appeals through its so-called shadow docket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  THREE Doses to Become Standard Covid Regimen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fauci-defends-covid-boosters-says-three-shots-will-likely-be-the-new-norm-210524610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci defended the administration’s decision to recommend coronavirus vaccine booster shots and said that three doses of an mRNA vaccine, not two, would be the new standard of full vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABBA unveils 'sensational' musical comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9951979/ABBA-releasing-new-songs-40-YEARS-play-hologram-tour.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABBA have revealed they are releasing their first new songs for 40 YEARS in the form of a studio album and will play a 'greatest hits'  tour as digital characters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested, charged over MSNBC TV confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/benjamin-eugene-dagley-msnbc-shaquille-brewster-assault-suspect-arrest-warrants-1234825163/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with arrest information: U.S. Marshals arrested Benjamin Eugene Dagley on Thursday at a shopping plaza in Dayton, Ohio, and the Gulfport Police Department in Mississippi has filed criminal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flights resume, SOME power restored in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-business-environment-and-nature-louisiana-hurricanes-840ac80b55ad6a6b3201631044a0dce5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Commercial flights resumed in New Orleans and power returned to parts of the business district Thursday, four days after Hurricane Ida slammed into the Gulf Coast, but electricity, drinking water and fuel remained scarce across much of a sweltering Louisiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuba diver has head bitten by tiger shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3589753/shocking-moment-tiger-shark-attacks-divers-head/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a massive tiger shark dubbed “Big Mama” chomps down on a diver’s head before pals kick the beast away. Real-time underwater footage shows the hungry sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELLEN'S REDEMPTION TOUR...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3589770/ellen-degeneres-show-guests-kim-kardashian-jennifer-aniston-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Kardashian and Jennifer Aniston are two of the celebrities lending their support for Ellen DeGeneres by agreeing to appear on her talk show. Despite claims of Ellen’s show having a “toxic workp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: 3 shots for everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/covid-vaccine-fauci-says-he-would-not-be-surprised-if-full-regimen-is-three-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giving people an additional dose several months after they've received their initial vaccination helps the immune system mature, Fauci said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Draft Tucked Into Defense Bill...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/democrats-tuck-female-draft-into-defense-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon will have to start drafting women in order to receive funding after House Democrats amended the defense budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF THE ROE?</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/supreme-court-just-effectively-overturned-201416160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And opened the door to armies of private vigilantes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOKer Rallies Fans to Bombard 'Whistleblower' Site With Fake Tips...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tiktoker-creates-script-to-bombard-texas-abortion-whistleblower-site-with-fake-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok “hacktivist” has created a script to flood a Texas website used to solicit information on people seeking abortions with fake reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI unveils new concept car as 'private jet for road'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/audi-unveils-grandsphere-concept-car-as-a-private-jet-for-the-road.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the vehicle can't fly, Audi said it designed the electric car with such luxury private travel in mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LISTEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/02/abba-drops-2-songs-announces-new-album-avatar-tour-now-look-like-steely-dans-becker-and-fagen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benny and Bjorn from ABBA now look like Donald Fagen and Walter Becker from Steely Dan. Forty years later, they’re releasing a new album on November 5th called “Voyage.” Two of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk declines to address law after Gov. suggests he supports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/texas-abortion-law-elon-musk-reacts-to-gov-greg-abbotts-comments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk declined to directly weigh in on Texas' abortion law after Gov. Greg Abbott said the Tesla CEO supported his state's "social policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel now world's Covid hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9951117/Israel-worlds-Covid-hotspot-0-2-population-catching-yesterday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country recorded 1,892 cases per million people on Wednesday - nearly 0.2 per cent of the entire population in a single day - stats compiled by an Oxford University research team show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' stars sued for fraud...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/02/shark-tank-stars-kevin-oleary-kevin-harrington-sued-for-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty hopeful entrepreneurs claim the famed business investors manipulated them into paying their companies and received no help in return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Gets Jab...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/02/tom-brady-vaccinated-bruce-arians-buccaneers-100-percent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buccaneers head coach Bruce Arians told the media on Thursday that 100 percent of the team's players, coaches, and staff have been vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular surfing instructor, Q, and an unspeakable horror...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/popular-surfing-instructor-qanon-unspeakable-120045161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Barbara residents are struggling to make sense of a tragedy involving Matt Coleman, head of a local surf school, and the killings of his two young children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning into landslide...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/Newsom-recall-poll-election-California-yes-Elder-16430710.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Newsom's most favorable recall poll in a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vows 'whole-of-government' response...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/unconstitutional-chaos-biden-vows-whole-government-response-after-texas-abortion-n1278380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden called the U.S. Supreme Court’s 5-4 ruling “an unprecedented assault on a woman’s constitutional rights under Roe v. Wade."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma Company Ready to Jab Dogs, Cats, Zoo Animals...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/09/01/although-covid-19-rare-in-cats-dogs-pharmaceutical-company-says-theyre-ready-with-a-vaccine-if-needed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If or when cats and dogs need COVID vaccine, Zoetis pharmaceutical company is ready to provide. At this time the virus is rare in pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK to Want to Exterminate People, Greece's New Health Minister Once Argued...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kv3za/its-ok-to-want-to-exterminate-people-greeces-new-health-minister-once-argued</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanos Plevris, the man in charge of Greece's pandemic response, has apologised if comments he made about Auschwitz while defending his own dad from Holocaust-denial offended any Jewish people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxxer's family ridiculed after 'begging' for money...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/global/antivaxxers-family-slammed-for-begging-for-money/news-story/6cb5726f9c1a9d03158c92c238c36f57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of a Covid-19 conspiracy theorist who ultimately died of the virus has been ridiculed for “begging” for money and launching a fundraising page — with strangers accusing them of “stupidity” and urging potential donors not “to help pay for the funeral of someone who caused others to die”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Must Face Claim That Siri Violates Privacy, Judge Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-02/apple-must-face-claim-that-siri-violates-privacy-judge-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge allowed a lawsuit against Apple Inc. to proceed with a claim that its Siri voice assistant violates users’ privacy, but he dismissed part of the complaint under California’s Unfair Competition Law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving workplace spawns new jobs: Social scientist, remote work evangelist, digital anthropologist....</title>
      <link>https://metropolismag.com/viewpoints/think-lab-future-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metropolismag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ThinkLab report finds that if we adapt as we go, the workplace could become a practical extension of our present conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Digital Currencies to Be Tested in Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/central-bank-digital-currencies-tested-040000941.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Bank for International Settlements will test the use of central bank digital currencies with Australia, Malaysia, Singapore and South Africa in an experiment that could lead to a more efficient global payments platform.Codenamed “Project Dunbar,” the study aims to develop prototypes for a common platform that will enable international settlement in digital fiat currencies issued by central banks, BIS said in a release Thursday. The system would allow direct transactions in cen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Store requires customers present pic of horse to purchase Ivermectin...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktnv.com/news/coronavirus/las-vegas-feed-store-sells-out-of-ivermectin-blames-customers-trying-to-treat-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktnv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At V &amp; V Tack and Feed, they normally stock and sell ivermectin for use on horses. But right now, they're completely sold out of the horse dewormer, and store associate Shelly Smith suspects a lot of her customers aren't using it as intended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL brings back 'social justice' decals...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32132328/nfl-brings-back-social-justice-helmet-decals-end-zone-stencils-part-inspire-change-platform</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players can wear social justice messages on their helmets again this season and "It Takes All of Us" and "End Racism" will be stenciled in end zones for the second straight year as part of the league's Inspire Change platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why human beings are obsessed with status...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/09/life-is-one-big-status-game/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle to be virtuous inspires endless political cruelty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets Turned Into Raging Rivers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/photo-galleries/2021/09/02/ida-remnants-batter-tri-state-with-historic-rain-tornado-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once category 4 hurricane passed through New York City, dumping 3.15 inches of rain in the span of an hour at Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIPER VENOM SHOWS PROMISE?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazilian-viper-venom-may-become-173012111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian researchers have found that a molecule in the venom of a type of snake inhibited coronavirus reproduction in monkey cells, a possible first step toward a drug to combat the virus causing COVID-19. A study published in the scientific journal Molecules this month found that the molecule produced by the jararacussu pit viper inhibited the virus's ability to multiply in monkey cells by 75%. "We were able to show this component of snake venom was able to inhibit a very important protein from the virus," said Rafael Guido, a University of Sao Paulo professor and an author of the study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Readying GOOGLE Antitrust Lawsuit Over Ad Business...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-doj-readying-google-antitrust-204728728.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. antitrust officials are preparing a second monopoly lawsuit against Alphabet Inc.’s Google over the company’s digital advertising business, according to a person familiar with the matter, stepping up the government’s claims that Google is abusing its dominance.The Justice Department has accelerated its investigation of Google’s digital advertising practices and may file a lawsuit as soon as the end of the year, said the person, who declined to be named because the investigati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than dozen deaths after Ida remnants slam Northeast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/northeast-us-new-york-new-jersey-weather-60327279197e14b9d17632ea0818f51c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The remnants of Hurricane Ida inundated large swaths of the northeastern U.S. with historic and unanticipated fury Wednesday night, killing at least 14 people in flooding in New York, New Jersey and Pennsylvania as basement apartments suddenly filled with water, rivers and creeks swelled to record levels and roadways turned into car-swallowing canals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans 'sissy men' from TV in new crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-business-religion-china-62dda0fc98601dd5afa3aa555a901b3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China’s government banned effeminate men on TV and told broadcasters Thursday to promote “revolutionary culture,” broadening a campaign to tighten control over business and society and enforce official morality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel prepares to step down...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-fb1b1e7e87232054548e7ab5d6a7d8a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Angela Merkel will leave office as one of modern Germany's longest-serving leaders and a global diplomatic heavyweight, with a legacy defined by her management of a succession of crises that shook a fragile Europe rather than any grand visions for her own country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/crazy-footage-shows-tornado-passing-over-burlington-bristol-bridge-in-new-jersey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Burlington-Bristol Bridge appears to have stood up to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT LEAST 15 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3583837/toddler-and-eight-others-dead-in-hurricane-ida-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORRENTIAL downpours and tornadoes have battered northeastern USA claiming the lives of at least 18 people, including a two-year-old boy. The powerful remnants of Hurricane Ida sparked chaos across…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TWISTERS IN NJ...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/01/video-shows-tornadoes-tear-through-new-jersey-penn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple tornados swirled through New Jersey, ripping apart and flattening homes amid furious downpours and flash floods from the remnants of Hurricane Ida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM, FORD halt some production as chip crisis grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-ed8ff73b019ccf0836f9032f2b02291e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The global shortage of computer chips is getting worse, forcing automakers to temporarily close factories including those that build popular pickup trucks. General Motors announced Thursday that it would pause production at seven North American plants during the next two weeks, including two that make the company's top-selling Chevrolet Silverado pickup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candace Owens Says Testing Facility Refused Her for 'Spreading Misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/candace-owens-covid-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candace Owens said Wednesday that a private facility in Colorado refused to test her for COVID for "spreading misinformation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Harms of Masking Young Students Are Real...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/09/school-mask-mandates-downside/619952/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The educational cost of face coverings for young students is far better established than the benefits of mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Warning Light on Branson's Space Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-red-warning-light-on-richard-bransons-space-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The F.A.A. is investigating the ship’s off-course descent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: 'Broke' Mohamed Hadid builds NEW $250M hilltop mansion in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9949529/Mohamed-Hadids-latest-250M-hilltop-mansion-Beverly-Hills-blasted-local-residents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohamed Hadid, the father of supermodels Gigi and Bella Hadid, has started construction on a new Beverly Hills property overlooking Coldwater Canyon with an asking price of $250 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs Now Run Haiti, Filling Vacuum Left by Years of Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/gangs-now-run-haiti-filling-a-vacuum-left-by-years-of-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gangs Now Run Haiti, Filling a Vacuum Left by Years of Collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man facing charges after escaping quarantine hotel in New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/570511-man-facing-charges-after-escaping-quarantine-hotel-in-new</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand authorities said Thursday that a man who tested positive for COVID-19 could face a fine or jail time after he escaped a quarantine hotel to return home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL returns social justice helmet decals, end zone stencils...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-nfl-c10867c92924cc9a59c99e220c8ee84e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players can wear social justice messages on their helmets again this season and “It Takes All of Us” and “End Racism” will be stenciled in end zones for the second straight year as part of the league’s Inspire Change platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Florida Hospital Full of Dying, Unvaxxed Thirtysomethings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-a-miami-florida-hospital-full-of-dying-unvaccinated-30-somethings-dying-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’ve never bagged so many thirtysomething-year-olds, leaving behind young kids, pregnant wives,” one nurse said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular surfing instructor, QANON, and an unspeakable horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-09-02/did-qanon-inspire-santa-barbara-surfer-to-kill-his-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Barbara residents are struggling to make sense of a tragedy involving Matt Coleman, head of a local surf school, and the killings of his two young children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear Of Fidgeting: 1 In 3 Suffers From 'Hatred Of Movements' By Others...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fear-fidgeting-hatred-of-movements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Misokinesia is a strong negative emotional response to viewing someone else's small and repetitive movements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNNING IMAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/stunning-images-emerge-of-catastrophic-and-deadly-flooding-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight individuals are dead, including one two-year-old, as the metropolitan area of New York City was ravaged by record rainfall, tornadoes, and flash flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Digital Currencies to Be Tested in BIS Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/central-bank-digital-currencies-to-be-tested-in-bis-experiment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants include Singapore, Australia, South Africa. Experiment may lead to new global digital payments platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of people with dementia set to jump 40%...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/number-people-with-dementia-set-jump-40-78-mln-by-2030-who-2021-09-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 55 million people worldwide are living with dementia, a neurological disorder that robs them of their memory and costs the world $1.3 trillion a year, the World Health Organization (WHO) said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel taps Cheney as vice chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/02/jan6-panel-liz-cheney-508715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move is likely to ignite further divisions among House Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Thousands Still Without Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/01/1033471531/ida-new-orleans-power-entergy-louisiana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some progress is being made three days after Ida made landfall, but the region's utility company, Entergy, faces a slew of obstacles in restoring power throughout the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas abortion ban opens up 'Wild West' of enforcement, critics say...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210902105929-ykfuv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/ABORTION-ENFORCEMENT (ANALYSIS):ANALYSIS-Texas abortion ban opens up 'Wild West' of enforcement, critics say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana towns still crawling out from Ida destruction...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210902095955-d4829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ (PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):Louisiana towns still crawling out from Ida's destruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST RAIN IN HOUR</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/flash-flood-emergency-new-jersey-flooding-york-city-hurricane-ida/10993344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a historic night as the National Weather Service Office in New York City issued its first ever Flash Flood Emergency - and had to do so more than once.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
