<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How OKCUPID Profile Helps Fuel Facial Recognition Software...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/13/technology/databases-faces-facial-recognition-technology.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large databases, built with images from social networks and dating services, contain millions of pictures of people’s faces. Some are shared worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW REPUBLIC Takes Down Bizarre Hit Piece on Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/update-the-new-republic-takes-down-bizarre-hit-piece-on-pete-buttigieg-editors-note-apologizes-for-inappropriate-and-invasive-content/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after publishing a bizarre hit piece on Pete Buttigieg, 'The New Republic' deletes it and posts an Editor's Note apologizing for its 'invasive content.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia launches major new telescope into space...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3609702f60864fe39906ee401791b49f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His former students speak out...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/852609/former-students-recall-jeffrey-epsteins-persistent-attention-teenage-girls-during-teaching-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financier Jeffrey Epstein has been hit with more accusations. Epstein allegedly recently paid two possible co-conspirators in a non-prosecution agreement with federal prosecutors in Florida 12 years ago a combined $350,000. That plea deal was approved by then-U.S. Attorney Alex Acosta, who on Friday announced his resignation as the Trump administration's labor secretary. The recent accusations were made by federal prosecutors in New York on Friday, who recently arrested and charged Epstein with sex trafficking minors. "This course of action, and in particular its timing, suggests the defendant was attempting to further influence co-conspirators who might provide information against him in light of the recently re-emerging allegations," prosecutors said. Concerned that Epstein will tamper with witnesses, they also argued that he should be denied bail while he awaits trial. Further, eight former students of Epstein, who in the 1970s taught math and physics at the Dalton School in New York, said that his conduct with teenage girls "had left an impression that had lingered for decades," The New York Times reports. One student recalled him attending a party where students were drinking. Others recalled his "persistent attention" on girls in hallways and classrooms, although none of the women interviewed by the Times accused Epstein of making unwanted physical contact with them. A few students did say Epstein had an uncomfortably close relationship with one of their female peers. Epstein has never been accused of any crimes related to his time at Dalton and denied having sexual contact with any of his students during a 2009 deposition, The Daily Beast reports. When asked during the deposition if he had any sexual contact with his former students after his teaching days, Epstein replied, "not that I remember." Read more at The New York Times and The Daily Beast. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant industry on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Planned-ICE-raids-are-putting-the-restaurant-14092681.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national restaurant industry is bracing for a U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement operation that could round up hundreds of migrant families that have received deportation orders. Restaurant owners and worker advocates hope the operation, planned to start on Sunday, will not disrupt an industry already hurting for staff, or broaden into a wider investigation of employees not on the Trump administration's deportation lists.  President Donald Trump announced on Monday that the roundups would move forward despite debate within the administration over the potential humanitarian issues (separating children from their parents) and political fallout (alienating Democrats as Congress debates a $4.6 billion supplemental aid package to deal with the crisis at the border) of the operation to remove up to 2,000 families. News reports later confirmed that the Department of Homeland Security and ICE would proceed with "family op," as the agencies call the plan, in up to 10 major immigrant destinations such as Los Angeles, Houston, Miami and other cities.  Restaurant associations and immigrant advocacy groups across the country were sending out mass emails to members and workers this week, alerting them to their rights should ICE agents knock on their doors. The California Restaurant Association, the Illinois Restaurant Association, Restaurant Opportunities Centers United (which advocates for restaurant workers), South Asian Americans Leading Together (which advocates for the rights of South Asians in the United States) and the Restaurant Law Center (the legal affiliate of the National Restaurant Association) were among the groups alerting constituents about the expected ICE actions.  Their messages were basically the same: They provided information on what both employees and employers can and cannot do when targeted as part...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEOPLE ON ROOFTOPS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_d32f00cc-a56d-11e9-aa91-1bef2a867e1e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Coast Guard says it is in the process of rescuing more than a dozen people stranded on a remote Louisiana island by flooding from Tropical Storm Barry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATER FLOWS OVER LEVEES...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/40770d54459a4cf9b74db2f965c7684f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Watching Porn Produces as Much Carbon Dioxide as Whole Countries...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201907131076235927-porn-carbon-dioxide-emissions-research/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital technology has an invisible environmental impact, but researchers suggest it might actually be very, very sizeable, so you better get your hands off your laptop if you don’t want to be a climate criminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Texas, allegiance to Beto vanishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/In-Texas-allegiance-to-O-Rourke-is-vanishing-14093220.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas - Just nine months ago, attorney Katie Baron was so inspired by Beto O'Rourke's Senate campaign in Texas that she commissioned a sprawling mural on the side of a building in east Austinfeaturing the candidate in a Superman-like pose.  After O'Rourke lost race and began mulling a presidential campaign, the artist added a sweeping "2020" in blue paint - providing what seemed to be yet one more call for O'Rourke to get into the crowded race.  Now, four months into O'Rourke's campaign, Baron wishes he had stayed out.  After the first Democratic presidential debate last month, Baron posted an altered picture of the mural on a Facebook page dedicated to the artwork. She had replaced O'Rourke's face with Sen. Kamala D. Harris's and wrote: "Don't worry, still got PLENTY of love for Beto, but Kamala earned herself a little recognition too last night!" The comments filled with messages from angry O'Rourke supporters and a few excited Harris backers.  While Baron says she will be forever grateful to O'Rourke for inspiring her and thousands of others to become politically active, she doesn't think he's the strongest candidate for president, nor has he shown he can nationalize the magic of his Senate campaign.  "If the primary vote was tomorrow, he wouldn't have my vote," said Baron, 35, who likes Harris, D-Calif., for her sharp intellect and Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., for her methodical policy papers.  "Being part of the Beto-mania that was fueling the fire, I can see why he kind of thought he had no choice but to enter," she said. "Honestly, I did get a little caught up. We were still riding the wave of the midterms."  As O'Rourke slogs through a difficult primary season, he's not only struggling to gain the support of voters who don't know of him, but also to hold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-cloning ticks that suck animals' blood dry spark concern humans next...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-self-cloning-ticks-suck-animals-blood-spark-concern-humans-20190712-wcx3nxiwrfbg7bin4kb6qxk5li-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-cloning super-ticks are sparking worry in some as the insects recently were linked with killing five cows by sucking their blood dry in North Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Republicans signed 'never Trump' letters. Now have second thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/These-Republicans-signed-the-2015-never-Trump-14093205.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two and a half years into President Donald Trump's tenure, the Republican national security heavyweights blacklisted from his administration for signing a pair of "never Trump" letters in 2016 face a crossroads - remain opposed or support him in 2020.  While some have become prominent figures of the anti-Trump resistance - denouncing him in op-eds and on cable news - others have offered policy advice from outside perches, and a select few have quietly, though mostly unsuccessfully, angled for administration jobs, hopeful that a mea culpa could end their days in purgatory.  This weekend, a few dozen once-prominent GOP foreign policy figures, including some original "never Trumpers," will gather at a private Reagan Institute retreat in Beaver Creek, Colorado, to promote and preserve the 40th president's "conservative internationalist" approach to foreign affairs. Yet the White House has shown little willingness to tap into this wellspring of expertise, even as Trump cycles through national security aides and faces a dwindling pool of experienced staffers in a potential second term.  The ostracism of the group has led some to reconsider their roles in a prominent public movement to stop Trump three years ago.  "I'm not comfortable with letters anymore," said Patrick Cronin, head of the Asia-Pacific security program at the Hudson Institute, who signed the first letter, which called Trump "fundamentally dishonest" and "utterly unfitted to the office." In March 2017, Cronin was forced to withdraw from a new position overseeing a Pentagon think tank after Trump allies blasted his appointment by then-Defense Secretary Jim Mattis.  "I don't regret the letter in 2016; I thought it was the right thing to do," said Cronin, who has been publicly supportive of some elements of Trump's policies on China and North Korea. "But I'm not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL: Greenwald gets death threats after reports on justice minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/U-S-journalist-in-Brazil-gets-death-threats-14093234.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - Glenn Greenwald was jittery. He had another big story in the works, and the atmosphere around his home office was frenetic: Dogs barking, 27 security cameras filming, big men with guns standing guard.  For weeks, from a house transformed into a bunker, Greenwald had published allegations casting doubt on the impartiality of the corruption investigation that led to the imprisonment of former Brazilian president Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva and contributed to the rise of President Jair Bolsonaro.  In two days, he would publish another story alleging that the judge who'd overseen Lula's case, Sérgio Moro, a national hero in Brazil for his role taking on corruption, had colluded with prosecutors to convict him.  "This material is going to come out," he said. "Even if they put me in prison."  The prospect felt real enough. Greenwald, the polarizing American journalist who came to prominence reporting on the U.S. government surveillance programs exposed by Edward Snowden, had promised months of stories - a steady drip of leaks that could imperil the Bolsonaro agenda. Some members of congress had called for his deportation. Others accused him of committing a crime. Death threats were rolling in.  Most recently, the federal police, commanded by Moro, now Bolsonaro's justice minister, reportedly began investigating Greenwald's finances in a probe that press advocates here see as an attempt to silence him.  The public threats against Greenwald represent an early test for Brazil under Bolsonaro, the right-wing former military officer who won the presidency last year with appeals to nationalism, homophobia and nostalgia for the country's two-decade military dictatorship.  Will this government tolerate damaging reporting by a gay foreign journalist? Or will it move to silence him, confirming fears of Bolsonaro's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political drama not selling books like it used to...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/12/political-drama-not-selling-books-like-it-used-to/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The book world has turned upside down when it comes to predicting a best-seller. A year ago, Michael Wolff’s “Fire and Fury” was in the No. 1 spot for the first half, and not far behind was former …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
In alcohol-soaked nation, more seek booze-free social spaces...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/sobering-up-in-an-alcohol-soaked-nation-more-seek-booze-free-social-spaces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A national trend of boozeless bars is cropping up nationwide to create social spaces without the hangovers, DUIs and alcoholism culture. It’s part of a new push for sober options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Remove U.S. Flag, Replace It With Mexican Flag Outside ICE Facility...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/07/12/protests-ice-aurora-immigration-raids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of protesters gathered in Aurora on Friday evening to march to the ICE detention facility where illegal and undocumented immigrants are being housed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protest Against Mainland Chinese Traders Turns Violent...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/hong-kong-protesters-target-mainland-chinese-traders-64311402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several thousand people have marched in Hong Kong against traders from mainland China in what is fast becoming a summer of unrest in the semi-autonomous Chinese territory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't stop us all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/9499236/almost-500000-people-plot-to-storm-mysterious-area-51-us-military-base-to-see-aliens-hidden-there-saying-they-cant-stop-us-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEARLY half a million people are planning to storm the Area 51 mystery base to see the US government are hiding aliens. The extra-terrestrial enthusiasts will gather forces in Amargosa Valley, Neva…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK police warning to media over diplomat's leaked memos stirs anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-britain-police/uk-police-warning-to-media-over-diplomats-leaked-memos-stirs-anger-idUSKCN1U80AO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior British politicians, including both contenders to be the next prime minis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half million people signed up to storm Area 51. What happens if show up? </title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/half-a-million-people-signed-up-to-storm-area-51-what-if-they-show-up-2068928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should everything go according to plan, more than half a million strangers will gather in a remote Nevada town in mid-September, united by a common goal: raid Area 51 in the wee hours of the morning - using a strength-in-numbers approach to reveal any extraterrestrial treasures stashed within the notoriously clandestine government base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGLES honor Skaggs with emotional no-hit masterpiece...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a6c8c71d4e8a4ab2b7595c70ec60b8e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial politics roil Dem Party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/452856-racial-politics-roil-democratic-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allegations of racial insensitivity are flying between the 2020 Democratic contenders, as well as between House Democrats, raising concerns within the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Paris, cars forced to make way for the two-wheel revolution...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/paris-cars-forced-way-two-wheel-revolution-034009730.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the wind rushing through their hair, they zip past on bikes, electric scooters and mono-wheels, effortlessly passing lines of hot-and-bothered drivers stuck in the endless Paris traffic. In the French capital, the new mobility revolution has caught on fast, with locals and tourists embracing the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternally stinky city? Rome garbage crisis sparks health fears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eternally-stinky-city-rome-garbage-crisis-sparks-health-025645469.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landfills in flames and rats feasting on waste in the streets have sparked health fears in Rome, as doctors warn families to steer clear of disease-ridden curbside garbage and locals launch a disgusting dumpster contest online. Crowds of summer tourists are forced to navigate overflowing bins in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico ranch linked to investigation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/billionaires-mexico-ranch-linked-investigation-64309329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire businessman Jeffrey Epstein's secluded New Mexico ranch has become tied to an investigation opened by the state attorney general's office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAIN IMPLANT RESTORES VISION TO BLIND...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jul/13/brain-implant-restores-partial-vision-to-blind-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medical experts hail ‘paradigm shift’ of implant that transmits video images directly to the visual cortex, bypassing the eye and optic nerve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson?</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/maui-brush-fire-forces-road-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (KHON2) — An arson investigation has been opened for the second Maui fire that broke out on Friday, July 12, according to the Maui Police Department. Problems for the Maui Fire Depar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger invites Trump to 'compare tax returns'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/452852-schwarzenegger-invites-trump-to-compare-tax-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former California Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger (R) hit back at President Trump Thursday after the president hammered the actor over his hosting of the NBC show “The Celebrity Apprentice.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/radar/us/la/new-orleans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Asylum Seekers Sent to Guatemala?</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/trump-poised-to-sign-a-radical-agreement-to-send-future-asylum-seekers-to-guatemala</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest, and most unsettling, question raised by the agreement is how Guatemala could possibly cope with such enormous demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS GIVE FACEBOOK $5 BLLION SLAP AFTER PRIVACY ABUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/ftc-votes-to-approve-dollar5-billion-settlement-with-facebook-in-privacy-probe/ar-AAEfbIQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUT COMPANY HAS MARKET VALUE OF $585 BILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/?symbol=FB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Facebook (FB:NASDAQ) real-time stock quotes, news and financial information from CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BIGGEST TECH FINE EVER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/12/ftc-fines-facebook-5-billion-for-privacy-lapses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Trade Commission announced a settlement with Facebook over the company's 2018 Cambridge Analytica scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW ORLEANS READY...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/storm-clouds-gather-over-new-orleans-as-city-braces-for-hit-by-barry/70008793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARES RISE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/12/facebook-shares-rise-on-report-of-5b-settlement-with-ftc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Trade Commission has reportedly slapped Facebook with a record-setting $5 billion fine over its privacy lapses, including a massive data leak to political research firm Cambridge Analyt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN'S TEMPLE OF SEX</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/whats-the-deal-with-the-bizarre-temple-like-structure-on-jeffrey-epsteins-private-island/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOODGATES AND LEVEES...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190712230104-yyxmx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-BARRY/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 6-'Life-threatening' Tropical Storm Barry grinds toward Louisiana</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
