<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Blitzer Called Out for 'Misleading' Photo of Gas Prices at DC EXXON...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/wolf-blitzer-called-out-for-misleading-photo-of-gas-prices-at-dc-exxon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolf Blitzer faced backlash from liberals on Twitter when he posted a photo depicting high gas prices at a DC Exxon station that many users found misleading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Dem seeks to become first openly trans statewide elected official...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/10/nevada-democrat-transgender-520572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lieutenant governor’s office is currently vacant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors seek longest prison sentences yet for insurrectionists...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211110134522-svf41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CAPITOL/ARRESTS (PIX):U.S. prosecutors seek longest prison sentences yet for Capitol rioters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Selloff Jeopardizes $1 Trillion-Club Status...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-shares-fall-fourth-day-122541946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc. slumped in premarket trading Wednesday, threatening to push the company’s valuation below the $1 trillion mark amid a selloff that has already erased more than $200 billion from its market capitalization.Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesDo Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?COP26 Protests: Inflatable Cows, Megaphones and a RainbowShares of the electric-vehicle firm have plunged nearly 17% since Thursday’s close, includi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer star 'hired masked men to attack team-mate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/premier-league/4037317/psg-diallo-police-attack-hamraoui/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS SAINT-GERMAIN have confirmed star Aminata Diallo is in police custody as they condemned a shocking attack on her team-mate Kheira Hamraoui with an iron bar by masked men. L’Equippe brok…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP billionaire Langone will hold fundraiser for Manchin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/republican-billionaire-ken-langone-says-he-will-hold-fundraiser-for-joe-manchin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican billionaire Ken Langone says he will hold a fundraiser for Joe Manchin after the conservative Democrat opposed elements of Joe Biden's agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices rising faster than incomes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/home-prices-are-now-rising-much-faster-than-incomes-studies-show.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the pandemic, home prices shot up while household income fell, creating an affordability crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis Deepens for Boris as Sleaze Row Engulfs Senior Tory...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/crisis-deepens-for-johnson-as-senior-u-k-tory-accused-of-sleaze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crisis Deepens for Johnson as Senior U.K. Tory Accused of Sleaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The last drugstore: Rural America losing pharmacies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-last-drugstore-rural-america-is-losing-its-pharmacies/ar-AAQx9c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 independent pharmacies in rural America have closed since 2003, leaving 41 million people stuck without easy access to drug stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure hunter got lost in Yellowstone. He must repay rescue costs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-treasure-hunter-got-lost-in-yellowstone-looking-for-a-millionaire-e2-80-99s-hidden-trove-he-must-repay-the-rescue-costs/ar-AAQxneb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Lantis told the judge who sentenced him that he doesn't believe that he "at any point ... made a bad decision."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes Rising Among Young...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/11/10/diabetes-affecting-younger-populations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diabetes is on the rise across the United States and it's affecting a population that once didn't have to worry about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 28% approval, say goodbye to Kamala being Plan B to aging Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/580857-at-28-percent-approval-say-goodbye-to-kamala-harris-being-plan-b-to-an</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 28 percent approval, it's hard to see how the VP ever takes the next step to the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces high stakes on Fed pick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/580827-biden-faces-high-stakes-with-progressives-on-fed-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is facing a high-stakes decision on the Federal Reserve’s leadership that could also shape his relationship with progressives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican centrists under increased attacks from own party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/580856-gop-centrists-come-under-increased-attacks-from-own-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 13 House Republicans who voted for the bipartisan infrastructure bill are being taunted as traitors and threatened with primary challenges from far-right lawmakers for breaking party lines to help give President Biden a long-sought legislative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man, 60, uses pocket knife to fight off crocodile...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/australian-man-60-uses-pocket-knife-to-fight-off-crocodile-2605118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 60-year-old Australian man escaped the jaws of a large crocodile by stabbing it repeatedly in the head with his pocket knife as it dragged him into a river,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches combat drills, dubs American lawmakers' Taiwan trip 'sneaky'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-launches-combat-drills-dubs-us-lawmakers-e2-80-99-taiwan-trip-e2-80-98sneaky-e2-80-99/ar-AAQwAUv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing’s bombastic response to a routine visit comes during escalating tensions in the Taiwan Strait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Taiwan, boat-burning festival aims to ward off sickness. Can it end pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Taiwan-a-boat-burning-festival-aims-to-ward-16608596.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONGGANG, Taiwan - The ancient ritual began just before dawn. On a beach in southern...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer prices likely surged at fastest pace in 30 years... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/consumer-prices-likely-surged-last-month-at-their-fastest-pace-in-about-30-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index is expected to have risen nearly 6% in October, the most in three decades. Inflation could remain elevated into early next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: FOX viewers more likely to believe untruths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-media-misinformation-health-b59e98ca50f37ddeea217903915a53fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — People who trust Fox News Channel and other media outlets that appeal to conservatives are more likely to believe falsehoods about COVID-19 and vaccines than those who primarily go elsewhere for news, a study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare STARBUCKS union vote set to begin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-business-national-labor-relations-board-health-6f9a1f9a53fc874ebdb6438df1f4223f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — Never in its 50-year history has Starbucks relied on union workers to serve up frothy lattes as its U.S. cafes. But some baristas aim to change that. Workers at three separate Starbucks stores in and around Buffalo, New York, are expected to begin voting by mail this week on whether they want to be represented by Workers United, an affiliate of the Service Employees International Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry says he warned TWITTER CEO coup was about to happen day before Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/prince-harry-says-he-warned-twitters-jack-dorsey-about-capitol-riot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry said he warned Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey that his platform was allowing a coup to be staged ahead of Capitol riot on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 political tribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10183647/Americas-NINE-political-tribes-according-Pew-Research.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report released by the Pew Research Center has segmented U.S. voters into nine political tribes - four that lean left, four that lean right, and the 'stressed sideliners.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHEN WILL KIDS UNMASK?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/we-need-off-ramps-when-will-kids-take-off-their-masks-in-schools-192359819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the approval of the Pfizer coronavirus vaccine for children ages 5 to 11, many parents who have dutifully been masking their children since the beginning of the pandemic are asking a question that closely tracks with the vaccine rollout: When can kids shed their masks?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC crumbling...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/11/09/brian-williams-leaving-msnbc-and-nbc-next-month-follows-rachel-maddow-plan-to-leave-daily-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: NFL Star Maced By Female Military Sergeant After She Illegally Entered His Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox9.com/sports/report-dalvin-cook-files-litigation-as-victim-in-domestic-abuse-extortion-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Vikings star running back Dalvin Cook is apparently the victim in a case involving domestic abuse and extortion, according to his agent Zac Hiller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casinos have best quarter ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/us-casinos-best-quarter-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's commercial casinos are marking the industry's best quarter ever and pushing U.S. casino revenue past what it was for all of 2020. Figures released Tuesday by the American Gaming Association show U.S. casinos are poised to have their best year ever in 2021 as more consumers feel comfortable visiting casinos amid the ongoing COVID19 pandemic, and as online and sports betting revenues continue to grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases Surging In Minnesota...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/09/covid-19-in-mn-latest-positivity-rate-nears-high-risk-threshold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after warning that COVID-19 case numbers are among the highest seen this year, Minnesota health officials reported 7,173 additional cases and 20 more deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN DISMISSES RUNAWAY INFLATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/yellen-says-fed-wouldn-t-allow-repeat-of-1970s-level-inflation/ar-AAQw1LW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen repeated her view that elevated U.S. inflation won’t persist beyond next year and said the Federal Reserve will act if needed to prevent a rerun of 1970s-style price rises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSUITS MULTIPLYING...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/live-nation-now-facing-at-least-35-lawsuits-over-concert-tragedy/ar-AAQw4dR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live Nation Entertainment Inc.’s legal exposure from the deadly crush of concertgoers at the Astroworld Festival in Houston last week is surging, with at least 35 lawsuits pending as of Tuesday against the promoter and U.S. rapper Travis Scott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA:  NO HUMAN ON MOON FOR YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nasa-says-wont-send-manned-204052539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) -NASA is extending its target date for sending astronauts back to the moon to 2025 at the earliest, the U.S. space agency's chief said on Tuesday, stretching out by at least a year the timeline pronounced under former President Donald Trump. Trump's administration had set the aggressive goal of returning humans to the lunar surface by 2024, an initiative named Artemis intended as a stepping stone toward the even-more-ambitious objective of sending astronauts to Mars. NASA Administrator Bill Nelson cited delays from legal wrangling https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-judge-rejects-blue-origin-challenge-nasas-pick-spacex-moon-lander-2021-11-04 over the SpaceX contract to build the Artemis lunar landing vehicle as a major reason for extending the target date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second U.S. Aircraft Carrier Missile Target Spotted in Chinese Desert...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/11/09/second-u-s-aircraft-carrier-missile-target-spotted-in-chinese-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second suspected missile target in the shape of a U.S. aircraft carrier has been spotted in a rural Chinese desert, according to satellite photos obtained by USNI News. The site consists of a single aircraft carrier target, miles from the nearest town in the Xinjiang region, according to photos provided to USNI News by …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey Says Texas Needs 'Aggressively Centric' Government...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/matthew-mcconaughey-says-texas-needs-225027252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Matthew McConaughey, the actor flirting with a run for Texas governor, said the state and rest of the country need “aggressively centric” governments to overcome partisan divides.Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesWhere Did All the Public Bathrooms Go?Do Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?COP26 Protests: Inflatable Cows, Megaphones and a RainbowThe Rising Pacific Forces a Native Village to Move. Who Will Pay?The 52-year-old native T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Activates Crisis Plan as Medical Staffing Dwindles...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/health/coronavirus/colorado-activates-crisis-standards-of-care-healthcare-staffing/73-7ef4857a-bd9e-46a8-9874-5c1376cb53f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado has activated the portion of its crisis standards of care plan that deals with staffing health care systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  BRIAN WILLIAMS LEAVING NBC...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/brian-williams-leaving-msnbc-nbc-news-1235108664/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Williams, the veteran anchor who became an integral part of MSNBC after a critical on-air gaffe in 2015 while behind the anchor desk at “NBC Nightly News” led to his removal from …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says conducted readiness patrol as U.S. lawmakers visit Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211109150219-6hbdx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/TAIWAN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China says conducted readiness patrol as U.S. lawmakers visit Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom appears, calls questions over absence 'interesting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/Gavin-Newsom-public-appearance-climate-cancel-16606470.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom characterized questions over why he had no public appearances last week as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Single men don't care about sex anymore...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/09/majority-of-single-men-care-less-about-sex-now-than-pre-covid-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve gone from a slutty summer to a flaccid fall. According to a study by Match, a stunning majority of single dudes said sex is now less important to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Fight Rodgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/scientists-fight-a-new-source-of-vaccine-misinformation-aaron-rodgers/ar-AAQt5nn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction: November 8, 2021 An earlier version of this article misstated the length of Aaron Rodgers's career. He is playing in his 17th season, not his 16th. This spring, he was auditioning to be the host of “Jeopardy!” Nearly every day, he pops up on television ads for national brands like State Farm insurance. And on Sundays this fall, he has led the Green Bay Packers to a division-best 7-2 record. Quarterback Aaron Rodgers is not just the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo refutes theories giraffes died from jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/conspiracy-theory-giraffe-deaths-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorists are falsely claiming that three giraffes at the Dallas zoo died after receiving the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY:  'Far be it from me to tell anyone what to put in their body'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/09/tom-brady-uses-aaron-rodgers-covid-vaccine-drama-to-sell-tb12-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never miss an opportunity to sell. Even if that opportunity is being asked about Aaron Rodgers’ decision not to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermont now 1st state to require condoms in all middle schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vermont-is-now-1st-state-to-require-access-to-condoms-in-all-middle-and-high-schools/ar-AAQvTCP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law was created in an effort to prevent sexually transmitted diseases and unintended pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general warns against memes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/surgeon-general-warns-against-memes-misleading-graphs-cherry-picked-stats-health-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. surgeon general released a brochure this week warning against misleading memes and graphs online in an effort to stamp out “health misinformation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Informers key in enforcing Biden mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/9/informers-key-in-enforcing-biden-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To enforce President Joe Biden’s forthcoming COVID-19 mandate, the U.S. Labor Department is going to need a lot of help. Its Occupational Safety and Health Administration doesn’t have nearly enough workplace safety inspectors to do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City OKs GOOGLE data centers amid secrecy, water worries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-the-dalles-oregon-droughts-62b3774442293497ceb2306a606471af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — The council of a small Oregon city has approved a deal with Google that will enable the technology giant to build two more water-guzzling data centers there, though some residents worry about drought and secrecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland says Putin masterminding border crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59226226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of migrants are at the Belarus-Poland border, camping in cold and dangerous conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media users could disable algorithms in new proposal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211109202619-ww2p2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TECH/LEGISLATION:Social media users could disable algorithms in new U.S. proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public allowed at Tomb of Unknown for first time in 100 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/politics/tomb-of-the-unknown-soldier-centennial-commemoration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in nearly a century, members of the public will be able to walk on the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier plaza and lay flowers before the sacred memorial site in Arlington National Cemetery on Tuesday and Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metallurgist admits faking steel test results for US Navy subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59186655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A metallurgist has pleaded guilty to fraud after faking the results of strength tests on steel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 shots and 1 booster later, this man has little protection against Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/health/immunocompromised-covid-19-booster-wellness-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are recommending third and even fourth shots to boost Covid resistance for people with certain conditions, but that hasn't eased the fears for some immunocompromised people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz Prepares To Jump Into Pennsylvania Senate Race...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/dr-oz-prepares-to-jump-into-pennsylvania-senate-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Mehmet Oz is preparing to jump into Pennsylvania Senate race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop Who Left Clergy for Erotica Writer Accused of Being 'Possessed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vgw7/bishop-who-left-clergy-for-erotica-writer-accused-of-being-possessed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Bishop Xavier Novell reportedly began a new job at Semen Cardona, a company which produces and exports high-quality pig semen to over 20 countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans have never been in so much debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/economy/fed-household-debt-inflation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American households are carrying record amounts of debt as home and auto prices surge, Covid infections continue to fall and people get out their credit cards again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faced with soaring Ds and Fs, schools ditch old way of grading...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/faced-soaring-ds-fs-schools-130030318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic-forced school closures revealed how grade-point systems hurt disadvantaged children, prompting educators to look for ways to bring equity to grading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Evidence' from witness who 'saw Prince Andrew groping Virginia Roberts' to air in new doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4031231/prince-andrew-virginia-roberts-witness-evidence-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE witness who says he saw Prince Andrew grope Virginia Roberts is set to make bombshell claims in a new documentary. Jeffrey Epstein’s former telecoms specialist Steve Scully is set to give his e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's taxpayer-funded political machine...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trumps-taxpayer-funded-hatch-act-13-f2cc1a45-163b-4c3d-b967-bff294478534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hatch Act bars the use of taxpayer resources for partisan politicking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of red UK phone boxes to be protected from closure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-technology-business-europe-c729398ca506057a1739a9f3bdc6bac9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of Britain’s iconic red phone boxes will be protected from removal under new rules, the U.K.'s telecommunications regulator said Tuesday. The public payphone boxes may look like obsolete relics in an age of ubiquitous smartphones, but regulator Ofcom said they can still be a “lifeline” for people in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: People under 30 should not get MODERNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/covid-19-people-under-30-should-not-get-moderna-vaccine-france-684457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna Inc applied for European authorization of its COVID-19 vaccine in children aged 6-11 years, weeks after it delayed a similar filing with US regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLOOD SACRIFICE'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4030813/astroworld-travis-scott-satanic-ritual-conspiracy-theories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRACKPOT conspiracy theorists have sensationally claimed that the tragic deaths of eight people at Travis Scott’s “hellish” Astroworld concert last week came as part of a “s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER CEO: People who spread vax misinfo are 'criminals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/covid-vaccines-pfizer-ceo-says-people-who-spread-misinformation-on-shots-are-criminals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They're criminals because they have literally cost millions of lives," Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuser details 'sex assault' allegations against CNN's Don Lemon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/08/accuser-details-sex-assault-allegations-against-cnns-don-lemon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dustin Hice, who accused CNN’s Dom Lemon of assaulting him in a Hamptons bar three years ago, claimed that the alleged behavior could be part of a “pattern.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switched Before Birth: Couple Suing Clinic After IVF Mixup Leads to Wrong Baby...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/08/it-was-truly-my-hell-couple-files-lawsuit-after-ivf-mishap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles couple is suing the California Center for Reproductive Health for in vitro fertilization after they learned the baby they had birthed and raised was not theirs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going To Bed At 10 P.M. May Save Life?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/bedtime-heart-health-10-pm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team finds that even bedtimes earlier than 10 p.m. increased the risk of cardiovascular disease in adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate, angry, destructive: How Americans morphed into mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desperate-angry-destructive-how-americans-morphed-into-a-mob/ar-AAQuRIB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we know about the people who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook Pumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/apple-ceo-tim-cook-says-he-owns-cryptocurrency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook dismissed suggestions that Apple might take cryptocurrency in exchange for products or buy it with corporate funds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Squid coin to memes, 'Wild West' of crypto...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/squid-coin-memes-wild-west-154732160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a dodgy digital currency inspired by Netflix hit "Squid Game" to highly-volatile dog-themed coins, the cryptocurrency sector has become riskier than ever as it soars in value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID hospitalizations rising in California, a potentially ominous sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/covid-19-hospitalizations-rising-in-parts-of-california-a-potentially-ominous-sign/ar-AAQuNrG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 hospitalizations have risen significantly in the Inland Empire and Central Valley, bringing new concerns about whether the shift represents a precursor to a wider spike in COVID-19 in California as the winter holidays approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin, Ether Hit Records Amid Broad Rally in Cryptocurrencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-ether-hit-records-amid-broad-rally-in-cryptocurrencies/ar-AAQtaeT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin and Ether hit all-time highs amid a broad rally in financial assets that some analysts attributed partly to the search for a hedge against inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAKE BREAKS SILENCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/drake-astroworld-statement-1235044619/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper featured during Travis Scott's set that later led to a crush and the death of eight people and injuries to many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now scale one of NYC's tallest skyscrapers: No walls, no railings..</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/news/local-news/manhattan/you-can-now-scale-one-of-nycs-tallest-skyscrapers-no-walls-no-glass-windows-no-railings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It gives thrill-seekers a unique perspective on New York that no observation deck could hope to match:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Producer prices rise 8.6%, matching record high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-producer-prices-prices-inflation-economy-56eee45eace6035280f7d3b0fe932bdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Inflation at the wholesale level rose 8.6% last month from a year earlier, matching September's record annual gain and offering more evidence that inflationary pressures are not yet easing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
