<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves forward on raising debt ceiling by $2.5 TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/14/democrats-raise-debt-ceiling-524204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amount is expected to carry spending until after the 2022 midterms, preventing another standoff over the debt limit until after elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Work: 60-Year Career...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/careersandeducation/the-future-of-work-is-a-60-year-career/ar-AAROm5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 100-year-old newspaper became go-to way to influence Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/14/joe-biden-news-journal-ad-targeting-524196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Biden era, the pages of The News Journal have become a way to reach a new audience of one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starup Pitched Tasing Migrants from Drones...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/12/13/brinc-startup-taser-drones-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well-funded Brinc positions its use of robots as nonviolent, but an early promo video undercuts this message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston STARBUCKS workers seek to unionize after Buffalo vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-boston-buffalo-labor-unions-4813d76fc45dbcf4ddc8fa5b11505d8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Starbucks workers at two locations in Boston are looking to unionize, days after a successful union vote at a Starbucks in Buffalo, New York, a first for the 50-year-old coffee retailer in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tells Israel new tanker jets, key to Iran strike, not coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-tells-israel-tanker-jets-key-to-iran-strike-wont-arrive-anytime-soon-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to NYT, during his visit to DC Defense Minister Gantz asked to accelerate delivery of KC-46 refueling planes but was told first aircraft unlikely to arrive before 2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea sees deadliest day after attempt to return to normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/south-korea-sees-deadliest-day-of-pandemic-after-attempt-to-return-to-normalcy/ar-AAROebT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo ordered to return $5.1M pandemic book profits to state...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/14/andrew-cuomo-ordered-to-return-pandemic-book-profits-to-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extraordinary resolution was approved by the Joint Commission on Public Ethics Tuesday in a 12 to 1 vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Jan. 6 itself, Trump allies understood Trump was catalyst...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/on-jan-6-itself-trump-s-allies-understood-that-he-was-the-catalyst/ar-AARMF7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Hosts Privately Begged Him to Act. Here's What They Said On Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-hosts-privately-begged-trump-act-during-capitol-riot-heres-what-they-said-on-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News hosts privately begged then-President Donald Trump to act during the Jan. 6 Capitol riot. However, on air, the Fox News hosts downplayed the violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs trained to sniff out covid from old socks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/canines-in-california-trained-to-sniff-out-covid-from-old-socks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs in Concord, Calif. are being trained to sniff COVID from old socks. The goal is to eventually use these COVID-sniffing canines in schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Political Polarization In USA Reaching 'Irreversible Tipping Point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/political-polarization-tipping-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most people eventually forgive and forget political disagreements, is there a point of no return where Americans can no longer co-exist with each other?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Rocket scientists and brain surgeons aren't necessarily smarter than rest of us...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/business/money-report/rocket-scientists-and-brain-surgeons-are-not-necessarily-smarter-than-the-rest-of-us-study-finds/3449502/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket scientists and brain surgeons aren't necessarily any smarter than the general population, a study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SPIDER MAN' TO SAVE THEATERS?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/12/14/review-spider-man-no-way-home-is-the-blockbuster-yet-sad-ending-to-tom-hollands-first-trilogy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid wreaking havoc on sports world...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/omicron-covid-sports-disruption-c23339ff-0265-46b0-b39f-7364a67ea75c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID is affecting the sports in ways not seen since before the vaccine became widely available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38-Year-Old Rodgers vs. 44-Year-Old Brady for NFL MVP...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/chalk/story/_/id/32865605/nfl-mvp-watch-tom-brady-vs-aaron-rodgers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is the MVP favorite, but are there better values out there? Doug Kezirian breaks down the main candidates and looks at other awards races to watch heading into Week 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IS SHE WINNING?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/is-ghislaine-maxwell-winning/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They gather outside the Thurgood Marshall courthouse in lower Manhattan. QAnonners, conspiracy podcasters, sceptics; private citizens who use their private time to make public placards about alleged sex traffickers. To them Ghislaine Maxwell is not a woman. She is an avatar of an elite that crushes the poor and the desperate with casual, contemptuous cruelty. [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON realized its own building was hit by twister from media...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/12/13/amazon-illinois-tornado-safety-protocols/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon employees have been discouraged from taking time off for natural disasters because it would slow down production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Jan. 6 itself, Trump allies understood he was catalyst...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2021/12/13/jan-6-itself-trumps-allies-understood-that-he-was-catalyst/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe Trump couldn't control the rioters, despite what his allies thought. But for hours he didn't really try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star suffered 'severe CTE similar to Aaron Hernandez' before killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4269729/phillip-adams-nfl-stage-2-cte/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILLIP Adams suffered from CTE before allegedly going on a gun rampage that killed seven, a coroner has said. Defensive back Adams, who previously played for the 49ers, shot himself after gunning …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Person Just As Smart As Brain Surgeons, Rocket Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/its-not-rocket-science-intelligent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phrase “It’s a walk in the park” is probably a more appropriate expression when someone wants to say a task will require little intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys Regroup Locally to Add to Ranks Before Midterms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/14/proud-boys-regroup-locally-to-add-to-ranks-before-2022-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They showed up last month outside the school board building in Beloit, Wis., to protest school masking requirements. They turned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Death Toll Nears 800,000...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-nfl-sports-health-football-f967f156fb205277266d2bb2483b858c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — Carolyn Burnett is bracing for her first Christmas without her son Chris, a beloved high school football coach whose outdoor memorial service drew a crowd of hundreds. The unvaccinated 34-year-old father of four died in September as a result of COVID-19 after nearly two weeks on a ventilator, and his loss has left a gaping hole for his mother, widow and family as the holidays approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-SPACEX Engineer Claims He's 'Sadistic,' Misogyny 'Rampant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxdn3x/ex-spacex-engineer-claims-elon-musk-is-sadistic-misogyny-is-rampant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After she reported sexual harassment, Ashley Kosak was told such claims were “too private to openly discuss with the perpetrators,” she says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Mandates Booster for Coaches, Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/nfl-mandates-booster-shot-for-coaches-and-staff-after-record-number-of-players-test-positive-for-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL distributed a memo to all teams Monday night, announcing Tier 1 and 2 personnel are now mandated to receive a Covid booster shot by Dec. 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five new symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/five-new-omicron-symptoms-including-25689711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NHS website is asking anyone with the traditional symptoms of coronavirus to get a free PCR test but Omicron symptoms test differently to other strands of Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXTS RAISE QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/politics/january-6-committee-mark-meadows/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump Jr. was frantic. Fox News personalities who now dismiss the violence at the US Capitol were begging the White House to do something. On January 6, then-President Donald Trump wasn't listening to his kids or his media enablers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 5 Rate Current Mental Health 'Fair-To-Poor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-not-optimistic-post-pandemic-life-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most adults say that the "new normal" of fearing viruses and overwhelming stress is impacting their well-being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel industry getting hit again. Can it take it?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/investing/premarket-stocks-trading/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Omicron variant of the coronavirus is spreading fast. But even as scientists urge patience while they assess the severity of the strain and its impact on the efficacy of vaccines, the travel industry is feeling the pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's biggest economy on brink of recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/economy/germany-recession-omicron/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany is teetering on the brink of recession this winter as supply bottlenecks and a wave of new coronavirus cases hobble the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  Vaccines Induce LOWER Antibody Levels Against Omicron?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-dose-vaccines-dont-induce-143327719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oxford University study published on Monday found that two-dose COVID-19 vaccines generate a lower antibody response against the omicron strain, suggesting that the variant could lead to more infections among the fully vaccinated and previously infected.The research, which has not yet been peer-reviewed, documented a "substantial fall" in the number of neutralizing antibodies among participants who received two doses of the AstraZeneca or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS WARNS RESTAURANTS COULD SHUT IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4269314/pubs-restaurants-shops-close-january-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUBS, shops and restaurants could be forced to shut in January because so many workers will be off sick with Omicron. In a “bleak” update to Cabinet the PM and chief medical officer Chr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGECOIN spikes over 20% after Musk says TESLA will accept it as payment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/14/dogecoin-price-surges-after-elon-musk-tweet-about-tesla-merch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogecoin skyrocketed more than 20% Tuesday morning after Elon Musk said Tesla would accept it as payment for some merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What pandemic? Miami airport sets travel record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-business-travel-76aa9de984f961234469390f54f2af8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Miami International Airport is finally seeing more passengers than it served before the pandemic, and set new records for Thanksgiving holiday travel despite growing concerns about the spread of the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Gas truck explodes in Haiti; Dozens killed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-haiti-ea8356ed1e9cd97041c0dafec09cb6f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — A truck carrying gasoline exploded in northern Haiti, killing more than 50 people and injuring dozens of others in the latest disaster to hit a country whose troubles deepened greatly this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesale prices measure rises 9.6%; Fastest pace on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/14/wholesale-prices-measure-rises-9point6percent-in-november-from-a-year-ago-the-fastest-pace-on-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Labor Department's producer price index was expected to rise 9.2% in November from a year ago, according to FactSet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's evangelical allies shocked by Trump's outburst on Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-s-staunch-evangelical-allies-shocked-by-trump-s-outburst-on-netanyahu/ar-AARNy0A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR MISSING RECORDS</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mark-meadows-personal-cellphone-is-becoming-a-personal-hell </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER Pill Protects Against Severe Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/effectiveness-pfizers-covid-pill-confirmed-analysis-company-says-rcna8662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional data on Pfizer's Covid oral antiviral pill suggests the pill is highly effective. The FDA has not yet scheduled a meeting of its advisory committee to reivew the pill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waitress served party that tipped $4,400. It led to her getting fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-arkansas-waitress-served-a-party-that-tipped-244400-it-led-to-her-getting-fired/ar-AARNtBK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was extorted for having affair. So he hired crew that killed blackmailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-married-man-was-extorted-for-having-an-affair-so-he-hired-a-crew-that-killed-his-blackmailer-feds-say/ar-AARNwtc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEADOWS MAGA MESS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/585667-meadows-moves-to-center-of-jan-6-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As House investigators charge ahead with their probe into the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol, their focus has shifted to a contentious former colleague they increasingly see as a crucial witness: Mark Meadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 of Every 100 Older Americans Has Perished...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/13/as-u-s-nears-800000-virus-deaths-1-of-every-100-older-americans-has-perished/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus pandemic approaches the end of a second year, the United States stands on the cusp of surpassing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across World, Covid Anxiety and Depression Take Hold...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/13/across-the-world-covid-anxiety-and-depression-take-hold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — A recent cartoon in the French daily Le Monde featured a bedraggled man arriving at a doctor’s office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: At least 88 dead in tornado aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tornadoes-business-kentucky-mayfield-abc2296191a26cb3487815093b689bc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAYFIELD, Ky. (AP) — Workers, volunteers and members of the National Guard fanned out in areas of Kentucky slammed by a series of tornadoes to begin the long process of recovery, including replacing thousands of damaged utility poles, delivering bottles of drinking water and continuing to search for the dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS secretly tested mobile voting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/usps-built-and-secretly-tested-a-mobile-voting-system-before-2020/ar-AARM2P1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew calls Child Victim Act unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/prince-andrew-calls-new-york-child-victim-act-unconstitutional-1.1695426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew said a New York law that gave victims of child sex abuse more time to sue is unconstitutional and can’t be used to allow the claims by an alleged former recruit of Jeffrey Epstein to take the British Royal to trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data hint Omicron cases poised to explode in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/omicron-coronavirus-cases-europe-us-c85be94d-8edf-4d61-9f05-de924bff6760.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Everything points to a large wave. A large wave is coming."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals worry rising infections will push them past breaking point...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/585664-hospitals-worry-rising-case-counts-will-push-them-past-breaking-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals increasingly are worried that a growing number of COVID-19 cases in several states will push them beyond their breaking point, even before the omicron strain really hits U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran vaunted tolerance dims amid brazen crimes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-sports-business-health-lifestyle-538efc664e9da0d2f0831f3f3ed9a4d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Caitlin Foster fell in love with San Francisco's people and beauty and moved to the city a dozen years ago. But after repeatedly clearing away used needles, other drug paraphernalia and human feces outside the bar she manages, and too many encounters with armed people in crisis, her affection for the city has soured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Hosts Frantically Begged Trump to Stop  MAGA riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/top-fox-news-hosts-don-jr-frantically-texted-meadows-during-jan-6-riot-begging-trump-to-act-hes-destroying-his-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He is destroying his legacy,” texted Laura Ingraham. “He's got to condemn this sh*t ASAP,” texted Trump Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON JR. TEXTS: 'Hes got to condemn this shit ASAP'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/meadows-contempt-charges-don-junior-0847b7ca-467f-4a61-ade2-98357248af39.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House select committee investigating the Jan. 6 insurrection unanimously approved a resolution for Meadows to be held in contempt of Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel votes to hold Meadows in contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/jan-6-committee-recommends-mark-meadows-face-contempt-charge-n1285564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is expected to vote as soon as Tuesday on whether to ask the Justice Department to prosecute Meadows, who served as a House lawmaker before joining the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dystopian'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/video-south-dakota-teachers-scrambling-092649863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teachers were seen stuffing cash in their clothes and helmets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Could Possibly Go Wrong? Biggest Economic Risks '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/what-could-possibly-go-wrong-these-are-the-biggest-economic-risks-for-2022-11639376012236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists have struggled to see ahead in the pandemic. They’re upbeat about next year, but could easily get blindsided again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S FIRST OMICRON DEATH IN UK</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10303843/Omicron-makes-40-new-Covid-cases-London-Boris-Johnson-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NHS leaders said No10 needs to be prepared to introduce stricter curbs than Plan B - which includes work from home and face masks - if Omicron is on the brink of overwhelming the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force discharges 27 for refusal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/13/air-force-discharged-vaccine-524167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force gave its forces until Nov. 2 to get the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg husband mocks Biden restarting student loan payments: 'No thank you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/buttigiegs-husband-biden-admin-restarting-student-loan-payments-next-month-no-thank-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg's husband, Chasten, appeared less than enthusiastic about having to repay his student loans, writing, "no thank you," in an Instagram story on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR porn use on rise as female users triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4264878/vr-porn-on-the-rise-more-female-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRTUAL reality porn is rising in popularity, according to a new study. Researchers interviewed thousands of people from the UK and US and found over 83% of VR headset users in the study had watche…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA to reimpose statewide indoor mask mandate for month...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/california-mask-mandate-covid-19-pandemic-rules/11335487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is reimposing an indoor mask mandate for counties that don't already have their own such measure in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Altering Weather to 'Fight Droughts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg3kb/scientists-are-altering-weather-to-fight-droughts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of evidence to support the effectiveness of cloud seeding has grown in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS:  Workers Threatened With Firing If They Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/kentucky-tornado-factory-workers-threatened-firing-left-tornado-employ-rcna8581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;heard the warning sirens and wanted to leave the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: At least 74 dead, over 100 still missing in tornado aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/13/kentucky-tornado-aftermath-dozens-dead-over-100-still-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 64 people are dead and more than 100 still missing in Kentucky after tornadoes ravaged the area, Gov. Andy Beshear said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA GETS 1ST OMICRON CASE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10305599/China-detects-case-Omicron-hundreds-thousands-placed-quarantine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in the northern city of Tianjin confirmed the case in an individual who entered the country from an undisclosed overseas location, according to the Tianjin Daily newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside abandoned sex dens...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/13/inside-the-abandoned-sex-dens-jeffrey-epstein-shared-with-ghislaine-maxwell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-before-seen photos of the estates the perv shared with his “lady of the house” have come to light amid the ongoing trial of Maxwell, who is charged with grooming many of the late …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid tension, Southern Baptist women lead where they can...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-baptist-6c5ea89af77883048855b41e4bc30963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacki King, the women’s minister at Second Baptist Church in Conway, Arkansas, first felt a call to ministry as a college student. She decided to follow it, giving up her pre-med major and her spot on a college softball team for ministry training at a small Bible school with a mostly male student body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway bans serving of alcohol in bid to halt outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211213191518-an8m4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NORWAY-OMICRON (URGENT):Norway bans serving of alcohol in bid to halt Omicron outbreak</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
