<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Well-known wild horse found dead on Outer Banks beach. Heat may have been factor...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article253184858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The horse was nearly 30 years of age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At extraordinary Games, acts of kindness abound...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-acts-of-kindness-sportsmanship-f7484946288e2a078b2a1f9eccbc1232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A surfer jumping in to translate for the rival who’d just beaten him. High-jumping friends agreeing to share a gold medal rather than move to a tiebreaker. Two runners falling in a tangle of legs, then helping each other to the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Social Network Flooded With ISIS Propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/02/trump-gettr-social-media-isis-502078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GETTR, the new platform started by members of the former president’s inner circle, is awash with beheading videos and extremist content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Matt Damon slammed after admitting using gay slur until 'just few months ago'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9850187/Matt-Damon-admits-stopped-using-homophobic-slur.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Damon admitted that his daughter wrote him a long essay detailing how the homophobic slur is 'dangerous' after the Hollywood actor said it at the dinner table as a 'joke'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama defies CDC guidance inviting 500 people to celeb-studded 60th bday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9850927/Obama-defies-CDC-guidance-inviting-500-people-60th-birthday-party-Marthas-Vineyard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama is planning to celebrate his 60th birthday with nearly 500 guests and 200 staff members on Martha's Vineyard, drawing some criticism online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Using AI To 'See Days In Advance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41771/the-pentagon-is-experimenting-with-using-artificial-intelligence-to-see-days-in-advance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon aims to use cutting-edge cloud networks and artificial intelligence systems to anticipate adversaries' moves before they make them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters swarmed St. Louis council meeting. Then, attendee tested positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-mask-protesters-swarmed-a-st-louis-county-council-meeting-then-an-attendee-tested-positive-for-covid/ar-AAMPN8r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of St. Louis Department of Health is trying to identify anyone who had close contact with the infected person and urged everyone who attended the council meeting to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats of violence spark fear of election worker exodus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/565722-threats-of-violence-spark-fear-of-election-worker-exodus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is growing concern that election workers will leave their posts in droves following a 2020 presidential contest that saw an unprecedented rise in violent threats against administrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Rouses Supporters in Protests Against Voting System...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/brazils-bolsonaro-escalates-rhetoric-over-232911585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA (Reuters) -Brazil's far-right President Jair Bolsonaro pleaded on Thursday for the adoption of printed ballots that can be counted, alleging that it is necessary to avoid fraud in the country's electronic voting system in next year's election. Bolsonaro showed a series of internet video clips as alleged evidence of past fraud, maintaining that democracy was at risk in Brazil. Critics say that Bolsonaro, like former U.S. President Donald Trump, is sowing election doubts to pave the way for him not to accept defeat in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender weightlifter in debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9837615/Laurel-Hubbard-Tokyo-Olympics-Petition-calling-rule-change-removed-hate-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 30,000 people signed the petition, which argued Hubbard's inclusion in the division put her competitors at a significant disadvantage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEALTHY AMERICANS TARGETED BY US IN PANAMA TAX-FRAUD PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://bermudapost.com/wealthy-americans-targeted-by-u-s-in-panama-tax-fraud-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bermudapost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities obtained a court order allowing them to demand financial information from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy is a fiction in the internet age. Priest's case proves it...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/08/01/privacy-is-fiction-internet-age-priests-case-proves-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress's failure to act permits an insidious data free-for-all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech's big week raises fears of 'Blade Runner future' of mega-company rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/01/big-techs-big-week-blade-runner-future-amazon-google-apple-microsoft</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, Google, Apple and Microsoft all reported record-breaking profits but recent Biden administration moves suggest US tech’s easy ride is over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL MEDIA GIANTS FAIL TO CURB 90% OF ANTISEMITISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/aug/01/a-safe-space-for-racists-antisemitism-report-criticises-social-media-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube and TikTok failing to act on most reported anti-Jewish posts, says study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups still spending donor money at his properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/his-campaign-is-over-but-trump-e2-80-99s-political-groups-are-still-spending-donor-money-at-his-properties/ar-AAMNNtc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former president Donald Trump's political action committees have continued spending money at his properties, filings show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires' space race just the beginning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/565759-the-billionaires-space-race-is-just-the-beginning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suborbital jaunts accomplished by some billionaires were not just expressions of egos. They constituted the next steps in the creation of a brand-new industry, space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lollapalooza drops DaBaby over AIDS comments...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-music-fest-lollapalooza-drops-221830181.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US music festival Lollapalooza announced Sunday it had dropped DaBaby from its lineup after the rapper made homophobic comments and false statements about AIDS during a recent performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican lawmaker who once spurned masks urges people to take covid seriously after eight-month illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gop-lawmaker-who-once-spurned-masks-urges-people-to-take-covid-19-seriously-after-eight-month-illness/ar-AAMOMFZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee state Rep. David Byrd, a Republican, had become so ill from infection that he had to get a liver transplant in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has more than $100 million in political cash after first six months of 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-built-war-chest-of-more-than-100-million/ar-AAMLDWg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite departing from office and being barred from the leading social media platforms, former President Donald J. Trump was the Republican Party’s most dominant fund-raiser in the first half of 2021 and ended June with a war chest of more than $100 million, according to new federal campaign filings made this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE removes dating app for unvaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/apple-removes-anti-vaxx-covid-dating-app-unjected-app-store-2021-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple said an anti-vaxx app called Unjected breached its App Store rules. Unjected's owners fought back, saying the decision was "censorship."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spray of bullets injures 10 people in NYC gang shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazen-coordinated-attack-spray-bullets-231500246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — Ten people were wounded when a pair of gunmen fired more than 40 shots down a Queens street in a brazen gang-related shooting, police said Sunday. The barrage of bullets on 37th Avenue near 99th Street in North Corona kicked off a bloody night in the city, where 18 people were either killed or wounded in seven separate shootings, police said. The masked and hooded Queens gunmen, who ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Doom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fauci-covid-cases-rise-26bea820b736cf4d9ac1692ccc0203ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci warned Sunday that more “pain and suffering” is on the horizon as COVID-19 cases climb again and officials plead with unvaccinated Americans to get their shots. Fauci, the nation’s top infectious disease expert, also said he doesn’t foresee additional lockdowns in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPPFACEBOOK, GMAIL users warned over Israeli spyware that can hack encrypted apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3391800/whatsapp-facebook-gmail-users-warned-hacking-startup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHATSAPP, Facebook, and Gmail users are being warned about a new Israeli surveillance startup, Paragon, that can “hack encrypted apps.” The Tel Aviv-based surveillance startup’s p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia deploys helicopters and soldiers to keep people inside during lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3388310/australia-deploys-military-to-enforce-covid-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUNG ho Aussie politicians have deployed the army and helicopters to order people to go home in what is one of the world’s strictest Covid lockdowns. One man caught a chopper shouting out sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China overtakes USA in GOLD medal count...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/olympic-medal-count-see-who-has-won-the-most-gold-and-overall/3179265/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States secured its spot back atop the medal throne at the Tokyo Olympics through Day 9 of competition. Team USA has the lead at the 2020 Tokyo Games with 59 overall medals — 20 gold medals, 23 silver and 16 bronze. The women of Team USA have won 35 medals, which is almost double the medals of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran TV claims attack on 'Israeli ship' was revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-tv-report-says-attack-on-israeli-ship-was-revenge-for-syria-raid-675430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian TV network reported on Friday that the attack on the Israeli-owned ship off the coast of Oman was a response to an Israeli attack in Syria, indicating Iranian involvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE suspends SKY NEWS Australia citing 'misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210801-youtube-suspends-sky-news-australia-channel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube suspends Sky News Australia channel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mask guidelines create more and more confusion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/565712-new-mask-guidelines-trigger-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s (CDC) new mask guidance is spurring confusion and backlash as the country tries to respond to the shifting threat of the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN 'DECLARED VICTORY TOO SOON'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/president-biden-absolutely-declared-a-victory-too-soon-leana-wen-says-140703432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I am hopeful as I look to the future,” Dr. Leana Wen writes in her new book, “Lifelines: A Doctor’s Journey in the Fight for Public Health.” On the day she spoke to Yahoo News, however, case counts were spiking across the United States, due almost entirely to the increased transmissibility of the Delta variant. Masks were back. So were concerns that schools might reopen in the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER and MODERNA raise prices for vaccines in EU...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-pfizer-moderna-raise-prices-121400124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer Inc and Moderna Inc have raised the prices of their COVID-19 vaccines in their latest European Union supply contracts, the Financial Times reported https://on.ft.com/3j8mbTb on Sunday. The new price for the Pfizer shot was 19.50 euros ($23.15)against 15.50 euros previously, the newspaper said, citing portions of the contracts seen. The price of a Moderna vaccine was $25.50 a dose, the contracts show, up from about 19 euros in the first procurement deal but lower than the previously agreed $28.50 because the order had grown, the report said, citing one official close to the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Trump be spoiler in Newsom recall?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-california-coronavirus-pandemic-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-db3a54763d961ece9b33c94fbe405e20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California could witness a stunning turnabout in a nation of deeply polarized politics if the liberal state dumps Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom and elects a Republican to fill his job in a September recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FLORIDA MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-7ca97f0d685ab25559cf9b51cfc077eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A day after it recorded the most new daily cases since the start of the pandemic, Florida on Sunday broke a previous record for current hospitalizations set more than a year ago before vaccines were available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri hospital treats record number of patients...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-michael-brown-8b3940fe31b030bcbf17c96ff905eb94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Mo. (AP) — A Springfield hospital reached a “sad new record” on Sunday when the number of coronavirus patients in its care rose to 187, an administrator said. CoxHealth CEO Steve Edwards urged residents via Twitter to get vaccinated “to protect others, to protect children, to protect our community.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House frustrated with 'hyperbolic' and 'irresponsible' coverage...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/07/30/media/variant-media-coverage-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter. You can sign up for free right here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homebuyers turn to baby boomer parents to help with purchases...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/real-estate/homebuyers-turn-baby-boomer-parents-help-purchases-n1275552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s absolutely everywhere": In suburbs and in cities, competitive home prices have millennials turning to their baby boomer parents for financial help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missed debt ceiling deadline kicks off high-stakes fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/565745-missed-debt-ceiling-deadline-kicks-off-high-stakes-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal limit on how much debt the U.S. government can owe was reimposed Sunday, kicking off a high-stakes battle over federal spending with dire implications for global financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outgoing Iran president says govt not always truthful...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-iran-coronavirus-pandemic-6951ab6b5e0b77efe435d1bab3b80f94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran's outgoing president on Sunday acknowledged his nation at times “did not tell part of the truth” to its people during his eight-year tenure, as he prepares to leave office with his signature nuclear deal with world powers in tatters and tensions high with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds defy ban in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-arrests-coronavirus-pandemic-berlin-874d5e69750ffbb0e8364d15351cc3ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — BERLIN — Hundreds of people turned out in Berlin on Sunday to protest the German government’s anti-coronavirus measures despite a ban on the gatherings, leading to arrests and clashes with police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says more 'pain and suffering' still ahead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-93924608c51944c64c05de736fafb168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation’s top infectious disease expert, is warning of “some pain and suffering in the future” as coronavirus cases continue to rise. Fauci, speaking on ABC’s “This Week” on Sunday, said he doesn’t foresee more lockdowns in the U.S., but warned that the situation surrounding the coronavirus pandemic will continue to get worse because so many Americans are still unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami of deferred debt to hit homeowners no longer protected by foreclosure moratorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/a-tsunami-of-deferred-debt-is-about-to-hit-homeowners-no-longer-protected-by-a-foreclosure-moratorium/ar-AAMOqX5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeowners behind on their mortgage payments who aren’t forced out will still be displaced if selling is their only option, and an estimated one in ten10 borrowers in forbearance will not have enough equity to sell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros' right-hand man accused of BDSM crimes in his sex dungeon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/31/how-george-soros-money-manager-was-accused-of-bdsm-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the glamorous public life and shocking private world of Howard Rubin — accused of beating up women in his secret sex lair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITAL HELL</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/30/covid-delta-variant-summer-spike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is becoming the epicenter of the coronavirus outbreak, and Just this week, cases jumped 50 percent, with more than 110,000 new cases reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-business-arts-and-entertainment-florida-01fa89e1d9491ab075c5deb689af1ea8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Florida reported 21,683 new cases of COVID-19, the state’s highest one-day total since the start of the pandemic, according to federal health data released Saturday, as its theme park resorts again started asking visitors to wear masks indoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As cases surge, Thai hospital uses containers to store bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/covid-19-thai-hospital-containers-store-bodies-15348720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK: A Thai hospital morgue overwhelmed by COVID-19 deaths has begun storing bodies in refrigerated containers, resorting to a measure it last ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For US teen Buddhist lama, it's faith, school, football...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-football-music-religion-0f95496cb1ed092694234f1d4284a741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA HEIGHTS, Minn. (AP) — In most ways, Jalue Dorje is a typical American teen — he grew up in a suburb of Minneapolis, loving football, Pokémon and rap music. Yet a few years from now, he’s expecting to say goodbye to his family and homeland and join a monastery in the foothills of the Himalayas — from an early age, he was recognized by the Dalai Lama and other Tibetan Buddhist leaders as a reincarnated lama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Caeleb: Dressel Joins Elite Club With 5 Golds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-sports-great-britain-olympic-team-italy-olympic-team-375d46aa731faa359d5103cdb07d6447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — There was no joy in the process for Caeleb Dressel. Sleepless nights. Hardly any appetite. A virtual cocoon of an Olympics, cut off from his wife, family and friends back in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day the Space Station Lurched...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-day-the-space-station-lurched/ar-AAMOj4W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent arrival at the International Space Station created a little too much excitement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer arrested after man assaulted, left with brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/influencer-hayes-grier-arrested-after-a-man-was-assaulted-and-left-with-brain-damage/ar-AAMO26u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influencer Hayes Grier was arrested in Charlotte, North Carolina, after a man was left with a broken eyeball socket, brain damage, and bruised ribs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will high-res image of monkey brain unlock secrets?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3143188/chinese-scientists-hope-unlock-secrets-human-brain-high-res</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found a way to get a full 3D image providing an unprecedented level of detail that could be used for research into neurological conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery nightly siren coming from Census HQ keeping residents awake...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/prince-georges-county/unidentified-noise-keeping-suitland-residents-up-at-night/2753920/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Suitland, Maryland, say an unidentified siren sounds off regularly through the night, making it difficult to sleep. They want to know where the noise is coming from and they want it to stop so they can get some sleep. “It sounds kind of like a combination of a tornado siren and a spaceship taking off, like the siren…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions at risk of eviction as moratorium expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210801-millions-of-americans-at-risk-of-eviction-as-moratorium-expires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pandemic-related U.S. government ban on residential evictions expired at midnight on Saturday, putting millions of American renters at risk of being forced from their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People experiencing hair loss months after Covid infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1470608/hair-loss-coronavirus-long-covid-symptoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONG COVID sufferers can experience hair loss months after an infection, a doctor has warned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
