<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How 'NULL' License Plate Landed One Hacker in Ticket Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/null-license-plate-landed-one-hacker-ticket-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security researcher Joseph Tartaro thought NULL would make a fun license plate. He's never been more wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY giving podcasters unprecedented access to listener data...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/8/13/20802018/spotify-for-podcasters-dashboard-live-beta-analytics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spotify for Podcasters comes out of beta today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein had portrait of Bill Clinton wearing Monica's blue dress in Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7353967/Did-Jeffrey-Epstein-portrait-Bill-Clinton-blue-dress-red-heels-NYC-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The painting was snapped inside convicted pedophile Jeffrey Epstein's $56m New York mansion in 2012, seven years before his suicide in the wake of new charges of sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel's sensitive preparations for visit of Omar, Tlaib...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ilhan-omar-rashida-tlaib-visit-to-israel-temple-mount-a7d2a029-e647-44bc-986e-6b6121711915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of the delegation may be barred from entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep Hasidic Out': Small-Town Housing Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/08/14/keep-the-hasidic-out-a-small-town-housing-showdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHESTER, N.Y. — In a peaceful corner of the Hudson Valley, a broad expanse of land sits at the ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Burden lifted off of my soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g1VeElBAeas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Google insider who anonymously leaked internal documents to Project Veritas made the decision to go public in an on-the-record video interview. The insider...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reverse Aging in Rat Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.eveningexpress.co.uk/news/boost-for-ms-treatment-as-scientists-reverse-ageing-process-in-rat-brain-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eveningexpress.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brains get stiff with age just like muscles and joints, scientists have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 2020 Rust Belt Pitch Threatened by Manufacturing Downturn...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-14/trump-2020-rust-belt-pitch-threatened-by-manufacturing-recession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-Year: Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-30-yield-falls-record-101045742.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. 30-year yields fell to their lowest level ever as investors sought shelter amid a fraught geopolitical backdrop and concern increased about the impact of the escalating global trade war on economic growth.Meanwhile, the stream of investors into the safest parts of the market has triggered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious drawings by da Vinci found hidden beneath painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9722419/leonardo-da-vinci-secret-hidden-painting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAWINGS made by Leonardo da Vinci underneath one of his most popular paintings have been revealed. Scribbles from the Renaissance master were found buried underneath his 16th Century work The Virg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Elizabeth Warren Surges to Statistical Tie With Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/just-in-elizabeth-warren-surges-in-new-national-poll-to-statistical-tie-with-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results of a new poll released conducted by YouGov for The Economist shows Sen. Elizabeth Warren surging into a statistical tie with former Vice President Joe Biden. The poll shows Biden earning 21% s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to gobble up more assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-a-merged-viacomcbs-boldly-go-media-assets-1231474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Bakish and Joseph Ianniello will preside over a film and TV empire that brings together 'Star Trek' and 'Mission: Impossible' — but many believe it needs to go on a buying spree to contend with Disney and Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Has TESLA Valet Key Implanted Into Arm!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/tesla-model-3-key-implant-biohack-cyberpunk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's only a matter of time before Elon tries to offer this as an option when purchasing your Model 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial AMAZON Facial Recognition Software Can Now Spot Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/amazons-rekognition-software-can-now-detect-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rekognition is also getting better at estimating a person's age, the company says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem contenders unload on corporate media...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/457302-democratic-contenders-unload-on-news-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential contenders are letting loose with a barrage of attacks against the news media, ripping national outlets for what they view as biased coverage of their campaigns or unfair double standards in covering President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: It's Gotten Too Hard to Strike It Rich...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gotten-too-hard-strike-rich-113004604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- In a free-market economy everyone is supposed to have the chance to get rich. The dream of making it big motivates people to take risks, start businesses, stay in school and work hard. Unfortunately, in the U.S., that dream seems to be dying.There are still plenty of rich people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Drops First-Look Images of Sacha Baron Cohen in 'THE SPY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/see-first-look-images-of-sacha-baron-cohen-as-an-undercover-agent-in-netflixs-the-spy-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has released three first-look images of Sacha Baron Cohen in "The Spy." The limited series is set to premiere September 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking sperm sorting could let parents choose baby sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/sperm-sorting-chemical-method-mice-male-female-ivf-a9056941.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Call to Scrap 'HUNT': Death Threats, Negative Feedback...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/behind-universals-call-scrap-hunt-death-threats-negative-test-screening-feedback-1231472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A politically charged satire denounced by Trump and the right sparked menacing emails as its violent marketing ran squarely into horrific news of a trio of mass shootings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First ever A-level where getting HALF answers wrong will get student A...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/08/14/first-ever-level-getting-almost-half-answers-wrong-will-get/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students who got almost half of the answers wrong in their Maths A-level this summer will get a grade A, it has emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAT APPLES, DRINK TEA FOR LONGER LIFE...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-live-longer-by-eating-apples-drinking-tea-flavonoids-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that eating foods rich in flavonoids, a compound found in high concentrations in foods like apples and beverages such as tea, lowers one's risk of death, particularly among heavy drinkers and smokers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chip implanted in obese people's brains zaps when think about food...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/chip-implanted-obese-peoples-brains-18932778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A clinical trial will aim to identify the pattern of brain activity that signals the start of a food binge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenspan says no barrier to treasuries falling below 0%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ex-fed-boss-greenspan-says-there-is-no-barrier-to-treasury-yields-falling-below-zero-2019-08-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is some $15 trillion in government debt that now yields less than zero, and former Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan believes there’s no reason...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vanishing $200 Million Blockbuster...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/vanishing-200-million-blockbuster-1231467 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an increasingly stratified box office landscape dominated by Disney, not a single film this year so far has topped out between $200 million to $300 million domestically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Suffers Shopping Slump!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/beverly-hills-suffers-shopping-slump-trump-china-trade-war-1231083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's battle with Beijing and visa policies on Gulf nations are taking a brutal toll on the tony retail zone, with sales down double digits and no relief in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror pics show abused elephant forced to take part in religious festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/abused-elephant-festival-sri-lanka-18930000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PICTURES of an elephant's emaciated body - normally hidden by its colourful costume - have gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like horror movie': Camper saves family from savage wolf attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Like-a-horror-movie-Camper-saves-family-of-14303149.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was about half past midnight when Russ Fee woke up to the sound of frantic shouts coming from a campsite next to his in Canada's Banff National Park. From within his tent, he listened, quickly discerning that the voices belonged to a man and a woman. They were screaming for help.  "I threw my shoes on. My wife tossed me a lantern," Fee said in an interview Tuesday with the radio show "Calgary Eyeopener." "I popped out of the tent and just started running toward their tent sort of yelling, 'I'm here! I'm here! What's wrong?'"  Fee, who is from Calgary, told the program that he expected to find "two really scared parents" whose child had wandered off into the woods. Instead, the sight that greeted him was much more distressing.  The family's tent was in shambles, Fee said, and sticking out of its entrance was the rear end of a large wolf.  In what officials with Parks Canada are calling a "very rare incident," a wolf attacked a New Jersey couple and their two children who were visiting the national park in Banff, Alberta, early Friday - a harrowing encounter that may have ended differently if it weren't for Fee's quick thinking, Canadian Broadcasting Corp. reported.  "We are forever grateful to Russ who came to our aid," Elisa Rispoli, whose husband, Matt, was injured in the attack, wrote on Facebook. Describing Fee as a "guardian angel," Elisa added that the Canadian man probably saved her husband's life.  "It could have been so so much worse, and we are just feeling so thankful that we are all still sitting here as a complete family," she wrote.  The Rispolis were asleep in their tent at the park's Rampart Creek Campground when they were jolted awake after midnight by the wolf.  "It was like something out of a horror movie," Elisa wrote in the Facebook post.  Matt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuser files suit against estate, 'madam'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/jeffrey-epstein-accuser-jennifer-araoz-sues-ghislaine-maxwell-3-other-n1041901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Araoz alleges she was repeatedly sexually assaulted by Jeffrey Epstein at his New York townhouse when she was 14 and 15, including a 2002 rape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS set to seize passport if owe money...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/taxpayers-owing-a-lot-of-money-could-have-their-passports-revoked.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may not be able to get a new passport or renew your existing one if you owe the IRS more than $52,000. Worse, your existing one might simply be revoked. Here's what you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish Court Finds Rapper A$AP Rocky Guilty of Assault...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201908141076549028-swedish-court-us-rapper-suspended-sentence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets late last month, President Donald Trump demanded that Sweden should “give [US rapper] A$AP Rocky his freedom”. Stockholm responded by stating that the Swedish judicial system is independent and that “everyone is equal before the law”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA descends on Icelandic lava field to prepare for Mars...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-08-nasa-descends-icelandic-lava-field.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To prepare for the next mission to Mars in 2020, NASA has taken to the lava fields of Iceland to get its new robotic space explorer ready for the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone Scam Targets Man With Bloody Pics; Threatens To Kill Family Unless Pays Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/13/scam-brooklyn-bloody-pics-cartel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, who hid his face in fear, says last week he got text messages with pictures of blood soaked and mangled people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing god: Temple puts faith in robot priest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/playing-god-japan-temple-puts-faith-robot-priest-043640106.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The android Kannon, based on the Buddhist deity of mercy, preaches sermons at Kodaiji temple in Kyoto, and its human colleagues predict that with artificial intelligence it could one day acquire unlimited wisdom. "This robot will never die, it will just keep updating itself and evolving,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S posts 48% drop in profit...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/macys-posts-48-drop-profit-121501023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company said on Wednesday inventory became a challenge as it also missed the mark with its key women's sportswear private brands and a higher decline in international tourism. "We had a slow start to the quarter and finished below our expectations," Chief Executive Officer Jeff Gennette</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman claims emotional support dog locked in plane restroom...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/woman-sues-american-airlines-claims-emotional-support-dog/story?id=64958059</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The passenger, Avigail Diveroli, said the dog helps her battle severe anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCNEWS: 36 cases invoking 'Trump' in connection with violence, threats, assaults...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/blame-abc-news-finds-17-cases-invoking-trump/story?id=58912889 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump insists he deserves no blame for divisions in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The No. 1 job in America: Tax manager...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-no-1-job-in-america-with-the-best-career-opportunities-pays-112000-a-year-and-its-not-in-tech-2019-08-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This analysis is based on median salary, overall job satisfaction and the number of job openings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant who contracted measles dies amid rise in outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Israeli-flight-attendant-who-contracted-measles-14301329.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli flight attendant died after contracting measles and falling into a coma, Israeli media reported Tuesday, the latest incident amid growing measles outbreaks worldwide.  More cases of the virus were reported in the first half 2019 than in any other year since 2006, the World Health Organization announced Monday. Compared to this time last year, there have already been nearly three times more reported cases of measles. While many of the measles outbreaks occurred in places with low vaccination rates, the WHO said, others are occurred in nations that have high rates, resulting from "lack of access to quality healthcare or vaccination services, conflict and displacement, misinformation about vaccines, or low awareness about the need to vaccinate."  "The United States has reported its highest measles case count in 25 years," the WHO said in the announcement.  The woman, a mother of three, is just the third death from measles in Israel in the past 15 years, according to the Times of Israel. In 2018 an 18-month-old child and an 82-year-old woman also died from the virus.  In a statement to the Jewish Press, the airline, El Al, said that "the company is bowing its head over the death of a member of El Al's aircrew. The company will continue to act on the matter in accordance with the health ministry's guidelines. Once the case became known, the company acted to vaccinate the company's aircrews. The company shares the deep grief of the family and will continue to accompany the family."  The Washington Post reported on April 17 that the 43-year-old flight attendant had flown in late March on an El Al flight from New York's John F. Kennedy International Airport to Israel and was later admitted to the hospital after developing encephalitis, a complication of the illness in which the brain swells.  In early April, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching sports good for you: Cardio workout similar to 90-min walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7355817/Watching-football-good-you.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of Leeds analysed 25 fans of the city's football team over three games. They found the supporters' heart rates increased by around 64 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Demotes top DC editor over tweets...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/jonathan-weisman-demoted-nyt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times on Tuesday demoted deputy Washington editor Jonathan Weisman following a series of questionable tweets about people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study reveals emotional journey of digital detox while travelling...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-08-reveals-emotional-journey-digital-detox.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research reveals the emotional journey that tourists go on when they disconnect from technology and social media while travelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 2020 Rust Belt Pitch Threatened by Manufacturing Recession...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-2020-rust-belt-pitch-080000058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. President Donald Trump has been boasting about creating manufacturing jobs in states key to his re-election, but an emerging recession in the sector threatens to reverse that trend and imperil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Brink of Blackouts, Texas Makes Case for Power Plant Boom...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brink-blackouts-texas-makes-case-052950761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It may be time to start building power plants in Texas again.The state’s generators made a killing this week as unrelenting heat sent electricity prices skyrocketing to unprecedented levels, briefly blowing past a $9,000 a megawatt-hour price ceiling. That put producers more than two-thirds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body odor? Bacteria-embedded bodysuit may help...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190814090751-fs65x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CLOTHING/SKIN II (PIX, TV):Body odour? Bacteria-embedded bodysuit may help</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: Video captures brutal attack on comedian Andy Dick...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/video-captures-brutal-attack-comedian-andy-dick-new-orleans-police-n1042086 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video appears to show the moment an unidentified man viciously sucker-punched the 53-year-old actor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guards were 'asleep and faked log entries'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7354679/Corrections-officers-prison-Jeffrey-Epstein-held-falsified-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corrections officers at a New York prison where Jeffrey Epstein was being held had 'fallen asleep and falsified reports' to show that they checked on him when they hadn't before his apparent suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How stocks performed under each president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2019/business/stock-market-by-president/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump often cites the stock market as a scorecard of his policies. Here’s how the S&amp;P 500 performed under each president from Reagan to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Say Can't Afford Vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/americans-say-they-can-t-afford-a-vacation-1.1301199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 40% of Americans have opted out of a getaway over the past year specifically because of the cost, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Meat Next Sin Tax?</title>
      <link>https://www.accountingtoday.com/articles/is-red-meat-more-expensive-could-be-next-sin-tax-after-sugar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accountingtoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat could be a target for higher taxes given criticism of the industry’s role in climate change, deforestation and animal cruelty, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: Yield curve nearly inverted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/13/us-bonds-yield-curve-at-flattest-level-since-2007-amid-risk-off-sentiment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The yield on the 10-year Treasury note threatens to break below that of the 2-year while the 30-year bond rate neared an all-time low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA bans some APPLE laptops from flights over fire risk...</title>
      <link>https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/faa-bans-recalled-apple-laptops-230926613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. airline safety regulators banned select MacBook Pro laptops on flights after Apple Inc. recently said that some units had batteries that posed a fire risk.In a statement, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said it was “aware of the recalled batteries that are used in some Apple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge overseeing key Jeffrey Epstein case dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/25/judge-jeffrey-epstein-case-dies-1292394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan-based U.S. District Court Judge Robert Sweet passed away Sunday at age 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waning of American Power? </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/13/world/asia/trump-asia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has taken a hands-off approach to conflicts — from Kashmir to Hong Kong to the rivalry between Japan and South Korea — as Asian officials escalate the battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs down again, delays new tariffs on China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/trump-backs-down-again-delays-many-new-tariffs-on-china-until-december/ar-AAFKH9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Scrambles As Rogue Drone Captures Epstein Raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/fbi-scrambles-as-rogue-drone-captures-epstein-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents cover windows with blankets, cardboard upon noticing peeping drone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women accuse opera legend Domingo of sexual harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2d51d690d004992b8cfba3bad827ae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Placido Domingo, one of the most celebrated and powerful men in opera, has tried to pressure women into sexual relationships by dangling jobs and then sometimes punishing the women...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING BATTLE BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89ed1bbe8bc442319d16cd615db8a5c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The newly combined ViacomCBS will invest in more movies and TV shows and try to sell more advertising as it seeks to become a bigger player in the growing business of streaming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSTONE MOST POWERFUL WOMAN IN MEDIA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/after-years-of-battle-shari-redstone-runs-an-empire-of-her-own/ar-AAFKMz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Sues CNN's Don Lemon for Alleged Assault at Bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/man-sues-cnns-don-lemon-for-alleged-assault-at-sag-harbor-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is suing Don Lemon, claiming the CNN host attacked him at a Hamptons bar last summer. The suit, obtained by Mediaite, was filed Sunday and seeks unspecified damages for "emotional pain and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC Chief Says Willing to Break Up Companies Amid Big Tech Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-13/ftc-chief-says-willing-to-break-up-companies-amid-big-tech-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA Made GOOGLE Give Up Info on Everyone in Area in Hunt for Antifa...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/manhattan-da-cy-vance-made-google-give-up-info-on-everyone-in-area-in-hunt-for-antifa-after-proud-boys-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;…and investigators ended up targeting the wrong people, at least in part from that information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Married 68 Years Has Worn Matching Outfits Every Day...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/secret-to-happy-marriage-couple-matches-outfits-for-seven-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s one thing to match on your wedding day but it’s another to match for 68 years. That’s what Francis and Rosemary Klontz have been doing for seven decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LYFT's 'Woke' Image Collides With Flurry of Sex Assault Suits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-13/lyft-s-woke-image-collides-with-flurry-of-sex-assault-lawsuits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Referred to HIMSELF as 'Fredo'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/13/chris-cuomo-once-referred-to-himself-as-fredo-in-radio-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN anchor Chris Cuomo, who was captured on a viral video getting into a profanity-laced exchange with a person who called him “Fredo,” once referred to himself as the hapless “Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery: Old TVs placed on porches of 50 homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/local/henrico/mystery-in-henrico-old-tvs-were-placed-on-front-porches/article_53bef019-a18e-593a-a5de-81c03a870826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 50 television sets were mysteriously left on the front porches of homes throughout the Hampshire neighborhood in western Henrico County, surprising residents who found them Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau calls for gun control as violence spikes in Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-guns-idUSKCN1V31U9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Tuesday that a recent spate of gu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim women 'sterilized' in Chinese 're-education' camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/chinas-sickening-acts-on-female-prisoners-at-reeducation-camps/news-story/34d531c19a5bb060881a76ac8b478609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is forcibly sterilising women held in its vast network of “re-education” camps which house political and religious prisoners, survivors have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller alum landing cushy jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mueller-alumni-landing-cushy-jobs-at-law-firms-universities-even-a-book-deal-after-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top investigators who worked alongside former Special Counsel Robert Mueller have certainly landed on their feet since the shuttering of the two-year Russia probe, securing big jobs at prominent law firms and universities -- and even a book deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Better than LeBron:' Meet basketball's next teen phenom...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/13/emoni-bates-is-basketballs-next-teenage-phenom-better-than-lebron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some teenage phenoms, such as LeBron James, live up to the insane hype assigned to them, while others end up like Freddy Adu. The world will be watching to see how 15-year-old hoopster Emoni Bates …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Paid Contractors to Transcribe Users' Audio Chats...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-paid-hundreds-contractors-transcribe-190743545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. has been paying hundreds of outside contractors to transcribe clips of audio from users of its services, according to people with knowledge of the work.The work has rattled the contract employees, who are not told where the audio was recorded or how it was obtained -- only</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Orthorexia' vying for classification as mental disorder...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/orthorexia-vying-for-a-place-in-the-dsm-as-more-people-become-obsessed-with-clean-eating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it’s a ‘real’ mental disease or an imaginary one, the behaviours and consequences are certainly real, according to a new study’s author</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway producer arrested on child porn charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1cac49f35090418e9c6f060db4f39154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Broadway producer whose first big-budget show was derailed by a con man's false financial promises has been arrested on child porn charges. The producer, Ben Sprecher, was...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
