<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown could threaten SUPER BOWL...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/politics/the-jolt-johnny-isakson-worries-shutdown-could-threaten-super-bowl/zXDUcSey3VHAk9wFtIcc8O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publicly, Republican lawmakers from Georgia are holding the line on the partial federal government s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first robot hotel fires half of 'annoying' non-human workforce...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/01/16/worlds-first-robot-hotel-fires-half-annoying-non-human-workforce-8352150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out the rise of the robots isn't something people working in the tourist industry have to worry about quite yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>86-year-old loses 120-lbs by walking in living room...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/2019/01/15/missouri-86-year-old-loses-120-pounds-by-walking-in-her-living-room-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS -- No gym, no problem! An 86-year-old St. Louis woman says she lost 120 pounds just by walking back and forth from her living room to kitchen every day in her one-bedroom apartment. "Even as a kid in Mississippi, I was always the fattest kid in the class. I got teased a lot," Jessica Slaughter told KSDK. "I didn't know how to stop eating. Fried chicken. Bacon and eggs. Desserts, like cakes and pies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mass casualties' via IEDs, anti-tank rocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/forsyth-county-man-charged-with-plot-to-attack-white-house-fbi-says/905525963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new information we're learning about the suspect, LIVE on the Channel 2 Action News Nightbeat at 11 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS THWART DC TERROR THREAT</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/georgia/articles/2019-01-16/fbi-georgia-man-arrested-in-plot-to-attack-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO, NO, NO!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/16/has-trump-met-his-match-pelosi-1106624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi’s move to derail Trump’s State of the Union address underscores her aggressive challenge to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-ft Great White spotted in Hawaii eating whale...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/great-white-shark-spotted-off-the-south-shore-eating-a-dead-whale/1704846429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's something you don't see very often. A great white shark in Hawaii waters.  The large white shark-- who researchers named "Deep Blue" --was spotted miles off of the south shore over the past two days.   She was feeding on a dead sperm whale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVERS IN DISBELIEF SNAP PICS...</title>
      <link>https://ftw.usatoday.com/2019/01/deep-blue-perhaps-the-largest-known-great-white-shark-spotted-off-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ftw.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strikingly massive great white shark, one of the largest ever documented, was spotted by divers in Hawaii on Sunday as the apex predator feasted on a sperm whale carcass. The sighting of “Deep Bl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Susan Rice, Obama officials to answer questions in Clinton email case...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/16/susan-rice-clinton-email-lawsuit/2592081002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Judge Royce Lamberth said the case of Clinton's email server involved "one of the gravest modern offenses to government transparency."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Elementary students 'put into effect plot to murder' child...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2019/01/16/details-reveal-roberts-elementary-students-planned-murder-plot-tallahassee-leon-county-schools/2585737002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the students brought a bag to school with a wrench, baseball batting gloves, adjustable clamp pliers, and a multitool with a blade on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN SACHS Tactic in Huge Fraud Case: Smear Ex-Partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/16/business/goldman-malaysia-1mdb-leissner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investment bank is campaigning to convince authorities that a former partner, Tim Leissner, was a master con man — and that is how the bank became ensnared in a vast fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First artificial meteor shower set to fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90293194/the-worlds-first-artificial-meteor-shower-is-set-to-fly-over-japan-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astro Live Experiences is going to put on a show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS waiving penalty for some in first filing season under tax law...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/425747-irs-waiving-penalty-for-some-in-first-filing-season-under-trumps-tax-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS on Wednesday announced that it will waive a penalty for some taxpayers who didn't have enough money withheld from their paychecks last year, in an effort to aid people as they adjust to the tax-code changes made by President Trump's t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs started helping humans 11,500 years ago, fossils suggest...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2019/01/16/Dogs-started-helping-humans-11500-years-ago-fossils-in-Jordan-suggest/8841547651352/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New archaeological evidence excavated in Jordan suggests dogs may have helped humans hunt as early as 11,500 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US submarine commander fired over hooker orgy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8211653/us-navy-commander-axed-prostitutes-hotel-orgy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE commander of a US Navy submarine has been given the sack after he hired ten prostitutes all at once to party in his hotel room. Captain Travis Zettel, of the USS Bremerton, paid for the women w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley Demands BBQ Restaurant Stop Barbecuing...</title>
      <link>https://sf.eater.com/2019/1/15/18183773/kcs-bbq-berkeley-city-violation-petition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sf.eater.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus a new East Bay coffee shop, pizza in Hayes Valley, and more intel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHERN POVERTY accused of racketeering, wielding 'hate label' to kneecap opponents...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/16/immigration-group-files-rico-lawsuit-splc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most prominent groups advocating for stricter immigration went to court Wednesday to demand a judge order the Southern Poverty Law Center to stop labeling it a “hate group,” accusing the self-described watchdog of running an illegal racket to silence political opponents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS GROW 'PERFECT' HUMAN BLOOD VESSELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/01/190116130820.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'10 Year Challenge' data scheme disguised as meme?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebook-10-year-challenge-meme-could-it-mine-your-data-facial-recognition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The simple meme that's taking over your Facebook feed might not be so simple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive rodeo cow evades police drone search, capture for months...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/anchorage/2019/01/16/rogue-cow-wandering-the-anchorage-hillside-has-managed-to-evade-a-police-drone-search/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not even two drones equipped with high-definition video cameras and infrared imaging could locate Betsy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal think tank fires staffers suspected of 'improper influence by UAE' leak involvement...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/16/center-for-american-progress-cap-uae-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staffers were investigated for leaking an email exchange to The Intercept that reflected improper influence by the UAE within the think tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAME-CHANGER...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/pa579z/researchers-create-perfect-blood-vessels-in-a-petri-dish-for-the-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers also demonstrated that it is possible to grow functioning human blood vessels in another species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complicates US withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/16/us-troops-killed-manbij-syria-1104355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS claimed responsibility for the attack via its Amaq news agency, saying it was carried out by a suicide bomber donning an explosive vest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star defense lawyer resigns from Weinstein team...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190116-star-defense-lawyer-resigns-weinstein-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star defense lawyer resigns from Weinstein team</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moms flock to new side hustle: Selling cannabidiol...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/lifestyles/ct-life-moms-sell-hemp-oil-20190108-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBD oil, whether in lotions, balms or inside of a dropper bottle, is the latest in a string of products that women, many of them mothers, are selling and recruiting others to sell — a modernized version of a decades-old trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The churchgoing patriot who spied for China...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46557096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He appeared to lead a typical suburban life - but he was secretly involved in international espionage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town To Hold 'Open Audition' To Fill Vacant Mayor Position...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/01/15/braddock-to-hold-open-audition-to-fill-vacant-mayor-position/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;t's a stunning opportunity for anyone living in this aging steel town -- an open audition to become Braddock's next mayor to fill the shoes of now Lt. Gov. John Fetterman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 inches of snow: Life-threatening blizzard to hit Sierra...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/sierra-nevada-snow-mlk-weekend-conditions-13538091.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A colossal storm is poised to barrel across the northern Sierra Nevada Wednesday evening, with high winds whipping heavy falling snow and creating blizzard conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive tennis match-fixing ring discovered...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d051d5ee704465087607376d88c33c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The crooked tennis players knew him as "Maestro." To European investigators, the Armenian based in Belgium is emerging as something else: The suspected ringleader of an organized gambling syndicate suspected of fixing hundreds of matches and corrupting more than 100 players from around Europe. As Roger Federer and other stars at the top of tennis compete in the Australian Open, players far lower down the sport's food chain are being questioned this week by police in France on suspicion of fixing matches for the Maestro, himself in detention in Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West moves to ban sunscreens...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/key-west-moves-ban-sunscreens-could-damage-reefs-n959416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some studies have shown that the chemicals encourage coral bleaching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions Boil Over At CBS Town Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-employees-voice-concerns-strategy-transparency-town-hall-1176430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One staffer asked what would happen to the $120 million in severance money that is being denied to former CEO Leslie Moonves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY SURVIVES 'NO CONFIDENCE' VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/16/brexit-uk-government-survives-no-confidence-vote.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chances of a General Election triggered by Brexit confusion look to have receded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remains of 127 dead migrants recovered in AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/border-issues/2019/01/16/remains-127-dead-migrants-recovered-southern-arizona-2018/2575080002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers searching the Barry Goldwater Range the weekend before Christmas found the remains of 8 people. A total of 127 remains were found in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Claims Abducted By Aliens In 1970s Breaks Silence...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/01/16/man-who-says-he-was-abducted-by-aliens-breaks-45-year-silence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mississippi man in declining health is telling a story he's kept secret from his own family for 45 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet student pretended to rescue horses; Sold 50 to slaughterhouses...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/i-team/vet-student-indicted-for-taking-horses-with-intent-to-defraud-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5atlanta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horse owners in Georgia and across the Southeast applaud the indictment of an Alabama woman accused of pulling a tragic scam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Rewrites Book Industry by Marching Into Publishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/they-own-the-system-amazon-rewrites-book-industry-by-turning-into-a-publisher-11547655267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The online retail giant, the world’s largest public company, commands an unrivaled customer base for the books, ebooks and audiobooks it publishes. As a result, it’s jolting the publishing industry, creating instant best sellers out of self-published writers and pushing down earnings for others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CATCH A PREDATOR' Host Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/16/to-catch-a-predator-host-chris-hansen-arrested-bounced-checks-larceny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'To Catch a Predator' host Chris Hansen Arrested for larceny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran calls for release of its journalist arrested in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-us-arrests/iran-calls-for-release-of-its-journalist-arrested-in-u-s-idUSKCN1PA0CY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran on Wednesday called for the immediate release of an American-born journalis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women caught twerking atop SUV on crowded interstate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/16/two-women-caught-twerking-atop-suv-on-crowded-interstate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caution — road twerk ahead! Two passionate passengers hopped atop the roof of a white SUV driving westbound along Interstate 64 in St. Louis on Monday, where a quick-thinking registered nurse pulle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conn. may require 'climate change' education...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e19029381ba24b9c9c567e0924621888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — A legislative proposal in Connecticut would mandate instruction on climate change in public schools statewide, beginning in elementary school. Connecticut already has adopted science standards that call for teaching of climate change, but if the bill passes it is believed that it would be the country's first to write such a requirement into law. "A lot of schools make the study of climate change an elective, and I don't believe it should be an elective," said state Rep. Christine Palm, a Democrat from Chester who proposed the bill. "I think it should be mandatory, and I think it should be early so there's no excuse for kids to grow up ignorant of what's at stake."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  President's approval gap widest in 60 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/pew-biggest-divide-ever-on-wall-trump-approval-gap-widest-in-60-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America has “never been more sharply divided” over border security as it is over President Trump’s call for a wall, and neither side is ready to throw in the towel, according to the latest survey on immigration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens if Ruth Bader Ginsburg Remains Too Sick to Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/01/16/ruth-bader-ginsburg-supreme-court-health-224014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing! History is full of Supreme Court justices who were incapacitated—or worse. That’s the price of life tenure, and it’s worth paying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise boosts brain, memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/16/well/move/exercise-brain-memory-irisin-alzheimer-dementia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irisin, a hormone that is released during exercise, may improve brain health and lessen the damage that occurs during Alzheimer’s disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST warns of fake edition circulating...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/fake-washington-post-newspapers-distributed-dc-1176560</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lead front page story of the fake paper read: "Unpresidented. Trump hastily departs White House ending crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' EXPOSES THE DIVIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/politics-roma-alfonso-cuaron-revisits-mexicos-turbulent-history-1176330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Alfonso Cuaron and star Yalitza Aparicio guide The Hollywood Reporter through the city's Roma neighborhood as they break down how the political forces of the director’s childhood (and what's happening now) shape the ideas on display in the potentially history-making Oscar contender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie PM' battles on alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190116-uks-zombie-pm-may-battles-alone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK's 'zombie PM' May battles on alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB Lets Hosts Put Cameras In Living Rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90293018/man-finds-secret-camera-in-rental-airbnb-says-he-agreed-to-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just another day in bizarro Airbnb world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP:  WALLS AROUND THE WORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6598459/Trump-turns-globalist-latest-wall-argument-says-45-countries-them.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Over 800 miles of Walls have been built in Europe since only 2015. They have all been recognized as close to 100% successful. Stop the crime at our Southern Border!' Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us2000j4bf/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.7 Mag Quake Reported Off Maryland Coast...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/01/15/4-7-magnitude-earthquake-reported-off-coast-of-ocean-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An earthquake was reported off the coast of Ocean City, Maryland, at 6:30 p.m. Tuesday according to the USGS Earthquake Hazards Program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN TURNS WEAPON</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190116151418-2t7f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-As shutdown lingers, Pelosi urges Trump to reschedule State of the Union</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taunts critics: 'What you got left?'</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ocasio-Cortez-s-reply-to-relentless-GOP-13537717.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The tweet landed Sunday evening and instantly triggered an online melee over age, class and politics. Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez "was so fiscally irresponsible that she hadn't saved up enough money to rent an apartment in the Washington D.C. area," wrote conservative commentator Candace Owens, adding the hashtag #SocialismSucks, as she blasted the New York freshman for complaining that some members of Congress have trouble paying for two residences. "But sure, let's trust her with the future fiscal-planning of America." Ever since she burst onto the national political scene as a socialist Democrat with a knack for making headlines, Ocasio-Cortez has been an obsession for many on the political right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joins effort to oust more incumbent Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/new-video-ocasio-cortez-joins-progressive-effort-oust-more-incumbent-n959121 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York lawmaker is likely to cause a stir in the party by lending her star power to a Justice Democrats' program to boost insurgents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Says She's Going to 'Run Train on Progressive Agenda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-says-shes-going-to-run-train-on-the-progressive-agenda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN DAY 26:  GOVT PARALYZED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d90578a1687049e9a67db01582ce4278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Shutdown pressure on President Donald Trump mounted Wednesday as House Speaker Nancy Pelosi called on him to delay his State of the Union address and his own economists acknowledged the prolonged standoff was having a greater economic drag than previously thought. In a letter to Trump, Pelosi cited security concerns, noting that both the Secret Service and the Homeland Security Department are affected by the partial government shutdown, now it its fourth week. She added that unless the government reopens this week, they should find another date or Trump should deliver the address in writing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  Ocasio-Cortez nearly matches Trump appeal!</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/general_politics/january_2019/ocasio_cortez_vs_trump_and_the_winner_is</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Man Must Decide Whether to Indict Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/this-man-must-decide-whether-to-indict-israels-netanyahu-11547647201 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Israel’s election approaches, Avichai Mandelblit, the country’s low-key attorney general, is under intense pressure from both Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and the public to decide whether to charge the leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man injects self with  own semen to treat back pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/man-injects-himself-with-his-own-semen-to-treat-back-pain-897934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Irish medical journal has warned the public of the dangers of medical experimentation after a man admitted injecting himself with his own semen to treat back pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians suffer increase in persecution; 245 MILLION face violence, oppression...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6598209/Christians-suffered-increase-persecution-year-245-MILLION-facing-violence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report by Open Doors, a Dutch charity that supports persecuted Christians showed that in total, 245 million faced violence or oppression in 2018, with 73 countries listed as danger zones for Christians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling wages, rising housing costs fuel homelessness among aging Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/sns-tns-bc-homeless-elderly-20190116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA If current trends continue, the number of aging homeless people will more than double in three major metropolitan areas, straining social and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes has thrown CHIEFS into NFL spotlight, with only PATRIOTS in way of super finish...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/nfl/la-sp-patriots-chiefs-mahomes-20190116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first year as a starter, Patrick Mahomes threw for 5,097 yards and 50 touchdowns in the regular season. Only Peyton Manning, who set NFL records with 5,477 yards passing and 55 touchdowns for Denver in 2013, topped both totals in the same season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS saved?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/15/sears-deal-with-chairman-eddie-lampert.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings reached a roughly $5 billion deal with Chairman Eddie Lampert early Wednesday morning to keep the company, and roughly 400 stores, in operations, according to a person familiar with the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: GOOGLE Manipulated Search Results for Hot Topics; 'Blackslists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/01/16/google-youtube-search-blacklist-smoking-gun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In sworn testimony, Google CEO Sundar Pichai told congress last month that his company does not “manually intervene” on any particular search result. Yet an internal discussion thread leaked to Breitbart News reveals Google regularly intervenes in search results on its YouTube video platform – including a recent intervention that pushed pro-life videos out of the top ten search results for “abortion.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.7 rattles San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/earthquake-felt-across-bay-area/1705604011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are working to get more information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials unable to recognize dashboard warning lights...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/01/15/study-millennials-car-dashboard-symbol/2585273002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study found 49 percent of young drivers were unable to recognize the tire pressure warning light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE clarifies rules on pranks as risky memes rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190116-youtube-clarifies-rules-pranks-risky-memes-rage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube clarifies rules on pranks as risky memes rage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS claims deadly suicide attack on US-led coalition patrol in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190116-islamic-state-group-claims-deadly-suicide-attack-us-led-coalition-patrol </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A blast struck near a U.S.-led coalition patrol in Syria’s northern city of Manbij on Wednesday, and a war monitor said 14 people were killed including two Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos founders warn on rising tension between the world's superpowers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/16/davos-founders-warn-of-rising-tension-between-the-worlds-superpowers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rising risk of political confrontations between major powers is hindering solutions to challenges like climate change and cyberattacks, a new report by the World Economic Forum said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers Say Brands Shouldn't Bring Politics to Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/consumers-say-brands-shouldnt-bring-their-political-stands-to-the-super-bowl-11547636401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-thirds of consumers call the Super Bowl an inappropriate place for advertisers to make political statements, according to a poll conducted by Morning Consult for CMO Today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON ALEXA 'goes rogue'; Ignores commands, won't turn off...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8205649/alexa-down-not-working-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON’S virtual assistant Alexa stopped working for some users around the world on Wednesday morning. The mysterious outage meant that Alexa – typically controlled by voice – was “igno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Concierges Offer 'Bespoke Experiences' in Fight For Ultra-Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/luxury-concierges-offer-bespoke-experiences-in-fight-for-the-ultra-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury Concierges Offer â€˜Bespoke Experiencesâ€™ in Fight For the Ultra-Rich</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alzheimer's Vaccine?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/united-neuroscience-s-alzheimer-vaccine-just-might-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Alzheimerâ€™s Vaccine Just Might Work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Brexit referendum looks more likely than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/how-a-second-brexit-referendum-would-work-d04bca8e-3216-4eae-931a-a02df6487c03.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But like everything else with Brexit, it would be more complicated than it seems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders does damage control...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/425532-sanders-to-meet-with-staffers-as-he-does-damage-control</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is in damage control mode following allegations of sexual harassment in his 2016 campaign, as he weighs a second presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alarming' burnout making doctors want to kill selves...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/16/alarming-burnout-is-making-doctors-want-to-kill-themselves/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctor burnout is becoming a huge problem, according to new research, which finds that nearly half of all physicians feel completely depleted, to the point where one in seven have contemplated suic…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
