<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Punishment for gay people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/589777/donald-trump-ralph-dollinger-coronavirus-bible-study-minister/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE minister who hosts a weekly bible study for President Donald Trump’s cabinet members has appeared to place blame for the coronavirus on gays and environmentalism. Ralph Drollinger, a former bas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires want people back to work, but employees not so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/coronavirus-billionaires-want-people-back-to-work-but-their-employees-arent-so</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (BLOOMBERG) - The billionaire Tom Golisano was smoking a Padron cigar on his patio in Florida on Tuesday afternoon (March 24). He was worried.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CABINET BIBLE TEACHER BLAMES PANDEMIC ON GOD'S WRATH...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/03/24/trump-cabinet-bible-studies-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ralph Drollinger argues the coronavirus is an act of God’s judgment. His Bible studies are attended by Mike Pompeo, Ben Carson, Betsy DeVos, and Alex Azar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Daily presidential tracking polls...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE CHARLES TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11216131/prince-charles-positive-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCES Charles, 71, has tested positive for coronavirus, Clarence House announced today. The future king had been displaying mild symptoms but remains in “good health” after being diag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prince-charles-tests-positive-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Charles has caught the coronavirus. Now courtiers are desperately hoping he wasn’t contagious when he last met the Queen on March 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First US child to die from virus diagnosed after death, 'didn't meet test criteria'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/585672/first-us-minor-not-meet-criteria-coronavirus-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE FIRST US child to succumb to coronavirus was only diagnosed with the deadly infection after he died as he did not “meet the criteria” for the test, the Sun has learned.  Lancaster, Los Angeles,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORGUES NEAR CAPACITY</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/25/dhs-briefing-nyc-morgues-near-capacity-148259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials were told that morgues in the city are expected to reach capacity next week, per the briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Londoners spooked after mystery air raid siren goes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/coronavirus-mystery-air-raid-siren-217519 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Licked Products at WALMART Charged with Terror Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/man-who-licked-products-at-walmart-charged-with-making-terrorist-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri man asked, 'Who's afraid of the coronavirus?' before licking various items on Walmart shelf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF DIGITAL DOLLAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/cashless-society-democrats-propose-digital-dollar-run-by-the-fed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New World Order using coronavirus to wage war on cash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gingrich trapped in Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/newt-gingrich-trapped-in-quarantine-in-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker Newt Gingrich and his wife have been in quarantine in Italy due to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man faces terror charges after coughing on grocery store worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-faces-terror-charges-after-coughing-on-grocery-store-worker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey man the governor described as a "knucklehead" faces multiple charges after he allegedly coughed on a grocery store worker and then claimed to have coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How govt can track social media posts to enforce quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/governments-could-track-covid-19-lockdowns-through-social-media-posts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A research group scrapes more than 500,000 Instagram profiles in Italy to see if people are abiding by the quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC COULD CLOSE STREETS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-new-york-city-weighs-closing-parks-playgrounds-and-streets-to-enforce-social-distancing-gov-cuomo-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor: Virus Of Demonic Origin...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/03/23/westmoreland-co-pastor-holds-services-amid-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Westmoreland County pastor held church services over the weekend as the coronavirus continues to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers to vote on 4th, 5th spending bill to fix 'mistakes'...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/lawmakers-ready-vote-4th-and-5th-coronavirus-stimulus-package-fix-mistakes-2t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We know this bill is going to be very good. It’s going to be over $2 trillion but it’s not going to be enough. We will have missed some people in certain places," Rep. Beyer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas, devastated by '08 economic crash, struggles with shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-gazette.com/news/nation-world/las-vegas-devastated-by-the-economic-crash-struggles-with-coronavirus/article_135623cc-b684-58dc-9167-e5c944b20ef2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS — It was just two weeks ago that Las Vegas native Carlos Rosales Jr. told his cousin that business at his new barbershop was doing so well that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 1940, Republicans Picked Candidate Who Hadn't Won Single Primary!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/03/could-a-draft-cuomo-movement-be-in-the-democrats-future/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not out of the question if Biden keeps looking out of touch and irrelevant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide hotline calls soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241493126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore says app can slow spread of coronavirus; Critics say it's govt surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/singapore-says-its-app-can-slow-spread-of-coronavirus-critics/article_6958f2b4-6a06-5813-b245-49629f642c3d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE — One of the most effective ways authorities can limit the spread of a pandemic is to immediately locate, test and isolate anyone who has had contact with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Thousands of inmates released as jails face coronavirus threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Thousands-of-inmates-released-as-jails-face-15155940.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid fears that the coronavirus will carve a deadly path through prisons and jails, counties and states are releasing thousands of inmates - New Jersey alone began freeing hundreds of people this week - and the federal prison system is coming under intense pressure to take similar measures.  Public health and corrections officials have issued dire warnings that cramped and unsanitary conditions could turn prisons into a haven for the virus, endangering not just inmates but also corrections officers and prison health-care workers as well as their families and communities.  Criminal-justice reform advocates from across the political spectrum urged President Donald Trump on Tuesday to use his clemency power to commute the sentences of inmates eligible for "compassionate release" and others who could be at risk, particularly the elderly and those with underlying medical conditions.  "This is a real disaster waiting to happen," David Patton, the executive director of he nonprofit Federal Defenders of New York, said Sunday, the day after the first federal inmate tested positive at the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn. "These are places that are particularly susceptible to contagion."  Inside a county jail in Alabama on Friday, two inmates threatened to commit suicide if newly arrived Immigration and Customs Enforcement detainees they feared had been exposed to the virus were not removed. According to video live-streamed on an inmate's Facebook page, the two detainees stood on a ledge over a common area, nooses fashioned from sheets wrapped around their necks, and threatened to jump.  "We're not having no more people come in here with that symptom," another inmate says in the video, which was obtained by The Washington Post. "We're not trying to put no more lives at risk."  The three new detainees had described being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus bill prevents Trump and  family from benefiting from loan programs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Stimulus-bill-prevents-Trump-and-his-family-from-15155772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Businesses controlled by President Donald Trump and his children would be prohibited from receiving loans or investments from Treasury Department programs included in a $2 trillion stimulus plan agreed to early Wednesday by White House and Senate leaders in response to the coronavirus crisis.  The provision, which was touted by Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., in an early-morning letter to colleagues, would also apply to Vice President Mike Pence, members of Congress and heads of federal departments, as well as their children, spouses and in-laws.  During a television interview Wednesday morning, Schumer stressed that the provision applies not only to Trump but to "any major figure in government."  "That makes sense. Those of us who write the law shouldn't benefit from the law," Schumer said on CNN.  The Senate plans to vote later Wednesday on the massive package, which aims to flood the economy with capital by sending $1,200 checks to many Americans, creating a $367 billion loan program for small businesses and setting up a $500 billion fund for industries, cities and states. The House is expected to act in coming days.  Trump's dual roles as both chief executive of the nation and owner of a sprawling business empire has been frequently criticized by Democrats, who accuse him of trying to profit from the presidency.  Representatives of the Trump Organization did not immediately respond to a request for comment Wednesday morning.  The Washington Post reported this week that Trump's private business has shut down six of its top seven revenue-producing clubs and hotels because of restrictions meant to slow the spread of the novel coronavirus, potentially depriving his company of millions of dollars in revenue.  So far, the Trump Organization - which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body count leaps...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/spain-reports-deadliest-day-of-outbreak-as-virus-crisis-deepens/article_03dc9cb8-17cc-594d-9c31-78dd56be2bf5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain reported another 738 deaths from the coronavirus on Wednesday, the deadliest day in the country to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will California look like Italy soon?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-crisis-look-italys-140024299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 2,600 cases of coronavirus infection have been confirmed in California and 55 people have died of COVID-19. Will the state be the next Italy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus hospital bills: A look at the costs...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/coronavirus-hospital-bills-cost-142902046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the Kaiser Family Foundation estimated that the total cost of coronavirus treatment in a hospital could top $20,000 when factoring in out-of-pocket costs and insurance coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are collapsing': Virus pummels medics in Spain and Italy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ec91dc45d8d7c2ea86b0a97446a303a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — By the time Patricia Núñez’s cough started, she was already familiar with the dreaded dry hacking sound tormenting patients who had for weeks been filling the Madrid emergency ward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile phone industry explores worldwide tracking of users...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/25/mobile-phone-industry-explores-worldwide-tracking-of-users-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talks about global data-sharing to counter coronavirus will raise privacy concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice from Mexico's president: 'Live life as usual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/25/coronavirus-advice-from-mexicos-president-live-life-as-usual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;López Obrador’s nonchalance and resistance to tough action in face of pandemic draws barrage of criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans rush to make online wills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-pandemic-triggers-rush-by-americans-to-make-online-wills.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With COVID-19 impacting more and more Americans, individuals across the country are scrambling to set up wills and end-of-life directives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNANKE: Disruptions 'closer to major snowstorm' than Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/bernanke-says-this-is-much-closer-to-a-natural-disaster-than-the-great-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If we don't get the public health right," no Fed monetary policy or Washington fiscal package is going to work, Bernanke added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complaining, inertia are seeds of the devil, pope says...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholic-sf.org/news/complaining-inertia-are-seeds-of-the-devil-pope-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholic-sf.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY -- Many Christians are caught in a trap of complaining about everything and doing nothing about it, Pope Francis said in his morning Mass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARCETTI: Water, power will be shut off for businesses that don't close...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/coronavirus/mayor-garcetti-expected-to-hold-daily-briefing-on-l-a-s-covid-19-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti opened his daily briefing Tuesday recognizing what may have been the first teenage COVID-19 death in L.A. County and went on to announce actions against nonessential…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Cuomo Walk Away From Brokered Convention With Dem Nomination?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/24/andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-brokered-convention-democratic-nominee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unexpected global pandemic could give New York Governor Andrew Cuomo what he wants most: a Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Hundreds Of CEOs Resign Just Before World Started Going Crazy?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/why-did-hundreds-of-ceos-resign-just-before-the-world-started-going-absolutely-crazy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months prior to the most ferocious stock market crash in history and the eruption of the biggest public health crisis of our generation, we witnessed the biggest exodus of corporate CEOs that we have ever seen.  And as you will see below, corporate insiders also sold off billions of dollars w</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of locusts cover streets in Oman with footage showing 'ground moving'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/millions-locusts-cover-streets-oman-21751908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating locust swarms continue to wreak havoc across east Africa and the Middle East in scenes described as "apocalyptic"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment claims could spike to 3.4 million...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/489300-unemployment-claims-could-spike-to-34-million-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly initial unemployment claims are on track to spike to a historic 3.4 million for the third week of March, according to an analysis by the left-leaning Economic Policy Institute (EPI).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick nurse kills self over fear of infecting others...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/25/italian-nurse-with-coronavirus-kills-herself-amid-fears-of-infecting-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniela Trezzi had been suffering “heavy stress” amid fears she was spreading coronavirus while working at the San Gerardo Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makeshift morgue outside hospital...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/24/makeshift-morgue-for-coronavirus-victims-set-up-outside-nyc-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two refrigerated trailers were trucked to the site at 30th Street and the FDR Drive, along with a customized RV labeled “MOBILE COMMAND CENTER — MEDICAL EXAMINER.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ally resigns as speaker of Israel parliament...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-ally-resigns-speaker-israel-parliament-112154165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's parliamentary speaker, an ally of Benjamin Netanyahu, resigned Wednesday, clearing the way for a vote that could see him replaced by an opponent of the embattled premier. Yuli Edelstein, a member of Netanyahu's right-wing Likud party, had refused to schedule a speakership vote until</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life under lockdown ups precarity for France's prostitutes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/life-under-lockdown-ups-precarity-frances-prostitutes-105514794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their health in jeopardy and customers evaporating, sex workers in France are struggling as the novel coronavirus threatens their livelihoods -- and there is no safety net in sight. France has been in lockdown for a week, with only essential trips outside allowed, in a bid to halt the acceleration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout revives talk of 'universal basic income'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-fallout-revives-talk-universal-basic-income-082539735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scoffed-at idea of paying everyone a basic income as machines take people's jobs is getting a fresh look as a possible remedy for economies cratered by the coronavirus pandemic. Aspiring Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang argued for it on the campaign trail, even as his opponents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner hands, bluer skies: What has coronavirus done for us?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cleaner-hands-bluer-skies-coronavirus-done-us-100533027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths, economic meltdown and a planet on lockdown: the coronavirus pandemic has brought us waves of bad news, but squint and you might just see a few bright spots. From better hygiene that has reduced other infectious diseases to people reaching out as they self-isolate, here are some slivers of silver</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bali's 'Day of Silence' even quieter than usual...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/balis-day-silence-hit-virus-fears-050654815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bali (Indonésie) (AFP) - Bali's "Day of Silence" was even quieter than usual this year as coronavirus fears prompted authorities to scale back an annual celebration that sees the Hindu-majority island in Indonesia come to a near standstill. Known as Nyepi, the festival calls on locals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST BAILOUT IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edd230801c0e181169915e67b1fd64c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House and Senate leaders of both parties announced agreement early Wednesday on an unprecedented $2 trillion emergency bill to rush sweeping aid to businesses, workers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of America and sacrifice: Is country ready to step up?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db49c4310a37161661b3d3f86a861e4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For most Americans alive today, the idea of shared national sacrifice is a collective abstraction, a memory handed down from a grandparent or passed on through a book or movie....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in WWII references, but is it merited?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/495f72d25c62c1fa455a622b643bd7a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — In the first week of June 2019, World War II was on many people's minds. It was the 75th anniversary of D-Day, a week filled with events honoring the sacrifice and blood of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's body count leaps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00cfd8fb188c237ee4e75031fcd85638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — The coronavirus outbreak hit home Wednesday among the well-born and the desperately poor alike as Britain's Prince Charles tested positive and India's 1.3 billion people, or nearly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>160-year-old Vatican newspaper succumbs to coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavius-vatican-newspaper/160-year-old-vatican-newspaper-succumbs-to-coronavirus-idUSKBN21C199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican daily L'Osservatore Romano, which Pope Francis has jokingly cal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who intentionally spread could be charged as terrorists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/24/coronavirus-terrorism-justice-department-147821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department offers guidance on how to deal with “purposeful exposure and infection of others.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress? Fear of COVID-19? Therapists treating vulnerable go online to help...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325104355-g6rxp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/COUNSELLING:Stress? Fear of COVID-19? Therapists treating the vulnerable go online to help</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn off microwave to boost wifi, says media regulator...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325100548-6dya8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-BROADBAND:Turn off the microwave to boost wifi, says UK's media regulator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On road through pandemic, truckers fear for lives...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325092335-y5hof</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRUCKERS (PIX):On the road through a pandemic, some truckers fear for their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese students fleeing virus-hit U.S. pay $20,000 for seats on private jets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325063102-go9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHINA-STUDENTS (PIX):Chinese students fleeing virus-hit U.S. pay $20,000 for seats on private jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Icelanders skip the hot springs for ice baths...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/icelanders-skip-hot-springs-ice-baths-042840206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using slow, deliberate movements and deep breathing, bathers immerse themselves in the waters of an ice-covered lake in southwestern Iceland. While others might opt for the soothing hot springs for which the country is famous, this hardy group prefers an ice bath, all in the name of wellness. The temperature</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired Americans Send Unemployment Websites Crashing Down...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fired-americans-send-unemployment-websites-105208498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been three weeks since Aaron Garza lost his job as a parts specialist at a Toyota dealership in Grand Rapids, Michigan. When he was dismissed, he joined a tidal wave of unemployed people swamping systems to help them and straining state finances to the breaking point.On Monday, Garza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST BAILOUT IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db4a954801ab08b492aedddfcf7132c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House and Senate leaders of both parties announced agreement early Wednesday on unprecedented emergency legislation to rush sweeping aid to businesses, workers and a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus spreads to at least 6 AMAZON warehouses...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/586612/six-amazon-warehouses-have-coronavirus/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORKERS from at least six different Amazon warehouses have tested positive for Covid-19, according to various local reports. The developments come after the company announced that it’s lookin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul: Why I didn't quarantine after getting tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/todaysdebate/2020/03/24/rand-paul-why-no-quarantine-after-getting-tested-editorials-debates/2912183001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul: Guidelines would not have called for me to get tested nor quarantined. It was my extra precaution, out of concern for my damaged lung.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries Are Starting to Hoard Food, Threatening Global Trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/countries-are-starting-to-hoard-food-threatening-global-trade/ar-BB11EY3M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink eye could be early symptom...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241463776.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Gov. derides those 'bringing the virus' from hot zone... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Gov-DeSantis-derides-those-bringing-the-virus-15154853.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. - Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, a Republican, spent Tuesday amplifying his order requiring fliers from the New York area to self-isolate for two weeks upon arrival in the Sunshine State, arguing that travelers from coronavirus hot zones would "seed" the illness here.  DeSantis said he discussed his approach with the Trump administration, which on Tuesday instructed every person who recently left the New York City area to self-quarantine for 14 days as a way to help halt the growing outbreak.  The executive order in Florida, released Monday, specifies travelers from New York, New Jersey and Connecticut, which all are contending with large outbreaks of the potentially deadly disease. DeSantis' order applies to people who enter Florida by airplane, but it does not apply to other modes of transportation - such as those who enter the state driving southbound on Interstate 95.  The restriction comes as DeSantis has been criticized for resisting calls for a stay-at-home order, something he said would wreck economies in parts of the state that haven't had a single confirmed coronavirus case. Nearly 1,500 Floridians have confirmed cases of coronavirus, and 20 have died. DeSantis has placed himself squarely in the group of political leaders who have questioned whether the most stringent efforts to stem the spread of coronavirus should be tempered before they inflict too much economic damage.  "You simply cannot lock down our society with no end in sight,'' he said at a news conference from the governor's office Monday night. He added that an enduring solution can't be "stay in your house for nine months. That's just not going to work."  DeSantis on Tuesday called for additional restrictions for people coming from New York, directing anyone who had traveled to Florida from that area in the past three weeks to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One patient could infect up to 59,000 others?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8149149/Expert-describes-one-coronavirus-patient-infect-59-000-others.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Hugh Montgomery, a professor of intensive care medicine at University College London, explained how the 'very infectious' virus could be passed from one person to thousands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 People In homeless shelters test positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/24/coronavirus-in-ny-30-people-in-homeless-shelters-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of homeless individuals in New York City’s crammed shelter system infected with the coronavirus exploded to 30 from just a single case reported last week – with one being referred from t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' warns terrorists may exploit pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/homeland-security-warns-terrorists-exploit-covid-19-pandemic/story?id=69770582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intelligence bulletin sent to law enforcement around the country warns that domestic and homegrown terrorists may try to exploit the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel offers luxury quarantine package including test... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/swiss-hotel-offers-luxury-quarantine-package-including-500-coronavirus-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus pandemic continues to surge around the world, the hospitality industry has all but shut down. Airlines are cutting flights. Governments are telling citizens to stay home. So, to secure reservations in this unprecedented climate, some hoteliers have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy May Set Heavier Fines for Lockdown Violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/italy-may-set-heavier-fines-for-coronavirus-lockdown-violations/ar-BB11D4NI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service Bankrupt By Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241470831.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Has Over 200 Coronavirus Cases, Thousands More Out Sick...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/news/de-blasio-says-nyc-doesnt-have-enough-equipment-for-2-weeks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio said Tuesday afternoon that the current amount of medical equipment in New York City is unlikely to be enough to get the city through the next two weeks of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of the world under virus lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-lockdown-warns-pandemic-accelerating-051357601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global giant India joined the countries ordering their citizens to stay at home Tuesday, putting a third of the world on lockdown as the coronavirus epidemic forced Japan to postpone the Olympics. Despite warnings from the United States and Europe that the unprecedented shutdown is pushing the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRLINES BEG FOR RESCUE </title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200324214236-79shj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AIRLINES-IATA (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Airlines beg for rescue as coronavirus hit soars to $250 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs call curfews in Rio favelas...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200324211101-ie7qp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL-FAVELAS (FEATURE, PIX):FEATURE-Gangs call curfews as coronavirus hits Rio favelas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC OUTLOOK DARKENS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200324194117-4o3pw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 7-New York's virus outlook darkens, even as Trump pushes to reopen economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Cuomo clash over federal response...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200324190108-cbc7g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TRUMP-CUOMO:Trump, New York's Cuomo clash over federal response to virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CALLS FOR 250,000 VOLUNTEERS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200324171818-o0avb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-UK calls for 250,000 volunteers as virus deaths surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors reject President's timeline...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/77fb69858ec3e1f13eccacdf6ef55ce9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Governors across the nation on Tuesday rejected President Donald Trump's new accelerated timeline for reopening the U.S. economy, as they continued to impose more restrictions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin dons hazmat suit as Moscow says outbreak worse than it looks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-dons-hazmat-suit-moscow-161407964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin donned a hazmat suit and respirator on Tuesday during a visit to a hospital treating coronavirus patients and the mayor of Moscow said the outbreak in the Russian capital was much worse than official figures showed. The comments, by Moscow Mayor Sergei Sobyanin, marked the strongest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside besieged ERs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b08afe589e0d6dae9469c8211157199c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A “cacophony of coughing” in packed emergency rooms. Beds squeezed in wherever there is space. Overworked, sleep-deprived doctors and nurses rationed to one face mask a day and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus briefings the new campaign rallies for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/969eafc8f5cb01e9b3e8fe941b3264eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has a new daily ritual now that a pandemic has put the kibosh on the signature campaign rallies that got him elected four years ago: the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS BEST DAY SINCE 1933</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44594c5f80e50524cd6325c00a2da0bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Dow Jones Industrial Average surged to its best day since 1933 as Congress and the White House neared a deal on Tuesday to inject nearly $2 trillion of aid into an economy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Facing Existential Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/03/post-pandemic-future-hollywood/608620/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The industry is confronting a grim future: What if theaters stay dark all year? What if people are too afraid to go back when cinemas reopen?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaped inmates previously held in same unit as COVID-19 inmate...</title>
      <link>https://www.inforum.com/news/crime-and-courts/5013436-Escaped-South-Dakota-inmates-previously-held-in-same-unit-as-COVID-19-inmate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inforum.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is currently looking at the situation regarding the eight escaped inmates to see if they had close proximity to the inmate who tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Dead Kid in America...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/24/california-child-dies-of-coronavirus-believed-to-be-first-kid-fatality-in-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child has died of the coronavirus in California, authorities said Tuesday — the first apparent fatality of someone under age 18 in the country. “A devastating reminder that COVID-19 in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gives Birth In Toilet Paper Section Of WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/03/24/oh-my-gosh-firefighters-help-woman-give-birth-toilet-paper-aisle-walmart-store/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers cheered after a woman gave birth in the toilet paper aisle of a Walmart store in Springfield, Missouri, last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service commission to propose women sign up for draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/24/service-commission-propose-women-sign-draft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A congressional commission is recommending that women should be required to sign up for the U.S. military draft for the first time ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAGTIME' playwright Terrence McNally dies from coronavirus complications...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2020/03/24/terrence-mcnally-dies-coronavirus-complications-playwright-81/2909972001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrence McNally, a four-time Tony Award-winning playwright, has died from complications due to coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns of 'Suicides By the Thousands'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-warns-of-suicides-by-the-thousands-if-u-s-descends-into-recession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump claimed there could be mass suicides throughout America if the economy doesn't go back to normal in the midst of the ongoing coronavirus pandemic. In his town hall intervie</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Begs for Bailout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/analysis/journalism-stimulus.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERDUE Workers Walk Out Over Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/03/24/this-not-game-food-plant-workers-walk-out-over-coronavirus-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 50 workers at the Perdue Farms plant in Kathleen, Georgia, walked off the job Monday morning, saying they don't feel safe working there during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With isolation, abuse activists fear 'explosive cocktail'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b9b15a1215611f69f02f4388100266d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Safer at Home.” It's a slogan of choice for the mandatory confinement measures aimed at curbing the spread of the coronavirus. But it's not true for everyone. As the world's families hunker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Dead Kid in America...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/health/coronavirus-socal-update-la-county-death-toll-rises-to-11/6045011/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus pandemic grows, health officials continue to monitor the number of confirmed cases in Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Newspapers cut staff, suspend print editions...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/business/career-workplace/2020/03/23/Newspapers-cuts-layoffs-print-editions-COVID-19-advertising-revenues/stories/202003230103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mammal study explains 'why females live longer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-52007780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across wild mammal species, females live over 18% longer than males because of genetics and environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK &amp; THE CITY: Photos Show Life In NYC During Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/photo-galleries/2020/03/24/life-in-new-york-city-under-the-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Social distancing" was an unknown term before the COVID-19 coronavirus led to an unprecedented shut down of New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working From Home? Turn off AMAZON Alexa, Lawyers Warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/working-from-home-switch-off-amazons-alexa-say-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the byproducts of doing all your work from home is that you might be discussing confidential matters. And who might overhear them? Well, there's your smart speakers....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Sheriff orders gun stores to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/la-county-sheriff-orders-gun-stores-to-close-adds-1300-deputies-to-patrol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a sit-down interview with FOX 11, Los Angeles County Sheriff Alex Villanueva declared gun stores as nonessential businesses that will be forced to close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American resurrection? Trump calls for reopening by Easter...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-coronavirus-restrictions-c3da2d28-b761-4b62-b6d6-734c059c6dba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health officials warn that easing social distancing restrictions could cause cases to skyrocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon sees crisis lasting months...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-sees-coronavirus-crisis-lasting-several-months-173422675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is assuming the coronavirus epidemic in the United States will last at least several months, and that some countries are at risk of "political chaos," its top officials said Tuesday. "I think we need to plan for this to be a few months long at least," US Defense Secretary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantined senators may show up in 'hazmat-like protective gear'  for bailout vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020/03/democrats-and-schumer-surrendering-on-senate-coronavirus-stimulus-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They couldn't take the heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Go home rats!' Furious locals in rural towns fight back... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8146283/Angry-locals-St-Ives-Cornwall-scrawl-messages-beach-second-home-owners-remain-defiant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Londoners and people living in big cities all over the UK are flocking to the seaside and their second homes to escape the virus, drawing the ire of locals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy toilet problem costs $400k a flush...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/amp/news/articles/2020-03-24/unclogging-toilets-at-400-000-a-flush-among-navy-cost-overruns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC closes businesses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/489216-dc-to-close-nonessential-businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., will order the closure of all nonessential businesses as the city ramps up its fight against the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC testing decision to haunt nation for months to come...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/cdc-coronavirus-testing-decision-likely-to-haunt-nation-for-months-to-come/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention gave huge cities roughly the same number of test kits as some rural spots, which crippled efforts by health officials to contain the virus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
