<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Birds that blush: scientists document mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/birds-blush-scientists-document-animal-mystery-204957548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you ever heard of macaws that blush, much like humans do at an emotional moment? Researchers still don't quite understand how it works, but a French team says they have observed the phenomenon multiple times in a group of five captive blue-and-yellow macaws (Ara ararauna) macaws. Blue-and-yellow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGHT IN TEX: BETO HEATING UP!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/first-read/poll-democrat-o-rourke-trails-ted-cruz-just-four-percentage-n902946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke has 45 percent support among registered voters compared with Cruz’s 49 percent; Abbott leads governors' contest by 19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY SAYS FAITH IN JUSTICE 'CONFIRMED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/romney-manafort-and-cohens-conduct-dishonorable-and-illegal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitt Romney condemned the conduct of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort and the president’s former lawyer Michael Cohen after they were found guilty of multiple federal crimes Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm beats humans sniffing out 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.futurity.org/fake-news-detecting-algorithm-1844942/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.futurity.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flood of fake news can overwhelm human editors and trick readers, but a new algorithm may help fight bunk stories. Here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGahn 'Not Consulted' About Hush-Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/2018/08/22/mcgahn-is-said-not-to-have-known-of-trump-s-hush-money-payments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Didn’t Consult McGahn About Hush-Money Payments, Source Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia stockpiling gold as shield from sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/22/news/economy/russia-gold-us-sanctions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian central bank has beefed up its holdings of gold at a time when Moscow's relationship with Washington remains tense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saga of early humans etched in DNA of mixed-species child...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saga-early-humans-etched-dna-mixed-species-child-170051899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicknamed by Oxford University scientists, Denisova 11 -- her official name -- was at least 13 when she died, for reasons unknown. "There was earlier evidence of interbreeding between different hominin, or early human, groups," said lead author Vivian Slon, a researcher at the Max Planck Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Lawyers Up...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/leslie-moonves-daniel-petrocelli-lawyer-sexual-misconduct-1202914215/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS Corp. chairman-CEO Leslie Moonves has hired powerhouse litigator Daniel Petrocelli to represent him in CBS’ internal probe into sexual misconduct allegations reported late last month by t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLTS' announcer retired after using racial slur in retelling story...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9271f613fb8d4750a58186a60c840b9e/Colts'-longtime-announcer-retired-after-using-racial-slur</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — An off-the-air racial slur prompted the immediate retirement of longtime Indianapolis Colts' radio voice Bob Lamey last weekend, team officials and Lamey's att</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS chief tells followers to persevere in rare speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/islamic-state-chief-rare-speech-urges-followers-persevere-192453436.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Islamic state leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, in his first purported speech in nearly a year, has called on followers to persevere, according to a statement posted on the group's media outlet. "For the Mujahideen (holy warriors) the scale of victory or defeat is not dependant on a city or town</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. prosecutors reviewing new Spacey sex assault case...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/l-prosecutors-reviewing-sex-assault-case-involving-kevin-192000068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles prosecutors said on Wednesday they were reviewing a sexual assault case involving actor Kevin Spacey. "A sex assault case was presented yesterday to our office by the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department involving Kevin Spacey. It remains under review," Los Angeles District</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest attacked by man yelling, 'For all the little kids'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/22/us/indiana-priest-beaten-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Catholic priest was beaten while praying at his church in Merrillville, Indiana, and authorities are investigating the attack as a hate crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl, 2, undergoes pioneering surgery to shrink head...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/22/girl-2-undergoes-pioneering-surgery-in-bid-to-shrink-head-7872526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maryam has had eight, four-hour operations over the year with doctors draining at least 500ml of fluid each time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Posing As Deputy Helps Boyfriend Escape County Jail...</title>
      <link>https://5newsonline.com/2018/08/21/fayetteville-woman-posing-as-deputy-helps-boyfriend-escape-county-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;5newsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAYETTEVILLE (KFSM) — The sheriff's office has arrested a Fayetteville woman who helped her boyfriend escape from the county jail last month by posing as a deputy from California.  Maxine Feldstein, 30, was arrested Friday (Aug. 17) in connection with forgery, accomplice to third-degree escape and criminal impersonation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-conscious China appoints new global propaganda czar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b96f5daa1f764c92a6ca0fbf6f785bb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's increasingly image-conscious government has appointed a trusted member of the ruling Communist Party to head up its international propaganda operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium knife attack: 1 dead, several wounded in restaurant horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1007029/Belgium-news-herve-knife-attack-wallonia-plombieres-police-latest-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN has died and several others have been injured after a stabbing in a restaurant in Belgium, according to a witness, as helicopters and ambulances scramble to the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lithgow to Play Roger Ailes in FOXNEWS Movie...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/john-lithgow-fox-news-movie-chief-roger-ailes-1202913585/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Lithgow will play Roger Ailes, the Fox News chief who masterfully exploited the country’s political divisions to rise to the top of the cable news heap, in Annapurna’s upcoming drama abo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  'LATER ON I KNEW' ABOUT PAYMENTS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/22/trump-cohen-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Its not even a campaign violation'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  'LATER ON I KNEW' ABOUT PAYMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/foxandfriends/status/1032319321920430080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“EXCLUSIVE: President @realDonaldTrump on if he knew about the Cohen payments. See more from his interview with @ainsleyearhardt tomorrow 6-9amET. https://t.co/HPJPslOG6X”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancels appearance...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6086009/Asia-Argento-admits-DID-sex-17-year-old-Jimmy-Bennett-texts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asia Argento allegedly sent the texts to a friend after the New York Times printed claims that she paid Bennett $380,000 to keep quiet over a tryst in a California hotel room when he was just 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters say VERIZON 'throttled' data, crippling communications during CA wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article217133835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Clara County’s fire agency, in a legal filing over net neutrality, blasted internet service provider Verizon for crippling its communications during the Mendocino Complex Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Called To Testify In Congress...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/403040-cummings-calls-for-oversight-hearing-with-cohen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Elijah Cummings (D-Md.) is calling for a House Oversight Committee hearing with Michael Cohen, who implicated the president in his guilty plea to campaign finance violations on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC calls FBI after detecting attempt to hack voter database...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/22/politics/democratic-national-committee-voter-database/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee contacted the FBI on Tuesday after it detected what it believes was the beginning of a sophisticated attempt to hack into its voter database, a Democratic source tells CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Law Chief Urges More Criminals To Become Magistrates For 'Diversity'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/people-with-criminal-records-urged-to-become-magistrates-11479016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bache says barring "anyone who's ever done anything wrong" is "no way at all to increase diversity".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arlington National Cemetery evacuated after bomb threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbaltv.com/article/arlington-national-cemetery-evacuated-after-bomb-threat/22800585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbaltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arlington National Cemetery has been evacuated Wednesday morning because of a bomb threat, WBAL-TV's sister station WRC in Washington is reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeQueer as LGBT community cries #MeToo...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180822155624-xap18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence against LGBT people is still</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Backed Candidate Loses in Wyoming Gov Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2018-08-22/wyoming-rebuffs-trump-picks-native-son-in-gop-governor-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once rallying cry, Obamacare suddenly sticky campaign issue for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.postbulletin.com/news/politics/once-their-rallying-cry-obamacare-is-suddenly-a-sticky-campaign/article_5d0d383e-36dd-5ffd-a87b-5fdbef5c9fb7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — For the first time in nearly a decade, Republicans are heading into a national election divided and defensive over health care, the very issue that once propelled them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how many bills it took to buy a chicken in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/slideshow/see-how-many-bills-it-took-buy-chicken-venezuela-n902491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once-booming nation is now suffering from Soviet-style product shortages and a mass exodus of citizens fleeing for other South American countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems worried Mueller getting fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/case-mueller-firing-break-glass-democrats-prep-emergency-plan-n902526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional action and protest rallies are among the contingencies being planned if Trump tries to shut down the Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Saudi Arabia plans to behead woman activist...</title>
      <link>http://www.theweek.co.uk/95992/saudi-arabia-plans-to-behead-female-political-activist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theweek.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights groups have condemned the decision by Saudi prosecutors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans gubernatorial nominee says she's getting death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/vermont-s-transgender-gubernatorial-candidate-getting-death-threats-n902851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christine Hallquist said she’s been getting a steady stream of death threats and other personal attacks since her candidacy began to draw national attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Tyler Demands Trump Stop Playing Aerosmith Songs at Rallies...</title>
      <link>http://variety.com/2018/politics/news/steven-tyler-aerosmith-trump-rally-song-cease-desist-1202913493/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aerosmith singer Steven Tyler is demanding President Donald Trump stop using the band’s songs at rallies, like the one held at the Charleston Civic Center in West Virginia on Tuesday (August …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVENATTI:   I WILL DEPOSE TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/porn-lawyer-avenatti-says-michael-cohens-admission-of-guilt-allows-him-to-depose-president-trump-for-questioning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort's Last Hope: Mueller or a Miracle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/manaforts-choices-work-with-mueller-wish-for-trump-pardon-or-die-in-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not over for the president’s sleazy ex-campaign boss. He’s facing life in prison before his next trial even begins. The only way out is to side with the prosecution or POTUS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audience Boos Lanny Davis Asking for Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/megyn-kelly-audience-boos-lanny-davis-for-seeking-donations-to-defend-michael-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/hnl/pages/HLS.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP...</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_31.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRIME ISN'T CRIME</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-rips-cohen-twitter-after-guilty-plea-don-t-retain-n902826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If anyone is looking for a good lawyer, I would strongly suggest that you don’t retain the services of Michael Cohen!” Trump wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Obama Campaign Fined $375,000 for Campaign Reporting Violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/flashback-remember-when-obama-campaign-was-fined-375000-for-campaign-reporting-violations-and-no-jail-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FIGHTS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-attacks-michael-cohen-says-hes-a-poor-lawyer-1534943248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump attacked Michael Cohen’s legal abilities, the morning after his former lawyer implicated him in a federal crime as he pleaded guilty to campaign-finance violations, among other charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer claims he was drugged and raped by classical music power couple...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-stasi-singer-claims-rape-classical-music-stars-20180821-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An up-and-coming baritone singer alleges he was drugged and violently raped in 2010 by two of opera/classical music’s shining stars, David Daniels and Scott Walters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FIGHTS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-lawyer-says-cohen-mueller-interest-124447137--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chazelle Shoots the Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/damien-chazelle-shoots-moon-oscar-s-youngest-best-director-grows-up-first-man-1136395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 18 months after the epic flub at the Academy Awards, the ‘La La Land' filmmaker returns with a Neil Armstrong drama and invites The Hollywood Reporter into the editing room to talk launching Ryan Gosling into space ("You're shocked by how much can go wrong"), managing his social anxiety (and a secret marriage) and that night the Oscars veered waaaay off course ("All of us are still processing it").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREAD: Asian Tick Befuddling Lyme Disease Experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-asian-tick-befuddling-lyme-disease-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We don’t yet know how the long-horned tick came to the United States, how it’s spreading, or what it’s capable of doing. All we know is that it’s here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Saudi Arabia plans to behead woman activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-plans-behead-woman-13119933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights groups have branded the provisional death sentence given to Israa al-Ghomgham, 29, 'monstrous'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: MCCLATCHY Newspapers Lay Off Staff in Cost-Cutting Move...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mcclatchy-newspapers-lay-off-nearly-4-percent-staff-cost-cutting-move/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"While these actions are necessary to protect and further our future, they are painful and difficult decisions," says McClatchy CEO Craig Forman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese State TV Mocks Trump in Sarcastic Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2160814/thanks-mr-trump-state-media-mocks-us-president-helping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broadcaster’s English-language video lists all the ways Donald Trump’s trade war has helped China improve itself</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi says internet must be 'clean and righteous'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180822124200-xk8b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-POLITICS/:China's Xi says internet must be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE will now filter out negative news and tell you 'something good' instead...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/22/because-everythings-so-bad-google-will-now-filter-out-negative-news-7870518/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Google Assistant has a new feature where it will only tell you positive news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgy Dome banned?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6085155/Burning-Man-grapples-consent-amid-MeToo-movement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Nevada festival is known for music, art, and plenty of sexual liberation. But it must now work to teach Burners that a free spirit on the infamous playa doesn't mean a free for all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would not accept pardon...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/402972-attorney-cohen-would-not-accept-a-pardon-from-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lanny Davis, an attorney representing Michael Cohen, said Wednesday that Cohen "would never accept" a pardon from President Trump after pleading guilty in Manhattan court to tax fraud and campaign finance law violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malibu residents fear serial attacker stalking scenic enclave...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/22/malibu-fears-serial-attacker-random-shootings-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious shootings have shocked an outpost of LA better known for its idyllic lifestyle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking pot ages brain 2.8 YEARS...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6086073/Smoking-cannabis-ages-brain-average-2-8-YEARS.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Amen Clinics, which are throughout the US, found that drinking alcohol ages a person's brain by 0.6 years. Brain ageing is defined as reduced blood flow through the organ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED reporter ejected from China...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/buzzfeed-reporter--effectively--ejected-from-china--foreign-media-10641414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Foreign Correspondents' Club of China said on Wednesday that the foreign ministry had "effectively" ejected BuzzFeed News's Beijing bureau ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant women going to Brazil to give birth...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180822110017-taart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several hundred thousand Venezuelans have fled the economic and political turmoil in their homeland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massage chain faces suit alleging it enabled sexual misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/08/21/bay-area-lawsuit-alleges-massage-envy-enabled-sex-crimes-by-employees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burlingame-based suit joins litigation surge alleging conspiracy to protect masseuses who sexually assaulted clients, including some who were later arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico opened 2,599 homicide investigations in July; Most ever in month...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-homicide-record-20180822-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year was Mexico's most violent on record, with 25,316 homicide investigations into 31,174 deaths. Killings this year are on pace to top that record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN: Plea deal is attempt to set up president...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/402959-cohens-plea-deal-is-prosecutors-attempt-to-set-up-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plot to get Donald Trump out of the White House thickens as his former lawyer turns on him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willing to tell Mueller about 'conspiracy to collude'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/21/cohen-willing-to-tell-mueller-about-conspiracy-to-collude-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen is willing to speak with Special Counsel Robert Mueller about a “conspiracy to collude” with Russia during the 2016 presidential campaign, his lawyer said on Tuesday night…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of unwanted advance divides Egyptians...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/video-unwanted-advance-divides-egyptians-072530170.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — It might have been another #MeToo moment: An Egyptian woman says a man stalked her at a bus stop, made inappropriate advances, and only backed off when she began filming him with her cellphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats gather to confront lingering 2016 frustration...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9426e9644df14629bf6acc3651af2ed0/Democrats-gather-to-confront-lingering-2016-frustration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are bullish about their prospects in the November midterms, and are peeking around the corner at a 2020 rematch with President Donald Trump. But first, they're confronting the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside catch and kill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27bb7773c8bc4d4292862057d89b5146/Inside-catch-and-kill:-Cohen,-a-porn-star-and-'Individual-1'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — His name is Donald John Trump, but federal prosecutors have a simpler moniker for the 45th president: Individual 1.        Dry legalese and generic aliase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT anti-hacking efforts make it internet cop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/191032549cca44b9b1b74e1d130a04e5/Microsoft's-anti-hacking-efforts-make-it-an-internet-cop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intentionally or not, Microsoft has emerged as a kind of internet cop by devoting considerable resources to thwarting Russian hackers.        The company's announcement Tuesday t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRAZY RICH ASIANS' Author Wanted for Draft Dodging...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/asia/crazy-rich-asians-author-kevin-kwan-wanted-draft-dodging-1202913534/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Kwan, author of the book underlying hit film “Crazy Rich Asians,” faces up to three years in jail in his native Singapore. He is accused of avoiding the country’s compulsory military service.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidency's Fate Rests With Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/22/us/politics/trump-cohen-impeachment.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOP GUN' sequel filming on Norfolk-based carrier, Navy says...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/military/local/article_23811e14-a53a-11e8-a333-73aec78d8ae9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A production crew for the much-anticipated sequel is filming F/A-18s from Virginia Beach-based Carrier Air Wing Seven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional farewells as North and South Koreans part for last time...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180822-emotional-farewells-north-south-koreans-part-last-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEGOOGLE Face Growing Revolt Over App Store 'Tax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/22/apple-and-google-face-growing-revolt-over-app-store-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple and Google Face Growing Revolt Over App Store ‘Tax’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.3 mag quake rocks west coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7073186/oregon-earthquake-portland-bandon-lates/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE 6.3-magnitude earthquake struck off the coast of Oregon on America’s west coast today. The quake, which registered 188 miles from the coastal city of Bandon, has sparked fears the so-c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flesh-eating STD causing genitals to 'rot away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/tropical-flesh-eating-sti-causes-13119783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been no previous cases of the rare sexually transmitted disease Donovanosis - until now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Backed Candidate Loses in Wyoming Gov Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/barrasso-wins-gop-senate-contest-in-wyoming-1534910398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy political donor Foster Friess lost to State Treasurer Mark Gordon in Wyoming’s Republican primary for governor, while U.S. Sen. John Barrasso fended off a well-funded challenger in his GOP primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat 5...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38890702/hurricane-watch-issued-for-hawaii-maui-counties-as-lane-nears-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hurricane warning has been issued for the Big Island as Lane barrels toward the state as a powerful Category 5 storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are all going to die': UBER driver taunted and kidnapped 3 women, they say...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article217097450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber driver Mark Filanov was arrested for kidnapping three ride-sharing passengers in June. He is being held on $375,000 bail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT FEARS HIT DC</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/21/trump-cohen-manafort-impeachment-legal-791009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conviction of Trump’s former campaign chairman, guilty plea of his former personal lawyer and indictment of a leading congressional supporter raise Trump’s risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Keep Falling Into Trump Trap; Reporters foolishly act like liberal political activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-media-keep-falling-into-the-trump-trap-1534892905</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters foolishly act like liberal political activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  What happens if Trump is impeached?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/can-donald-trump-impeached-russia-comey-scandals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen's bombshell admission that he paid hush money to two women before the 2016 election at the direction of Donald Trump has once again fulled talk of the US president being impeached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen testifies Trump told him to commit crime by paying off women...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-cohen/cohen-testifies-trump-told-him-to-commit-crime-by-paying-off-women-idUSKCN1L61PD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen testified on Tuesday that Trump had directed him to commit a crime by arranging payments ahead of the 2016 presidential election to silence two women who claimed to have had affairs with Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak: Death toll SOARS as authorities announce crisis plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/724842/ebola-outbreak-africa-democratic-republic-of-congo-warning-death-toll-vaccines-borders </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisonings from 'herbal supplement' rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/poisonings-from-kratom-sold-as-an-herbal-supplement-are-rising/article_17be5140-6951-57f5-8f99-c23fb7a3a156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — An unregulated herbal product that advocates say can relieve pain and help with opioid withdrawal has been linked to at least four deaths in the Philadelphia region, but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA forecasts asteroid bigger than pyramid for close Earth approach... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/724721/nasa-news-asteroids-2016-nf23-great-pyramid-of-giza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Blasts Big Tech, Defends 'Right of Americans to Speak Their Minds'... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/21/donald-trump-blasts-big-tech-americans-have-the-right-to-speak-their-minds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Tuesday that he would continue standing against social media censorship by companies like Facebook and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research suggests evolution favor 'survival of the laziest'...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-08-evolution-favor-survival-laziest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you've got an unemployed, 30-year-old adult child still living in the basement, fear not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champagne, private chefs and drugs: How the 1% do 'Burning Man'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/21/champagne-private-chefs-and-drugs-how-the-1-percent-do-burning-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you do when you’ve got the munchies in the middle of an unforgiving desert? If you’re an elite “Burner,” just ring for your private chef. Burning Man is an otherworldly, nine-day-long arts …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More and more hospitals close; No end in sight...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagobusiness.com/health-care/hospitals-shut-30-year-pace-us-no-end-sight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Saudi Arabia seeks death penalty for woman activist...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180821234931-vodsf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-ARRESTS/:Saudi Arabia seeks death penalty for woman activist -rights groups</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HELL HOUR</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/150816/worst-day-yet-trumps-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal trouble surrounding him just got a lot closer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News fuels partisan furor over probe...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/21/paul-manafort-michael-cohen-developments-fuel-part/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conviction of Paul Manafort and guilty plea by Michael Cohen on Tuesday fortified both the pro- and anti-Trump camps in the political war over special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURLEY: Manafort verdicts raise chances of pardon...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/402922-manafort-guilty-verdicts-raise-chances-of-pardon-by-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This obviously is not the set of crimes that special counsel Robert Mueller was appointed to pursue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: Cohen plea may spark impeachment calls, but charges unlikely...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/cohens-claim-about-trump-may-spark-calls-for-impeachment-but-is-unlikely-to-lead-to-charges/2018/08/21/4e432aec-a167-11e8-93e3-24d1703d2a7a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s former attorney said he arranged payments to Stormy Daniels and Karen McDougal “at the direction” of Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mueller Won...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-mueller/follow-the-money-how-muellers-team-made-the-manafort-case-idUSKCN1L7009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort's $15,000 ostrich skin jacket and other evidence of the former Trump campaign chairman's conspicuous consumption grabbed the headlines during his tax and bank fraud trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HELL HOUR</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trumps-ex-campaign-chief-manafort-guilty-fraud-214604655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's former campaign chief Paul Manafort was found guilty of fraud Tuesday, in the first trial resulting from the investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 presidential election. While the jury was unable to reach a verdict on 10 counts, prompting the judge to declare a partial mistrial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN SAYS VIOLATED CAMPAIGN LAW AT DIRECTION OF 'CANDIDATE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/21/michael-cohen-strikes-plea-deal-with-prosecutors-790646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement came as part of a plea deal that Cohen struck Tuesday afternoon with federal prosecutors in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT: GUILTY</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/manafort-convicted-8-counts-n901231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial was the first public test of special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into possible Russian meddling and obstruction of justice by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN:  I'M GUILTY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/michael-cohen-plea-deal-details-today-2018-08-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen testified Donald Trump himself directed him to violate the law, Cohen's attorney says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators suggest claims contradict testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/burr-and-warner-say-they-have-re-engaged-michael-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen testified before the Senate Intelligence Committee in September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT EVALUATING 'ALL OPTIONS'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e1477cd2f234270a037108cd9b0b1aa/The-Latest:-Dems:-Conviction,-plea-show-probe-not-witch-hunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. (AP) — The Latest on the Paul Manafort trial (all times local):        5:35 p.m.        Democratic Sen. Richard Blumenthal of Connecticut says the Wh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble for last-minute supplies...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38933132/shoppers-scramble-for-last-minute-supplies-as-lane-churns-toward-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents descended on grocery stores, gas stations and hardware stores Tuesday as Hurricane Lane churned toward the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROWD CHANTS 'LOCK HIM UP!'</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/402924-people-chant-lock-him-up-at-cohen-after-pleading-guilty-to-eight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen was met with "lock him up" chants outside a New York City federal courthouse on Tuesday after pleading guilty to charges of bank fraud, tax fraud and campaign finance law violations.&amp;nbsp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Pilot Killed In Iraq -- On 9th Combat Deployment...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/army-pilot-killed-iraq-9th-deployment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE puts AI in charge of keeping data centers cool...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/google-just-put-an-ai-in-charge-of-keeping-its-data-centers-cool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeepMind's neural networks will tweak data center conditions to cut power usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'TRUST RATINGS' FOR USERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7067261/facebook-trust-rating-score-check/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK is rating users based on how “trustworthy” it thinks they are. Users receive a score on a scale from zero to one that determines if they have a good or bad reputation – but it&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'K2' turns inmates into zombies, fuels historic death toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/special-reports/florida-prisons/article215642855.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Synthetic marijuana — known as K2 — heroin and other drugs are easy to get in Florida prisons. A recent spike in inmate deaths has been associated with overdoses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number Of Bugs Test Positive For 'West Nile' On Long Island...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/21/west-nile-virus-warning-suffolk-county-long-island-mosquitoes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A West Nile warning has been issued on Long Island. A record number of mosquitoes are testing positive for the virus, including more than two dozen samples in one week alone in Suffolk County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sock row causes mayhem at swinger's club masquerade ball...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/21/sock-row-sees-swingers-party-end-violence-jealous-man-accuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A masquerade ball at a swingers club ended in mayhem after a jealous man accused a fellow participant of trying to seduce his partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Unveils Radical Anti-Corruption Platform...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/21/elizabeth-warren-unveils-radical-anti-corruption-platform/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren would ban foreign lobbying, shut (or slow) the revolving door, in a series of reforms that would transform Washington's political economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Congressman Indicted On Campaign Finance Charges...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/watchdog/sd-me-hunter-indict-20180821-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Duncan Hunter, R-Alpine, and his wife, Margaret, were indicted Tuesday on charges including wire fraud and campaign finance crimes, according to a federal indictment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSUNAMI ALERT...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6084477/Buildings-evacuated-powerful-7-3-magnitude-earthquake-hits-coast-Venezuela.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful earthquake has shaken eastern Venezuela, causing buildings to be evacuated in the capital of Caracas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador to organize regional migrant crisis summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ecuador-organize-regional-venezuela-migrant-crisis-meeting-220120224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador will organize a meeting of 13 Latin American countries to discuss the Venezuelan migrant crisis, Quito's top diplomat said on Tuesday. More than two million people have fled economic collapse in Venezuela during a four-year recession, according to the United Nations, piling pressure on neighboring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us1000gez7#executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3 MAG QUAKE SHAKES VENEZUELA... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180821215949-h0f9p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-QUAKE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Magnitude 7.3 quake hits northern Venezuela coast -USGS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.0 MAG QUAKE SHAKES VENEZUELA... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/usgs-magnitude-7-0-earthquake-shakes-venezuela-buildings-214351362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USGS: Magnitude 7.0 earthquake shakes Venezuela; buildings evacuated in Caracas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal charged with murder of missing Iowa jogger...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/local/2018/08/21/mollie-tibbetts-found-dead-missing-iowa-student-search-brooklyn-update-latest-girl-facebook-reddit/1050165002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are working to identify the body found Tuesday morning, Iowa Division of Criminal Investigation Assistant Director Mitch Mortvedt said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfers shot at while riding waves at 'invite only' beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12110906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDITORIAL: Gunshots are no way to lay claim to a surfing spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Plans 40 Days on Campaign Trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/2018/08/21/trump-is-said-to-plan-40-days-on-campaign-trail-for-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Plans 40 Days on Campaign Trail for Midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA: Record Opposition To Taking More Immigrants...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/survey-shows-spike-in-opposition-to-higher-immigration-in-canada-but-too-soon-to-call-it-a-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growing opposition to accepting more immigrants includes ‘a significant segment’ of the left-of-centre base, says Shachi Kurl of the Angus Reid Institute</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
