<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Genealogy website, DNA from napkin trashed at hockey game tie suspect to 1993 murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.twincities.com/2019/02/14/minneapolis-stabbing-1993-dna-cold-case-murder-jerry-westrom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.twincities.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators followed a 52-year-old Isanti, Minn., man to a hockey game, where he ordered food from the concession stand. After he wiped his mouth with a napkin and dropped it the trash, they reco…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ginger' alligators turning heads in South Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.islandpacket.com/news/local/news-columns-blogs/untamed-lowcountry/article226203480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.islandpacket.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD internal review after officer allegedly tells cops to shoot 50 Cent 'on sight'...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/2019/02/17/nypd-doing-internal-review-after-commanding-officer-allegedly-tells-cops-to-shoot-rapper-50-cent-on-sight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD has confirmed to PIX11 News that there is an internal review into Deputy Inspector Emmanuel Gonzalez of the 72nd precinct after the New York Daily News reported the precinct commander told his officers during roll call to shoot rapper 50 Cent "on sight." The comments were allegedly made last June when the artist was "expected to attend an NYPD sanctioned boxing match" in the Bronx, according to the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 naked men hunt 'good luck' sacred sticks in dark temple...</title>
      <link>http://www.asahi.com/ajw/articles/AJ201902170014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asahi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKAYAMA--A whirlpool of near-naked men massed on a dark temple compound here on Feb. 16 as they soug</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Gulf States Commend Jared's Peace Effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/israel-gulf-states-commend-kushners-peace-effort-11550182508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Kushner said that a show of unity among Israeli and Arab officials at a U.S.-backed conference in Warsaw made him feel optimistic about prospects for peace in the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake university set up by ICE lured foreign students...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/17/emails-reveal-fake-university-lured-students/2884848002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emails obtained by the Detroit Free Press offer a glimpse into how a fake university in Detroit may have convinced students it was real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Democracy is at risk'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/pa/article-6715499/Social-media-sites-face-compulsory-ethics-code-MPs-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a major report, MPs warned that democracy is at risk from the `malicious and relentless´ targeting of citizens with disinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Louvre snubs 'Leonardo da Vinci' painting months after Saudi prince spent $500 million on it! </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6714655/Is-worlds-expensive-painting-FAKE-Louvre-snubs-Leonardo-da-Vinci-painting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Salvator Mundi broke auction records at Christie's in New York when it was bought for £342million. Doubts have been cast over the painting's authenticity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka delivers rousing speech in front of world leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6712027/Ivanka-Trump-leads-way-Munich-Security-Conference.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump is said to be working hard behind the scenes of Washington DC to implement her paid family leave initiative - and she certainly didn't shy away from the spotlight in Munich this week either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCABE 60 MINUTES OF FAME:  THE FULL INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/andrew-mccabe-60-minutes-interview-full-transcript-watch-acting-fbi-director-trump-investigation-james-comey-russia-investigation-2019-02-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former acting FBI director Andrew McCabe tells 60 Minutes about taking over for James Comey, starting investigations of President Trump, interactions with the president and his own firing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Acts Increase in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/spreading-like-a-poison-anti-semitic-acts-increase-in-france-11550433296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spate of anti-Semitic incidents has accompanied France’s yellow-vest protests in recent weeks, raising fears that the movement is stirring up hatred in the nation that is home to Europe’s largest Jewish population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAND JURY?</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/17/jussie-smollett-grand-jury-attack-brothers-trump-empire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett case will go to Grand Jury, cops say, "No Trump supporter watches Empire so MAGA doesn't make sense."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American woman who joined ISIS:  I made a big mistake!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/17/us-woman-hoda-muthana-deeply-regrets-joining-isis-and-wants-return-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Muthana is only American among 1,500 foreign women and children at a Syrian refugee camp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Northam to Smollett, Black History Month has been a total disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ralph-northam-to-jussie-smollett-how-black-history-month-2019-has-been-a-total-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe we need a do-over for this Black History Month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Bid to Conquer Oscars, NETFLIX Mobilizes Savvy Campaigner and Huge Budget... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/17/business/media/netflix-movies-oscars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Taback, who worked with Harvey Weinstein on awards campaigns for best picture winners like “The Artist” and “The King’s Speech,” is in charge of the lavish effort behind “Roma.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMDANI:  Vicious media 'boys club' trying to shut women up is as prevalent as ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/ligue-du-lol-metoo-france-media-sexism-women-britain-facebook-a8783461.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump quotes Limbaugh: Mueller investigators 'ought to be in jail'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6715021/Trump-quotes-Rush-Limbaughs-claim-Muellers-investigators-ought-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Limbaugh cited a former deputy FBI director who says there were of Justice Department discussions about removing Trump from office: 'The Mueller investigation, I believe, is a cover-up of all of that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old arrested after refusing to stand for Pledge of Allegiance...</title>
      <link>https://www.baynews9.com/fl/tampa/news/2019/02/14/mother-upset-after-son-kicked-out-of-class-over-pledge-of-allegiance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baynews9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother and student spoke to Spectrum Bay News 9</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido calls for 'million volunteers'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-guaido-calls-million-volunteers-aid-standoff-180421089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido set a goal Sunday of enlisting a million volunteers within a week to confront a government blockade that has kept tons of humanitarian aid, most of it from the United States, from flowing into the country. Guaido has given February 23 -- one month to the day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian city braces for showdown as US amasses aid on Venezuelan border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelans-send-sos-signal-colombian-border-014840253.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ureña (Venezuela) (AFP) - Desperate doctors and nurses are protesting at Venezuela's border with Colombia, demanding that President Nicolas Maduro allows in humanitarian aid that remains tantalisingly out of reach. "Right now it's a critical situation, it's terrible because we have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTHONY WEINER OUT OF PRISON...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/3162b34a724c48b6a6e913aa82add004/disgraced-ex-congressman-anthony-weiner-released-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AYER, Mass. (AP) — Disgraced former Congressman Anthony Weiner has been released from federal prison after being convicted of having illicit online contact with a 15-year-old girl in 2017.The Federal Bureau of Prisons website shows the 54-year-old New York Democrat is currently in the custody of its Residential Re-entry Management office in Brooklyn, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED:  Chicago police to re-question actor...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/jussie-smollett-attack-police-new-interview-evidence-chicago-empire-1202559282/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things may be moving towards some sort of formal prosecution in the Jussie Smollett alleged attack case but Chicago PD have definitely yet to have a new sit-down with the Empire actor as more “deve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Miller makes the case...</title>
      <link>https://video.foxnews.com/v/6003160755001/#sp=show-clips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's critics announce plans to challenge the president's bid to secure funds for his border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Police Seek Authority to Take Down Drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-police-seek-authority-to-take-down-drones-11550419320?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police officials said they are concerned that propaganda abroad showing weaponized drones can inspire terrorists to use drones for lone-wolf attacks in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Ready to Challenge Emergency Declaration...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-ready-to-challenge-trumps-emergency-declaration-11550427992?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats signaled they are gearing up to challenge President Trump’s use of his emergency powers to fund construction of a wall along the southern U.S. border, which would likely tie up implementation of one of his core campaign promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Lashed Out at Hateful Doubters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/flashback-actor-of-the-year-jussie-smollett-cries-and-lies-on-gma-lashes-out-at-hateful-doubters-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's richest man plans move to Monaco...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/britains-richest-man-plans-move-14010824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Brexiteer Sir Jim Ratcliffe, who built up the chemicals giant Ineos, has been working with the accountant PwC on the tax avoidance plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas claims Israel sent bugged shoes to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Hamas-claims-Israel-sent-bugged-shoes-to-spy-on-them-580897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shipment of suspicious shoes that came through the Kerem Shalom Crossing were sent to Hamas to examine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  ONION BLEEDS MONEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/univision-reveals-write-down-struggling-gizmodo-media-group-assets-1186776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company reported that the assets lost $32.5 million in the fourth quarter of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump erupts at 'SNL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6714353/Trump-says-Alec-Baldwins-Saturday-night-Live-parody-looked-into.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin had lampooned him on the show nine hours earlier, telling a mock press conference in his Trump voice that 'you can all see why I have to fake this national emergency.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehearsed attack?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/02/17/jussie-smollett-pals-reportedly-rehearsed-alleged-attack/?_ga=2.207625489.267642857.1550199666-2051527208.1550003555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops have said the pair of budding model-actors have a “relationship” with Smollett and worked on “Empire.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers, fashion brands struggle with racial insensitivity...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/5e7aa8fe93484c8d9d0e172736948a7a/retailers-fashion-brands-struggle-racial-insensitivity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Retailers and top fashion brands like Gucci and Prada keep apologizing for products that smack of racial insensitivity.The big question is: Why does it keep happening?Experts say many of these fashion companies live in a sort of bubble and lack the diversity in their staff that could vet their fashions. They also blame the increasing pressures facing the industry to push products from the design board to the stores and online in weeks rather than months without taking time to thoroughly review products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Call to Pressure Tehran Falls on Deaf Ears...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pences-calls-to-pressure-iran-fall-on-deaf-ears-in-europe-11550415611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European officials brushed off U.S. Vice President Mike Pence’s call for the bloc to ratchet up pressure on Iran, saying they will continue defending the 2015 nuclear deal and stay engaged with Iran’s government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toasters Toxic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/health-news/8445285/burnt-toast-more-toxic-traffic-fumes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURNT toast can expose people to more pollution than if they were standing at a busy road junction, a study has claimed. Researchers at the University of Texas at Austin found burnt toast was espec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Straight White Male Dem Run? Very Carefully...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/02/17/white-male-democrats-2020-225101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very carefully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Heckled for Native American Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/elizabeth-warren-heckled-at-campaign-stop-about-her-native-american-claims-why-did-you-lie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President tells Europe to take back ISIS fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/17/politics/donald-trump-isis-fighters-europe-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets, President Donald Trump has said European countries should take back and put on trial hundreds of ISIS fighters who have been captured in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala off to best start, say strategists, donors...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/430298-harris-off-to-best-start-among-dems-in-race-say-strategists-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris is off to the fastest start among Democrats who have already entered the 2020 presidential race, say party strategists and donors closely following the contest’s early stages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie' deer disease spreads to 24 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/02/16/zombie-deer-chronic-wasting-disease-could-affect-humans/2882550002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are in an unknown territory situation," infectious disease expertÂ Michael Osterholm said of Chronic wasting disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China data leak exposes vast hi-tech surveillance operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/2186547/china-data-leak-exposes-vast-hi-tech-surveillance-operation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch researcher says tracking firm left database of personal details unprotected for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$133 million Albuquerque electric bus system going nowhere fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-abq-art-albuquerque-electric-buses-20190213-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was said Albuquerque Rapid Transit would revitalize the city and make it a mass transit leader. Instead, ART is a target of contempt, mired in problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer seriously injured in Australia shark attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190217-surfer-seriously-injured-australia-shark-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surfer seriously injured in Australia shark attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver encrypts police radio traffic, blocking public from listening...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/02/15/denver-encrypt-police-radio-traffic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public will no longer be able to tune into Denver police radio traffic once the department switches to new radio technology in the coming months that will encrypt all communications, though new…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTHONY WEINER OUT OF PRISON...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/17/anthony-weiner-out-of-prison-early-pre-release-sexting-minor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Weiner is no longer behind bars, but he's still has a few months under federal custody before he's freed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller questions CAMBRIDGE ANALYTICA director...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/feb/17/brittany-kaiser-trump-russia-robert-mueller-cambridge-analytica</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second former employee of controversial data firm to be questioned by special counsel’s inquiry into Russia collusion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black snot, cancer risks: NYC subway air dirty...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-air-quality-subway-mta-20190215-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t be fooled by the fact that the trains run on electricity: Diesel fumes stink up subway air, adding to a toxic brew of pollution that researchers say is bad for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long before City Hall rats, L.A. struggled with rise of typhus...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-ln-typhus-20190217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases have been increasing in California for more than a decade. A total of 167 people were diagnosed with typhus last year, compared with 13 in 2008. Almost all of the cases were in Los Angeles and Orange counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-top FBI lawyer: 2 Cabinet officials were 'ready to support' 25th Amendment effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-top-fbi-lawyer-2-trump-cabinet-officials-were-ready-to-support-25th-amendment-effort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former top FBI lawyer James Baker, in closed-door testimony to Congress, detailed alleged discussions among senior officials at the Justice Department about invoking the 25th Amendment to remove President Trump from office, claiming he was told Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein said two Trump Cabinet officials were “ready to support” such an effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds stranded as British airline collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/17/flybmi-british-airline-collapses-strands-hundreds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of passengers throughout Europe have been stranded by the abrupt collapse of the British regional airline Flybmi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the horrifying, unspoken world of sexually abusive nuns...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/16/inside-the-horrifying-unspoken-world-of-sexually-abusive-nuns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“God is Love,” Sister Mary Juanita Barto told Cait Finnegan as she repeatedly raped her in classrooms at Mater Christi High School in Queens in the late 1960s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flames shoot from ground in NYC manhole explosions...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/flames-shoot-from-ground-in-midtown-manhole-explosions/5142405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flames shot from the ground after two manholes exploded in Manhattan on Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential privacy lapse found in Americans' census data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aba8e57c145047b5bab11b62baaa7f7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An internal team at the Census Bureau found that basic personal information collected from more than 100 million Americans during the 2010 head count could be reconstructed from obscured data, but with lots of mistakes, a top agency official disclosed Saturday. The age, gender, location, race and ethnicity for 138 million people were potentially vulnerable. So far, however, only internal hacking teams have discovered such details at possible risk, and no outside groups are known to have grabbed data intended to remain private for 72 years, chief scientist John Abowd told a scientific conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster Patrick Caddell Dies at 68...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a85453edd1a478288d7d2a5f07003a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Patrick Caddell, the pollster who helped propel Jimmy Carter in his longshot bid to win the presidency and later distanced himself from Democrats, has died, a colleague said Saturday night. He was 68. Caddell died Saturday in Charleston, South Carolina, after suffering a stroke. That's according to Professor Kendra Stewart of the College of Charleston, who confirmed the death to The Associated Press. After working with Democrats in the 1970s and 1980s, Caddell eventually drifted away from the Democratic Party and began advising supporters of Republican Donald Trump and was a contributor to Fox News for a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett's Lawyers Call Cops Liars...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/jussie-smollett-attack-suspect-lawyers-lie-statement-chicago-police-empire-1202559103/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREAKING… As Chicago police declare a significant shift in “the trajectory of the investigation” of the alleged attack on Jussie Smollett nearly three weeks ago, the attorneys for the E…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
