<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Second quake shakes Tennessee-North Carolina border...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article249422900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a dozen people reported feeling the tremor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media users more likely to believe misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/social-media-users-more-likely-162941874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans who rely on social media as their main source of news are more likely believe false or unproven stories about important topics such as politics and Covid-19, a survey showed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen Signals Interest in Digital-Dollar...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-signals-interest-backing-digital-164843289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen signaled the Biden administration supports research into the viability of a digital dollar, a shift from the lack of enthusiasm shown for the concept under her predecessor, Steven Mnuchin.“It makes sense for central banks to be looking at” issuing sovereign digital currencies, Yellen said at a virtual conference on Monday hosted by the New York Times.She said a digital version of the dollar could help address hurdles to financial inclusion in the U.S. among low-income households.“Too many Americans don’t have access to easy payments systems and banking accounts, and I think this is something that a digital dollar, a central bank digital currency, could help with,” she said. “It could result in faster, safer and cheaper payments, which I think are important goals.”A number of central banks, including the U.S. Federal Reserve, have been conducting research into how digital versions of their own currency would work. Officials generally see both opportunity and risks and many central banks have moved slowly to embrace the idea, while China has proceeded with pilot-program tests of a digital yuan.Treasury ‘Endorsement’“This is the most forward-leaning a Treasury secretary has ever been in endorsing a digital dollar,” Josh Lipsky, director of the Atlantic Council’s GeoEconomics Center, said of Yellen’s comments Monday. “I read it as an endorsement for Treasury to be involved in the exploration of central bank digital currencies, and we hadn’t seen that before.”The U.S. central bank announced last year that staff members at the Federal Reserve Bank of Boston were conducting research in conjunction with the MIT Media Lab in Cambridge, Massachusetts, seeking to construct and test a hypothetical digital dollar.Some lawmakers have expressed interest. Senate Banking Committee Chair Sherrod Brown, an Ohio Democrat, has advocated using digital technology to help reduce costs for accessing and transferring money, especially those outside the traditional banking system.Bitcoin, for its part, is championed by its supporters as essentially a separate financial system, independent from the control of central banks and any potential state-sponsored digital currencies.Even so, Fed Chair Jerome Powell has stressed it’s more important for the U.S., as keeper of the world’s most popular reserve currency, to be right rather than first on this front.Yellen echoed that, saying officials must first address a number of issues -- including how a digital currency might affect traditional bank deposits, financial stability, consumer protection and illicit transactions.“There’s a lot to consider here, but it’s absolutely worth looking at,” she said.Yellen’s predecessor was cool on the idea. In 2018, he said the Fed and Treasury were studying the pros and cons of digital dollars, but “we don’t think there’s any need for that at this point.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunter slammed for posing with bloody giraffe heart after kill...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14125206/trophy-hunter-slammed-bloody-giraffe-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TROPHY hunter posed with a bloody giraffe heart which was cut out of the beast she shot. Merelize Van Der Merwe, 32, infuriated campaigners by sharing the photo of her “perfect” Valen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARY:  Pranksters strap 'gun' on BOSTON DYNAMICS police dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/boston-dynamics-robot-spot-paintball-mschf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet will get a chance to remotely control one of Boston Dynamics' $75,000 'Spot' robots complete with a mounted paintball gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic changing the digital nomad scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Like-summer-camp-for-grown-ups-The-pandemic-is-15969657.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 300 miles off the coast of Morocco, a tiny archipelago seems like Portugal's take...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organ Transplant Patient Dies After Receiving Covid-Infected Lungs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-02-22/transplant-patient-dies-after-receiving-lungs-infected-with-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident appears to mark the first proven case of coronavirus transmission via an organ transplant in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCA-COLA racism training asks staff to 'try to be less white'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2379531/coca-cola-racism-training-staff-to-be-less-white/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COCA-COLA employees were told in an online training to “try to be less white” in an effort to combat racism discrimination. Photos of Coca-Cola’s online training seminar were shar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA to Require 'License Plate' for All Drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/02/faa-releases-remote-id-largest-regulatory-change-drones-years/172062/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part of the purpose is to allow for more complex operations in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALLS CLOSING IN ON THE DON?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/this-is-the-end-of-the-road-nbc-justice-correspondent-breaks-down-ruling-that-grand-jury-can-see-trumps-tax-returns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News justice correspondent Pete Williams said that Monday marks the end of former President Donald Trump’s attempts to keep his tax returns secret. The Supreme Court issued a one-line ruling that Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance can obtain Trump’s tax records for his grand jury investigation into the president’s companies. “It’s the end of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Studios Start to Conceal Box Office Grosses...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/more-hollywood-studios-start-to-conceal-box-office-grosses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Searchlight Pictures didn't provide any numbers at all for 'Nomadland' when the Oscar hopeful expanded nationwide over the Feb. 19-21 weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Detain Black Teen For Walking In Street During Snowstorm...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/22/texas-black-teen-jailed-walking-during-snowstorm-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Black teenager in North Texas was arrested for walking home on a street during the winter storm and spent one night in a county jail. Now the misdemeanor charge against Rodney Reese has been dropped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS:  UK 'NORMAL' BY JUNE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14125374/lockdown-roadmap-boris-johnson-revealed-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOPS, pubs and hairdressers will return from April 12 – and the PM will FINALLY reveal whether the nation can book a foreign summer holiday. Boris Johnson today outlined his plan for unlocki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen, Soon-Yi Blast HBO Docuseries as 'Hatchet Job'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/21/woody-allen-responds-to-hbo-documentary-the-farrows-and-their-enablers-put-together-a-hatchet-job-riddled-with-falsehoods</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is  Woody Allen and Soon Yi Previn’s official response to the HBO documentary, “Allen vs. Farrow”: “These documentarians had no interest in the truth. Instead, they spe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Job Rating: 58% Approve, 34% Disapprove...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun provocation reveals tensions in Michigan tourist haven...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-michigan-coronavirus-pandemic-detroit-local-governments-ee408979013d5d7ea8f690d570131449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAVERSE CITY, Mich. (AP) — Some 90 minutes into a routine meeting of the Grand Traverse County board, its agenda packed with mundane topics such as roads and libraries, came a surprising seven...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAFT PUNK Call It Quits...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/daft-punk-call-it-quits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary dance duo have called it quits 28 years after forming in Paris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffling 'crop circles' frozen into surface of creek prompt debate on origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.register-herald.com/news/baffling-crop-circles-frozen-into-surface-of-alabama-creek-prompt-debate-on-origins/article_fcd6264e-7492-11eb-9b27-27a9de263671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.register-herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious swirls found atop a frozen Alabama creek have challenged meteorologists and rattled social media, with some likening the formations to alien-created crop circles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns Break Rules to Attend Exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/nuns-break-covid-rules-exorcism-1570918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The religious event was held in Dublin on December 8, a time where travel was banned in Ireland unless deemed essential – e.g. for medical care or to buy groceries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry youths rattle Spain in support of jailed rap artist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-hip-hop-and-rap-violence-barcelona-dada0c3bc487f5e05e2fcb1ae09c162c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — The imprisonment of a rap artist for his music praising terrorist violence and insulting the Spanish monarchy has set off a powder keg of pent-up rage this week in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgusted? Good. It could be beneficial to health...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/disgusted-good-it-could-be-beneficial-to-your-health-a-new-study-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's no need to feel there's something wrong with you if you recoil when foodie friends talk about the interesting delicacies they've tried. And you don't need to change — in fact, these reactions could keep you healthy. Here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They were terrorists': Capitol Police officer recounts Jan. 6 attack...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/capitol-police-officer-recounts-jan-attack-exclusive/story?id=76036587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Is this America? They beat police officers with Blue Lives Matter flags." Capitol Police Officer Harry Dunn exclusively told ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bite Club': Shark attack survivors find solace in unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bite-club-shark-attack-survivors-find-solace-in-unity/ar-BB1dTgby</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first rule of Bite Club is you talk to Dave Pearson, a shark attack survivor who connects hundreds of people from around the world to support each other "beyond the bite". The 58-year-old almost died a decade ago when a bull shark tore into his arm while he was surfing off Australia's east coast. Since the day when friends hauled him to shore -- away from the three-metre predator that dragged him around the bottom of the ocean before losing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're Getting Out of L.A. and Going to Joshua Tree': Desert Area Booming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/were-getting-out-of-l-a-and-going-to-joshua-tree-why-the-desert-area-is-booming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As creatives seek an escape from the big city, prices jump and cutting-edge architecture rises in the High Desert area: "75 percent of my clients are investors from L.A."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Power Giant Sounded Alarm Days Before Blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/days-blackouts-one-texas-power-014130098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Vistra Corp., one of the largest power generators in Texas, said it warned state agencies days before cascading blackouts plunged millions into darkness that internal forecasts showed electricity demand was expected to exceed supply.Despite the warning, “the coordination and planning by authorities across the broader energy sector were seemingly disproportionate to the severity of the situation,” Vistra said in an emailed statement late Sunday. The company didn’t identify which state entities it contacted. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas is the state’s grid operator, while the Texas Public Utility Commission regulates power generators.Ercot said in a statement its “operating notices incentived all available generation to serve customers” and didn’t immediately comment on the Vistra letter. Andrew Barlow, an official with the PUC, said he wasn’t privy to any correspondence between the agency and Vistra and referred the matter to Ercot.“Days ahead of this event, Vistra and others forecasted insufficient generation would be available, and we began winter emergency preparations,” the statement said. “The warning signs were there, but the public was unaware of the gravity of the situation, which led to people being unable to respond and make the necessary adjustments for their families.”Read more: How Extreme Cold Turned Into a U.S. Energy Crisis: QuickTakeAt its peak, more than 4 million Texans were without power over several days of unprecedented cold. Dozens have perished in the wake of what has now become known as the largest forced power outage in U.S. history. Even when electricity was restored as temperatures rose, millions remained without safe drinking water after power outages hit treatment plants and water pumps used to pressurize lines.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Beat Cancer at 10. Now She's Set to Be Youngest American in Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/22/she-beat-cancer-at-10-now-shes-set-to-be-the-youngest-american-in-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hayley Arceneaux, 29, had hoped this would be the year that she would complete her aim of visiting all seven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mogul vs Mogul: Australia's tech law pits Murdoch against Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/mogul-vs-mogul-australias-tech-081001805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's push to regulate tech giants has become a power struggle between two of the world's most powerful men, with Rupert Murdoch and Mark Zuckerberg locked in a generational battle for media dominance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peacock who became London lockdown symbol of hope killed by foxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/RIP-Kevin-Peacock-who-became-a-London-lockdown-15968848.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - Kevin the peacock, a sassy blue bird who mysteriously appeared at the beginning of lockdown last March and became a symbol of hope for locals confined to their homes, has been killed by foxes.  In a somber email sent to parents on Sunday, Chris Evans, the principal of Yardley Primary School - the place Kevin chose as home for almost a year, said that their cherished mascot had been killed by a fox, or possibly several over the weekend. His remains were found by the school's devastated janitor who had developed a close bond with the animal, often feeding him mixed seeds and fruit and generally making a fuss over him.  For the residents of Chingford, this leafy town on the edge of east London, Kevin was so much more than an animal that squawked long into the night. He was an "icon" and local treasure. A majestic creature who danced in their gardens like a Spice Girl, perched on their walls and rooftops elegantly and brought comfort to those grieving the loss of loved ones to covid-19.  For the hundreds of children that attend Yardley school, Kevin was the celebrity that they searched for in the grounds each day. He was the novelty guest who once interrupted a spelling test by repeatedly banging his beak on the classroom door.  "He adopted us," Evans said of the bird last year, describing Kevin as the "pandemic peacock" that landed to "brighten our days."  On Sunday many parents were faced with the difficult task of explaining to their children that when they returned to school Kevin would no longer be present.  "When we heard the bad news, we dreaded telling the kids as we knew they would be upset," explained Rob and Zoe Warner, whose children Mia, 4, and Leo, 8, attend the school. Like many young pupils, the Warner siblings would keep an eye out for Kevin each day,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen, Soon-Yi Blast HBO Docuseries as 'Hatchet Job'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/woody-allen-soon-yi-previn-respond-to-allen-v-farrow-filmmakers-these-documentarians-had-no-interest-in-the-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Animated Flying Cat With Pop-Tart Body Sold for $600,000...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/22/why-an-animated-flying-cat-with-a-pop-tart-body-sold-for-almost-600000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 10 years since Chris Torres created Nyan Cat, an animated flying cat with a Pop-Tart body leaving a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet in mental health crisis died after police knelt on neck for five mins, family says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Navy-veteran-in-mental-health-crisis-died-after-15968784.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angelo Quinto lay facedown on the hardwood floor of his mother's bedroom with blood...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz tries to repair public image after Cancun trip...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Cruz-tries-to-repair-public-image-after-Cancun-15968250.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already in hot water after a trip to Cancún, Mexico, amid a statewide emergency, Sen....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of  boy who died during winter storm suing TX energy company for $100M...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/family-conroe-boy-died-winter-storm-sues-ercot-entergy/285-ba585381-54b0-426f-ae4b-34afff7d32c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit alleges gross negligence by the power grid operator and the electricity provider, saying it led to the death of 11-year-old Christian Pavon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH director slams maskless Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/collins-nih-maskless-republicans-covid-coranvirus-12d2e026-48cb-4989-b512-5e47f909059a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Failing to wear masks led to thousands of deaths, Francis Collins tells "Axios on HBO."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA orders stepped-up inspections of BOEING 777s...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221223409-2vnq8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO-AIRPLANE/FAA (URGENT):FAA orders stepped-up inspections of Boeing 777s after United engine failure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB spring training still hot ticket in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-arizona-mlb-spring-training-coronavirus-pandemic-bf8b608e58f45f5289267500b881a4e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Even during a pandemic, the appetite to sit in the sun and watch Major League Baseball spring training appears robust. The Arizona Diamondbacks sold out their entire spring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Parts fall from sky in plane scare...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/denver-explosions-honolulu-05e113b0fdff51c3ab1324e7a4c500df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOMFIELD, Colo. (AP) — David Delucia was settling back into his airplane seat and starting to relax on his way to a long-awaited vacation when a huge explosion and flash of light interrupted an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona sees sixth night of unrest for jailed rapper...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-violence-spain-barcelona-42d5da0f6722b1328b069923c7e412f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Protests in support of a jailed rapper turned violent for a sixth consecutive night in Barcelona on Sunday with clashes between police and groups of mostly angry youths in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State confronts its energy, politics and culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/02/20/they-were-not-prepared-after-winter-crisis-texas-will-have-to-confront-its-energy-politics-and-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the snow and ice melts, the Lone Star State faces a host of questions — technical, political and cultural. What went wrong? Who is responsible? How do...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea's concentration camps reviewed on GOOGLE Maps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/google-maps-users-find-reviews-23540461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have been leaving largely positive reviews for the Yodok Concentration Camp on Google, which has previously been reported by one ex-detainee as being "worse than Auschwitz"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black, female and high-profile, Kamala Harris is top target in online fever swamps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/black-female-high-profile-kamala-155005192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president's high profile, race and gender have made her a target of some of the worst internet smears. The problem is only getting worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed with camera, an ER doctor captures faces of virus war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/armed-camera-young-er-doctor-130004840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the COVID-19 pandemic began last spring, Dr. Scott Kobner knew history was unfolding. Soon he began showing up at the hospital on his days off with his Leica M6 and M10 cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY WARNS</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-virologist-italy-virus-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases in Italy are on the rise again, in large part due to the more infectious British variant, a top virologist warned in a newspaper interview published Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFECTIONS IN GERMANY RISE AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-germany-urges-caution-covid-infections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Health Minister Jens Spahn urged caution on Sunday in the face of rising coronavirus infection numbers, just as schools across the country prepare to reopen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People who wear glasses are three times LESS likely to catch Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2376949/glasses-wearers-less-likely-catch-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEARING glasses makes you up to three times less likely to catch Covid, a study has found. Researchers found people with spectacles rub and touch their eyes less, which is a “significant route of i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION PASSES 500,000 COVID DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/u-s-reaches-500-000-deaths-coronavirus-n1257992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of dead rivals the population of Atlanta or Sacramento, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm X's family releases letter alleging FBI, police role in his death...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221151255-tedkj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil rights leader's family urge investigation into letter suggesting security forces behind his death in a 1965 shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  MASKS ANOTHER YEAR</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221143523-j7r4j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 1, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-Americans may still need masks to fight COVID in 2022, Fauci says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French city of Nice asks tourists to stay away...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221110647-2nxex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are mulling a weekend lockdown to put off visitors as it battles a spike in coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubbed as Obama high court pick, Garland in line to be AG...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-biden-cabinet-merrick-garland-judiciary-coronavirus-pandemic-12978c008b81f1cc59e0d650cd4c7cb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The last time Merrick Garland was nominated by the White House for a job, Republicans wouldn't even meet with him. Now, the once-snubbed Supreme Court pick will finally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How  winter storm pushed Texas into crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/houston-football-storms-coronavirus-pandemic-hurricanes-5fd491ed5bfd9aa0ae08426c6078539e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Two days before the storm began, Houston’s chief elected official warned her constituents to prepare as they would for a major hurricane. Many took heed: Texans who could stocked up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists clone endangered ferret!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/1st-cloned-endagered-species-ferret-23cde3908e496692648dc28d4b8121ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEYENNE, Wyo. (AP) — Scientists have cloned the first U.S. endangered species, a black-footed ferret duplicated from the genes of an animal that died over 30 years ago. The slinky predator...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
