<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ACADEMY SLAPS BACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/will-smith-oscars-ban-664346ac2d2441939764f35be2d8026b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The motion picture academy on Friday banned Will Smith from attending the Oscars or any other academy event for 10 years following his slap of Chris Rock at the Academy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia or die:  These Ukrainians were given only one way out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/07/europe/ukraine-mariupol-russia-deportation-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Russian forces and allied separatist soldiers arrived offering a path to safety, it felt like a sick twist of fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Theft Rings Stealing Fuel Across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/gas-theft-rings-have-now-stolen-more-140k-worth-fuel-across-us-1696543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of gallons of gas have allegedly been stolen around the country as prices have soared in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest speaks out against war despite threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-priest-speaks-out-against-war-in-ukraine-despite-threats/ar-AAW0Dc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreaks give taste of living with virus: 'Get used to it'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-living-with-virus-outbreaks-26ce89a748b27b3a47730d29a947237a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is getting a first glimpse of what it’s like to experience COVID-19 outbreaks during this new phase of living with the virus, and the roster of the newly infected is studded with stars. Cabinet members, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, Broadway actors and the governors of New Jersey and Connecticut have all tested positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department: WH gift records for Trump, Pence missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ab704b1bb2945bc04a31c12a81248e56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The State Department says it is unable to compile a complete and accurate accounting of gifts presented to former President Donald Trump and other U.S. officials by foreign governments during Trump's final year in office, citing missing data from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: 6 human skulls found at mail facility on way to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5083967/human-skulls-chicago-iowa-netherlands-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A K-9 dog has discovered six human skulls going through the US mailing system. The human skulls were shipped from the Netherlands and en route to Iowa before being taken away at O’Hare’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Braces for President Getting Covid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3262454-white-house-acknowledges-biden-could-get-covid-stresses-hes-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Friday acknowledged President Biden could get COVID-19 amid an uptick in positive cases surrounding the president but stressed he has taken steps to protect himself. “We take eve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DANCING WITH THE STARS' Moving To DISNEY+; Stunning Move After 16 Years On ABC...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/dancing-with-the-stars-leaving-abc-disney-plus-season-31-1234996886/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Hold on to your Danskins: Dancing with the Stars is relocating to Disney+ in a groundbreaking arrangement. DWTS has received a two-year pickup — for Seasons 31 and 32 — and w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: GMAIL favors left-wing candidates, sends far more emails from conservatives to spam...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/google-gmail-favors-left-wing-candidates-conservatives-spam-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that Google’s Gmail favors liberal candidates, allowing the vast majority of emails from left-wing politicians to land in the user’s inbox while more than two-thirds of messages from conservative candidates are marked as spam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invading sea lions take over fish farm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/sea-lions-take-over-bc-fish-farm-1.6407888?cmp=TW_Feed_CBCMain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of hungry sea lions have taken over a fish farm off the coast of Vancouver Island, feasting on untold numbers of farmed Atlantic salmon as staff struggle to kick them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More politicians test positive as virus spreads among DC power players...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/more-politicians-test-positive-for-covid-19-as-virus-spreads-among-dc-power-players/ar-AAW15kO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who bought cruise ship on CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/the-man-who-bought-a-cruise-ship-on-craigslist/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former web developer Chris Willson has spent the last 14 years renovating a 293-foot "pocket" cruise ship he bought from Craigslist and hopes to transform it into a museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Art Gallery Selling Dinosaurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvn3m8/theatrum-mundi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorites, spacesuits and Hollywood memorabilia: Everything can be bought at Theatrum Mundi, if you have the cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SMITH BANNED FROM OSCARS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/will-smith-punishment-oscar-ban-chris-rock-slap-ampas-1234997251/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(UPDATED with Will Smith statement) With their options rather limited, the  Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences’ Board of Governors have just decided that Will Smith will not be able to att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 acquitted in alleged plot to kidnap Michigan Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/grand-rapids/2022/04/2-men-acquitted-in-alleged-plot-to-kidnap-michigan-gov-gretchen-whitmer-jury-deadlocks-on-other-2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial was held in Grand Rapids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfers Chase Freedom in Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2022/04/08/surfers-chase-freedom-in-cuba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;I&gt;Havana Libre&lt;/I&gt; tells the story of Cuba’s underground surfers struggling to practice their sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK EYE FOR DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whitmer-kidnap-plot-trial-michigan-gretchen-whitmer-grand-rapids-adam-fox-e5b58234b134e32d9655288a51f107fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. (AP) — Two of four men were acquitted Friday in a conspiracy to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer in 2020, motivated by fury at the Democrat’s tough COVID-19 restrictions early in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 In 10 Parents Now Seeking Therapy For Entire Family...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/parents-therapy-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds children are just as stressed out as their parents – and the pandemic may be to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen pulls out of Easter event ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/5082479/queen-pulls-out-easter-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has “regretfully” pulled out of an Easter event next week. Her Majesty, 95, had been due to attend a service at St George’s Chapel in Windsor on April 14, but she will i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents struggle to find baby formula...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/baby-formula-shortage-abbott-nutrition-recall-supply-chain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some states, more than half of baby formula products were out of stock, new data shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rape exceptions to abortion bans were once widely accepted. No more...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rape-exceptions-abortion-bans-were-100023781.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative statehouses are dropping rape exceptions from abortion bans as they look ahead to the Supreme Court's expected decision in a major abortion case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law reduced prison time for man tied to Sacramento shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-shootings-prisons-arrests-26a5da7716f51d24cce3f12eadf09523</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A suspect arrested in connection with last weekend's mass shooting outside bars in Sacramento served less than half his 10-year sentence because of voter-approved changes to state law that lessened the punishment for his felony convictions and provided a chance for earlier release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissatisfied With Their Party, Wealthy Republican Donors Form Secret Coalitions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/04/06/us/politics/republican-donors-rockbridge-network-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eager to offset a Democratic advantage among so-called dark money groups, wealthy pro-Trump conservatives like Peter Thiel are involved in efforts to wield greater influence outside the traditional party machinery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading Proud Boys member pleads guilty to Capitol riot charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/leading-proud-boys-member-pleads-guilty-to-us-capitol-riot-charges/ar-AAW0Edw?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bans all troops from social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-troops-social-media-over-26662904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deputy commander of Russia’s western military district ordered officers to restrict troops' use of social media, so they don't reveal sensitive information and because morale is already low</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEIRD CLOUD OVER ALASKA IGNITES TALK OF UFO CRASH, WEAPONS TEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.bellinghamherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article260230970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bellinghamherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many people aren’t buying the explanation from Alaska State Troopers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE TURNS RIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61029655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel Macron is now looking over his shoulder before the first round of the presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: NETFLIX Has Lost Hundreds of Millions on Ryan Murphy...</title>
      <link>https://theankler.com/p/shonda-v-ryan-whos-winning-at-netflix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theankler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESG analyzes head-to-head the two richest deals in TV and their return on investment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'For our children'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10699187/Thirty-dead-100-wounded-Russian-missile-hits-Ukrainian-railway-station.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strike was on Kramatorsk's station, with graphic pictures showing bodies strewn across floor, lying amongst abandoned luggage and children's prams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In response to killings, El Salvador's bitcoin president attacks civil liberties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-response-to-killings-el-salvadors-bitcoin-president-attacks-civil-liberties/ar-AAVZYfT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The plan to release genetically engineered mosquitoes in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/the-plan-to-release-genetically-engineered-mosquitoes-in-california/ar-AAW02Nc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful 'space laser' beaming directly at Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5080540/powerful-space-laser-earth-lightyears-detected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POWERFUL space laser emitted from a distant galaxy has been discovered by astronomers. The beam of radio waves is what scientists call a “megamaser” and this one is the most distant y…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin takes 'nuclear briefcase' to funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5081150/putin-secret-nuclear-briefcase-world-war-three/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARANOID Vladimir Putin was seen attending a Moscow funeral today surrounded by military guards carrying Russia’s ‘secret nuclear briefcase’. The Russian president arrived at Chri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Infertility New Symptom Of Long COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/male-infertility-long-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even mild-to-moderate cases of COVID-19 can result in detrimental protein-level changes in relation to male reproductive functions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Detailee Entangled in Secret Service Bribery Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2022/04/08/biden_detailee_entangled_in_secret_service_bribery_scheme_.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More details are emerging about the four Secret Service employees entangled in an alleged bribery scheme carried out by two men accused of masquerading as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists rejuvenate skin cells by 30 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-60991675</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers rejuvenate a 53-year-old woman's skin by decades, but clinical applications are a way off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM gives security agencies free rein to act...</title>
      <link>https://www.al-monitor.com/originals/2022/04/israeli-pm-gives-security-forces-free-rein-act-after-attack </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al-monitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of climbing as therapy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2022/apr/08/my-head-was-completely-free-the-rise-of-climbing-as-therapy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of climbing therapy say it can help people focus on the here and now and provide relief from the whirlwind of modern life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Resignation: 1 In 4 Workers Have Quit Job Over Mental Health Issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mental-health-quit-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The survey finds that stress from work ranks as having the second-worst impact on a person's mental health -- finishing only behind stress due to their finances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic 'automat' dining thrived century ago. Can covid revive it?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/futuristic-e2-80-98automat-e2-80-99-dining-thrived-a-century-ago-can-covid-revive-it/ar-AAVZFaj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelenskyy tells '60 MINS' what he saw in Bucha...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/volodymyr-zelenskyy-60-minutes-interview-preview-2022-04-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Pelley interviewed Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy in Kyiv for a two-part report that airs Sunday on 60 Minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA warns 'recession shock' coming...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recession-shock-coming-bofa-warns-101801015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The macro-economic picture is deteriorating fast and could push the U.S. economy into recession as the Federal Reserve tightens its monetary policy to tame surging inflation, BofA strategists warned in a weekly research note. The Federal Reserve on Wednesday signalled it will likely start culling assets from its $9 trillion balance sheet at its meeting in early May and will do so at nearly twice the pace it did in its previous "quantitative tightening" exercise as it confronts inflation running at a four-decade high. In terms of notable weekly flows, BofA said emerging market equity funds enjoyed the biggest inflow in ten weeks at $5.3 billion in the week to Wednesday while emerging market debt vehicles attracted $2.2 billion, their best week since September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the tale of Hunter Biden and $3.5 million from Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Unraveling-the-tale-of-Hunter-Biden-and-3-5-17066341.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"She [Russian billionaire Elena Baturina] gave him [Hunter Biden] $3.5 million so now I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York attorney general seeks to hold Trump in contempt of court...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/ny-ag-seeking-hold-donald-trump-civil-contempt-rcna23431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Letitia James' office wants to fine the former president $10,000 a day until he turns over subpoenaed documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia war dead belie slogan no one left behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-e2-80-99s-war-dead-belie-its-slogan-that-no-one-is-left-behind/ar-AAVZJ3T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No sign of anti-Putin bump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/no-sign-of-anti-putin-bump-in-france-as-macron-risks-losing-to-le-pen/ar-AAVZ7fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing military power, Scholz tries to lead Germany into new era...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/embracing-military-power-olaf-scholz-tries-to-lead-germany-into-a-new-era/ar-AAVZChh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to address TWITTER staff after internal outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-to-address-twitter-staff-after-internal-outcry/ar-AAVZaVY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-thirds of adults OK if child lesbian, gay, bisexual, but only 50% fine with trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.eagletribune.com/region/two-thirds-of-us-adults-would-be-ok-if-their-child-came-out-as-lesbian/article_3e36b62e-16e6-5bba-8f0a-922990670d0e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eagletribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of adults in the United States say they would be comfortable if their child came out as lesbian, gay or bisexual, according to a new survey, but only</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academy set to discuss sanctions for Smith over slap...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscars-governors-set-discuss-sanctions-234026083.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Academy governors including Steven Spielberg and Whoopi Goldberg were due to meet Friday to discuss possible sanctions against Will Smith for slapping comedian Chris Rock at the Oscars last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First private mission readies for launch to ISS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-private-mission-readies-launch-053536619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first fully private mission to the International Space Station is set to blast off Friday with a four-member crew from startup company Axiom Space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson confirmation takes Biden political story full circle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-stephen-breyer-us-supreme-court-covid-a21e7efb46744abaf5f9ed64b22b192a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s a moment 46 days — and more than 46 years — in the making. President Joe Biden on Friday will celebrate the confirmation of Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson as the first Black woman to reach the Supreme Court, marking the pinnacle of her legal career and bringing his political story full circle.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
