<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Vacation that's out of this world: First space hotel set to start construction...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/2021/03/03/space-hotel-orbital-assembly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mega-rich are already gearing up for space travel. Now there's a space hotel in the works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stockton's Basic-Income Experiment Pays Off?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/03/stocktons-basic-income-experiment-pays-off/618174/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study of the city’s program that sent cash to struggling individuals finds dramatic changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Allen Opens Up About Infamous Drug Arrest; Laughs Off Trump Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/tim-allen-opens-up-about-infamous-drug-arrest-laughs-off-trump-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Allen is making headlines after opening up about his cocaine arrest and prison time, as well as the delight he took in Donald Trump riling up critics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warnings of possible attempt to attack Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210303143857-yqehw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/SECURITY (URGENT):Warnings of possible attempt to attack U.S. Capitol by militia group-U.S. Capitol Police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICC prosecutor announces investigation into Israeli 'war crimes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/icc-prosecutor-announces-formal-investigation-into-israeli-war-crimes-660818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Israelis could find themselves at risk by court decision; Israel bracing for protracted legal battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left in dark: Millions hit by internet shutdowns in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210303140415-x16mh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access Now report finds almost 30 countries restricted access to the web at least 155 times last year, preventing millions from getting information about COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'When will it end?': Changing virus reshaping scientists' views...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210303133322-kwdag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VARIANTS (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-“When will it end?”: How a changing virus is reshaping scientists’ views on COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDS exits Strip with sale of VENETIAN...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-asia-sheldon-adelson-frank-sinatra-las-vegas-645b6166fb6fa2b2fe7ce8925773345f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas Sands is selling the iconic Venetian casino resort and its Sands Expo and Convention Center for $6.25 billion, withdrawing from gambling operations on the Las Vegas Strip after changing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval Drops to 38 From 71 in Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-cuomo-approval-drops-to-38-from-71-in-a-year-amid-multiple-controversies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple sexual harassment claims and the New York state nursing home scandal appear to have caught up with Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D-NY), according to one new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/10-rockets-hit-iraq-base-hosting-us-troops-security-sources-01614760206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rocket attack on an Iraqi base hosting US-led coalition troops Wednesday claimed a contractor's life, security sources said, just two days before Pope Francis is due to visit the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supernatural Thriller Asks if Children Can Be Genuinely Evil...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-hidden-gem-danish-supernatural-thriller-the-innocents-asks-if-children-can-be-genuinely-evil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Dark Danish Supernatural Thriller 'The Innocents' Asks if Children Can Be Evil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarkozy conviction triggers right-wing backlash against 'judges' republic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210303-sarkozy-conviction-triggers-right-wing-backlash-against-judges-republic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tough-talking politicians from the right are accustomed to demanding “exemplary” punishments. This week, they did not appreciate the judiciary making an example of their champion, Nicolas Sarkozy, ve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police disarm pipe bomb at Iowa polling site...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/541347-police-disarm-pipe-bomb-at-iowa-polling-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Ankeny, Iowa, say they disarmed a live pipe bomb after it was found by a pair of dog walkers at a polling location as voting took place in a local election Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex tape satire at Berlin fest tackles pandemic-era 'hypocrisy'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sex-tape-satire-berlin-fest-134033269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Eastern Europe's most acclaimed directors argues corruption, hypocrisy and racism are far more obscene than pornography in a Berlin film festival contender about a teacher whose sex tape winds up on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists closer to explaining mysterious 'brain fog'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/scientists-inch-closer-explaining-mysterious-brain-fog-symptom/story?id=76184080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As larger numbers of people recover from COVID-19, researchers are learning more about "brain fog" in those affected by the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Attacks Woman With Sock Full Of Coins On NYC Subway...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/03/subway-sock-of-coins-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said a man kicked the 45-year-old woman's foot and then hit her in the head with a sock full of coins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Warrant Executed To Obtain Black Box Data In Tiger Woods Crash...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/03/03/search-warrant-executed-to-obtain-black-box-data-in-tiger-woods-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The black box could give them information such as how fast Woods was traveling at the time of the wreck, whether he hit the brakes and whether the air bags inflated properly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DR. SEUSS books won't be published for racist images...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-dr-seuss-d8ed18335c03319d72f443594c174513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Six Dr. Seuss books — including “And to Think That I Saw It on Mulberry Street” and “If I Ran the Zoo” — will stop being published because of racist and insensitive imagery, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch test center hit by suspected bomb attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/03/dutch-covid-test-centre-hit-by-suspected-bomb-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows damaged but no one hurt in explosion at drive-through test centre in Bovenkarspel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alzheimer's Pill' Stops Disease In Tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/alzheimers-pill-successful-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the drug works by destroying rogue proteins that form sticky clumps in the brain and destroy neurons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dr. Oz' aids police in resuscitating man at Newark airport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dr-oz-newark-airport-rescue-2bc2c7aed137e3d44290e803e3497720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWARK, N.J. (AP) — When a traveler became stricken at Newark Liberty International Airport, the police got an assist from a celebrity doctor: Mehmet Oz. The incident occurred late Monday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' man comes alive moments before autopsy...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/bengaluru/bengaluru-27-year-old-dead-man-comes-alive-on-postmortem-table/articleshow/81303718.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A youth, who was believed to be dead by health personnel, came alive and had a narrow escape from undergoing a postmortem in Mahalingapura town of Rab</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard troops sick after eating raw meat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/03/national-guard-troops-at-capitol-sick-after-eating-raw-meat-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Guard soldiers defending the US Capitol have gotten ill after being fed meat that is almost completely raw — with shaved metal also found in the disgusting meals, according to whistl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones With 'Most Advanced AI Ever' Coming Soon To Local Police Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2021/03/03/drones-with-most-advanced-ai-ever-coming-soon-to-your-local-police-department/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Founded by Google veterans and backed by $340 million from major VCs, Skydio is creating drones that seem straight out of science fiction—and they could end up in your neighborhood soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Attorney General Sessions regrets migrant family separations...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210303085722-gkp3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/FAMILIES (PIX):Former Trump Attorney General Sessions regrets migrant family separations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$21 Trillion Treasuries Mystery Bedeviling Markets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/21-trillion-treasuries-mystery-bedeviling-214109520.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bond traders have been saying for years that liquidity is there in the world’s biggest bond market, except when you really need it.Last week’s startling gyrations in U.S. Treasury yields may offer fresh backing for that mantra, and prompt another bout of soul-searching in a $21 trillion market that forms the bedrock of global finance. While stocks are prone to sudden swings, such episodes are supposed to be few and far between in a government-debt market that sets the benchmark risk-free rate for much of the world.Yet jarring moves occur periodically in Treasuries, forming a bit of a mystery as no two events have been the same. Some point to heightened bank regulations in the wake of the 2008 financial crisis. Scrutiny over liquidity shortfalls intensified in October 2014 when a 12-minute crash and rebound in yields happened with no apparent trigger. Panic selling during the pandemic-fueled chaos a year ago, exacerbated when hedge funds’ leveraged wagers blew up, brought the issue to the fore again.And then came last week, when the gap between bid and offer prices for 30-year bonds hit the widest since the panic of March 2020.The latest events “are a stark reminder what happens when liquidity suddenly vanishes in the deepest, largest bond market,” said Ben Emons, managing director of global macro strategy at Medley Global Advisors.At issue is whether this vast market is more vulnerable to sudden bouts of turbulence thanks to measures that have made it more difficult for banks to hold Treasuries. Some analysts say the tumult last week was magnified by questions over whether the Federal Reserve will extend an easing of bank capital requirements, which is set to end March 31. Put in place early on in the pandemic, the measure is seen as making it easier for banks to add Treasuries to their balance sheets.The 2014 episode triggered a deep dive into the market structure, and regulators have pushed through some changes -- such as increased transparency -- and speculation has grown that more steps to bolster the market’s structure may be ahead.“While the scale and speed of flows associated with the COVID shock are likely pretty far out in the tail of the probability distribution, the crisis highlighted vulnerabilities in the critically important Treasury market that warrant careful analysis,” Fed Governor Lael Brainard said Monday in prepared remarks to the Institute of International Bankers.There are plenty of potential culprits in last week’s bond-market tumble -- which has since mostly reversed -- from improving economic readings to more technical drivers. Ultra-loose Fed policy and the prospect of fresh U.S. fiscal stimulus have investors betting on quicker growth and inflation. Add to that a wave of convexity hedgers, and unwinding by big trend-following investors -- such as commodity trading advisers.Based on Bloomberg’s U.S. Government Securities Liquidity Index, a gauge of how far yields are deviating from a fair-value model, liquidity conditions worsened recently, though it was nothing like what was seen in March.For Zoltan Pozsar, a strategist at Credit Suisse, the action began in Asia with bond investors reacting to perceived hawkish signs from the central banks of Australia and New Zealand. That sentiment then carried over into the U.S. as carry trades and other levered positions in the bond market were wiped out. A disastrous auction of seven-year notes on Thursday added fuel to the unraveling.Last week’s drama “brings to mind other notable episodes in recent years in which a deterioration in the Treasury market microstructure was primarily to blame,” JPMorgan &amp; Chase Co. strategist Henry St John wrote in a note with colleagues.One key gauge of Treasury liquidity -- market depth, or the ability to trade without substantially moving prices -- plunged in March 2020 to levels not seen since the 2008 crisis, according to data compiled by JPMorgan. That severe degree of liquidity shortfall didn’t resurface last week.The bond-market rout only briefly took a toll on share prices last week, with equities surging to start this week, following a sharp retreat in Treasury yields amid month-end buying.The Fed cut rates to nearly zero in March 2020, launched a raft of emergency lending facilities and ramped up bond buying to ensure low borrowing costs and smooth market functioning. That breakdown in functioning has sparked calls for change from regulators and market participants alike.GLOBAL INSIGHT: Recovery? Yes. Tantrum? No. Yield Driver ModelFor now, Treasuries have settled down. Pozsar notes that the jump in yields has provided an opportunity for some value investors to swoop in and pick up extra yield, effectively helping offset the impact of the leveraged investors who scrambled for the exits last week.“Some levered players were shaken out of their positions,” Pozsar said in a forthcoming episode of Bloomberg’s Odd Lots podcast. “It’s not comfortable -- especially if you’re on the wrong side of the trade -- but I don’t think that we should be going down a path where we should redesign the Treasury market.”Why Liquidity Is a Simple Idea But Hard to Nail Down: QuickTake(Updates with details on Bloomberg’s liquidity index in 10th paragraph, and a chart)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California clinics: More going to rich than at-risk..</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-los-angeles-san-francisco-coronavirus-pandemic-california-f03c01fa37789edf32d0414ddde072ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Teresa Parada is exactly the kind of person equity-minded California officials say they want to vaccinate: She's a retired factory worker who speaks little English and lives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World first: Robot able to 'hear' through ear of locust...</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-03/tu-awf030221.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, the ear of a dead locust has been connected to a robot that receives the ear's electrical signals and responds accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon IG finds ex-Trump doctor Jackson made sexual comments, violated alcohol policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/02/politics/ronny-jackson-dod-inspector-general-report/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense inspector general has issued a scathing review of Rep. Ronny Jackson during his time serving as the top White House physician, concluding that he made "sexual and denigrating" comments about a female subordinate, violated the policy for drinking alcohol while on a presidential trip and took prescription-strength sleeping medication that prompted concerns from his colleagues about his ability to provide proper care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: High alert as new QANON date approaches Thursday...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/541306-high-alert-as-new-qanon-date-approaches-thursday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities will be on high alert Thursday over a QAnon conspiracy theory prediction, but according to experts chances of violence appear minimal compared to the deadly insurrection on January 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis rising profile fuels 2024 talk...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/541318-desantiss-rising-gop-profile-fuels-2024-talk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) has seen his star rise over the past year as Republicans look to him as a potential successor to former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The East Is Rising': Xi Maps Out China's Post-Covid Ascent...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/03/the-east-is-rising-xi-maps-out-chinas-post-covid-ascent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Xi Jinping has struck a confident posture as he looks to secure China’s prosperity and power in a post-Covid world,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Exercise Enhances Aging Brains...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/03/how-exercise-enhances-aging-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise can change how crucial portions of our brain communicate as we age, improving aspects of thinking and remembering, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong House Costs Record $2 Million Year to Rent!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/hong-kong-house-costs-a-record-2-million-a-year-to-rent/ar-BB1eaDj4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong’s luxury property market has set another record, as its recovery from the pandemic gathers steam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFLICTING MESSAGES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210302195147-7blpz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Texas governor lifts state's mask mandate, business restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Seeks Crew for 'Fun' Trip Around the Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fly-me-to-the-moon-japanese-billionaire-is-looking-for-volunteers-11614736065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It will take three days to get to the moon, loop behind it, and three days to get back," Yusaku Maezawa said in a video Tuesday. "I will pay for the entire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military wages war on extremism in its own ranks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-military-wages-war-extremism-014451483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two months after some active service personnel and veterans took part in the deadly attack on the US Capitol, the United States military has begun to tackle extremism within its ranks -- but the fight promises to be a difficult one, by the very admission of its leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris ratings soared when he interviewed his brother last spring on CNN -- now that's off-limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Chris-Cuomo-s-ratings-soared-when-he-interviewed-15994172.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, CNN had a sensible policy about whether Chris Cuomo could interview his older...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When U.S. blamed Saudi crown prince for role in Khashoggi killing, fake TWITTER accounts went to war...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/When-U-S-blamed-Saudi-crown-prince-for-role-in-15994516.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi-based Twitter accounts using fake profile pictures, repetitive wording and spammy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo under pressure to quit as third woman alleges harassment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuomo-faces-growing-pressure-quit-182533693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo was fighting for his political life on Tuesday after a third woman accused him of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OPEN 100%'</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article249627903.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is now time to open Texas 100%,” Gov. Abbott said in Lubbock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS OFF TEXAS!</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/texas-biggest-us-state-lift-covid-19-mask-76208428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is lifting a COVID-19 mask mandate that was imposed last summer but has only been lightly enforced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donors gave House candidate $8+ million. Consultants took half of it...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/After-donors-gave-a-House-candidate-more-than-8-15994730.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. House candidate Kim Klacik walked onto Mike Huckabee's cable talk show last August...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men turn to makeup after one-too-many ZOOM calls...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/02/why-zoom-is-boosting-sales-in-mens-cosmetics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When realtor Ben Dixon caught sight of his face during an early morning Zoom call with a client in January, he was distracted by what he perceived were bags and discoloration under his eyes. “I tho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Jumpstart Gun-Control Efforts...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/guns/dems-jumpstart-gun-control-efforts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new Democratic proposals could force gun buyers to wait up to three times longer to receive their weapon and could ban the private sale of used guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith Mulls Entering Politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/02/us/will-smith-politics-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Will Smith teased the idea of running for political office one day during an interview on Pod Save America released on Monday, a politics podcast hosted by a group of aides to former President Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus Checks Should Continue Until Covid Is History, Senators Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stimulus-check-recurring-covid-19-senate-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans say $1,400 payments included in rescue package will last them less than three months, lawmakers argue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  ENOUGH SHOTS FOR ALL ADULTS BY MAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-covid-19-pandemic-statement-watch-live-stream-today-2021-03-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president said in an address that he's directing states to prioritize vaccinating K-12 educators and staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was quick to tell others to resign over sex harass claims...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/02/andrew-cuomo-was-quick-to-tell-others-to-resign-over-sex-harassment-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY — Gov. Andrew Cuomo has been quick to call for the resignations of powerful Albany lawmakers accused of sexually harassing aides — including known harassers Vito Lopez, Micah Kel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant races through Italy, especially among children...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-mario-draghi-italy-coronavirus-pandemic-d763a3e484cc74be866067a6adf16ced</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The variant of the coronavirus discovered in Britain is prevalent among Italy's infected schoolchildren and is helping to fuel a “robust” uptick in the curve of COVID-19 contagion in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Lawmakers Plan to Curtail Powers...</title>
      <link>https://nystateofpolitics.com/state-of-politics/new-york/ny-state-of-politics/2021/03/02/state-lawmakers-plan-to-curtail-cuomo-s-pandemic-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nystateofpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers have a two-way deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada suffers biggest contraction since Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/news/economy/canadian-press-newsalert-canadian-economy-contracted-5-4-per-cent-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 96% of schoolchildren still unsafe for full-time in-person learning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/enrichment/education/541258-according-to-cdc-96-percent-of-schoolchildren-still</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many are antsy to get kids back in school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Months Later, One Of NJ's First Patients STILL Battling Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/01/covid-1-year-long-haulers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study published by the Journal of the American Medical Association found about 30% of COVID-19 patients reported persistent symptoms as long as nine months after illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Political Flash Point: Passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccine-passports-covids-next-political-flash-point/ar-BB1ea13K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next major flash point over coronavirus response has already provoked cries of tyranny and discrimination in Britain, protests in Denmark, digital disinformation in the United States and geopolitical skirmishing within the European Union. The subject of debate: vaccine passports — government-issued cards or smartphone badges stating that the bearer has been inoculated against the coronavirus. The idea is to allow families to reunite,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY GOV GOES INTO HIDING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-avoids-public-amid-harassment-allegations-74d0eabed103e173b50f1a0ad7853671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo has avoided public appearances for days as some members of his own party call for him to resign over sexual harassment allegations. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC nominee mulls corporate political spending disclosures...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/02/gensler-sec-corporate-political-spending-472607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate disclosure was a dominant theme and key tension at Gensler's confirmation hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS OPENS 100%; ENDS MASK MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/03/02/abbott-hints-at-exciting-news-tuesday-that-could-include-rollback-of-texas-covid-19-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story and will be continously updated. AUSTIN — Texans will no longer be required to wear a face mask in public and all businesses can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat on par with ISIS!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2435097/christopher-wray-senate-hearing-capitol-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Director Chris Wray has blasted the deadly Capitol riot as “domestic terrorism” and said the homegrown threat is on par with ISIS. The director was speaking during a Senate hearing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL JAZEERA Staffers Concerned After Launch of Conservative Platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/a-betrayal-of-the-values-that-we-work-toward-al-jazeera-insiders-troubled-by-launch-of-conservative-platform-rightly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees at Al Jazeera’s English language platforms are deeply concerned that the launch of Rightly, a new digital platform aimed at conservative American audiences, may lead to a shift in editorial direction for Al Jazeera's English-language properties, including AJ+ and Al Jazeera English.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can physics prove if God exists?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210301-how-physics-could-prove-god-exists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there is a God, would they be bound by the laws of physics?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Synthetic Street Drug 'Benzo Dope' on the Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3anmy5/a-deadly-synthetic-street-drug-called-benzo-dope-is-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emerging drug contains two highly-potent highs, fentanyl and etizolam, and has been linked to a string of drug deaths in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boom looking more like baby bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/birth-rate-declining-baby-bust-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data provided to CBS News by 27 states shows births dropped by about 7.2% in December 2020, nine months after COVD-19 was declared a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service accidentally triggers tornado warning in multiple states...</title>
      <link>https://wgem.com/2021/03/02/tornado-warning-test-sparks-confusion-for-cell-phone-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgem.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tornado Warning alert was inadvertently sent to some cell phones by the National Weather Service on Tuesday without any indication it was part of a monthly test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular flea collar linked to 1,700 pet deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2021/03/02/seresto-dog-cat-collars-found-harm-pets-humans-epa-records-show/4574753001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Seresto pet collars were introduced, the EPA has received more than 75,000 reports related to the collars, including 907 involving human harm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent archdiocese urges Catholics to avoid shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article249627163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Johnson &amp; Johnson shot is the third coronavirus vaccine to be authorized by the FDA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Over Declining Birth Rates Among Younger Generations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/declining-birth-rate-younger-generations-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the global population is still growing, a major study from 2020 predicts it will peak in 2064 and then fall by nearly a billion people by the end of the century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 15 killed, dozen hospitalized in California crash... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-us-news-el-centro-33f54179647c0a7160c527b35163887d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El CENTRO, Calif. (AP) — An SUV believed to be carrying 27 people crashed Tuesday into a semitruck in Southern California, killing 15 people and leaving others injured, hospital officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military May Make Jab MANDATORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/03/01/military-may-revisit-making-covid-19-vaccines-mandatory-after-fda-grants-approval.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military leaders are unable to force service members to get the COVID vaccinations at this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of personnel refusing to take...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316827/A-military-personnel-refusing-receive-COVID-19-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some units just 30% of enlistees are willing to have a shot - despite the fact that the coronavirus pandemic continues to rage across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS and WALGREENS to use customer data for 'keeping in touch' and promoting services...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316739/Prepare-onslaught-texts-coupons-COVID-shot-CVS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans can get their vaccines from pharmacies like CVS and Walgreens, but as customers book their appointments they'll also be sharing their data so the retailers can promote their services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says domestic terrorism cases have soared in recent months...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/FBI-director-says-domestic-terrorism-cases-have-15993309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- FBI Director Christopher Wray said Tuesday that his agents are pursuing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vernon Jordan dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Vernon-Jordan-lawyer-and-D-C-political-power-15993038.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vernon Jordan never held elective office, was never a member of the Cabinet and never...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay men detained after kissing on Mexican beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/crowd-rallies-around-gay-men-detained-on-mexico-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of people on a beach in Mexico rallied around three men who were being detained by police after someone reportedly complained about “obscene acts of exhibitionism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Threatens Retribution...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-03-02/biden-sanctions-putins-inner-circle-for-navalny-imprisonment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move, though largely symbolic, represents an abrupt departure from the way President Donald Trump approached Russia, White House officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHMIDT GROUP:  USA not prepared to defend or compete in the A.I. era...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/02/us-not-prepared-to-defend-or-compete-in-ai-era-says-eric-schmidt-group.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is drastically underprepared for the age of AI, according to the National Security Commission on AI, which is chaired by Eric Schmidt.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
