<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GORBACHEV: Peace In Jeopardy...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5471437/mikhail-gorbachev-george-hw-bush-war-peace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A remembrance by the only President of the USSR</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly brain-dead woman survives after being removed from life support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/nearly-brain-dead-woman-survives-after-being-removed-life-support-n944276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michele De Leeuw, of Sterling Heights, Michigan, has almost fully recovered after open heart surgery, speech and physical therapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Heading To SUNDANCE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/sundance-2019-new-frontiers-lineup-eminem-arthur-ashe-movies-1202514594/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No word yet if Eminem will be showing up in Park City for one of those late night concerts that only happen at Sundance but the Oscar winning 8 Mile star is certainly part of the New Frontier slate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not enough to contain public anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c692e0741894b4cb8b7c120382bf4db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on mass protests in France (all times local): 9:20 p.m. French protesters are welcoming President Emmanuel Macron's decision to scrap a fuel tax rise planned for next year — but say it may not be enough to contain public anger. Jacline Mouraud, one of the group's self-proclaimed spokespeople, told The Associated Press "I think it comes much too late." She said each of the disparate protesting groups will decide what to do next, but many will probably keep protesting. She says Macron's move on Wednesday night "is on the right path but in my opinion it will not fundamentally change the movement." She urged protesters to seize on the French government's weakness to push other demands such as a rise in the minimum wage. The anti-government protests started last month over the fuel tax but have grown to encompass a broad range of grievances and anger at Macron. More protests are planned Saturday in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg, 25 years after 'SCHINDLER'S LIST,' warns against collective hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nightly-news/spielberg-25-years-after-schindler-s-list-warns-against-collective-n944416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When collective hate organizes and gets industrialized, then genocide follows," the legendary director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board Backs Sandberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-board-backs-sheryl-sandbergs-handling-of-research-into-investor-george-soros-1544038662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s board said it backs Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg’s handling of research into George Soros, calling her request to probe whether the investor shorted the company’s stock “entirely appropriate.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC radio host found dead after walking out during show...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/bbc-radio-presenter-found-dead-walking-mid-way-radio-show-inquest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BBC radio presenter found dead at her home hours after leaving work mid-way through her radio show intended to take her own life, a coroner has ruled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRAZY RICH ASIANS' flops in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-isnt-crazy-at-all-about-crazy-rich-asians-1544031975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hit U.S. movie has turned out to be a flop in the world’s largest population of Asians, where it plays to empty theaters; “Americans just don’t understand us.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Caves...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/latest-leading-protest-activist-macron-speak-59624047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on mass protests in France (all times local): 8:55 p.m. French President Emmanuel Macron has scrapped a fuel tax rise amid fears of new violence, after weeks of nationwide protests and the worst rioting in Paris in decades. An official with the Elysee palace told The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Launches 20th Rocket Of Year, But Can't Stick Landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/05/spacex-launches-its-20th-rocket-of-the-year-but-doesnt-quite-make-the-landing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX has successfully launched its 20th rocket of the year, a mission to the International Space Station (ISS) to take food and supplies, after a problem with some mice food on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES columnist hit by bus awarded $85M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/05/new-york-times-columnist-hit-by-sightseeing-bus-awarded-85m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “Vows” columnist for the New York Times who was run over by a double-decker sightseeing bus won a whopping $85 million award from a Manhattan jury late Tuesday. Devan Sipher, who desc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest 84 in European crackdown on Italian mob...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a6b91b27ea7404c9b29c77212e85f5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — In an investigation that underscored an Italian crime syndicate's role as a leading player in international cocaine trafficking, police in four countries arrested at least 84 suspected mobsters Wednesday in a series of carefully coordinated raids. Those detained allegedly work for the Italian 'ndrangheta criminal network that traffics in cocaine on a global scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New satellite images reveal activity at unidentified NKorea missile base...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/north-korea-satellite-images-missile-base/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New satellite images obtained exclusively by CNN reveal North Korea has significantly expanded a key long-range missile base located in the mountainous interior of the country, offering yet another reminder that diplomatic talks with the US have done little to prevent Kim Jong Un from pursuing his promise to mass produce and deploy the existing types of nuclear warheads in his arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug dealer released from prison carjacks woman in parking lot...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/local/westmoreland/14371705-74/police-youngwood-carjacking-suspect-attacked-woman-outside-westmoreland-county-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Philadelphia man's freedom from the Westmoreland County Prison on Tuesday was short-lived. Moments after Thomas Lee Williams, 36, was released from the Hempfield jail at about 6:15 p.m., police said he attacked a West Leechburg woman in the parking lot, took her sport-utility vehicle and fled with her 1-year-old ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY tower suggested as source of Legionnaires disease...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8cca373502854283815c8a9bb4dd067f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A cooling tower that provides mist to make Disneyland visitors comfortable was the likely source for 22 cases in a Legionnaires' disease outbreak last year near the theme park, a health official testified this week. Most of those who got sick visited the park in the fall of 2017. Disneyland has denied it was the source, pointing to three infected people who had been in the city of Anaheim where Disneyland is located, but not at the park itself. One of them died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops, medics called on mob after CHEESECAKE FACTORY offers free slices...</title>
      <link>https://www.arlnow.com/2018/12/05/developing-large-crowd-reported-at-clarendon-cheesecake-factory-amid-free-cheesecake-promotion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arlnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Updated at 2:15 p.m.) Arlington County police and medics have responded to Clarendon after a promotion for free cheesecake got out of control. Police were called to the area of the Cheesecake Factory at 2900 Clarendon Blvd earlier today for a report of a large crowd and heavy traffic in the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Employees Have Difficulty Breathing After Being Exposed To Animal Repellent...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/firefighters-respond-to-amazon-warehouse-in-robbinsville-after-reports-of-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are looking into "fumes" that reportedly caused the employees to have difficulty breathing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students Caught On Video Having Sex In High School Hallway...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/lawrence-high-school-video-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Public Schools are investigating a video of two students engaged in a sexual act on the high school campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old horse being led to slaughter saves self with great escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article222657875.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alachua County Sheriff’s Office announced a happy ending for the horse that was injured after falling from a trailer on a Florida highway last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W:  The Brightest of  Thousand Points of Light'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-w-bush-eulogizes-his-father-the-brightest-of-a-thousand-points-of-light/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 VISION:  Michael Bloomberg heads to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/bloomberg-iowa-alesci-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg says now that Democrats have won the House, they have to "do something."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY MAG deletes story calling Priyanka Chopra 'scam artist'...</title>
      <link>https://scroll.in/reel/904658/us-website-takes-down-offensive-article-calling-priyanka-chopra-a-global-scam-artist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scroll.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Upon further editorial review, we found this story did not meet our standards,’ said a note on the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Republican Lawmakers Pass Bills to Restrict New Dem Governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wisconsin-gop-lawmakers-pass-bills-to-restrict-new-democratic-governor-1544027159</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin’s Republican-led legislature on Wednesday passed bills that would strip some powers of the incoming Democratic governor, Tony Evers, and curb early voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Cuomo Becomes Most-Watched Anchor on CNN...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/chris-cuomo-ratings-cnn-cable-news-1203080856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has learned that there’s nothing wrong with a little attitude. In just six months, the network’s new 9 p.m. program, “Cuomo Prime Time,” has become the most-watched show on the AT&amp;T-owned c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Dems really do love Republicans  --  when they're dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/04/democrats-really-do-love-republicans-when-theyre-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was a patriot, a hero, a ­genial gentleman and a great American. You can’t pick up a newspaper or go near a television without hearing leftists gush with praise for the late President George H.W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEACHEM: Bush 'A 20th Century Founding Father'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/historian-jon-meacham-delivers-stirring-eulogy-at-george-h-w-bushs-funeral-a-20th-century-founding-father/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Moonves Destroyed Evidence, Misled Investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/les-moonves-obstructed-investigation-into-misconduct-claims-report-says/ar-BBQvr67?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL TOGETHER FOR AN HOUR!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0e443c78c337423db71b9270303888c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The nation's capital is bidding its final farewell to former President George H.W. Bush on Wednesday in a service of prayer and praise that has drawn together world envoys, Americans of high office and many others who were touched by Bush's life in office and afterward. A military band played "Hail to the Chief" as the casket of the 41st president was carried down the U.S. Capitol steps in a solemn procession, with members of the Bush family watching and a cannon salute. His son, former President George W. Bush, placed his hand over his heart. Military pallbearers carried the casket up the steps to the cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clintons snub Trumps?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/bitter-clintons-snub-trumps-at-bush-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton is still bitter. The failed presidential candidate snubbed President Donald and First Lady Melania Trump as the entered former President George H.W. Bush’s funeral today. Watch: ﻿ “President Trump shaking the hands of the Obamas. The Clintons did not acknowledge President Trump,” the CBSN anchor noted. Hillary stared forward as Trump acknowledged the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Is This It?  A Trump-Hater's Guide to Mueller Skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/a-trump-haters-guide-to-mueller-skepticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel is going to put together one hell of a report. But even the president’s foes should ask themselves: was it worth it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEACE IN OUR TIME!  No Trump-slamming at  ceremony 'after deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7903860/george-hw-bush-funeral-no-trump-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE HW’s funeral won’t feature any criticism of Donald Trump after the president “cut a deal with the Bush family” to ensure he wouldn’t be targeted. The US President was disin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC REMEMBERS BUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6463597/George-H-W-Bush-funeral-Final-salute-41st-President.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president died on Friday at his home in Houston, Texas, aged 94 on Friday. His death has silenced political disputes and has brought the country to a standstill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY JEER IN WISCONSIN:  Scott Walker shouted down over Republican attempt to weaken his successor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d95d1190247b4bc6a611c053214cf77e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Demonstrators booed outgoing Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker on Tuesday during a Christmas tree-lighting ceremony, a sign of tumult as Republicans in the Legislature met to push through measures to gut the powers of his Democratic successor. The Legislature met deep into the night Tuesday to pass a series of bills, first unveiled Friday, that would weaken the governor's office and transfer power away from the Democratic-elect attorney general and give it to the Legislature. The Legislature wasn't expected to complete its work until early Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Tensions Boiling Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/charliewarzel/facebooks-tensions-zuckerberg-sandberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s the bunker mentality. These people have been under siege for 600 days now. They’re getting tired, getting cranky — the only survival strategy is to quit or fully buy in.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He thinks he's God': Macron's style fuels French protesters' ire...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/thinks-hes-god-macrons-style-fuels-french-protesters-140657294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French have soured on their 40-year-old President Emmanuel Macron who has been heckled and booed in recent days as he grapples with a tax revolt. Why does he inspire such hatred among "yellow vest" protesters? At a blockade outside a fuel depot in the city of Le Mans -- famous for motor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 1 in 3 US physicians born abroad...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-12-physicians-born.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when immigration is a hot-button issue, the American health care system is highly dependent on professionals born in other countries, an analysis of U.S. census data shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special access to user data...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-k-releases-internal-facebook-emails-deliberating-data-access-1544022496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.K. Parliament released about 250 pages of internal Facebook Inc. emails that lawmakers said show how the social-media company gave some developers special access to user data and contemplated charging developers for data access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUTANT DOUBLE-MUSCLE 'FRANKENSWINE' PIGS SOLD ON FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7905141/sperm-mutant-double-muscle-pigs-facebook-frankenswine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN AMBITIOUS pig farmer raising muscle-bound mutant porkers for the bacon market is selling their sperm on Facebook. The Cambodian-based breeder is flogging the semen – along with inseminatio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Accuser Speaks Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/new-les-moonves-accuser-speaks-what-i-told-cbs-investigators-1166407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;June Seley Kimmel, who has recounted her experience with the ousted CBS mogul to company lawyers, recalls her traumatic 1985 encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC REMEMBERS BUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6462365/George-H-W-Bushs-funeral-held-Washington-DC-attended-four-ex-presidents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George H.W. Bush will be given a public farewell in the Washington National Cathedral on Wednesday, with four ex presidents in attendance, led by his son George W. Bush, who will give a eulogy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: FUNERAL</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?455342-1/president-george-hw-bush-state-funeral-service&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A National Day of Mourning includes a state funeral service for former President George H.W. Bush at the Washington National Cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret FACEBOOK documents published...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-documents-six4three-case-published-british-parliament-2018-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British parliament has published a cache of secret Facebook documents which it obtained from Six4Three.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversal?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-05/after-historic-commons-contempt-vote-jpm-raises-odds-no-brexit-40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUNERAL: LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9yhgCDfQX08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stream your PBS favorites with the PBS app: https://to.pbs.org/2Jb8twG Find more from PBS NewsHour at https://www.pbs.org/newshour Subscribe to our YouTube c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Penn in Istanbul to film Khashoggi documentary: reports...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/sean-penn-istanbul-film-khashoggi-documentary-reports-141405549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American actor Sean Penn was in Istanbul on Wednesday to film a documentary about the murder of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in the kingdom's consulate, Turkish media reported. In one image shared by state news agency Anadolu, two-time Oscar winner Penn was seen outside the mission where the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ceremonies for Bush draw together presidents, world envoys...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0e443c78c337423db71b9270303888c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The nation's capital bids its final farewell to the late former President George H.W. Bush on Wednesday in a service of prayer and praise that is drawing together world envoys, Americans of high office and a guy from Maine who used to fix things in Bush's house on the water. A viewing for the 41st president at the hushed Capitol Rotunda closed Wednesday morning. A ceremony at Washington National Cathedral, the nexus of state funerals, will cap three days of remembrance by dignitaries and ordinary citizens as they honored the Republican president who oversaw the post-Cold War transition and led a successful Gulf War, only to lose re-election in a generational shift to Democrat Bill Clinton in 1992.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has Bluetooth COMPASS implanted in chest; Can 'feel' North...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/man-bluetooth-compass-implanted-chest-13689144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chip vibrates every time Liviu Babitz faces north, transforming his body into a functioning navigational system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant cyborg able to move self to preferred light source...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2018-12-cyborg-source.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of researchers at the MIT Media Lab built a cyborg that combines a plant with electronics and ultimately allows the plant to choose when it would like to move to a brighter spot. The cyborg is the brainchild of team leader Harpreet Sareen, and he has named it Elowan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Shows Off Laser Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/russia-shows-off-new-laser-weapon-after-u-s-threatens-1830874116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian state media published video earlier today of its latest laser weapons system, the Peresvet. The move comes just a day after the U.S. said it would likely pull out of a key arms treaty between the two countries, and the timing of the video’s release doesn’t appear to be a coincidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoids Join Students In High School Classroom...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/04/robots-join-students-in-boston-high-school-classroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a unique adventure in learning, with an eye towards the future and what these robots can do is entirely up to the students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE ROBOTAXI SERVICE</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/autos/la-fi-hy-waymo-one-20181205-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waymo's driverless taxi service will start with only a few hundred customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE launches nation's first commercial self-driving taxi service in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/12/5/18126103/waymo-one-self-driving-taxi-service-ride-safety-alphabet-cost-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Google self-driving car project is going commercial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKET CLAWS BACK?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/05/us-futures-following-tuesdays-market-rout-stateside.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures implied a slight recovery for the major indexes when they return to trade on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby Jesus In CAGE Part Of Church's 'Immigration-Themed' Nativity Scene...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/dedham-nativity-scene-saint-susana-parish-immigration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Massachusetts church that made headlines over its nativity scene last Christmas is attracting attention again this holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Kelly documentary premiere cancelled after shooting threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/05/surviving-r-kelly-documentary-premiere-cancelled-after-shooting-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anonymous caller claimed that an audience member would fire a gun if the documentary, detailing allegations of sexual assault by the R&amp;B singer, was screened, reports say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemicals in frying pans, fast food packaging shrink penises...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6462775/Mens-penises-half-inch-smaller-chemicals-non-stick-frying-pans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Padua in Italy found chemicals called PFCs, which are in hundreds of everyday items, can lower testosterone levels in babies and teenagers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby name 'Melania' soars 227%, Ivanka spikes 362%...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/baby-name-melania-soars-227-ivanka-spikes-362</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump women are popular in hospital nurseries with new parents looking to name the babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of new arms race...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6462505/Moscow-receives-notification-US-ditching-key-arms-treaty.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin's remarks come after US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said the US will suspend its obligations under the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty in 60 days, citing Russian 'cheating.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest billionaire, 100, still goes to office every day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/05/worlds-oldest-billionaire-yun-chung-chang-goes-to-work-every-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's my habit. I cannot stay at home," says Chang Yun Chung, founder of Pacific International Lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelter says starved Great Dane ate own foot to survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/south-carolina/article222649830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An animal shelter in South Carolina says it has rescued a starved Great Dane that ate one of his own feet to survive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba set to tighten screws on private sector...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181205-cuba-set-tighten-screws-private-sector</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba set to tighten screws on private sector</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt tax revenues record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oecd-tax/government-tax-takes-at-record-high-with-france-in-top-spot-oecd-idUSKBN1O411Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France overtook Denmark as the most taxed country in 2017 as government tax reve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women with longer fingers 'more likely to cheat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6459875/How-tell-girlfriend-cheat-Check-FINGERS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An academic at Oxford University studied 274 women's fingers and concluded that women with long index fingers on their left hands are more likely to have affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog owner revives newborn puppy with mouth-to-mouth resuscitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6462403/Dog-owner-revives-lifeless-newborn-Husky-puppy-mouth-mouth-resuscitation-heart-massage.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dog gave birth to six puppies in Samut Sakhon, central Thailand. One was born not breathing. Owner owner Nontawit Vasee brought it back to life by blowing air into its mouth and massaging its heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danes Spar Over Island to House Deportees...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/danes-spar-over-island-to-house-deportees-1543958866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tiny teardrop-shaped island off the coast of Denmark has become the focus of a dispute between the government and human-rights campaigners over how the country treats failed asylum seekers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring hospital admissions for stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/soaring-hospital-admissions-stress-amid-office-culture-never/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital admissions for stress and anxiety have risen by more than a quarter in a decade, amid the rise of a working culture that never &amp;ldquo;switches off,&amp;rdquo; new figures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump eyes Post Office price hike for AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-post-office-trump/trump-panel-wants-to-give-usps-right-to-hike-prices-for-amazon-others-idUSKBN1O32MC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Postal Service should have more flexibility to raise rates for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Sculpture Installed At Illinois Statehouse, Just In Time For Holidays...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/12/04/673422143/satanic-sculpture-installed-at-illinois-statehouse-just-in-time-for-the-holidays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a Nativity scene for Christmas, a menorah for Hanukkah, and something a little different: an arm holding an apple, with a snake coiled around it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia U Students Throw 'SNL' Writer Off Stage for 'Offensive' Jokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/12/04/snl-comedian-nimesh-patel-kicked-off-columbia-university-stage-by-offended-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday Night Live comedian Nimesh Patel was kicked off stage by Columbia University students on Friday night halfway through his performance because students found his jokes "offensive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72% of Immigrant Households in CA on Welfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/12/04/study-more-than-7-in-10-california-immigrant-households-are-on-welfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 7-in-10 households headed by immigrants in the state of California are on taxpayer-funded welfare, a new study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat to journalists at highest level in 10 years, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/dec/05/threat-journalists-highest-level-10-years-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy-eight journalists killed and 326 imprisoned around world last year, study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test to detect cancer within just 10 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/12/04/blood-test-detect-cancer-within-just-10-minutes-developed-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A blood test can detect cancer within just 10 minutes, scientists have found, raising hopes that hard-to-spot diseases could be picked up early when treatment is most effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's protesters are part of global backlash against climate change taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/France-s-protesters-are-part-of-a-global-backlash-13443080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The single most effective weapon in the fight against climate change is the tax code - imposing costs on those who emit greenhouse gases, economists say. But as French President Emmanuel Macron learned over the past three weeks, implementing such taxes can be politically explosive. On Tuesday, France delayed for six months a plan to raise already steep taxes on diesel fuel by 24 cents a gallon and gasoline by about 12 cents a gallon. Macron argued that the taxes were needed to curb climate change by weaning motorists off petroleum products, but violent demonstrations in the streets of Paris and other French cities forced him to backtrack - at least for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive work for Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/mueller-gives-new-details-flynn-s-secretive-work-turkey-n943926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors for special counsel Robert Mueller say that Flynn’s lies "impeded the ability of the public" to know the extent of Turkey's efforts to influence public opinion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF's Lagarde urges USA, others to reject 'dystopian' path...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181205-imfs-lagarde-urges-us-others-reject-dystopian-path</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMF's Lagarde urges US, others to reject 'dystopian' path</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind reading breakthrough: Scientists can now 'see thoughts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/746267/mind-reading-brain-map-scientists-neurons-rats-hippocampus-jozsef-csicsvari</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Substantial assistance' to probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/robert-mueller-files-sentencing-memo-trump-ex-national-security-adviser-michael-flynn-today-2018-12-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former national security adviser Michael Flynn admitted last year he had lied to the FBI about his contacts with Russian Ambassador Sergey Kislyak after the 2016 election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service testing facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/419762-secret-service-testing-use-of-facial-recognition-outside-of-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A facial recognition program is being tested by the U.S. Secret Service in the vicinity of the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$68 MILLION?  Miami Beach penthouse could smash Florida record...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/04/this-miami-beach-penthouse-could-smash-a-florida-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive Miami Beach penthouse at the 66-unit Eighty Seven Park is poised to hit the market Wednesday — and with a massive price tag to match. The duplex pad, with 12,410 square feet of inte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Spends $300K On Private Jet Travel In One Month...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/04/bernie-sanders-private-jet-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Climate change is a planetary crisis'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer crashes through cop car's windshield...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/deer/deer-accident-650921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Carolina cop escaped injury Monday night when a deer, struck by another motorist, went airborne and crashed through a patrol car window, landing in the cruiser’s front seat. According to cop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Lose $120 Million Payout... </title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/les-moonves-lose-120-million-payout-obstructing-investigators-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times says a report by CBS's lawyers found that CBS can withhold Les Moonves' $120 million payment because he obstructed them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK ON THE BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/12/04/brexit-deal-latest-mps-vote-contempt-motion-theresamay-pleads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May suffered humiliation on an historic scale on Tuesday as her Government became the first to be found in contempt of Parliament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER FILES FLYNN SENTENCING MEMO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/04/robert-mueller-sentencing-memo-for-former-trump-advisor-michael-flynn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel in a sentencing memo said Michael Flynn's "substantial assistance" to his probe warrants a light criminal sentence — which could include no jail time for the retired Army lieutentant general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High School Newspaper Suspended After Publishing 'Disruptive' Investigation...</title>
      <link>http://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/12/04/high-school-newspaper-suspended-after-publishing-disruptive-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High school students in northwest Arkansas are getting an unforgettable lesson on censorship and First Amendment rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web troubles:  'Everyone's for Sale'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/a-generation-of-digital-media-darlings-prepares-for-a-frigid-winter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice, Vox, and BuzzFeed, which once heralded the dawn of a new media age, are now grappling with decidedly old-media problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing 'substantial assistance' to probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/special-counsel-robert-mueller-s-office-recommends-little-no-jail-n943446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flynn "provided firsthand information about the content and context of interactions between the transition team and Russian government officials," the memo says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sat for 19 interviews with special counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/flynn-mueller-filing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller told a federal court Tuesday that former Trump national security adviser Michael Flynn has given "substantial assistance" to the Russia investigation and should not get jail time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller recommends no prison time for Flynn...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/mueller-files-key-sentencing-recommendation-trump-adviser-michael/story?id=59597161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller has issued a highly-anticipated sentencing memo for retired Lt. Gen. Michael Flynn, the president’s former national security adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/12/4/18126388/mueller-michael-flynn-sentencing-memo-read</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s former national security adviser pleaded guilty to lying to the FBI about his contacts with the Russian ambassador.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Moonves Obstructed Investigation Into Misconduct Claims, Report Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/business/media/les-moonves-cbs-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leslie Moonves, the former CBS chief, destroyed evidence and misled investigators looking into his alleged misconduct, according to a draft of a report prepared for the company’s board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Hart to host OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/academy-eyes-kevin-hart-host-oscars-1155972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star and comedian is emceeing the event for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free tickets to NFL game fail to fill stadium...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/12/04/free-tickets-didnt-fill-up-tampa-bays-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Buccaneers, desperate to fill Raymond James Stadium, offered two free tickets to every season-ticket holder for last Sunday’s game against the Panthers. It didn’t work. As recently …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury developments come with sky ports for flying cars...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/04/luxury-miami-developments-now-come-with-sky-ports-for-flying-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami is now cleared for takeoff — launching its first three luxury residences with their own rooftop landing pads. The Paramount Miami Worldcenter — a 27-acre mixed-use super project that claims t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to disguise weapons as useless space junk to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7901568/space-spy-satellites-weapons-junk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE United States may have come up with a novel way of concealing its spy satellites – by concealing them in ever-increasing amounts of space junk, according to reports. Jim Cantrell, who set up hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCARDMICROSOFT Plan For 'Universal Digital ID'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276216/mastercard-and-microsoft-announce-frightening-universal-id-partnership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two companies are creating “digital identity” solutions that will definitely alarm privacy activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: GOOGLE gives different results for different users who search identical terms...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-search-leaves-users-dark-duckduck-go-ceo-214438103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you use Google’s search engine, “There’s no way of knowing what you’re missing,” says Gabriel Weinberg, CEO and founder of search engine DuckDuckGo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Man handcuffs roommate to chair, hammers ICE PICK through genitals...</title>
      <link>https://fox13now.com/2018/12/04/police-utah-man-arrested-after-driving-tool-resembling-ice-pick-into-housemates-genitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAYLORSVILLE, Utah -- Police say a man held another man at gunpoint, bound him to a chair and then told him he could choose between death in the desert or having a nail hammered through his genitals. According to charging documents filed September 5, the assault occurred on August 30 in Salt Lake County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Baby it's cold outside' returns to radio airwaves, listeners vote 'not offensive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/local-news/-baby-it-s-cold-outside-returns-to-denver-airwaves-after-feedback-from-kosi-1011-listeners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A classic holiday song some say promotes a corrupt message of consent is back on the radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK removes post accusing it of having 'black people problem'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/facebook-temporarily-pulls-down-post-by-ex-employee-who-accused-tech-firm-of-black-people-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of the post says the removal proves his point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born via uterus transplant from deceased donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/12/04/for-the-first-time-a-baby-is-born-via-a-uterus-transplant-from-a-deceased-donor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers said that if transplant teams can reliably use uteruses from deceased donors, it could expand the availability of organs for those in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ brings charges in first 'Panama Papers' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/panama-papers-investigation-four-men-charged-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say quartet went to ‘extraordinary lengths to circumvent US tax laws’ to boost the wealth of their clients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO HUDDLES WITH OBAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/beto-orourke-met-with-barack-obama-as-he-ponders-a-2020-presidential-campaign/2018/12/04/fa895cc8-f7fb-11e8-8d64-4e79db33382f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting occurred as some Democrats, including former Obama aides, implored the Texas congressman to form his own hope-and-change candidacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAANG stocks shed $140,000,000,000 in market rout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/04/faang-stocks-shed-140-billion-in-tuesdays-market-rout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The losses extend pain periods for Apple and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Maneuvers to Snag Top-Secret Satellite Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-maneuvers-to-snag-top-secret-boeing-satellite-technology-1543943490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founders of a small Los Angeles company, which ordered a satellite from Boeing, say the firm was financed and is now controlled by China, in violation of rules designed to keep such technology out of Beijing’s hands. Some worry China could use the technology for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ charges 4 in first 'Panama Papers' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/justice-department-charges-four-in-its-first-panama-papers-case-2018-12-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATES: Lesser-knowns to share stage with front-runners?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/wary-of-repeating-2016-mistakes-democrats-prepare-to-shake-up-2020-presidential-debate-plan/2018/12/04/cd50e8c6-f741-11e8-8c9a-860ce2a8148f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party was chided last cycle as deferring to the needs of Hillary Clinton over other candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturers struggle to find workers, turn to high schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2018/12/04/US-manufacturers-struggling-to-find-workers-turning-to-high-schools/7841543589283/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across America, manufacturing companies in desperate need of skilled labor are turning to a previously untapped pool -- high school students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Arab Emirates now world's most powerful passport...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/travel/news/article.cfm?c_id=7&amp;objectid=12170816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Arab Emirates now has access to the greatest number of countries visa-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of WEEKLY STANDARD uncertain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/media/weekly-standard-future-uncertain/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fate of The Weekly Standard, the conservative magazine that has staked out a position as a publication on the right still critical of President Donald Trump, is uncertain, Editor-in-Chief Stephen Hayes told staff in a series of phone calls Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
