<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Foreign policy setbacks raising questions; 'We're courting danger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/05/11/trump-foreign-policy-foiled-amid-new-crises-iran-north-korea-venezuela/1158106001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has suffered a series of stunning foreign policy setbacks this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden entry provides jolt to Bernie candidacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-s-entry-into-the-Democratic-race-provides-a-13838004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's been no more consistent performer in the field of Democratic presidential candidates than Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt. From the day he first announced his candidacy in the spring of 2015 straight on through to today, as he makes his second run for the White House, his message has remained constant, his style has varied not at all. Bernie is Bernie.  The policy ideas he put forward in the 2016 race, during his surprisingly strong challenge to Hillary Clinton, have become more broadly accepted within the Democratic Party. He has defined and expanded the party's progressive wing and given voice to liberals who found Barack Obama's presidency disappointing for its timidity in areas of policy. He has made the words "democratic socialism" part of the political lexicon.  Sanders has redefined presidential fundraising, demonstrating in 2016 that the traditional approach of relying on wealthy individuals to write checks for the maximum allowed under the law and building a big team of bundlers who would raise hundreds of thousands of campaign dollars through their personal networks wasn't the only way. Sanders showed that small but regular contributions from hundreds of thousands of people can fuel and sustain an underdog candidacy.  The senator from Vermont's first-quarter performance - financially, politically and rhetorically - helped establish him as a power in the contest for the nomination. As the Democratic field took shape in those earlier months, he became the biggest name and impressed some of the skeptics who discounted him.  But Sanders is no longer the biggest name in the field. That title now goes to former Vice President Joe Biden, who became a candidate just two weeks ago. His entry into the 2020 fray and the initial impact of his candidacy have pointed to questions about the trajectory of Sanders' candidacy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete to Trump Over Nickname: 'What, Me Worry?'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mayor-pete-president-trump-over-164238311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To those of a certain age -- particularly white men -- Alfred E. Neuman was the geeky, gap-toothed, smiling face of subversion featured in Mad Magazine. As a result, Buttigieg, the 37-year-old South Bend, Indiana, mayor running for the 2020 Democratic nomination, had no idea what Trump was talking about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXORCIST: Temptation Most Significant Demonic Activity...</title>
      <link>http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/exorcist-temptation-not-possession-is-the-most-significant-demonic-activity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ncregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exorcist since 1994, Dominican Father Francois Dermine serves in the Italian Archdiocese of Ancona-Osimo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/11/severe-weather-houston-faces-more-flooding-la-state-emergency/1174543001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a one day break from heavy rain, water-logged Houston braced for another round from a lingering storm system that hasÂ prompted the governor of Louisiana to declare a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: How Much Coffee Too Much? 6 Cups In Day Bad For Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drinking-six-cups-coffee-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's no shortage of research showing how drinking coffee is good for health, but is there a point where consuming too much can be harmful?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police using facial recognition daily -- raising privacy concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/how-facial-recognition-became-routine-policing-tool-america-n1004251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology is proliferating amid concerns that it is prone to errors and allows the government to expand surveillance without much oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is what world's largest single-room speaker system sounds like...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/london-royal-albert-hall-this-is-what-the-worlds-largest-single-room-speaker-system-sounds-like/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Albert Hall now sounds as beautiful as it looks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hits retweet button 60 times in massive TWITTER spree...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/11/trump-hits-retweet-button-60-times-in-massive-twitter-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump went on a retweeting spree Saturday morning, sharing other conservative voices more than 60 times. The tweets covered many of the president’s passions, ranging from border sec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor plans to withdraw life support in French right-to-die case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/doctor-plans-withdraw-life-support-french-die-case-153912341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor of a Frenchman whose family has kept him alive in a vegetative state for a decade has informed them that he plans to take the patient off life support this month, lawyers said Saturday. Vincent Lambert, 42, was left a tetraplegic after a car accident in 2008, with doctors later determining</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Crash Fight Will Set Price on Victims' Minutes of Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-11/boeing-crash-fight-will-set-price-on-victims-minutes-of-terror </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's status of the wall?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/10/trump-wants-border-wall-what-status-its-construction/1145825001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's signature campaign promise was the construction of a wall on the southern border. Is the wall being built?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside HUAWEI where staff forced to sleep under desk on 'endless' shifts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9051537/huawei-campus-pictures-factory-china-5g-spy-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE fascinating pictures show the grim reality of life inside Huawei’s £1.2bn research and development centre – where exhausted employees sleep at their desks and endure endless gruel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Sex Lives of Nuns...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-secret-sex-lives-of-nuns </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question of sex in the sanctuary is not always one of victimization for women. What is certain is that it is complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detention cells so overcrowded US using aircraft to move migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Border-detention-cells-in-Texas-are-so-13837856.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overcrowding at Border Patrol stations in South Texas has become so acute in recent days that U.S. authorities have taken the rare step of using aircraft to relocate migrants to other areas of the border simply to begin processing them, according to three Homeland Security officials.  The first flight left McAllen, Texas, on Friday, transferring detainees to Border Patrol facilities in Del Rio, Texas. There are daily flights scheduled for the next several days, with two planned for Tuesday, according to officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the operations.  The flights are conducted by U.S. Customs and Immigration Enforcement, but the detainees remain in the custody of Border Patrol, officials said. Though ICE routinely uses aircraft to move detainees among its detention facilities, it is very unusual for Border Patrol to fly recent arrivals from one part of the border to another to perform routine booking procedures.  Homeland Security officials requested the aircraft because Border Patrol urgently needs to move single adults out of the lower Rio Grande Valley of South Texas. The agency is scrambling to make room for the large volume of families and children who have come across the border in dramatically higher numbers in the past several days, officials said.  One official said the U.S. government has resorted to using aircraft because all available buses were already in use and authorities needed every available transportation option.  "This is the worst I have ever seen it, by far," said one veteran Border Patrol agent in South Texas who was not authorized to speak to reporters.  The number of people taken into custody along the Mexico border has exceeded 5,500 each day for several days in a row, and Border Patrol currently has more than 17,500 people in holding cells and tent sites set up in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat to donate brain after suffering mysterious injury in China...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/11/diplomat-to-donate-his-brain-after-suffering-mysterious-injury-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US diplomat who suffered a mysterious brain injury in China — and believes it was a microwave attack by a foreign government — has pledged to donate his brain to the Concussion Legacy Foundation.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of rage: Are we really living in angrier times?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/11/all-fired-up-are-we-really-living-angrier-times</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a world in which populists whip up anger that spreads on social media, it’s easy to conclude we have never been more furious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Spending Sets Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/2573708000000-federal-spending-sets-all-time-record-through-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela braces for fresh protests as Maduro clamps down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guaido-deputy-being-held-military-prison-165946513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela braced Saturday for another day of nationwide protests after President Nicolas Maduro clamped down further on opposition leader Juan Guaido, locking up his deputy in a military prison following a dramatic arrest. Edgar Zambrano, deputy speaker of the opposition-majority National Assembly,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Names Its Price...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-names-trade-deal-price-060802514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wide-ranging interview with Chinese media after talks in Washington ended Friday, Vice Premier Liu He said that in order to reach an agreement the U.S. must remove all extra tariffs, set targets for Chinese purchases of goods in line with real demand and ensure that the text of the deal is “balanced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climber's Camera Captures 60-Foot Free-Fall Off Rock Face; Miraculously Lives...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/05/10/kyle-walker-flatiron-fall-scrambler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who fell while climbing the Flatirons in Boulder is hoping video of the incident while serve as a warning to others. On April 16, Kyle Walker was climbing the second Flatiron in Boulder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida takes shape as Biden firewall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/11/joe-biden-florida-1317604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president is crushing the Democratic field in the nation’s third-largest state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-impeach? Talk shifts toward defiance of Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/55869d792c66493e97c5c96ea87dc8ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi has introduced a new concept into the debate over President Donald Trump's actions: "self-impeaching." As Trump all but goads Democrats into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto plans 'reintroduction' as 2020 buzz fizzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1e32cf3855734117b0aa1a1d55867b6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWTON, Iowa (AP) — Beto O'Rourke barreled into the 2020 presidential race with breakneck energy and a fly-by-the-seat-of-his-pants campaign style that saw him leap atop tables to address overflow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LORD OF AMAZON WANTS MOON'S WATER</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/05/jeff-bezos-moon-nasa/589150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon CEO unveiled a sleek-looking lunar lander—and he hopes the White House takes notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The extraordinary battle over an aging Hollywood titan's care...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/the-extraordinary-battle-over-an-aging-hollywood-titan-s-care/article_19247d1d-3656-53ef-9f83-0844b31c3e49.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Last May, Eric Semel, the eldest child and only son of former Warner Bros. chief Terry Semel, filed a petition in Los Angeles County Superior Court to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Will Measles Break Out Next? Chicago, L.A. or Miami, Scientists Predict...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-met-cook-county-worst-measles-outbreak-risk-20190509-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers who in 2015 correctly predicted where the Zika outbreak would strike now are placing their scientifically backed bets on the next measles outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assault ship, missiles to Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-sends-assault-ship-missiles-mideast-amid-iran-220835740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon announced Friday that it is deploying an amphibious assault ship and a Patriot missile battery to the Middle East to bolster an aircraft carrier force sent to counter alleged threats from Iran. The USS Arlington, which transports marines, amphibious vehicles, conventional landing craft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff intensifies as Dems subpoena Trump tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/standoff-intensifies-democrats-subpoena-trump-tax-returns-214443035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US House Democrats issued subpoenas Friday against top government officials demanding President Donald Trump's tax returns, the latest twist in the sharpening battle between the White House and opponents in Congress. House Ways and Means Committee chairman Richard Neal said he subpoenaed Treasury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriot system deployed...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pentagon-deploying-patriot-anti-missile-battery-middle-east/story?id=62968486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military is deploying a Patriot anti-missile battery to the Middle East to further deter threats from Iran, the Pentagon announced on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Builds Deterrent Force Against Possible Iranian Attack...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190510201918-6m6er</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 1-U.S. warns merchant ships of possible Iranian attacks; cleric threatens U.S. fleet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failure to reach trade agreement raises risk of permanent tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/President-Trump-s-tariffs-once-described-as-13837022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The failure of the United States and China to reach agreement Friday on a comprehensive trade deal raises the risk that President Donald Trump's favorite negotiating tool - high tariffs on imported goods - may be hardening into a permanent feature of the U.S. economy.  Two days of talks ended Friday with no sign of the agreement that both governments once had predicted would be achieved by this point. After parting company with Chinese Vice Premier Liu He, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin pronounced the latest discussions "constructive" but declined to elaborate.  Less than 12 hours earlier, U.S. tariffs on $200 billion of Chinese goods had increased to 25% from 10%, in a sign of the president's waning patience with the negotiations.  Trump, who has started the process of imposing tariffs on all remaining U.S. imports of Chinese goods, also issued a flurry of tweets embracing tariffs as his preferred economic policy and hinting that the China levies might linger.  "The relationship between President Xi and myself remains a very strong one, and conversations . . . into the future will continue. In the meantime, the United States has imposed Tariffs on China, which may or may not be removed depending on what happens with respect to future negotiations!" the president tweeted.  Trump's enthusiasm for tariffs has been no secret since his calls during his presidential campaign for a 45% tariff on everything Americans buy from China. But his focus on tariffs is a striking departure from the policies pursued by his Democratic and Republican predecessors - especially if he proceeds with his threat to apply tariffs to all $540 billion of annual U.S. purchases from China.  "Tariffs will bring in FAR MORE wealth to our Country than even a phenomenal deal of the traditional kind," he said in an earlier tweet, adding that raising...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstar rapper Drake, who rails against climate change, buys massive private jet...</title>
      <link>https://www.climatedepot.com/2019/05/10/superstar-rapper-drake-who-rails-against-climate-change-buys-massive-private-jet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORDS SMASHED: WETTEST YEAR IN HISTORY OF USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Genuinely-scary-Torrential-rain-in-Houston-13834973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clusters of violent and slow-moving thunderstorms converged on the Houston area Thursday night, unleashing torrential rain and enormous hail. The deluge wrought havoc on the city, spurring floods reminiscent of Hurricane Harvey in some areas.  And the heavy rain threat is not over.  Houston is under a flash flood watch through Saturday night given the potential for at least one to three additional inches of rain on top of the two to five inches which fell Thursday night and two to three inches Tuesday.  "Soils remain saturated from recent rainfall and many bayous, creeks and rivers remain high so any additional rainfall should run off quickly and cause flooding," the National Weather Service office serving Houston wrote.  Houston is in a slight risk zone for excessive rainfall both Friday and Saturday.  Additional rainfall is not predicted to be as intense as Thursday night's deluge, but the Weather Service urged residents to "stay put" if extreme rainfall returns: "Do not attempt to travel," it warned. "Underpasses and low-water crossings will be life-threatening. If caught in a sinking vehicle, get OUT. Bayous will likely exceed banks and structure flooding could be possible."  By all accounts, Thursday night's storms in Houston, which have left the region susceptible to more flooding, were wild. "This is probably the most hellacious rain I've ever heard in my life," tweeted Matt Lanza, meteorologist for the Houston weather website SpaceCityWeather.com.  The storms left "at least three bayous flowing over the top of their banks, nearly 90,000 residents without power and dozens reportedly trapped for a time in floodwater on Interstate 10," The Washington Post's Timothy Bella reported.  As much as five inches of rain reportedly fell in one hour in east Houston's Greens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SATURDAY:  President Trump takes over Fourth of July celebration, changing its location and inserting himself into program...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/05/11/president-trump-takes-over-fourth-of-july-celebration-changing-its-location-and-inserting-himself-into-the-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s starring role has the potential to turn what has long been a nonpartisan celebration of the nation’s founding into another version of a Trump campaign rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk faces trial for 'pedo' insult of diver...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb8b1cbc1fb1407e951a667fbe03b297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Tesla CEO Elon Musk will have to go to trial to defend himself for mocking a British diver as a pedophile in a verbal sparring match that unfolded last summer after the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba launches widespread rationing in face of crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/42b62f24be9b4e0d9f764f1a3fa9647a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — The Cuban government announced Friday that it is launching widespread rationing of chicken, eggs, rice, beans, soap and other basic products in the face of a grave economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders bilingual ballots for Florida counties...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/politics/os-ne-bilingual-ballot-ruling-20190510-fuj2enp2ajfj5fuenzv6obu77u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Friday ordered 32 Florida counties, including Lake and Brevard, to provide Spanish-language ballots beginning with the 2020 presidential primaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon shifting $1.5 billion to wall construction...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fde3f382fb1943e69d773eaac9f75eb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon is shifting $1.5 billion in funds originally targeted for support of the Afghan security forces and other projects to help pay for construction of nearly 80 miles...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake Salvador Dali 'takes selfies' with museum visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/5/10/18540953/salvador-dali-lives-deepfake-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s surreal, all right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Can't Force Phone Unlock Via Fingerprint, Another Judge Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2019/05/10/the-us-government-cant-force-you-to-unlock-your-phone-with-your-fingerprint-another-judge-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government asks a judge if it can force a Google Pixel phone open with a fingerprint. The judge says no, it would violate the individual's Fifth Amendment rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In NC swamp, researcher finds tree older than Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article230191724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE withdraws from battle to obtain Kraft spa tape...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/05/10/boston-globe-withdraws-from-legal-fight-to-obtain-robert-kraft-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the effort by multiple media companies to obtain the “sneak and peek” surveillance video created when Patriots owner Robert Kraft allegedly engaged in sexual activity at a Florida…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin scores 8 hockey goals -- then faceplants during victory lap...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/may/10/vladimir-putin-hockey-fall-hockey-exhibition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian president took a face-first spill after leading his team in scoring during a Friday night exhibition at Sochi’s Bolshoy Ice Dome</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera can photograph you -- from 28 miles away!</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/613457/a-new-camera-can-photograph-you-from-45-kilometers-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developed in China, the lidar-based system can cut through city smog to resolve human-sized features at vast distances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY coffin clubs taking sting out of death...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/business/money/112644819/new-zealands-diy-coffin-clubs-take-the-sting-out-of-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five groups have sprung up in New Zealand for people wanting to build and customise their caskets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extinct bird back from dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/10/africa/white-throated-rail-extinction-scli-intl-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previously extinct species of bird returned from the dead, reclaiming the island it previously lived on and re-evolving itself back into existence, scientists have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems subpoena Mnuchin, IRS chief over POTUS tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/10/house-democrats-subpoena-treasury-secretary-mnuchin-irs-chief-over-trump-tax-returns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mnuchin said Monday that a request for Trump's income tax returns "lacks a legitimate legislative purpose."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR SCARE: 'Suicidal' Passenger Tries Opening Door In Flight...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/10/flight-to-new-york-report-suicidal-passenger-open-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta flight operated by Republic Airways was forced to return to LaGuardia Airport after a passenger allegedly tried to open a door to the plane while in flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Gene-Edited Food Be Government Regulated?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/05/10/717273970/will-gene-edited-food-be-government-regulated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crops that have had their DNA tweaked with new gene-editing tools are entering the food supply. But governments are struggling to figure out how — or even whether — to regulate them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER BUST: 'One of most disappointing IPOs ever'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/840751/uber-having-most-disappointing-ipos-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber is not having the uberprofitable day it was hoping for. The ride-hailing company set its IPO at $45 per share on Thursday night, but ended up selling at $42 as soon as the market opened on Friday morning. Shares soon fell even lower to $41.06, nearly recovered to their original asking price by mid-day, and dropped once again to point Uber toward one of the worst first-day IPO performances of the decade. Forecasts originally predicted Uber would price itself at $46-$48 per share, though its eventual decision of $45 per share with an $81 billion IPO was still massive. Still, the company never actually saw that set price materialize, and only peaked at $44.74 around 1 p.m. Uber's immediate 6 percent fall after the floor opened makes it one of just 60 companies who've seen a debut day loss of 5 percent or more in the past 10 years, Bloomberg notes. And there's a strong chance it could become the eighth of those companies to actually end up in the red for its first day. Uber has barely gone a day without some kind of public scandal or outcry in the past two years, and this past week was no exception. Drivers for Uber and rival companies went on strike by turning off their apps on Wednesday to protest low wages and a lack of worker benefits. Uber later said it reached settlements with many of the 60,000 drivers who've protested, adding that those settlements would cost upwards of $170 million. The strike was planned to coincide with Uber's first day on the market, though it's unclear if the uproar had anything to do with Uber's dismal performance. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated LAKERS Fans Protest Team Outside Arena...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/10/frustrated-lakers-fans-to-protest-team-outside-staples-friday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Lakers coming off their sixth straight season missing the playoffs, and still without a head coach, angry fans are holding a protest outside Staples Center Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper charged in campaign finance case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/852e3aa86a604597b99c5e81179a7b6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One of the founding members of the 1990s hip-hop group the Fugees has been charged in a campaign finance conspiracy that took place during the 2012 U.S. presidential election,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From A bomb to AI bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190510-nuclear-weapons-artificial-intelligence-ai-missiles-bombs-technology-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From autonomous nuclear submarines to algorithms detecting a threat, to robot-guided high-speed missiles, artificial intelligence could revolutionise nuclear weapons – risking some profound ethical conundrums – a recent report reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hackers Still Accessing Baltimore Gov't Computers 3 Days After Attack...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/05/10/fbi-investigating-baltimore-city-ransomware-attack-as-network-continues-to-have-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is investigating a ransomware attack on Baltimore City's network, while city officials try to bring back the network to its full capacity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
