<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Diet soda prompts food cravings -- especially in obese...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/10/07/1044010141/diet-soda-may-prompt-food-cravings-especially-in-women-and-people-with-obesity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research adds to growing concern over zero-calorie drinks. Consuming artificial sweeteners may confuse our body, leading to increased hunger and weight gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studies confirm waning immunity -- only 2 months effective?!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/06/health/pfizer-vaccine-waning-immunity/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two real-world studies published Wednesday confirm that the immune protection offered by two doses of Pfizer's Covid-19 vaccine drops off after two months or so, although protection against severe disease, hospitalization and death remains strong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL ratings see big jump in first month of season...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/oct/5/back-where-it-was-nfl-ratings-see-big-jump-first-m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday’s dramatic game between the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and New England Patriots that featured a Brady-Belichick showdown produced a whopping 26.75 million viewers on television and 1.83 million on digital streaming platforms — marking NBC’s second most-watched “Sunday Night Football” broadcast ever, behind only 2012’s Cowboys-Redskins contest that decided the NFC East.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADELE, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.co.uk/arts-and-lifestyle/article/adele-british-vogue-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her remarkable songs of heartbreak and redemption have won Adele many millions of fans. Now, she tells Giles Hattersley, in her first interview for five years, she is poised to release her strongest album yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hannity's Cable News Career Turns 25  --  Along With FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/exclusive-sean-hannity-takes-mediaites-hot-seat-as-his-cable-news-career-turns-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean Hannity’s cable news career turns 25 this week. Hannity joined Fox News at its inception in 1996, after a few years on radio (“I was god-awful,” he recalls), and a few more years before that working construction and restaurant jobs. Over the course of two decades, Hannity has gone from being one half of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER shots for kids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-coronavirus-vaccine-health-b9a0e105be709a4d7a1c7d604e8d05f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer asked the U.S. government Thursday to allow use of its COVID-19 vaccine in children ages 5 to 11 in what would be a major expansion that could combat an alarming rise in serious infections in youngsters and help schools stay open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai ruler hacked ex-wife using NSO Pegasus spyware...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/06/dubai-ruler-hacked-ex-wife-using-nso-pegasus-spyware-high-court-judge-finds-sheikh-mohammed-princess-haya</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheikh Mohammed used spyware on Princess Haya and five associates in unlawful abuse of power, judge rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  GROWING ECON THREAT FROM CHINA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/americans-sense-china-eclipsing-us-economically-and-say-protecting-us-jobs-should-be-priority-poll-finds/ar-AAPeJa2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans said U.S. foreign policy does not benefit working-class Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES Now Says ALL Workers Must Be Fully Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/american-air-says-workers-must-be-fully-vaccinated-by-nov-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Air Says Workers Must Be Fully Vaccinated by Nov. 24</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France summons archbishop over 'confession above law' stance...</title>
      <link>https://timesofmalta.com/articles/view/france-summons-archbishop-over-confession-above-law-stance.906295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofmalta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government on Thursday summoned for explanation a top archbishop who said priests should not go to the police after hearing about child sexual abuse during confession. Archbishop Eric de Moulins-Beaufort made the remark after a government inquiry lifted the lid on "massive" sexual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  44% OF REPUBLICANS WANT HIM TO RUN AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/575678-44-percent-of-republicans-want-trump-to-run-again-in-2024-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Republicans want former President Trump to run for office again in 2024, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30% of  pilots holding out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-presses-airlines-employees-205316223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines, Alaska Airlines and JetBlue are joining United Airlines in requiring employees to be vaccinated against COVID-19, as the Biden administration steps up pressure on major U.S. carriers to require the shots. The companies say that makes them government contractors who are covered by President Joe Biden's order directing contractors to require that employees be vaccinated. American Airlines CEO Doug Parker told employees late Friday that the airline is still working on details, but “it is clear that team members who choose to remain unvaccinated will not be able to work at American Airlines.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber fans 'confused' as Diane Keaton plays love interest in new video...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3807756/justin-bieber-confused-diane-keaton-75-love-interest-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUSTIN Bieber’s fans are “confused” as Diane Keaton appears in his new music video. The 75-year-old actress plays the Canadian singer’s love interest in the video for Ghost. Justin took to Instagra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 former NBA players arrested and charged with defrauding league...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/18-former-nba-players-arrested-federal-authorities-alleged-health-care-n1281022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glen "Big Baby" Davis, who won an NBA title with the Boston Celtics, and former high school sensation Sebastian Telfair are among the defendants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone tourist gets jail time after getting too close to grizzly...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article254825962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, the woman was spotted on video standing within feet of a grizzly bear at the national park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Diaper Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/diaper-shortage-hits-us-amid-covid-19-pandemic-supply-chain-issues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Diaper Bank Network said the country has a diaper shortage with nearly 33% of American families in need of the baby item.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Used To Select Targets From Satellite Photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/10/how-well-can-ai-pick-targets-satellite-photos-army-test-aims-find-out/185916/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Scarlet Dragon exercise is evaluating ways the service might put new tools to use in the very near term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T quietly becomes powerhouse in conservative politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/local/dallas/2021/10/07/att-criticized-funding-conservative-lawmakers-texas-abortion-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T, the world’s largest communications company, has covertly become a powerful player in conservative politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1 MAG QUAKE JOLTS TOKYO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007150806-us98q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Magnitude 6.1 quake jolts Tokyo, causing blackouts but no tsunami warning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATT LABASH</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/welcome-to-slack-tide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Konnichiwa. Or as my English-speaking readers prefer, “hello.” I’m Matt Labash, and welcome to Slack Tide, my brand spanking-new Substack. Just saying those words makes me feel like a honking cliché. Not the Matt Labash part. There aren’t many of us. The only other one who shows up in my Google alerts is a star college lacrosse player. I keep meaning to ask if he’d like to trade lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia wants FACEBOOK held liable for anonymous comments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-scott-morrison-australia-social-media-e68fe4edc2bcdb71f33a9392bb9d5471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia’s prime minister on Thursday described social media as a “coward’s palace” and warned that digital platforms including Facebook should be held liable for defamatory comments posted anonymously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian leader hopes to stay on amid bribery allegations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-austria-0dcdba427328a0de32c17f923bd75fbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz denied wrongdoing and made clear he did not plan to step down after anti-corruption prosecutors said he is a target in a bribery investigation. However, the partner party in Kurz's coalition government said Thursday that the probe created a “disastrous” impression and raised questions about the chancellor's “ability to act.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repairs To San Fran's Leaning Tower -- Caused It To Sink MORE!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/10/07/update-despite-warnings-repairs-on-san-franciscos-millennium-tower-caused-additional-sinking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction on a fix for San Francisco's leaning Millennium Tower came to a stop in late August because the fix was actually making the tower sink even more. Now it appears some of that damage could have been avoided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT: Russia behind 58% of detected state-backed hacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-china-europe-united-states-e13548edf082992a735a0af1da39b6c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Russia accounted for most state-sponsored hacking detected by Microsoft over the past year, with a 58% share, mostly targeting government agencies and think tanks in the United States, followed by Ukraine, Britain and European NATO members, the company said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Harrelson involved in altercation at Watergate Hotel, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/woody-harrelson-involved-in-altercation-at-watergate-hotel-police-say/ar-AAPeR0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the move star struck a man “in self-defense” at the hotel’s rooftop bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet New Face of Russia's Anti-Putin Movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/yevgeny-roizman-is-the-new-face-of-russias-anti-putin-movement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Believe me, I am aware of all the risks,” career politician Yevgeny Roizman told The Daily Beast in an exclusive interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1 MAG QUAKE JOLTS TOKYO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007135828-bk79l/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (URGENT):Earthquake 6.1 jolts Tokyo, preliminary magnitude estimated at 6.1 - NHK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorced parents going to court over dosing children...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/divorced-parents-are-going-to-court-over-vaccinating-their-kids-against-the-coronavirus/ar-AAPeIbD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family lawyers are seeing a surge in vaccine disputes, often caused by misinformation, bringing stress and legal bills to already worried parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary Committee details attempt to overturn election...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/07/politics/senate-judiciary-committee-investigation-trump-2020-election/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee on Thursday released a sweeping report about how former President Donald Trump and a top lawyer in the Justice Department attempted to overturn the 2020 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA mystery: Why didn't auto-braking stop crashes?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/a-tesla-mystery-why-didnt-auto-braking-stop-these-crashes/ar-AAPeA2O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While regulators investigate a spate of Teslas steering themselves into parked vehicles, Tesla owners have been reporting faulty collision avoidance systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World waking up to Iran drone threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/the-world-is-waking-up-to-irans-drone-threat-681312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s drone program, unlike its nuclear weapons program, is not secretive. The Islamic Republic openly brags about its drone capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of inflation to average household: Extra $175 a month...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/06/cost-of-inflation-to-american-household-extra-175-a-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Americans whose income has not kept pace with inflation — up 5.3 percent in August as compared with last year — have had to foot the bill for more expensive products due to price …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trust in judgment of voters, politicians new lows...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/355430/trust-politicians-voters-continues-ebb.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than half of U.S. adults say they have confidence in people who hold or are running for public office. Meanwhile, a small majority express confidence in the judgments of the American people under the democratic system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trust in media nears record low...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/355526/americans-trust-media-dips-second-lowest-record.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' trust in the media to report the news fully, accurately and fairly has edged down four points to 36% since last year, making it the second-lowest reading in Gallup's trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harsh public justice and private despair reign in Taliban-ruled Herat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/harsh-public-justice-and-private-despair-reign-in-taliban-ruled-herat/ar-AAPem1F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the city in western Afghanistan, the Taliban has put corpses on display to deter crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan seeks international support after Chinese incursions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007045052-h72xt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-FRANCE/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Taiwan seeks international support after Chinese incursions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship anchored near oil pipeline made unusual movements...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-california-environment-and-nature-0e3d71b1f161822bb157ce8d73dbbd11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — A massive cargo ship made a series of unusual movements while anchored in the closest spot to a Southern California oil pipeline that ruptured and sent crude washing up on beaches, according to data collected by a marine navigation service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAULT DELAYED</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/senate-poised-pull-nation-back-060000898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Senate is nearing a deal on a short-term increase in the debt ceiling that would pull the U.S. from the brink of a payment default but threatens to exacerbate year-end clashes over trillions in government spending. Most Read from BloombergLeft-Wing Rage Threatens a Wall Street Haven in Latin AmericaHow Singapore's $50 Billion Financial District Will Change After Covid-19Before Interstates, America Got Around on InterurbansChristmas at Risk as Supply Chain ‘Disaster’ Only Gets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-SS camp guard, aged 100, on trial for 3,518 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007112545-uqmr9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (UPDATE 1, PIX,TV):UPDATE 1-Ex-SS camp guard, aged 100, on trial for 3,518 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland joins Sweden, Denmark in limiting MODERNA vax...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007092437-11532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FINLAND-MODERNA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Finland joins Sweden and Denmark in limiting Moderna COVID-19 vaccine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World food prices hit 10-year peak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007084335-s8h2o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-ECONOMY/FOOD (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-World food prices hit 10-year peak -FAO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heart Damage Plagues Survivors Year After Infection...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/americas/heart-damage-plagues-covid-19-survivors-a-year-after-infection-study-shows-1.1633593286136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heart damage from COVID-19 extends well beyond the disease's initial stages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lib Activist Who Targets Republicans With MAGA Masquerade...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/07/the-liberal-activist-who-targets-republicans-with-a-maga-masquerade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Pence told her, “I love your heart.” Representative Jim Jordan of Ohio confided in her that Donald J. Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused in death of pharmacist brother for 'killing people' with jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-burnham-killed-pharmacist-brother-covid-vaccine-shots-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court documents show Jeffrey Burnham "wanted to confront" his brother "with the government poisoning people with COVID vaccines." He's also charged in two other deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Mystery: Where's $69 Billion Backing Stablecoin Tether?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-07/crypto-mystery-where-s-the-69-billion-backing-the-stablecoin-tether</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Beach' coworking spaces new craze in Sao Paulo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beach-coworking-spaces-craze-sao-024000094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 18 months of being locked up by coronavirus pandemic restrictions, Brazil's largest city Sao Paulo is breathing again, thanks in part to open-air coworking spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'HARDER THEY FALL' Vicious And Unapologetic Action Western...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/the-harder-they-fall-review-idris-elba-jonathan-majors-regina-king-1234851278/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When thinking of Western genre icons, John Wayne and Clint Eastwood often come to mind. It wasn’t until Mario Van Peebles’ 1993 film Posse was released and the first of its kind to trul…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WORRIES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/the-world-is-questioning-washington-e2-80-99s-competence-fearing-prospect-of-us-default/ar-AAPdNBY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political dysfunction on display could further erode perceptions of U.S. leadership on the world stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden, Denmark halt MODERNA shot for younger people...</title>
      <link>https://www.theolympian.com/news/nation-world/world/article254817917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theolympian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM — Sweden and Denmark decided to halt vaccinations with Moderna Inc.’s COVID-19 shot for younger people because of potential side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATA:  More people in USA have died so far THIS year than last...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-more-deaths-2021-than-in-2020-johns-hopkins-coronavirus-20211006-2fpfjpomqzflnkpjgqtxf6mioy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has killed 700,000 people, more than half of them this year. Since Jan. 1 of this year, more than 353,000 deaths have been reported from COVID-19, about a thousand more than last year’s 352,000 for the first 10 months of the pandemic last year, according to data from Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manilow Set to Break Presley's Vegas Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/06/barry-manilow-set-to-break-elvis-presleys-las-vegas-record-by-booking-105-shows-through-2023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence tests whether there is political life after MAGA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-weighing-2024-run-pence-tests-whether-there-is-political-life-after-trump/ar-AAPcY4h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president is hopscotching the country giving six-figure speeches, sitting down for interviews with friendly conservative media outlets and hosting fundraisers for Republican candidates and causes as he considers a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD OF ITALY:  34 inches in 24 hours breaks Europe's rainfall record...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/extreme-rainfall-in-liguria-italy-breaks-europe-record/1028429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rainfall that AccuWeather forecasters described as "ridiculous" set a new record for Europe and left one city with nearly a year's worth of rainfall -- in less than a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Schlocky, overheated melodrama that's only degree or two removed from 'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/08/31/impeachment-american-crime-story-review-fx-monica-lewinsky-bill-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV docudramas always walk a fine line between illumination and exploitation. But American Crime Story’s first installment, The People v. O.J. Simpson, broke the mold by doing the impossible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorilla dies in arms of person who rescued her 14 years earlier...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/gorilla-dies-in-arms-of-person-who-rescued-her-14-years-earlier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A beloved orphaned mountain gorilla died in the arms of her caretaker and lifelong friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient's Kidney Op Cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/uchealth-kidney-transplant-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to UCHealth, the majority of transplant recipients and living donors are now required to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Neither woman has received their shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUNISHMENT:  KAISER Puts 2,200 Employees On Unpaid Leave...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/kaiser-permanente-covid-vaccine-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaiser Permanente says 2,200 of its employees are now on unpaid administrative leave after not meeting a COVID-19 vaccination deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Silent As Chappelle Blasted By GLAAD Over Gay Jokes In New Special...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/dave-chappelle-glaad-lgbtq-trans-netflix-special-homophobia-national-black-justice-coalition-1234851038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day before Dave Chappelle’s Untitled documentary is set to screen at the Hollywood Bowl and the comedian is expected onstage, his new Netflix special The Closer is generating a growing back…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic super-yachts will feature crazy design detail...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/yacht-design-void</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Italian-built vessel features a customizable “void”—along with six luxurious suites—for unmistakable star power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Class Clowns Also Most Intelligent Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/class-clowns-intelligent-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers report children with higher than average levels of general knowledge and verbal reasoning tend to excel at humor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Now Largest City To Decriminalize Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/05/seattle-just-became-the-largest-u-s-city-to-approve-quasi-decriminalization-of-natural-psychedelics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The resolution urges police to refrain from arresting people for noncommercial production and distribution as well as possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Coke Users Stealing Meat to Pay Organized Crime for Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78m9v/cape-breton-police-cocaine-meat-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cape Breton cop claimed cocaine use has risen during the pandemic and blamed Canada's COVID emergency benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Concrete Cancer' Detected In Buildings At NH Nuclear Power Plant...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/iteam-seabrook-nh-nuclear-power-plant-concrete-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nuclear watch dog group says several structures at the Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant have concrete cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find culprit behind nearly all neurological diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10065423/Hope-dementia-Parkinsons-scientists-drive-diseases-affecting-brain-function.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists claim to have found a type of cell which normally help keep the brain healthy could be driving force behind nearly all diseases affecting brain function in what could help treat a variety of diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pandemic phase' ending soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/06/covid-dr-scott-gottlieb-says-antiviral-pills-kids-vaccines-key-to-ending-pandemic-phase.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former FDA chief and current Pfizer board member believes vaccines for kids and oral antiviral drugs will be "very important psychological events."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flush with Covid aid, schools steer funding to sports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-school-funding-sports-5b468b260ebd2593e53f03f9104d9bca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — One Wisconsin school district built a new football field. In Iowa, a high school weight room is getting a renovation. Another in Kentucky is replacing two outdoor tracks — all of this funded by the billions of dollars in federal pandemic relief Congress sent to schools this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL SUPPORTS RAISING DEBT CEILING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/06/mitch-mcconnell-may-offer-short-term-debt-ceiling-extension-following-pressure-from-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and Democratic leaders in Congress amped up pressure on Republicans to act on the debt limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Sentenced 15 Months For Spreading Covid FACEBOOK Hoax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-hoax-facebook-texas-christopher-charles-erez-15-months-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 40-year-old posted two false, threatening messages on Facebook, claiming he paid someone infected with COVID-19 to lick items at a grocery store. He later admitted he lied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Cases, Deaths Declining...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-10-06/who-global-coronavirus-cases-deaths-have-been-declining-since-august</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. reported the most new coronavirus cases of any country last week, according to a World Health Organization report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Suspends MODERNA For Those Under 30...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/06/sweden-suspends-moderna-vaccine-for-those-30-and-under/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish health authorities on Wednesday suspended the use of Moderna’s COVID-19 vaccine for those ages 30 and under, saying the move was done out of precaution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 4 Injured In Shooting At TX High School; Teen Gunman Still At Large...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/06/possible-shooting-at-timberview-high-school-in-arlington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “all clear” has been given at Timberview High School in Arlington after an active shooter situation Wednesday morning, but the search continues for a suspected teenaged gunman.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
