<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In Hawaii it's 'raining' green crystals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/14/hawaii-volcano-green-crystals-olivine/701389002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the never-ending parade of weird phenomena erupting from Hawaii's Kilauea volcano comes a "rain" of green crystals, which have been spotted on the ground after falling from the sky. "It is literally raining gems," tweeted meteorologist Erin Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  National Guard soldiers sent to border are shoveling manure, changing flat tires...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/06/14/trump-ordered-troops-to-the-border-but-theyre-doing-busywork-218821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this ramshackle town, National Guard soldiers are doing everything from shoveling manure to changing tires. What they’re not doing: Watching the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hitler Of South Africa Tells White People, He Won't Kill Them -- Yet!</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-15/hitler-south-africa-tells-white-people-he-wont-kill-themyet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine Peso Resumes Plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-15/dramatic-rebound-for-argentine-peso-as-caputo-takes-over-bank </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Argentine peso resumed its slide to a historic low as a major shakeup that put a former Wall Street trader at the helm of the nation’s central bank failed to curb the currency’s massive volatility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Three Californias' would give Dems more seats...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/392488-three-californias-plan-would-give-dems-more-seats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal to split the nation’s most populous state into three smaller states would give Democrats a huge boost in the perpetual battle for control of the United States Senate — likely dooming the plan even before voters have a chance t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM HOPE:  Tattooed, iron-pumping West Virginia candidate breaks mold...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/unconventional-west-virginia-candidate-heartens-democrats-162345055--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — Richard Ojeda is a retired Army paratrooper with combat medals, 26 tattoos and a 300-pound bench press — no ordinary candidate for Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another cash-strapped NYC cabbie commits suicide...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/15/another-cash-strapped-nyc-cabbie-commits-suicide/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another cash-strapped city cabbie has committed suicide — hanging himself in his Brooklyn apartment, multiple sources told The Post on Friday. Abdul Saleh is now at least the sixth financiall…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/392493-watergate-prosecutor-says-manafort-may-never-again-see-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Watergate prosecutor Nick Akerman said on Friday that Paul Manafort may never again “see the outside of a jail cell” after his house arrest arrangement was revoked on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCEAN'S 8 stars blame dominance of male critics for film's mixed reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jun/15/oceans-8-dominance-men-film-reviews </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mindy Kaling and Cate Blanchett echo Brie Larson in calling for greater diversity among reviewers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup already beset by empty seats, and FIFA baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-World-Cup-is-already-beset-by-empty-seats-12998062.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may have noticed something strange during Friday's World Cup match between Uruguay and Egypt at Ekaterinburg Arena in Russia: swaths of empty seats, helpfully visible to television viewers in bright orange. It must have come as an even bigger surprise to Russian World Cup officials, considering they added temporary seating that jutted outside of the arena in anticipation of big crowds for world soccer's quadrennial tournament. FIFA, meanwhile, is baffled. It estimates that there were 6,000 empty seats for the Uruguay-Egypt game. "We can confirm that 32,278 tickets have been allocated for the match between Egypt and Uruguay in Ekaterinburg," a FIFA spokesman told the Telegraph's Ben Rumsby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimps and orangutans could be completely extinct by the end of century...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6546359/chimps-and-orangutans-could-be-completely-extinct-by-the-end-of-the-century-scientists-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHIMPANZEES and orangutans are on the brink of extinction, a top scientist has warned. Brazil, Madagascar, Indonesia, and the Democratic Republic of Congo alone harbour two thirds of all primate sp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE signs Oprah...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/oprah-winfrey-inks-content-deal-apple-1120552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will continue to serve as chairman and CEO of Discovery-backed cable network OWN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Agent: 'I'm Done Interviewing PRESIDENT... You Know, HRC'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/fbi-agent-who-questioned-hillary-email-probe-called-her-president-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Comey speaking at the White House, flanked by then-FBI Director Robert Mueller and President Barack Obama, on the day Obama announced he was nominating Comey to replace Mueller, June 21, 2013. (Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Inside Shelter for Illegal Alien Children Separated from Parents...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/california/2018/06/15/photos-inside-shelter-for-illegal-alien-children-separated-from-parents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shelter in El Cajon is a comfortable facility providing lodging, meals, clothing, medical care, education, and recreation to illegal alien children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Charges Against THERANOS Elizabeth Holmes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-files-criminal-charges-against-theranoss-elizabeth-holmes-ramesh-balwani-1529096005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors filed criminal charges against Theranos founder Elizabeth Holmes and Ramesh Balwani, the blood-testing company’s former No. 2 executive, alleging that they defrauded investors out of hundreds of millions of dollars and defrauded doctors and patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCARTHY: Mueller Would Have Squeezed Clinton Tech To Roll Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2018/06/ig-report-fbi-no-bias-conclusion-may-not-supported/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But who knows? In dealing with the FBI, Clinton got kid gloves while Trump got scorched earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George P. Bush Says Don't Believe 'Liberal Media Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/texas-politics/2018/06/15/george-p-bush-greeted-boos-cries-remember-alamo-texas-gop-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO — Land Commissioner George P. Bush was met with cheers — and jeers — at the 2018 convention of the Republican Party of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter startup fastest company to reach $1B valuation...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1305719/electric-scooter-company-bird-is-the-fastest-startup-ever-to-become-a-unicorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now the e-scooter company is zipping along to $2 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How legal drug companies helped revive heroin trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2018/06/15/how-legal-drug-companies-helped-revive-the-heroin-trade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heroin traffickers set up shop in the areas of the United States with the highest prevalence of prescription opioid addiction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketers stand to lose majority of e-mail lists as few Americans open privacy update notes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/15/gdpr-emails-going-unopened.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One email marketing company said some of their clients have lost up to 80 percent of their email lists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Stabbing followed hot sauce incident...</title>
      <link>http://www.seacoastonline.com/news/20180615/police-stabbing-followed-hot-sauce-assault-at-gilleys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seacoastonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTSMOUTH  A May 29 fight inside Gilley's PM Lunch, that led to a stabbing outside the Fleet Street eatery, began with a hot-sauce squirting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago strip club cancels Stormy shows because she wants more money...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-stormy-daniels-chicago-20180615-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels only had a one-night stand at the Admiral Theatre. The Chicago strip club owner pulled the plug after what he says is a dispute over money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozzy Osborne to serve 30 years in barber shop shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/montgomery/index.ssf/2018/06/al_man_named_ozzy_osborne_to_s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores Rare 0% on ROTTEN TOMATOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/john-travoltas-gotti-gets-zero-percent-rotten-tomatoes-score-1120603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the actor's third film to receive that dubious distinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Strife Hits WASHPOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.futureofcapitalism.com/2018/06/washington-post-labor-strife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.futureofcapitalism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A union representing employees at the Washington Post is stepping up a public pressure campaign against the newspaper's owner, Jeff Bezos. There's also a petition the union says was signed by more than 400 employees that says in part: All we are asking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIMEWARNER unveils new name: WARNERMEDIA...</title>
      <link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/06/15/media/warnermedia-john-stankey-announcements/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Stankey, the new CEO of the company, announced the rebranding and a series of structural changes in an internal memo on Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT JAILED</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/judge-sends-trumps-former-campaign-chief-manafort-to-jail-idUSKBN1JB12X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. federal judge on Friday sent Paul Manafort to jail pending trial after he was charged with witness tampering, in the latest episode in a slow fall from grace of a man who was President Donald Trump's campaign chairman in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Wave Device Claims To Provide Equivalent Of 20,000 Sit-Ups...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/14/emsculpt-burns-fat-while-building-muscle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often people with stubborn fat pockets resort to liposuction, tummy tucks or some other fat-freezing and lasering techniques. Emsculpt may be the alternative many have been looking for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When, not if: USA poised to quit UN human rights council...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c7037593a84a43f799282a94fca0a957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Diplomats say the United States is about to quit the United Nation's main human rights body, primarily over Washington's claim that the Human Rights Council is biase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, China announce new tariffs in escalation of trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/15/china-announces-retaliatory-tariffs-on-34-billion-worth-of-us-goods-including-agriculture-products.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a quick response to U.S. tariffs, Beijing announced on Friday its own duties on American products, including agriculture products and automobiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER Publisher Adds Celeb Gossip Collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/national-enquirer-publisher-adds-to-its-celebrity-gossip-collection-1529085394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America Media Inc., the dominant publisher of celebrity gossips publications sold mainly at supermarket checkout lines, agreed to buy three more—In Touch, Life &amp; Style and Closer—from rival Bauer Media USA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother kills rabid bobcat with bare hands...</title>
      <link>http://www.onlineathens.com/news/20180615/hart-county-grandmother-kills-rabid-bobcat-with-bare-hands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rabid bobcat recently attacked a Hart County grandmother in her yard, spurring a furious battle that ended with the cat’s strangulation death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend broke into email account to reject full-ride scholarship...</title>
      <link>http://montrealgazette.com/news/local-news/mcgill-music-student-awarded-350000-after-girlfriend-stalls-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;montrealgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She wrote an email posing as him, turning down a $50,000-a-year scholarship so that he wouldn’t leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican's stolen Christopher Columbus letter found in Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/vatican-stolen-christopher-columbus-letter-found-atlanta/vxIpLCpeVlN0m4NyGBLa3O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For at least 14 years, investigators searched the world for a stolen letter written by Christopher C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD CUP RATINGS FALL HARD...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/06/world-cup-ratings-opening-game-russia-saudi-arabia-fox-1202411344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The opening game of the 2018 World Cup was a winner for Vladimir Putin but not so much for Rupert Murdoch, at least when it comes to the ratings. The Russian President got to strut his stuff on the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress Test: Saliva Swab Detects Workplace Burnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/stress-test-saliva-swab-detects-workplace-burnout-162145768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A simple saliva test can show within hours whether someone on the job is overly stressed and at risk of burnout, researchers said Friday. Measuring levels of the anti-stress hormone cortisol at different times of the day more accurately reveals stress levels than more complicated measures, including</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stands firm against demands to close borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-ally-bavarian-governor-acting-bonsai-trump-075051510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel remains firmly opposed to unilateral moves to turn some refugees back at the border, her spokesman said Friday, warning such action — demanded by conservative allies in her own government — would weaken the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says Cohen no longer his lawyer...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392463-trump-says-cohen-is-no-longer-his-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday sought distance from Michael Cohen, his longtime personal attorney, who is under criminal investigation in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, China announce new tariffs in escalation of trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-imposes-import-taxes-on-Chinese-goods-and-12996976.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump followed through Friday on his threat to crack down on China for its "very unfair" trade practices, announcing that he is imposing a 25-percent tariff on $50 billion in Chinese imports. Beijing quickly responded. In a late-night statement, China's Ministry of Commerce said it would impose trade barriers of the "same scale and the same strength." The Chinese government said Trump's tariffs were "damaging" relations and "undermining the world trade order." U.S. and Chinese officials in recent weeks had made progress on a deal that involved up to $70 billion in additional purchases of American products. But the Chinese offer was now "invalid," the statement said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAIL FOR MANAFORT</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/federal-judge-jails-ex-trump-campaign-chair-paul-154529077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal judge jails ex-Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort ahead of trial, citing recently filed obstruction charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DISEASE X' FEAR:   New strain of bird flu kills half of those who contract it...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/2790957/terrifying-new-strain-of-bird-flu-that-kills-nearly-half-of-those-who-contract-it-discovered-in-china-amid-fears-of-new-global-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW strain of deadly bird flu which kills 38 per cent of those infected and could spark a global pandemic has been identified in China. Scientists around the world believe the new pathogen, dubbe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage Over White Woman Selected To Perform Selena Tribute...</title>
      <link>http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/controversy-white-selena-tribute-singer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of the Hispanic community in North Texas are upset that a Dallas concert venue picked a white singer to perform songs by Tejano legend Selena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Opens Up To Oprah On Anthem Kneeling, Spirituality...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/14/oprah-tom-brady-kneeling-national-anthem-spirituality-gisele/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady sat down for an interview with Oprah Winfrey, and it's a conversation that involves some topics that generally don't get covered in Brady's usual press conferences at Gillette Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok denies throwing 'cocktail party' for judge on surveillance court...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/peter-strzok-denies-throwing-cocktail-party-for-judge-on-surveillance-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior FBI official Peter Strzok says he didn't arrange a cocktail party with a federal judge who serves on the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court, despite telling his mistress in a text message that he would.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORIOLES $161 Million Slugger In Danger Of Worst Season Ever By Player...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/orioles-chris-davis-is-on-pace-for-historically-bad-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To say that the O's first baseman has struggled out of the gates this season would be an understatement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'I'm With Her'... </title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/eric-felten/meet-the-other-amorous-fbi-staffers-who-texted-about-the-clinton-email-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parsing the Inspector General’s report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Fueling L.A. Comedy Club Gold Rush; 'I Sold the Same Special Twice!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/netflix-is-driving-la-comedy-gold-rush-1119236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Reporter tags along with a top agent as he pops into packed venues to take in veteran comics trying out new material, newbies attempting to stand out from the crowd and everyone hoping to land that career-changing deal with the dominant streamer: "That's what’s selling tickets these days."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo fined $20 million, two years suspended jail after tax fraud case...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/6540542/cristiano-ronaldo-accepts-two-year-suspended-prison-sentence-and-ordered-to-pay-16-5m-fine-after-tax-fraud-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRISTIANO RONALDO has “agreed to accept a two-year suspended prison sentence and pay a whopping £16.5million fine”, according to reports in Spain. The Real Madrid superstar had been see…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOTTI' SCREENING FROM HELL; AUDIENCE WALKS OUT AS MOVIE TRASHED BY CRITIC...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/15/john-travoltas-gotti-movie-is-as-bad-as-you-thought-the-all-you-can-eat-buffet-version-of-goodfellas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Gotti” starring John Travolta is just as bad as you might imagine, and then some. I can’t say I blame director Kevin Connolly, who took over from a long series of unfortunate inc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  CHECK DRUDGE!</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-well-crush-midterms-check-top-drudge-best-jobs-numbers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We have the strongest economy in the history of our nation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/15/trump-matt-drudge-is-great/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'He really, has ability'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship CARNAGE as 'drug-fuelled orgies erupt on lawless trip'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/travel/travel-news/709863/Cruise-ship-carnage-Anchored-drug-fuelled-orgies-Spain-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT PRAISES DRUDGE...</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/trump-calls-matt-drudge-a-great-gentleman-2018-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump called conservative media personality Matt Drudge "a great gentleman" and his website Drudge Report as "great" in an interview with Fox News on Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freak gust of wind sends portable toilet 100ft into air, sprays 'liquid' on screaming crowd below...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5847587/Freak-gust-wind-sends-Porty-Potty-flying-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the moment a freak gust of wind sends a set of Porty Potty flying into the air. People were forced to diver for cover after a huge blast of wind whipped through a park in Commerce City, Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea creatures fall from sky after 'sucked from ocean by waterspout'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5847383/Storm-photos-appear-starfish-octopus-flying-streets-China.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The images, taken in the coastal city of Qingdao in eastern China's Shandong Province, went viral on social media after a ferocious tempest blew through the town on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY 'CRIMINAL'</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5848345/Trump-says-Comeys-conduct-criminal-den-thieves-ringleader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Friday that James Comey's actions prior to his firing were 'criminal.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP wants Trump in 2020, more popular than Obama, JFK, Reagan...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/gop-wants-trump-in-2020-more-popular-than-obama-jfk-reagan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican voters are demanding that President Trump run for reelection in 2020, the latest evidence that support among his backers is stronger than it was for nearly every recent president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious explosions in past 2 months rattle Pennsylvania residents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/mysterious-explosions-past-months-rattle-pennsylvania-residents/story?id=55916084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating a string of suspicious explosions in Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo 'accepts two-year prison sentence' as soccer star strikes agreement over tax evasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/cristiano-ronaldo-accepts-two-year-12714662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Real Madrid superstar was accused by Spanish prosecutors in June last year of defrauding tax authorities of €14.8m (£12.9m).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RIPS FBI 'SCUM'</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/15/trump-unloads-on-comey-scum-on-top-fbi-day-after-damning-ig-reports-release.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday broke his silence on the damning Justice Department IG report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GISELE: I'm too old and wise for INSTA...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/14/gisele-bundchen-is-too-old-and-wise-for-instagram-modeling/?_ga=2.129027724.1021424398.1529053503-591381504.1529053502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s not my generation — I have to be honest about that. I’m older, wiser.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball Sees Sharp Drop in Attendance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/major-league-baseball-sees-a-sharp-drop-in-attendance-1529063246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;League-wide attendance of 27,328 per MLB game is down 6.6% from this time last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAIL FOR MANAFORT?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/former-trump-campaign-chief-manafort-to-ask-judge-not-to-jail-him-idUSKBN1JB12X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort is set to ask a federal judge on Friday not to revoke his bail and send him to jail pending trial after Special Counsel Robert Mueller filed new charges of witness tampering last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky man to be sentenced in Rand Paul attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1fd104e391d7451482b6226aa666f2ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOWLING GREEN, Ky. (AP) — U.S. Sen. Rand Paul's neighbor is set to be sentenced in federal court for an attack last year in the lawmaker's yard.        Rene Boucher pleaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguans flood migration offices in bid to flee crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nicaraguans-flood-migration-offices-bid-flee-crisis-013829885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One evening as she watched some local kids play outside in her Managua neighborhood, Nicaraguan Mireya Alegria was shocked to see police, motorcycles and a white van carrying hooded men speed past. Now Alegria is one of the thousands of Nicaraguans desperately seeking to process migration documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to tax tourists as influx grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/zealand-tax-tourists-fund-infrastructure-052910321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists to New Zealand are to be charged a special tax, under new government plans announced Friday to deal with the growing influx of holidaymakers coming from overseas. Visitor numbers have surged by nearly a third in the past three years to 3.8 million in the 12 months to April -- almost as big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President preps China tariff target list, Beijing ready to retaliate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-prepares-china-tariff-target-list-confrontation-escalates-014628928--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Friday was due to unveil a final list of Chinese imports that would face punishing tariffs, fanning fears of a trade war as Beijing warned that it could swiftly strike back. The threat of massive duties on billions of dollars of goods sent Shanghai stocks to their lowest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawking's voice to be beamed into space during memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hawkings-voice-beamed-space-during-memorial-044308410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A message from late British astrophysics giant Stephen Hawking will be beamed towards the nearest black hole as his remains are laid to rest in London's Westminster Abbey on Friday. As the ashes of the British theoretical physicist are interred, a specially-written composition featuring his famous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban chief who ordered Malala assassination 'killed in airstrike'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/taliban-chief-ordered-malala-assassination-104729550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the Pakistan Taliban has been targeted in a United States drone strike in eastern Afghanistan. Afghan officials said Mullah Fazlullah, who is one of the world's most wanted militant leaders, had been killed in Kunar province, but Pakistan security sources said his death had not yet been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Flee and Thieves Loot Venezuela's Reeling Oil Giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/workers-flee-and-thieves-loot-venezuela-s-reeling-oil-giant/17628941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL TIGRE, Venezuela — Thousands of workers are fleeing Venezuela’s state-owned oil company, abandoning once-coveted jobs made worthless by the worst inflation in the world. And now the hemorrhaging is threatening the nation’s chances of overcoming its long economic collapse, union leaders, oil executives and workers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's World Cup star accused of helping drug lord...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-rafael-marquez-20180615-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican soccer legend Rafael Marquez, who is preparing to compete in his fifth World Cup, was sanctioned last year by the U.S. Treasury Department for allegedly aiding a notorious drug trafficker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man On Horse Charged With DUI...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/horse-dui-boy-trampled-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armando Martinez Ruiz is now facing DUI charges. The spooked horse trampled an 8-year-old boy in the crowd, breaking his leg.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
