<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  2 mushrooms a day halves cancer risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/health-wellness/article/3135636/eating-two-mushrooms-day-could-lower-cancer-risk-45-cent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who incorporate mushrooms in their daily diet lower their risk of getting cancer, analysis suggests. Mushrooms are high in antioxidants and contain chemical components thought to boost immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Spawns Tornadoes, Heavy Rains to South...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/tropical-storm-claudette-spawns-tornadoes-and-brings-heavy-rains-to-the-south/ar-AALd9uz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Claudette, the third named storm of the Atlantic hurricane season, formed in the Gulf of Mexico and brought “copious rainfall” of five to 10 inches across the Mississippi Delta and Gulf Coast before being downgraded to a tropical depression on Saturday, forecasters said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia accused of 'excessive, unnecessary' secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-australia-15029370cec301172244fe168b4b9dd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia’s suppression of information seen as pivotal to a free and open media is at the center of accusations that the country has become one of the world’s most secretive democracies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruel, Twisted Discoveries at Germany's Stonehenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-cruel-and-twisted-discoveries-at-germany-s-stonehenge/ar-AALedt0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you think of Stonehenge what do you think of? England? Druids? Partygoers celebrating the solstice? A unique piece of ancient heritage?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOORDASH app crashes leaving drivers stuck with orders... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/doordash-app-temporarily-crashes-company-working-to-resolve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DoorDash company leaders said they're having difficulties with their app Saturday after frustration mounted on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUCK 'TERROR'</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/06/19/2-people-hit-by-truck-at-pride-parade-in-wilton-manors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two people were run over by a pickup truck as the LGBTQ Pride parade in Wilton Manors was just getting started around 7 p.m. Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit sex guide on Norwegian public television causes stir...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9700987/Explicit-sex-guide-Norwegian-public-television-causes-stir.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING -- EXPLICIT CONTENT: Public broadcaster NRK offered a guide of 60 different positions, with models simulating sexual positions including 'the squeezing koala' and 'spaghetti'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE KILLED</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/mayor-1-dead-1-hospitalized-after-truck-hits-pedestrians-at-stonewall-pride-parade-driver-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, FLA. (WSVN) - One person has died and another has been taken to the hospital after they were run over by a truck...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIDE SCARE SOUTH FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-florida-8ba2e46151a5592ed0e54c004cbedf85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, Fla. (AP) — A driver slammed into spectators Saturday at the start of a Pride parade in South Florida, injuring at least two people. Fort Lauderdale Mayor Dean Trantalis confirmed the crash occurred Saturday evening at the Stonewall Pride Parade in the nearby city of Wilton Manors, WSVN-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Square becomes no-go zone after dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9704729/The-rotten-core-Big-Apple-iconic-Washington-Square-Park-no-zone-locals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com spoke to park visitors after a woman was trampled by terrified crowds trying to flee a man armed with a large knife and a taser during a late-night rave at the Manhattan landmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  As king, Charles will not let grandson Archie be prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9704475/Prince-Charles-wont-let-Archie-prince-plans-slim-monarchy-save-costs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heir to the throne has made it clear that Harry and Meghan's son will have no place among frontline Royals as he plans a slimmed-down Monarchy after he becomes King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addiction treatment had failed. Could brain surgery save him?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Addiction-treatment-had-failed-Could-brain-16260047.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGANTOWN, W.Va. - After nearly two decades of hardcore drug addiction - after overdoses...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police battle party-goers at curfew-busting rave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/several-hurt-french-police-break-182529476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five police officers were injured in western France as they broke up a 1,500-strong illegal rave, authorities said Saturday, with one party-goer losing a hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downtown Chicago emerges from pandemic --  hobbled by crime wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/downtown-chicago-emerges-pandemic-hobbled-011618733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businesses in downtown Chicago that survived the pandemic-related economic slump and two spasms of looting last summer should be ecstatic with Monday's reopening of America's third-largest city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Turns Into Test Case Endgame...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/britain-turns-into-test-case-for-covid-endgame/ar-AALdGLM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson has promised no more delays to lifting restrictions, yet cases are surging and more deaths are inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Says it Sent 'Completely Normal' Vaccines to Palestinians...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/israel-says-it-sent-completely-normal-vaccines-to-palestinians/article_8047d6ed-63d6-52c4-865b-0deaeec9a5f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel — The first batch of Pfizer vaccines Israel sent to the Palestinian Authority on Friday as part of a larger swap deal was “completely normal” and identical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe goes to church day after challenge from bishops on abortion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-goes-church-day-challenge-224324432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden went to church Saturday in his hometown a day after US Roman Catholic bishops issued a challenge to him over his support for abortion rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City shuts down classes again, enters higher risk tier...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619165131-1hkfj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO (PIX):Mexico City shuts down classes again, enters higher COVID-19 risk tier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck plows into crowd at Pride Parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/3118900/two-run-over-truck-man-florida-pride/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN is in custody after he allegedly ran over two people during a Pride march in Florida on Saturday, according to local reports. The horrifying incident unfolded during the Stonewall Pride in Wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Heckled With Boos and Cries of 'Traitor' at Evangelical Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/mike-pence-gets-heckled-at-faith-freedom-coalition-summit-with-boos-and-cries-of-traitor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence owes a great deal of his political career to support from evangelical conservatives, and Friday’s Faith &amp; Freedom Coalition Summit has been home turf for him for years. But the Republican base is still very devoted to former President Donald Trump, and Pence’s apostasy on Jan. 6 — refusing to oppose […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Nikki Haley's road to White House start in Jerusalem?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/does-nikki-haleys-road-to-the-white-house-start-in-jerusalem-671276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Israel should not be fighting alone," said the former-US ambassador to the UN on a solidarity mission to Israel's rocket-ravaged south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom assaulted by aggressive homeless on Oakland street...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2021/06/18/chp-gov-newsom-assaulted-by-aggressive-person-in-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of TV news and newspaper reporters nearby heard the commotion. All they could see was the governor’s security detail detaining a man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman claims she's in love with alien after UFO abduction...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/woman-says-shes-fallen-alien-24356799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Abbie Bela claims she has fallen for an alien after being abducted by a UFO from her bedroom window this month. The actress, who is in her 30s, says her ET paramour is her “soul mate” – and better than any earthling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang unloads on rival and media in raw, late-night interview...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/nyc-mayoral-race-andrew-evelyn-yang-blast-eric-adams.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Brazil tops 500,000 deaths, protests against president Bolsonaro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-coronavirus-pandemic-health-bb2f9632be7a8a484d35d4e7fb642406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Anti-government protesters took to the streets in more than a score of cities across Brazil on Saturday as the nation's confirmed death toll from COVID-19 soared past half a million — a tragedy many critics blame on President Jair Bolsonaro's attempt to minimize the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm brings flooding rainfall to Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-claudette-hits-gulf-coast/965344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communities near the Gulf Coast are taking the brunt of Tropical Storm Claudette with roads underwater and some homes damaged by suspected tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLCE &amp; GABBANA 'light therapy' collection celebrates life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-health-coronavirus-pandemic-arts-and-entertainment-1b19ef45352408683580b6daf411a54d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana are coaxing men off their sofas and back into the world with a resplendent collection inspired by the extravagant lighting installations of southern Italian street festivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral Rivals Team Up, Aiming to Weaken Race's Front-Runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/nyc-elections-2021/ny-nyc-andrew-yang-kathryn-garcia-mayor-campaign-trail-20210619-pwwwn5b52vftbe5ygu256qb62a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pair planned to barnstorm across the city as they seek out voters in each others strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden struggles to sell democracy abroad when it faces challenges at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-struggles-to-sell-democracy-abroad-when-it-faces-challenges-at-home/ar-AALdy15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has made promoting democracy central to his role on the world stage. That’s complicated by events in the United States stemming from falsehoods about the last election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American breaks shot put world record that stood for decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/19/sport/ryan-crouser-shot-put-world-record-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Crouser toppled the men's shot put world record on Friday with a 23.37-meter throw on the first night of the US Olympic Track and Field Trials in Eugene, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records fall as heat continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/records-fall-as-heat-wave-continues-for-fathers-day-weekend/965582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dozens and dozens of heat records fell the past week, AccuWeather forecasters say relief is on the way for some, but not all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan City Council candidate caught with dominatrix in leaked video...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/nyc-council-candidate-caught-with-dominatrix-in-leaked-bdsm-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was filmed at Parthenon studio in Midtown — which is known for its high-quality BDSM dungeons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Challenger crew likely survived explosion before plunge to earth...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/challenger-crew-likely-survived-explosion-before-fatal-plummet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book reveals how Christa McAuliffe was chosen as the first civilian in space, and why the Challenger crew likely survived the explosion before their fateful plunge to earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ties with Gulf Arabs may hinge on nuke pact...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619153729-d2ie7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ELECTION/GULF (PIX):As Iran veers right, ties with Gulf Arabs may hinge on nuclear pact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinking straw device 'instant cure for hiccups'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/18/drinking-straw-device-is-instant-cure-for-hiccups-say-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sipping water through an L-shaped ‘suction and swallow tool’ cured 92% of attacks, according to study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Rockefeller Heir Eaten by Cannibals?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/was-this-rockefeller-heir-eaten-by-cannibals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockefeller heir Michael Rockefeller disappeared in 1961. Some believe he drowned. Others say he was eaten by cannibals. The truth may be more complex and mysterious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had pregnant women tortured?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3115267/iran-new-president-ebrahim-raisi-butcher/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRANIAN hardline cleric Ebrahim Raisi has won a landslide victory to be declared the country’s next president – but he has a bloody history steeped in murder and executions, activists c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pack of wolves chases actors on stage at theater...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3113514/video-wolves-chasing-actors-chinese-theatre-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TERRIFYING video of a live stage show in China has gone viral after it appeared to show a group of actors being chased by THIRTY wolves. The clip, filmed in a theatre in the city of Xi’an, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INDIANA JONES' filming '24/7 hell' for residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3113220/indiana-jones-nimby-filming-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANA Jones has been caught up in a Nimby row after filming of the new movie took over a street. Producers paid one neighbour a reported £50,000 to let cameras into their home. The homeowner then…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans, spurred by unlikely figure, see political promise in critical race theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-spurred-by-an-unlikely-figure-see-political-promise-in-critical-race-theory/ar-AALd4W9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Rufo, once a documentary filmmaker, has become a go-to activist for the GOP in a political fight over race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians reject doses...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/vaccine-exchange-deal-between-israel-and-pa-has-been-announced-671413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came after Israel delivered a first shipment of Pfizer COVID vaccine to the Palestinian Authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMNESTY calls for investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210619-amnesty-calls-for-iran-s-raisi-to-be-investigated-over-rights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amnesty calls for Iran's Raisi to be investigated over rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My battle to save Princess Diana: Doctor gives first ever account...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9702355/First-minute-minute-testimony-doctors-fight-save-Princess-Diana.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview, MonSef Dahman recalled how he was summoned to the emergency department of the Pitié-Salpêtrière Hospital, Paris, to attend to Diana, Princess of Wales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral Rivals Team Up, Aiming to Weaken Race's Front-Runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-19/nyc-mayoral-rivals-team-up-aiming-to-weaken-race-s-front-runner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move to shake up the race to become New York City’s next mayor, former Sanitation Commissioner Kathryn Garcia and celebrity entrepreneur Andrew Yang agreed to campaign together Saturday in each other’s political strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Boasts Sour Amid Explosive Rise in Infections...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/europe/putins-covid-19-boasts-sour-amid-explosive-rise-in-infections/articleshow/83663038.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe News: Already among the pandemic’s worst-hit countries, Russia’s experiencing a resurgence of the deadly virus aided by the rapid spread of the highly-conta</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: CDC can't regulate cruises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/559248-cdc-cant-regulate-cruises-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal in Florida judge on Friday ruled that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's (CDC) coronavirus-era sailing orders were an overreach of power, issuing a preliminary injunction temporarily barring the CDC from enforcing the guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taser-wielding madman sparks mayhem in park...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/19/taser-wielding-man-sparks-mayhem-in-washington-square-park-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was left covered in blood after she was “run over” in the stampede to safety, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombies, Semen, Big Racks: Inside Deer Breeding Industry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zombies-semen-big-racks-inside-130649327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Photos via GettyTexas-bred deer are currently infected with an incurable, highly contagious, zombie-like disease, and as if that weren’t bad enough, the likelihood that the disease has spread across the state among the wild population is increasing by the minute. And while the disease has been found in several other states prior, grassroots groups are pointing the finger at Texas deer breeders, who they believe, through political-will have skirted regulation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-person marches, music and reflection as Americans mark Juneteenth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619090141-6yv50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrations and activism planned for Juneteenth holiday after a year that sparked a reckoning over racism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Severe' Blood Shortage Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/06/18/severe-blood-shortage-nationwide-impacting-minnesota-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At one of the Red Cross donation sites in Bloomington, they say some of their most common donors are frontline healthcare workers, who are seeing this shortage firsthand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Move Here, You Make Deal With Nature': Life in Fire-Prone Canyon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/19/if-you-move-out-here-you-make-a-deal-with-nature-life-in-a-fire-prone-canyon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPANGA, Calif. — The Palisades Fire that forced hundreds to evacuate last month on the outskirts of Los Angeles never</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memphis erases Confederate general from public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tn-state-wire-memphis-racial-injustice-race-and-ethnicity-7e5941b9a05b0e01247b1bc89d7da348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Confederate Gen. Nathan Bedford Forrest’s polarizing presence has hung over Memphis since he moved here in 1852 — his legacy cemented by a giant statue that loomed over all who passed his gravesite in a popular park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit by ransomware attack? Payment may be deductible...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-government-and-politics-d8c1e9958ad1e89eab83f44e6ca70a94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As ransomware attacks surge, the FBI is doubling down on its guidance to affected businesses: Don't pay the cybercriminals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-line judiciary head wins Iran presidency..</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-judiciary-4d60554fd608a5dea2c76a303ec352d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran's hard-line judiciary chief won a landslide victory Saturday in the country's presidential election, a vote that both propelled the supreme leader's protege into Tehran's highest civilian position and saw the lowest turnout in the Islamic Republic's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 inches?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/la-state-wire-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-storms-2a55717d3441af8d128a476932aeaca2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Thunderstorms and high winds on the east side of Tropical Storm Claudette battered the Florida panhandle and much of Alabama on Saturday, as the weather system moved toward the North Carolina coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partygoers, police injured at curfew-busting rave in France...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-097cff85c058bfadf6dcb3a4f4637828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French police clashed with party-goers as they tried to break up an unauthorized rave in western France, authorities said Saturday. A 22-year-old man lost his hand and several others were injured amid the violence, including police.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
