<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New York Police Seek Authority to Take Down Drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-police-seek-authority-to-take-down-drones-11550419320?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police officials said they are concerned that propaganda abroad showing weaponized drones can inspire terrorists to use drones for lone-wolf attacks in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Ready to Challenge Emergency Declaration...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-ready-to-challenge-trumps-emergency-declaration-11550427992?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats signaled they are gearing up to challenge President Trump’s use of his emergency powers to fund construction of a wall along the southern U.S. border, which would likely tie up implementation of one of his core campaign promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Lashed Out at Hateful Doubters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/flashback-actor-of-the-year-jussie-smollett-cries-and-lies-on-gma-lashes-out-at-hateful-doubters-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's richest man plans move to Monaco...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/britains-richest-man-plans-move-14010824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Brexiteer Sir Jim Ratcliffe, who built up the chemicals giant Ineos, has been working with the accountant PwC on the tax avoidance plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas claims Israel sent bugged shoes to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Hamas-claims-Israel-sent-bugged-shoes-to-spy-on-them-580897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shipment of suspicious shoes that came through the Kerem Shalom Crossing were sent to Hamas to examine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  ONION BLEEDS MONEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/univision-reveals-write-down-struggling-gizmodo-media-group-assets-1186776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company reported that the assets lost $32.5 million in the fourth quarter of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump erupts at 'SNL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6714353/Trump-says-Alec-Baldwins-Saturday-night-Live-parody-looked-into.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin had lampooned him on the show nine hours earlier, telling a mock press conference in his Trump voice that 'you can all see why I have to fake this national emergency.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehearsed attack?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/02/17/jussie-smollett-pals-reportedly-rehearsed-alleged-attack/?_ga=2.207625489.267642857.1550199666-2051527208.1550003555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops have said the pair of budding model-actors have a “relationship” with Smollett and worked on “Empire.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers, fashion brands struggle with racial insensitivity...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/5e7aa8fe93484c8d9d0e172736948a7a/retailers-fashion-brands-struggle-racial-insensitivity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Retailers and top fashion brands like Gucci and Prada keep apologizing for products that smack of racial insensitivity.The big question is: Why does it keep happening?Experts say many of these fashion companies live in a sort of bubble and lack the diversity in their staff that could vet their fashions. They also blame the increasing pressures facing the industry to push products from the design board to the stores and online in weeks rather than months without taking time to thoroughly review products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Call to Pressure Tehran Falls on Deaf Ears...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pences-calls-to-pressure-iran-fall-on-deaf-ears-in-europe-11550415611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European officials brushed off U.S. Vice President Mike Pence’s call for the bloc to ratchet up pressure on Iran, saying they will continue defending the 2015 nuclear deal and stay engaged with Iran’s government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toasters Toxic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/health-news/8445285/burnt-toast-more-toxic-traffic-fumes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURNT toast can expose people to more pollution than if they were standing at a busy road junction, a study has claimed. Researchers at the University of Texas at Austin found burnt toast was espec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Straight White Male Dem Run? Very Carefully...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/02/17/white-male-democrats-2020-225101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very carefully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Heckled for Native American Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/elizabeth-warren-heckled-at-campaign-stop-about-her-native-american-claims-why-did-you-lie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President tells Europe to take back ISIS fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/17/politics/donald-trump-isis-fighters-europe-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets, President Donald Trump has said European countries should take back and put on trial hundreds of ISIS fighters who have been captured in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala off to best start, say strategists, donors...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/430298-harris-off-to-best-start-among-dems-in-race-say-strategists-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris is off to the fastest start among Democrats who have already entered the 2020 presidential race, say party strategists and donors closely following the contest’s early stages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie' deer disease spreads to 24 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/02/16/zombie-deer-chronic-wasting-disease-could-affect-humans/2882550002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are in an unknown territory situation," infectious disease expertÂ Michael Osterholm said of Chronic wasting disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China data leak exposes vast hi-tech surveillance operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/2186547/china-data-leak-exposes-vast-hi-tech-surveillance-operation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch researcher says tracking firm left database of personal details unprotected for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$133 million Albuquerque electric bus system going nowhere fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-abq-art-albuquerque-electric-buses-20190213-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was said Albuquerque Rapid Transit would revitalize the city and make it a mass transit leader. Instead, ART is a target of contempt, mired in problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer seriously injured in Australia shark attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190217-surfer-seriously-injured-australia-shark-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surfer seriously injured in Australia shark attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver encrypts police radio traffic, blocking public from listening...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/02/15/denver-encrypt-police-radio-traffic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public will no longer be able to tune into Denver police radio traffic once the department switches to new radio technology in the coming months that will encrypt all communications, though new…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTHONY WEINER OUT OF PRISON...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/17/anthony-weiner-out-of-prison-early-pre-release-sexting-minor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Weiner is no longer behind bars, but he's still has a few months under federal custody before he's freed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller questions CAMBRIDGE ANALYTICA director...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/feb/17/brittany-kaiser-trump-russia-robert-mueller-cambridge-analytica</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second former employee of controversial data firm to be questioned by special counsel’s inquiry into Russia collusion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black snot, cancer risks: NYC subway air dirty...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-air-quality-subway-mta-20190215-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t be fooled by the fact that the trains run on electricity: Diesel fumes stink up subway air, adding to a toxic brew of pollution that researchers say is bad for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long before City Hall rats, L.A. struggled with rise of typhus...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-ln-typhus-20190217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases have been increasing in California for more than a decade. A total of 167 people were diagnosed with typhus last year, compared with 13 in 2008. Almost all of the cases were in Los Angeles and Orange counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-top FBI lawyer: 2 Cabinet officials were 'ready to support' 25th Amendment effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-top-fbi-lawyer-2-trump-cabinet-officials-were-ready-to-support-25th-amendment-effort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former top FBI lawyer James Baker, in closed-door testimony to Congress, detailed alleged discussions among senior officials at the Justice Department about invoking the 25th Amendment to remove President Trump from office, claiming he was told Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein said two Trump Cabinet officials were “ready to support” such an effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds stranded as British airline collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/17/flybmi-british-airline-collapses-strands-hundreds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of passengers throughout Europe have been stranded by the abrupt collapse of the British regional airline Flybmi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the horrifying, unspoken world of sexually abusive nuns...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/16/inside-the-horrifying-unspoken-world-of-sexually-abusive-nuns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“God is Love,” Sister Mary Juanita Barto told Cait Finnegan as she repeatedly raped her in classrooms at Mater Christi High School in Queens in the late 1960s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flames shoot from ground in NYC manhole explosions...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/flames-shoot-from-ground-in-midtown-manhole-explosions/5142405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flames shot from the ground after two manholes exploded in Manhattan on Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential privacy lapse found in Americans' census data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aba8e57c145047b5bab11b62baaa7f7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An internal team at the Census Bureau found that basic personal information collected from more than 100 million Americans during the 2010 head count could be reconstructed from obscured data, but with lots of mistakes, a top agency official disclosed Saturday. The age, gender, location, race and ethnicity for 138 million people were potentially vulnerable. So far, however, only internal hacking teams have discovered such details at possible risk, and no outside groups are known to have grabbed data intended to remain private for 72 years, chief scientist John Abowd told a scientific conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster Patrick Caddell Dies at 68...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a85453edd1a478288d7d2a5f07003a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Patrick Caddell, the pollster who helped propel Jimmy Carter in his longshot bid to win the presidency and later distanced himself from Democrats, has died, a colleague said Saturday night. He was 68. Caddell died Saturday in Charleston, South Carolina, after suffering a stroke. That's according to Professor Kendra Stewart of the College of Charleston, who confirmed the death to The Associated Press. After working with Democrats in the 1970s and 1980s, Caddell eventually drifted away from the Democratic Party and began advising supporters of Republican Donald Trump and was a contributor to Fox News for a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett's Lawyers Call Cops Liars...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/jussie-smollett-attack-suspect-lawyers-lie-statement-chicago-police-empire-1202559103/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREAKING… As Chicago police declare a significant shift in “the trajectory of the investigation” of the alleged attack on Jussie Smollett nearly three weeks ago, the attorneys for the E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD GET 3 YEARS IN PRISON FOR FILING FALSE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6713267/Chicago-police-believe-Jussie-Smollett-PAID-two-Nigerian-brothers-ATTACK-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police want to speak to Jussie Smollett as investigators believe he paid two men - Olabinjo Osundairo (top inset) and Abimbola Osundairo (bottom inset) - to stage an assault against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELF HATE!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/16/entertainment/jussie-smollett-attack/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two law enforcement sources with knowledge of the investigation tell CNN that Chicago Police believe actor Jussie Smollet paid two men to orchestrate an assault on him that he reported late last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED:  Chicago police to re-question actor Jussie Smollett...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-jussie-smollett-police-question-20190216-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police said Saturday they have reached out to the attorney for "Empire" star Jussie Smollett because they want to speak to Smollett after releasing two brothers they had been questioning about a reported attack against the actor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  'EMPIRE' STAR STAGED ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jussie-smollett-case-brothers-say-empire-actor-paid-them-to-participate-in-alleged-attack-source-says-2019-02-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source close to the investigation confirms to CBS News the brothers told detectives Smollett paid them to participate the alleged attack on January 29</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAID BROTHERS TO USE NOOSE</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/hoax-police-think-empire-star-jussie-smollett-paid-two-men-to-attack-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'finish the wall' becomes 2020 push... </title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/nation-world/2019/02/trump-seeks-to-turn-his-failure-to-build-the-wall-into-a-campaign-rallying-cry.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump and his political team plan to make his yearslong quest for a border wall one of the primary thrusts of his re-election effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster Patrick Caddell Dies at 68...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/16/obituaries/patrick-caddell-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades after aiding the Democratic presidential campaigns of George McGovern and Jimmy Carter, Patrick Caddell began to advise conservatives including Stephen Bannon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: US military planes filled with humanitarian aid for Venezuelans land at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article226330885.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate panel to investigate meetings between Russians, Obama officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/16/senate-panel-probing-meetings-between-russians-and/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Finance Committee is probing meetings reportedly held in 2015 between two of former President Barack Obama’s top economic officials and Maria Butina, a Russian national who later pleaded guilty to conspiring to covertly influence U.S. foreign policy, the panel said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  Homeland Security replacing troubled biodefense system with another flawed approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-biowatch-replacement-20190215-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is quietly moving to replace BioWatch, the nation’s problem-plagued system for detecting an airborne attack of anthrax spores or other infectious agents, with technology that also has severe shortcomings, a Times investigation has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay mayor accused of sexual harassment as #MeToo reckoning comes to West Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-weho-sexual-scandal-protests-20190216-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, John Duran has been a kind of public avatar for West Hollywood's cheekily sexual culture at City Hall. Now, amid a scandal involving new allegations of sexual misconduct by the mayor and, separately, a prominent West Hollywood donor, cracks are showing in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Feminist writer suing TWITTER for deceptive trade practices...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/meghan-murphy-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' star hires Michael Cohen's criminal defense lawyer...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/02/16/jussie-smollett-hires-michael-cohens-criminal-defense-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Monico did not say how long he’s been representing Smollett, or in what capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden in Munich: America Is 'an Embarrassment'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-europe-america-today-embarrassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The America I see values basic human decency, not snatching children from their parents or turning our back on refugees at our border’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic at 'HAMILTON'! Fears of gunman as audience flee theatre...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/9c7e96a6ebef4747a2e2f1ed4806d44f/medical-emergency-triggers-stampede-san-francisco-theater</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Chaos broke out during a performance of the musical "Hamilton" at San Francisco's Orpheum theater Friday night after audience members mistook a medical emergency for a shooting.A woman had a heart attack and someone broke open an emergency defibrillator, activating an alarm at the same time that gunfire went off on stage as part of the show's duel scene, city fire department spokesman Jonathan Baxter said.The scene depicts the deadly duel between Alexander Hamilton and Aaron Burr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING NEWS:  CNN Reporter helps Kamala Harris try on clothes during campaign stop...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/this-is-cnn-reporter-helps-kamala-harris-try-on-clothes-during-campaign-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris went clothes shopping as a part of her campaign for president, and a CNN reporter couldn’t help but assist the candidate with picking out a new jacket. CBS reporter Kaitlin Huey-Burns tweeted a video of Harris in a Columbia, South Carolina boutique trying on a jacket. When the campaign trail takes you to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Wishes Everyone 'Happy Thanksgiving' On Valentine's Day... </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/confusion-pelosi-wishes-happy-thanksgiving-on-valentines-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is wrong with Nancy Pelosi? The House Speaker held a public bill signing on Thursday, and during her remarks, she wished reporters a “Happy Thanksgiving.” It was Valentine’s Day. She was a mere 84 days late. Watch: ﻿ The woman second in line to the presidency didn’t correct herself. Earlier in the day, the …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
