<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump Picks Lag...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-picks-lag-cheney-gop-incumbents-in-fundraising/ar-AAPAhri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three House Republicans targeted by former President Donald Trump raised more money in the third quarter than his hand-picked candidates to defeat them, according to Federal Election Commission filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Quants Could Disrupt Process That Sways Power in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/math-quants-could-disrupt-process-that-sways-power-in-washington-1.1667150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State judges bedeviled by weirdly shaped and obviously partisan congressional district maps can now get expert help from an unusual source: math nerds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Abbott, DeSantis Compete for National Limelight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/republican-governor-frenemies-compete-for-national-limelight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Governor ‘Frenemies’ Compete for National Limelight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Parts: Cars Stuck at Garages for WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/car-parts-shortages-are-hitting-u-s-garages-creating-weeks-long-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars Get Stuck at U.S. Garages for Weeks in Spare-Parts Shortage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax stand-off between Chicago mayor, police hits courts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-vaccine-stand-off-between-073631289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago judge on Friday banned a police union president from making public statements on the city's Covid-19 policy as a stand-off over vaccine mandates sparked dueling lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After months in lockdown, a weary world is ready to dance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-cuba-4d54c5429b5238d2d1c086290881d4fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in the depths of the pandemic -- even when the world locked down, leaving billions isolated and desolated -- there were those who danced. “I did not stop dancing for a second,” says Federico Carrizo, who competed in the Tango World Championship in Buenos Aires last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhappy with prices, ranchers look to build own meat plants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-iowa-nebraska-d95ef3d2aee8e80aa5aca6d06ffa50a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Like other ranchers across the country, Rusty Kemp for years grumbled about rock-bottom prices paid for the cattle he raised in central Nebraska, even as the cost of beef at grocery stores kept climbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands demonstrate in Rome against neo-fascists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-rome-italy-49b05744b74f06230af52e7f829e1006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Tens of thousands of union members and other Italians gathered in Rome to stand up against rising fascism Saturday, a week after right-wing extremists forced their way into the headquarters of Italy's most powerful labor confederation while protesting a COVID-19 certification requirement for workplaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furious Manchin slaps Sanders: 'I won't take orders from socialist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10098231/Joe-Manchin-criticizes-stater-Bernie-Sanders-op-ed-West-Virginias-biggest-newspaper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders, senator for Vermont, took the highly unusual step on Friday of publishing an op ed in the main newspaper in West Virginia, home state of Senator Joe Manchin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem incumbents bolster advantage in key Senate races...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/577034-democratic-incumbents-bolster-fundraising-advantage-in-key-senate-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic senators waging tight reelection bids saw a windfall in fundraising in the third quarter of 2021, beefing up their war chests ahead of what are expected to be brutal fights to retain their seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden giving stiff-arm to press interviews...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/577020-biden-giving-stiff-arm-to-press-interviews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has only given 10 one-on-one press interviews since taking office in January, a low number that is drawing more attention toward the White House’s efforts to control and manage the way Biden interacts with reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX can't shake Chappelle controversy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/576998-netflix-cant-shake-chappelle-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix can't seem to close the door on "The Closer," with the streaming giant only further inflaming controversy with its defense of Dave Chappelle's mocking of the transgender community in his latest comedy special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short on Staff, Hospices Ask New Patients To Wait...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/short-on-staff-some-hospices-ask-new-patients-to-wait/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anne Cotton had enjoyed her years at an assisted living facility in Corvallis, Ore. But at 89, her health problems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money Floods Race for Control of Congress, More Than Year Early...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/money-floods-the-race-for-control-of-congress-more-than-a-year-early/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dizzying amount of money is already pouring into the battles for the House and the Senate more than a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Venezuela, Rum Maker Offers Gangsters Life Outside of Crime...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/in-venezuela-a-rum-maker-offers-gangsters-a-life-outside-of-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the process, the family running the company, Ron Santa Teresa, has gone from bankruptcy to exporting an award-winning vintage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finneas, Pop Star's Secret Weapon, Strides Into Spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/15/finneas-a-pop-stars-secret-weapon-strides-into-the-spotlight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — There’s a ghoul hanging around Finneas’s house. A dark shadow spinning past the window of his otherwise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graveyard of Empires: Beijing Spooked by Afghanistan Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-14/afghanistan-quagmire-threatens-to-lure-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent attack in Afghanistan carried out by a Uighur Muslim has shaken China’s top national security decisionmakers, who now question the value of promises from the Taliban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio ignores?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/15/radio-nowhere-so-far-adeles-easy-on-me-ignored-by-two-biggest-pop-stations-in-new-york-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sulu Calls Kirk 'Unfit Guinea Pig'...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/10/william-shatner-blue-origin-space-ride-draws-celebrity-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Takei called him an “unfit guinea pig” for space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to Discharge All Sailors Refusing Vax... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/10/14/new-navy-guidance-will-discharge-sailors-refusing-covid-19-vaccination-without-exemption</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This story has been updated with additional information about the Navy vaccine mandate. All active-duty Navy personnel must be vaccinated by Nov. 28 or face separation, according to a Navy administrative message released Wednesday. Any active-duty Navy service members who do not get fully vaccinated or do not have an approved or pending exemption will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bill Clinton in hospital for infection; ICU for days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-business-california-bill-clinton-575328d3d0411d5186465c6712ee3d8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORANGE, Calif. (AP) — Bill Clinton is doing fine and will be released soon from a Southern California hospital where he's being treated for an infection, President Joe Biden said. Biden said Friday during remarks at the University of Connecticut that he had spoken to Clinton and the former president “sends his best.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  76ERS Star Faked Exposure To Evade NBA Playoff Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/bombshell-report-claims-76ers-star-ben-simmons-may-have-faked-covid-19-exposure-to-evade-nba-playoff-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Simmons is back with the Philadelphia 76ers, returning just one week before the regular season tips off, but all does not appear to be resolved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Defends:  'Good Thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jen-psaki-defends-rising-prices-good-thing-because-it-means-more-people-are-buying-goods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Jen Psaki defended the idea of economic fragility as a "high-class problem," saying it meant "more people" were buying goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to Stage Largest Robot Tank Experiment Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/10/us-army-stage-largest-robot-tank-experiment-ever/186110/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its lessons will inform the Army’s next-gen-unmanned-vehicles plan to ask tech firms to deliver the brains and established firms to deliver the wheels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launch to target 8 mysterious asteroids...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/10/15/NASA-Lucy-spacecraft-launch/7741634241303/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most complicated space journeys ever planned, NASA's Lucy mission to eight asteroids, is scheduled for liftoff early Saturday from Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERGRANDE crisis shines light on China's millions of empty homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/14/business/evergrande-china-property-ghost-towns-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evergrande's troubles are part of a much bigger problem. Here's a look at how it first originated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden admits 'not going to get $3.5 trillion' plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2021/oct/15/trump-allies-subpoena-orders-capitol-attack-committee-bannon-biden-us-politics-live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President says reconciliation bill price tag will be below $3.5tn: ‘We’ll get less than that’ – follow all the latest politics news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Dem Wipeout Inevitable?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/is-a-democratic-wipeout-inevitable/ar-AAPywIj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even when the president’s party passes historic legislation, voters don’t seem to care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Broken Heart Syndrome' Becoming More Common Among Middle-Aged Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/broken-heart-syndrome-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notably, broken heart syndrome diagnoses have also seen an uptick since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of inmates riot in Russian prison...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211015192752-vm4yy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PRISON/RIOTS:Hundreds of inmates riot in Russian prison - reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Taking Out Loans Against NFTs -- And Defaulting...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7e58j/people-are-taking-out-loans-against-their-nftsand-defaulting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The endless search for profit is spawning increasingly ridiculous schemes centered on the financialization of NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real reason inflation becoming so worrisome: Getting in our heads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-real-reason-inflation-is-becoming-so-worrisome-it-s-getting-in-our-heads/ar-AAPzEPP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American families and businesses are changing their habits as they increasingly believe high prices are here to stay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY mulls spinning off ESPN?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/disney-shares-whipsaw-as-report-on-espn-split-called-inaccurate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney Shares Whipsaw as Report on ESPN Split Called Inaccurate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires Employee for Sharing Confidential Data...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/netflix-fires-employee-confidential-data-reporter-1235090416/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has terminated an unidentified staffer who shared “commercially sensitive information” with someone outside the company that was included in a Bloomberg news report, violating t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY mulls spinning off ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://puck.news/could-disney-spin-off-espn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;puck.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Chapek has asked some of his closest deputies to explore the strategic rationale for potentially spinning off the sports network, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Katey Sagal Hit By Car In LA, Hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/10/15/katey-sagal-hit-by-car-hospitalized-injuries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Katey Sagal got hit by a car while crossing the street in L.A., but she's going to be okay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Puts First Responders on Leave -- While Crime Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/law-and-order/2021/10/15/san-francisco-puts-nearly-200-unvaccinated-first-responders-on-leave-while-crime-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 180 first responders in San Francisco face termination for refusing to get the coronavirus vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area skateboarder chased down, stabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Skateboarder-Chased-Down-Stabbed-Wednesday-Night-16532413.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLEASANT HILL (BCN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male contraceptive 'testicle bath' considered ground-breaking...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/relationships/sex/male-contraceptive-bath-device-wins-dyson-award/news-story/8a0e4cbc6a80dad774ac9331ee56430a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A groundbreaking form of male contraception which uses a kind of “testicle bath” to prevent pregnancy has been unveiled in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket blasts off for longest crewed mission to space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211015-china-rocket-blasts-off-for-longest-crewed-mission-to-space-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China rocket blasts off for longest crewed mission to space station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol cop indicted for obstruction after riot...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/10/capitol-police-officer-indicted-for-obstruction-after-riot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Capitol Police officer has been indicted on obstruction of justice charges after prosecutors say he helped to hide evidence of a rioter’s involvement in the Jan. 6 insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: More Than HALF Of Patients Develop 'Long Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/half-will-develop-long-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both adults and children may experience several potential health issues for as long as six months post-recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOOTERS waitresses complain new shorts are basically underwear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/some-hooters-servers-tiktok-are-saying-new-shorts-are-too-n1281610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One employee on TikTok described the new shorts as "like underwear."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOUSANDS PROTEST MANDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/italy-protests-erupt-covid-regulations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests erupted in Italy as one of the most stringent anti-coronavirus measures in Europe went into effect Friday, requiring all workers, from magistrates to maids, to show a health pass to get into their place of employment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oddsmakers:  The Don favorite to win in '24...</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/british-bookies-trump-favorite-win-2024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday former president Donald J. Trump became favorite on Betfair to be the 2024 presidential winner, with his ‘shortest odds ever’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkins scarce...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pumpkin-shortage-hits-the-us-ahead-of-halloween</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You could have trouble getting a pumpkin this Halloween season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAFF, CONSTITUENTS WITNESS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10096107/Police-swoop-road-outside-building-MP-David-Amess-holding-constituency-surgery-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tory MP for Southend West, 69, was holding a surgery at the Belfairs Methodist Church, in Eastwood Road North, Leigh-on-Sea when his attacker ran into the building wielding a knife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver Shortage Only Making Supply Issues Worse...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/13/truck-driver-shortage-supply-chain-dilemma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With fewer drivers on the road, trucking companies can raise their rates according to the demand for their services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defends 'space tourism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3861530/william-shatner-hits-back-prince-william-space-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STAR Trek’s William Shatner has hit back after Prince William slammed ‘space tourism’ following the actor’s flight to the edge of space. The 90-year-old became the oldest ev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Amoral algorithm cult'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/hannah-gadsby-attacks-netflix-dave-chappelle-ted-sarandos-1235031808/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Now I have to deal with even more of the hate and anger that Dave Chappelle’s fans like to unleash on me every time Dave gets 20 million dollars," the Australian comedian says in an Instagram post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatner Shrugs Off Prince William After Joyride to Stratosphere...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/william-shatner-reacts-to-prince-williams-disapproval-of-space-race-exclusive-173739</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor recently became the oldest person to travel to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extremely dangerous societal experiment'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/technology-to-automatically-scan-all-iphones-threatens-democracy-researchers-warn-12434352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of cryptographers and computer engineers say introducing the scanning tool would be "an extremely dangerous societal experiment".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARANDOS DOUBLES DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/hannah-gadsby-slams-netflix-ted-sarandos-dave-chappelle-defense-1234856317/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the moment Netflix announced itself as an original programming player with House Of Cards, the streamer has been touting its great relationship with talent. That reputation has taken hit over …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaped Maryland Zebra Found Dead in Illegal Snare Trap...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2021/10/15/rest-in-peace-and-run-wild-forever-maryland-zebra/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the famously evasive zebras has died in Prince George's County; two others remain at large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed-up employees now Big Tech's biggest fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/newsletters/sourcecode/tech-worker-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your five-minute guide to what's happening in tech this Friday, from how tech workers are turning the tables to LinkedIn leaving China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Wants Wearables to Track Employee Health Everywhere They Go...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/10/dhs-wants-wearables-track-employee-health-work-and-home/186106/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biometric tech will be used to help employees manage physical and mental health in high-stress mission areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE censors Quran, Bible apps in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/apple-took-down-a-quran-app-and-a-bible-app-in-china-on-the-request-of-chinese-officials/ar-AAPyNqz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple told the BBC that Chinese officials had complained that the Quran and Bible apps broke laws on hosting illegal religious texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery beast with no eyes, ears or mouth stuns diver...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/mystery-beast-no-eyes-ears-25221579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lukas Ostertag, from Heidelberg, Germany, was one of those who encountered the freaky sea beast, which he described as being a “long square rubber pipe-like thing”, while diving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump harps on 'golden showers' at Republican retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-gop-meeting-putin-xi-jinping-b1938858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump takes credit for reviving ‘dying’ Republican party, despite it losing control of Congress during his presidency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS:  +5...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/576877-mcauliffe-holds-slim-lead-over-youngkin-in-fox-news-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia gubernatorial candidate Terry McAuliffe (D) held a slim lead over his Republican opponent Glenn Youngkin, according to a new poll published Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Cher sues Sonny widow over royalties...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/music/cher-sues-mary-bono-over-1960s-hits-rights-and-royalties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cher filed a lawsuit against Sonny Bono's widow Mary on Wednesday and is seeking $1 million in damages. The lawsuit claims rights and royalties from the songs Cher and Sonny recorded as a duo including "I Got You Babe" and "The Beat Goes On" are allegedly being withheld from Cher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SHOCK</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/david-amess-mp-dies-after-being-stabbed-at-constituency-surgery-police-say-12434589</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sir David, who represented Southend West in Essex, was attacked on Friday afternoon at Belfairs Methodist Church in Leigh-on-Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Musk Walloped Bezos...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-walloped-jeff-bezos-082104139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastIn 2019, President Donald Trump was already planning to end his second term in office with a mighty blast that would secure his place in history. He would get Americans back on the moon in 2024—four years sooner than NASA planned.The last American astronaut to walk on the moon was Eugene Cernan, in December 1972, for Apollo 17. Those missions had been a momentous achievement, matching American technical mastery with human courage and the aspirati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer sentiment slips to near decade lows...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-consumer-sentiment-slips-to-near-record-lows-as-confidence-in-biden-policies-significantly-declines-11634307758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Michigan's gauge of consumer sentiment fell to a preliminary October reading of 71.4 from a final September reading of 72.8. Economists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not into golden showers': Donald's unprompted defense at donor dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10094475/Im-not-golden-showers-Trump-bizarrely-brings-Steele-dossier-GOP-donor-retreat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump delivered a speech to donors at a Florida retreat organized by a group dedicated to getting more Republicans elected to the Senate on Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says it chased U.S. naval destroyer away from its waters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211015144824-fqyh9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/SECURITY (UPDATE 3, TV):UPDATE 3-Russia says it chased U.S. naval destroyer away from its waters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP STABBED TO DEATH IN CHURCH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-london-england-eda5b4786c84e68a59de9075efecbcf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Conservative lawmaker David Amess was stabbed to death on Friday during a routine meeting with constituents at a church in eastern England, an attack that united the U.K.'s fractious politicians in shock and sorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China set to send three astronauts to new space station...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/china-set-send-astronauts-longest-crewed-mission-80574582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is preparing to send three astronauts to live on its space station for six months — a new milestone for a program that has advanced rapidly in recent years</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
