<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet the virus hunters: Scientists track diseases X, Y and Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/29/scientists-hunt-diseases-x-y-z/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the pandemic threat currently keeping scientists awake at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He'll be the next mass shooter'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5899859/Woman-stalked-Annapolis-shooter-say-warned-police-5-years-ago-mass-shooter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annapolis shooter Jarrod W. Ramos, 38, had been flagged up to police as 'the next mass shooter' by a woman he obsessively stalked to the point where she had to change her name and flee the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 797-horsepower DODGE can gulp gallon of gas in 11 seconds...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2018/06/29/dodge-unveils-new-797-horsepower-hellcat-redeye/743960002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successor to Dodge's Demon has slightly less horsepower, but is still potent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Mexico's presidential frontrunner promising revolution. Can he deliver?</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/opinion/article/Mexico-s-presidential-frontrunner-is-promising-a-13036538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two failed attempts, Andrés Manuel López Obrador is on the verge of becoming Mexico's next president. According to opinion polls, the 64-year-old leftist has a likely insurmountable lead ahead of Sunday's election, buoyed by widespread anti-establishment sentiment. Sitting in the United States, there's a temptation to view the Mexican vote through the prism of President Trump, a deeply unpopular figure south of the border. But the support for López Obrador - or Amlo, as he's commonly called - is far more about revulsion with the domestic status quo than the current occupant of the White House, no matter what he says about a border wall and who will pay for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risks to Lake Mead, Colorado River intensifying greatly, federal officials say...</title>
      <link>https://tucson.com/news/local/risks-to-lake-mead-colorado-river-intensifying-greatly-federal-officials/article_ed5a3146-29fb-59ba-ab6b-a65d34ba258b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tucson.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depending on what assumptions are made in its computer models, the risks of catastrophically low levels at Mead by 2026 have jumped three to six times since 2007, Bureau of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German spy agency acknowledges employing Himmler's daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-nazis/german-spy-agency-acknowledges-employing-himmlers-daughter-idUSKBN1JP1BO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's intelligence service acknowledged on Friday that it had employed the daughter of top Nazi Heinrich Himmler in the 1960s, although she never renounced her father or Nazism, and remained active in far-right extremism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper covers own tragedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-paper-attacked-shooting-covers-own-tragedy-105902035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local newspaper targetted in a shooting that left five dead managed to publish on Friday, covering its own tragedy and leaving its editorial page blank in honor of those slain. "We are speechless," read a brief comment in the otherwise empty editorial page of The Capital, the print version</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender row makes waves in London park pond...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/transgender-row-makes-waves-london-park-pond-041452915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tranquil pond on London's Hampstead Heath has become the latest battleground over gender identity after a decision to allow transgender people to bathe in the women-only enclosure. The oasis amid the noise of the British capital is one of three fee-paying ponds that have been open for swimming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French nudists get cheeky with theme park and museum outings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-nudists-cheeky-theme-park-museum-outings-045358236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a nude yoga class in a Paris park and a "no clothes day" at the city's trendiest art museum, hundreds of naturists are due to descend on a theme park near the French capital Sunday for a spot of trampolining. France may be the world's top destination for naturist tourism -- with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAL-like robot to help astronaut in space odyssey...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hal-robot-help-astronaut-space-odyssey-080402803--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Joey Roulette Cape Canaveral, Fla. (Reuters) - A science fiction-inspired robot hardwired to assist astronauts will launch from Florida early Friday morning to become the first personal, artificial intelligence-powered companion in space.  The Crew Interactive Mobile Companion, or CIMON, is an English-speaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freaked Out Americans Desperately Seek to Escape the News...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/29/freaked-out-americans-desperately-seek-to-escape-the-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freaked Out Americans Desperately Seek to Escape the News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: We Have to 'Put Our Bodies on the Line' to Stop President...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-moore-we-have-to-put-our-bodies-on-the-line-to-stop-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Trump is not going to leave,” Moore predicted to Stephen Colbert, urging Democrats to do everything they can to get him out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Mueller Using Manafort To Target Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/28/even-blind-person-can-see-mueller-using-manafort-t/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge says “even a blind person” can see that Special Counsel Robert Mueller is prosecuting Paul Manafort as a way to acquire evidence against his “true target,” President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's trucker shortage could undermine economy...</title>
      <link>http://www.savannahnow.com/news/20180628/americas-trucker-shortage-could-undermine-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.savannahnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE MILTON, Ohio - Bob Blocksom, an 87-year-old former insurance salesman, needs a job. He hasn't saved enough money for his retirement. And trucking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts poised to be swing vote on high court...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-supreme-court-justice-anthony-kennedy-retires-20180627-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Anthony Kennedy says he is retiring. That will give President Donald Trump the chance to cement conservative control of the high court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump floats chief of staff replacements amid shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-floats-chief-staff-replacements-amid-shakeup-010702752--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's embattled Chief of Staff John Kelly is back in the spotlight this week as Trump prepares to overhaul his communications team amid a string of staff departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most intense heat to peak ahead of July 4th in Northeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/most-intense-heat-to-peak-ahead-of-july-4th-in-northeastern-us/70005343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touts new FOXCONN plant in Wisconsin...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-trump-foxconn-groundbreaking-wisconsin-20180628-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s visit to southeastern Wisconsin on Thursday for a groundbreaking ceremony for Foxconn highlights how his trade policies are playing out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VENDETTA'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jarrod-ramos-annapolis-shooting-suspect-identified-maryland-shooting-capital-gazette-today-2018-06-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court records show Ramos had a long-running legal dispute with the newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Was Like A War Zone'...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/capital-gazette-reporter-firsthand-account/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reporter at the Capital Gazette shared horrifying details of the deadly shooting in Annapolis Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VENDETTA'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Active-Shooter-Reported-at-Newspaper-Building-in-Maryland-486855471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people have died and several others are 'gravely injured' after a shooting Thursday at the Capital Gazette newspaper building in Annapolis, Maryland, local and federal officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACIAL RECOGNITION TECH USED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/multiple-people-reported-shot-maryland-newspaper-office-n887526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Gunman shot through the glass door to the office and opened fire on multiple employees," said a reporter for the Capital Gazette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Damaged fingertips to avoid identification...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/annapolis-shooting-five-dead-in-shooting-at-capital-gazette-newspaper-in-maryland-suspect-in-custody-2018-06-28-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people were killed Thursday in a shooting at a local newspaper building in Maryland, police say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Killer Lost Defamation Case Against Paper...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5898141/At-four-shot-gunman-Marylands-Capital-Gazette-newspaper-building.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people have been killed and more than a dozen injured during a mass shooting at Maryland's Capital Gazette newsroom on Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made Threats On Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/maryland/5-dead-in-targeted-attack-at-capital-gazette-newspaper-in-annapolis/65-568683955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people are dead and others were injured after a man opened fire Thursday inside the Capital Gazette newspaper office in Annapolis, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOOTING AT NEWSPAPER</title>
      <link>http://www.capitalgazette.com/bs-md-gazette-shooting-20180628-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting has occurred at the Capital Gazette in Anne Arundel County, a paper that is owned by The Baltimore Sun, according to reports from Gazette staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: No limit to how long humans can live...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/62942-human-life-span-limit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As technology advances, prospects for increasing the human life span are seemingly everywhere. But is there a limit to how long humans can live?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPITAL GAZETTE Says Will Publish Friday Paper...</title>
      <link>http://wjla.com/news/local/capital-gazette-paper-will-be-published-friday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capital Gazette will publish an issue on Friday, despite the fact that five people were shot and killed in the building where the newsroom is located Thursday afternoon.That's according to a tweet written by a photojournalist who works there, Joshua Mc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/reports-of-shots-fired-in-annapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five people are dead and several others were injured after a gunman opened fire inside the building that houses the Capital Gazette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shot Through Glass Door, Opened Fire On Employees...</title>
      <link>http://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/crime/bs-md-gazette-shooting-20180628-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting has occurred at the Capital Gazette in Anne Arundel County, a paper that is owned by The Baltimore Sun, according to reports from Gazette staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOTGUN INVOLVED...</title>
      <link>http://wjla.com/news/local/large-police-presence-in-annapolis-for-reported-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people are dead after a shooter opened fire at the Capital Gazette newspaper on Bestgate Road in Annapolis around 2:30 p.m. Thursday, police say. Authorities describe the suspect as a white man with a pony tail. After a lengthy search of the building,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 DEAD... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/reports-of-shots-fired-in-annapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five people are dead and several others were injured after a gunman opened fire inside the building that houses the Capital Gazette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov't anti-drone gun shoots drones -- at other drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2173039-the-us-has-an-anti-drone-gun-that-shoots-drones-at-other-drones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new anti-drone system built by the US can fire interceptor drones from a tube as well as jam the controls of potential incoming attackers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificially Intelligent Droid About To Invade Space..</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/robot-artificial-intelligence-invade-space-210554635.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A robot with true artificial intelligence is about to invade space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America cheese stockpile record high: 1.385 BILLION lbs!</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/america-has-a-record-high-stockpile-of-cheese-at-1385-billion-pounds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's stockpile of cheese is at its highest in more than 100 years, according to the United States Department of Agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweeping CA consumer privacy bill approved...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article213993229.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California lawmakers sent Gov. Jerry Brown a sweeping consumer rights privacy bill on Thursday, likely averting a more expansive initiative from going to voters in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dark Patterns' Push FACEBOOKGOOGLE Users Towards Less Privacy...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/06/27/study-calls-out-dark-patterns-in-facebook-and-google-that-push-users-towards-less-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More scrutiny than ever is in place on the tech industry, and while high-profile cases like Mark Zuckerberg's appearance in front of lawmakers garner headlines, there are subtler forces at work. This study from a Norway watchdog group eloquently and painstakingly describes the ways that companies l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITE AIDS blast Barry Manilow tunes to deter vagrants...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/28/rite-aids-are-blasting-barry-manilow-tunes-to-deter-vagrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He writes the songs that make people run. Some Rite Aid stores in California have taken to blasting Barry Manilow tunes as part of a plan to make loiterers scramble. Employees told the Wall Street …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>575 Arrested In Capitol Office Building...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/28/dem-congresswoman-among-anti-trump-protesters-arrested-inside-capitol-office-building.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Democratic Rep. Pramila Jayapal is among the numerous female protesters who were arrested inside a Capitol office building on Thursday while demonstrating against President Trump’s illegal immigration policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivy Leaguer known for fighting sex violence charged with child sex crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/06/28/ivy-league-student-known-for-fighting-sexual-violence-is-charged-with-child-sex-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities came across Joel Davis when an FBI agent posted a message on a 'fetish' website where people leave ads soliciting children for sex, according to the criminal complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gowdy Tells Rosenstein to Hurry Mueller Probe: 'Finish The Hell Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/finish-the-hell-up-gowdy-tells-rosenstein-to-show-evidence-of-wrongdoing-by-trumps-camp-or-end-mueller-probe-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROUP MEMBERSHIP SOARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/democratic-socialists-of-america-membership-surges-after-alexandria-ocasio-cortezs-stunning-victory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The day after the self-described democratic socialist unseated a long-serving Democratic congressman on Tuesday, DSA experienced a membership surge 35 times larger than normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive data leak could affect all Americans, researcher says...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/28/massive-data-leak-could-affect-nearly-all-american-adults-security-researcher-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactis, a marketing and data-aggregation firm, leaked information on individual adults and businesses. The leak involved about 340 million records on a publicly available server, security research…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEAT DOME' EXPANDS: Dangerous heat wave to scorch USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/28/heat-wave-dangerous-weather-central-eastern-us/741841002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dangerous and oppressive heat wave is forecast to scorch the central and eastern U.S. over the next few days. The worst of the heat will start in the Midwest on Friday before creeping its way east toward the Northeast and Mid-Atlantic by Saturday and Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA homes raided by feds in mystery explosions investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yorkdispatch.com/story/news/local/pennsylvania/2018/06/28/pennsylvania-homes-raided-investigation-mystery-explosions/36455421/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yorkdispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents and state and local police have swarmed two homes as part of an investigation into a series of mysterious explosions around a county about an hour north of Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Host city shopping malls evacuated after bomb threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-world-cup-host-city-12815215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll be bringing you the very latest updates, pictures and video on this breaking news story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crows 'reverse engineer' tools from memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/2265/crows-reverse-engineer-tools-memory-study-doc-16s2cf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French lawmakers urge fix for 60-year-old typo in constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-lawmakers-urge-fix-60-old-typo-constitution-161552735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French lawmakers are pushing for an official correction to a decades-old grammatical error which slipped into the country's constitution 60 years ago. The constitution was revised in 1958 when France switched from being a parliamentary to a presidential regime. MPs from the right-leaning UDI-Agir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranormal Researcher Claims To Find 'Time Warp' Near Vegas...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/time-warp-las-vegas-paranormal-investigator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Warren says he is the first person to ever discover a time warp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel graduates first women tank commanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-graduates-first-women-tank-commanders-161531054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jérusalem (AFP) - The Israeli army on Thursday graduated the first four women from its tank commanders' school, a step toward the formation of all-female tank crews. Another six have completed training as crew members, but actual deployment of any of the women will depend on the outcome of a review</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Weighing Senator Mike Lee for Supreme Court Vacancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-28/trump-is-said-to-weigh-senator-mike-lee-for-high-court-vacancy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has asked advisers their opinions about nominating Utah Senator Mike Lee to replace Justice Anthony Kennedy on the Supreme Court, according to three people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders press ahead with tough new migrant plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cc82506a683f4a8eab8aa436eed8e2db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — European Union leaders vowed Thursday to move forward with plans to screen migrants in northern Africa for asylum eligibility to dissuade many of them from setting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>84% support turning illegals into authorities...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/394624-mark-penn-84-percent-support-turning-undocumented-immigrants-over-authorities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent Democratic pollster Mark Penn said on Thursday that a vast majority of Americans don’t really support so-called "sanctuary cities" that shield undocumented immigrants from deportation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Readies For Busiest Day -- EVER!</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/tsa-busiest-day-friday-fourth-of-july-airport-screening-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA projects it will screen about 2.7 million passengers and crew on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil ace blames 'soft mattress' for World Cup injury...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6645736/marcelo-brazil-injury-bed-mattress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCELO’s mysterious injury during Brazil’s win over Serbia was reportedly caused by a BED. That’s according to doctor Rodrigo Lasmar, who believes a mattress at Brazil’s hotel in Moscow was respon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED SEALS DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trumps-no-1-deal-maker-jared-kushner-takes-winning-streak-to-wisconsin-for-13-000-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh from a whirlwind peace mission through the Middle East, the administration’s top deal maker, Jared Kushner, is heading to Wisconsin with President Trump to celebrate the biggest jobs deal of his young White House career, the groundbreaking of the massive Foxconn Technology Group project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Aide to Stone Subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/28/us/politics/roger-stone-andrew-miller-subpoenaed-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former aide, Andrew Miller, worked for Roger Stone, a longtime informal adviser to President Trump, during the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel eyeing Russians granted 'unusual access' to inauguration parties...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-eyeing-russians-granted-unusual-access-trump/story?id=56232847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several billionaires with deep ties to Russia attended exclusive, invitation-only receptions during Donald Trump’s inauguration festivities, guest lists show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space weapons in 'Near Future'... </title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/06/pentagon-intelligence-chief-russia-and-china-will-have-weapons-space-near-future/149335/?oref=d-channelriver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Intelligence Agency’s director says the U.S. lead in space is diminishing and tomorrow’s skies will be filled with enemy robot satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touts new FOXCONN plant in Wisconsin... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/trump-heads-to-wisconsin-to-tout-a-new-foxconn-plant-while-harley-dav.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A groundbreaking for a massive $10 billion Foxconn factory complex in Wisconsin is supposed to be evidence that the manufacturing revival fueled by President Donald Trump's "America First" policy is well underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rx: Zucchini, brown rice, turkey soup. Medicaid plan offers food as medicine...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/rx-zucchini-brown-rice-turkey-soup-medicaid-plan-offers-food-as-medicine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small group of insurers offers some members with serious illnesses medically tailored meals to improve their health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOCIALIST REVOLUTION'</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-wins-democratic-socialist-21st-century-vision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a values-based campaign that championed Medicare for All and the abolition of ICE, the 28-year-old Latina beat a top Democratic incumbent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ WANTS TO BE PREZ!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/27/ocasio-cortez-wants-to-be-president-mom-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurgent Democrat Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez wants to take her budding political career all the way to The White House, her mother told The Post on Wednesday. “Her aspiration is to be the pres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA HELL: Inflation rises to 43,378%!</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/781952/minimumwage-worker-venezuela-could-afford-5-cups-coffee-each-month--nothing-else</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five million Venezuelan bolivars is the equivalent of $1.45. It's also roughly a minimum-wage worker's entire monthly salary in the South American country. Thanks to stunning inflation, it now takes 1 million bolivars to buy a cup of coffee in a Venezuelan cafe, Bloomberg reports. That's one-fifth of Venezuela's monthly minimum wage, and 10,000-bill stack of Venezuela's most common bank note, the 100-bolivar bill. To illustrate Venezuela's rampant inflation, Bloomberg has tracked the price of a cup of coffee since December 2016 on its Cafe Con Leche index. One dose of caffeine cost 450 bolivars when the index launchedtwo years ago, but 43,378 percent inflation in the last year has led to today's astronomical price. Incredibly bleak moment milestone for Venezuela. The cost of one cup of coffee just hit 1 million Bolivars. https://t.co/Fbv2NqnAFl pic.twitter.com/LvziiWUynI — Joe Weisenthal (@TheStalwart) June 28, 2018 Additionally, if the pace of inflation over the past three months continues, Bloomberg estimates that inflation would be 482,153 percent after a year. Check out the Cafe Con Leche index at Bloomberg for a detailed — and astonishing — visual. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman drove 19 miles with ex-boyfriend clinging to car's hood...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/wild-car-hood-ride-178592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 28--A woman who drove nearly 20 miles with her ex-boyfriend clinging to the hood of her speeding car has been arrested on a negligence charge in connection with her vehicular antics on a Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Man Knocked Out Cold, Robbed In Middle Of NYC Intersection......</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/police-man-attacked-robbed-by-two-groups-of-suspects-in-the-bronx/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a man was attacked, knocked out and robbed in the Bronx by two different groups of suspects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star Ron Jeremy sued for sex assault...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/27/ron-jeremy-sued-sexual-assault-battery-washington-radio-model/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron Jeremy isn't out of the woods in Washington State -- his sexual assault case is going to civil court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Abramson, Ex-NEW YORK TIMES Editor Slams Paper: Making 'Horrible Mistakes,' Needs 'Course Correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jill-abramson-ex-new-york-times-editor-the-narcissistic-nyt-is-making-horrible-mistakes-needs-a-course-correction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her ‘pissed off’ tweet, the former editor slams the newspaper staff’s ‘narcissism,’ its ‘crucifying’ Ali Watkins profile, and ‘missing’ the rise of Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog trapped in hot car honks horn...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/dog-trapped-inside-hot-truck-12810651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small dog was filmed apparently locked inside the truck amid 27C temperatures by 17-year-old customer Gabrielle Dart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin summit set...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-putin/trump-putin-summit-to-unfold-in-cold-war-venue-helsinki-on-july-16-idUSKBN1JO1A5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin will hold their first summit on July 16 in Helsinki, a renowned venue for Cold War diplomacy, with nervous U.S. allies in Europe and Russia skeptics looking on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP new battleground for political warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-big-picture-yelp-battleground-political-warfare-fake-posts-8b22b23f-f6b4-4ce6-ad8e-956f5c3fa63c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politically-motivated "fake reviews" are on the rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches direct attack on Mueller...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5896975/Trump-goes-Robert-Mueller-hiding-conflicts-interest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump rarely targets Special Counsel Robert Mueller but took that step on Thursday, questioning on Twitter whether he has undisclosed conflicts that taint his Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBORG ALERT: Lab-grown human brains put into droids...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/frankenstein-cyborg-crabs-artificial-intelligence-12812604 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US scientific study is trying to find out why Neanderthals went extinct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  OIL SPIKES TO HIGHEST PRICE IN 4 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/iran-sanctions-could-soon-push-oil-prices-above-90-a-barrel-boaml-sa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s sustained bid to disrupt Iran’s petroleum exports could soon help to push oil prices above $90 a barrel, analysts told CNBC on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE barricades DC headquarters to prevent 'occupation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/ice-barricades-washington-dc-headquarters-to-prevent-activist-occupation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers barricaded an employee and visitor entrance Wednesday to prevent activists from performing an "occupation" of the agency's D.C. headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump Get Another?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/politics/with-kennedy-gone-everybody-is-looking-at-85-year-old-ruth-bader-ginsburg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA attendant kicks passengers off plane over airplane mode dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/nation-now/2018/06/28/delta-attendant-kicks-passengers-off-plane-over-airplane-mode-dispute/741161002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta Air Lines flight attendant forced passengers off a plane at Fort Wayne International Airport after a dispute with a black flier over whether or not her phone was turned to airplane mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents interrupt news interview with whistleblower...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/394575-government-agents-interrupt-news-interview-with-ice-whistleblower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents from the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) interrupted an interview with a former Immigrations and Customs Enforcement (ICE) spokesman on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Sheeran Sued for $100 Million for Ripping Off Marvin Gaye...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/28/ed-sheeran-sued-thinking-out-loud-lets-get-it-on-marvin-gaye/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Sheeran sued over "Thinking Out Loud" for allegedly ripping off Marvin Gaye's "Let's Get it On."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI ambulances and robot doctors: China seeks to ease hospital strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/ai-ambulances-and-robot-doctors--china-seeks-digital-salve-to-ease-hospital-strain-10480900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the eastern Chinese city of Hangzhou, an ambulance speeds through traffic on a wave of green lights, helped along by an artificial intelligence ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP Revised Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/final-reading-on-first-quarter-2018-gdp.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final reading on first-quarter gross domestic product was expected to show an increase of 2.2 percent, in line with the previous estimate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Chain to Introduce Driverless Grocery Deliveries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/kroger-to-soon-begin-driverless-grocery-delivery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kroger is partnering with autonomous car company Nuro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal cops move in on ICE protest in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://www.kgw.com/article/news/local/federal-cops-move-in-on-ice-protest-in-sw-portland/283-568461821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kgw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officers in riot gear moved into the protest siege of ICE headquarters in Southwest Portland at 5:30 a.m. Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now AMAZON to Sell Meds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/walgreens-cvs-shares-tank-after-amazon-buys-online-pharmacy-pillpack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania to make second visit to immigration centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jun/28/melania-trump-border-immigration-visit </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No details of Thursday’s trip to migrant shelters yet released after previous visit last week overshadowed by jacket controversy</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
