<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How Newsom could lose job to Republican in recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-california-e2-80-99s-gavin-newsom-could-lose-his-job-to-a-republican-in-a-recall/ar-AANIUPw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what you need to know to follow the special election to recall California Governor Gavin Newsom, why his job is threatened and who is running to replacement should he lose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For NFL teams with unvaccinated QBs, this could be long, complicated season...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/For-NFL-teams-with-unvaccinated-quarterbacks-16410338.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots gathered for practice Tuesday in Foxborough, Mass., without...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban shows off 'special forces' in propaganda blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210825-taliban-shows-off-special-forces-in-propaganda-blitz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban shows off 'special forces' in propaganda blitz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more ICU beds in Arkansas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/569293-no-more-icu-beds-in-arkansas-for-covid-19-patients-governor-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arkansas Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R) on Tuesday revealed that his state has run out of intensive care unit (ICU) beds to treat COVID-19 patients amid a surge of new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After takeover, concerns mount over U.S. counterterrorism ability...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825113009-xmjll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-COUNTERTERRORISM (PIX):After Taliban takeover, concerns mount over U.S. counterterrorism ability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam to pay recovered COVID patients to help in hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825091730-ytc07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIETNAM (PIX):Vietnam to pay recovered COVID-19 patients to help in hospitals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital detox: Can taking break from tech improve well-being?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825035945-ws30l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic fuels tech fatigue, researchers cast doubt on the benefits of a 'digital detox'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias hidden in mortgage-approval algorithms?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-technology-business-race-and-ethnicity-mortgages-2d3d40d5751f933a88c1e17063657586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new four-bedroom house in Charlotte, North Carolina, was Crystal Marie and Eskias McDaniels’ personal American dream, the reason they had moved there from pricey Los Angeles. A lush, long lawn, 2,700 square feet of living space, gleaming kitchen, and a neighborhood pool and playground for their son, Nazret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Cities Pitch Wall Street-Style Sign-On Bonuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/desperate-us-cities-pitch-wall-street-style-sign-on-bonuses/ar-AANJ0eS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The labor constraints jeopardize essential services such as trash pick-up, and exacerbate shortages in demanding jobs like 911 dispatchers that predated the Covid-19 crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Drought Crushing Ranchers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/25/the-worst-thing-i-can-ever-remember-how-drought-is-crushing-ranchers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOWNER, N.D. — Darrell Rice stood in a field of corn he’d planted in early June, to be harvested in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIRVANA Sued by Baby From Album Artwork for Child Pornography...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/nirvana-sued-by-baby-from-nevermind-album-artwork-for-child-pornography/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spencer Elden is suing the band for child sexual exploitation, saying he was unable to consent to having his image used for the iconic 1991 album</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pain compliance': Video shows trooper pummeling Black man...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-louisiana-monroe-ronald-greene-6c56ef6f5f3bc413d150737bf705e944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONROE, La. (AP) — Graphic body camera video kept secret for more than two years shows a Louisiana State Police trooper pummeling a Black motorist 18 times with a flashlight — an attack the trooper defended as “pain compliance.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student athletes wear ANKLE MONITORS so they can be alerted if another player tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9924171/Washington-State-high-schools-faces-controversy-asking-students-wear-COVID-ankle-monitors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents have deemed Eatonville High School's decision to implement COVID-19 trackers as 'intrusive and overreaching,' as school say they are 'proximity monitors' not trackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly $5 TRILLION spending plans win key House vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-democrats-advance-bidens-almost-204659880.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Joe Biden's plans to spend nearly $5 trillion to change the world's largest economy advanced in the House of Representatives on Tuesday, after Democratic leaders reached an agreement with centrist lawmakers to end a dispute threatening the bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil detains two travelers for perching atop iconic Christ statue...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-detains-two-french-travelers-002624464.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian authorities have detained two French men for watching the sun rise over Rio de Janeiro from the top of the iconic Christ the Redeemer statue while the monument was closed, one of the travelers told AFP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury, disgust that thousands will be left behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/fury-disgust-cia-pentagon-congress-thousands-afghans-will-be-left-n1277552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evacuations are likely to slow greatly by Friday to give U.S. troops time to withdraw. That's not enough time to evacuate all the Afghans who helped the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two House members make unauthorized trip to Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/two-congress-members-make-unauthorized-trip-to-kabul-amid-evacuation-efforts/ar-AANHPju?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps. Seth Moulton (D-Mass.) and Peter Meijer (R-Mich.), who both served in Iraq before being elected to Congress, returned home via a U.S. military flight used for evacuating U.S. citizens, allies and vulnerable Afghans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Attorney General's own agency produces report clearing him of bribery...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/08/24/texas-ag-ken-paxtons-own-agency-produces-report-clearing-him-bribery-abuse-of-office-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton’s office released a report Tuesday claiming to clear him of allegations that he repeatedly misused his power to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST US TROOPS START TO LEAVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/afghanistan-news-taliban-refugees-08-24-21/h_c4ad841c86a6d6123a9d5615bb97588d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one week after the Taliban takeover of Kabul, the situation at the capital's airport has become increasingly desperate as thousands still wait to depart the country. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's causing worst die-off of manatees? Starvation from Florida ecosystem collapse...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-08-worst-die-off-manatees-starvation-florida.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manatee deaths reported in the past half-century include nearly 5,000 from boat strikes, water structures and red tides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes DOUBLES among American youth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824220833-ug1b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HEALTH/DIABETES-YOUTH (PIX):Diabetes surges among American youth, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia gov. deploys National Guard medical staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/governor-deploys-national-guard-troops-hospitals-across-state/577SPPRU45HQTA7X3D7HBKRS5E/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The members of the Georgia National Guard are being deployed to hospitals across the state to assist hospital staff as emergency rooms near capacity because of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO SHOWS PARIS POLICE CHECKING BAR CODES...</title>
      <link>https://vm.tiktok.com/ZMRjpFGfV/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;vm.tiktok.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XposeTheCxntz (@xposethecxntz) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Police in Paris patrolling coffee shops scanning COVID passports 🤯 #woketok #STAYWOKE #covidvaccinesideeffects #spikeprotein #covidpassport #fypシ | Paris police scanning covid passports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahamas hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.travelandleisure.com/travel-news/cdc-adds-bahamas-level-4-travel-warning-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.travelandleisure.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention raised six more destinations to its highest warning level on Monday, including popular vacation hotspot the Bahamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SOAR MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/23/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks were marginally higher Tuesday following a broad-based rally on the first fully approved Covid-19 vaccine and ahead of the Fed summit this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices hit new record highs...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/569233-new-home-sales-tick-higher-as-prices-hit-new-record-highs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New home sales ticked higher in July while prices climbed to another record high, according to data released Tuesday by the Census Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAFD captain attacks city's vaccination requirement, prompting internal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lafd-captain-attacks-citys-vaccination-120021975.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles fire captain, Cristian Granucci, recorded a video of himself criticizing the city's COVID-19 vaccination requirement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Suppliers Having Trouble Keeping Shelves Stocked...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-food-suppliers-having-trouble-183524384.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some of the largest U.S. food distributors are reporting difficulties in fulfilling orders as a lack of workers weighs on the supply chain. Sysco Corp., North America’s largest wholesale food distributor, is turning away customers in some areas where demand is exceeding capacity. The company also said prices for key goods such as chicken, pork and paper products for takeout packaging are climbing amid tight supplies. In particular, production has slowed for high-demand, labor-inte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $3.5 TRILLION budget after deal with moderates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/house-passes-budget-blueprint-0a1258e07b1a8b9aeddb69980093c838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Striking a deal with moderates, House Democratic leaders muscled President Joe Biden’s multitrillion-dollar budget blueprint over a key hurdle Tuesday, ending a risky standoff and putting the party’s domestic infrastructure agenda back on track.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 leaders can't sway Biden to delay Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-afghanistan-g-7-summit-13631be5beba847935719ec4d8a4d5ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States clashed with some of its closest allies Tuesday over President Joe Biden’s insistence on sticking to an Aug. 31 Afghanistan withdrawal date that will shut down a frantic international evacuation effort from Taliban rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As chaos unfolds, White House projects calm: 'Gaslighting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/24/biden-afghanistan-evacuation-chaos-506753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t think the president’s rhetoric matches the conditions on the ground,” one former State Department official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA cancels annual meeting due to concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-texas-coronavirus-pandemic-b340c4bec89088fa69032c0ea84963f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The National Rifle Association announced Tuesday it has canceled its annual meeting, which had been set to be held next month in Houston, due to concerns over COVID-19. The NRA’s meeting had been set for Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passed out man found with 300 ballots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-95b6935d64ab60da519e2296d46df99a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORRANCE, Calif. (AP) — California authorities are investigating why a man found passed out in a car had more than 300 unopened mail-in ballots for the gubernatorial recall election. The man was arrested Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Early Test Case' for China-Led World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-early-test-case-for-a-china-led-world/ar-AANFZIY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing’s policies now that the Taliban is in charge will provide clues as to how it views global leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon masks required outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-health-oregon-coronavirus-pandemic-947bd5fe02d802978cf4318f5ab93e40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — People in Oregon, regardless of vaccination status, will once again be required to wear masks in most public outdoor settings — including large outdoor events where physical distancing is not possible — beginning Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Cop Fired for Saying N-Word...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aqwz5/a-black-cop-was-fired-for-saying-the-n-word-he-finally-got-his-job-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delvin White, a Tampa School Resource Officer, was fired last March. He just got his job back this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House authorizes $3.5 trillion of spending as national debt climbs to $29 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/democratic-led-house-authorizes-35-trillion-spending-national-debt-climbs-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi was ultimately able to secure yes votes from nine moderate House Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvanian who coughed on market produce, claimed virus gets jail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-3600f8f977c8105c3030641787149873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILKES-BARRE, Pa. (AP) — A Pennsylvania woman who pleaded guilty to coughing and spitting on food at a supermarket in the early days of the coronavirus pandemic was sentenced Tuesday to at least a year in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Expect a 'red shift'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/ballots-Gavin-Newsom-recall-counting-when-how-long-16405981.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 2020 presidential election, a few critical swing states reported Election Day...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee Admits to Suspicions About 'Official Explanations' of 9/11 Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/spike-lee-admits-to-suspicions-about-official-explanations-of-9-11-attacks-i-got-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spike Lee has admitted to questioning the "official explanations" of the 9/11 World Trade Center attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herschel Walker running for Senate in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/politics-blog/breaking-herschel-walker-is-running-for-us-senate-in-georgia/6GZ3BDZBHJHRFFJA76PT2K2XLA/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia football legend Herschel Walker launched a campaign for the U.S. Senate at the urging of former President Donald Trump, bringing both his high-profile celebrity and his untested political background to one of the premier national contests on the 2022 ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funds Hot Again...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hedge-funds-hot-again-good-040102845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Confined to their desks in the midst of the global pandemic, former Citadel traders Niall O’Keeffe and Tio Charbaghi made the rounds on video calls to woo investors for their new hedge fund.It should have been a hard sell. The price tag was high for a fledgling fund — a 20% cut of profits on top of a hefty 2% annual fee. The investment style, betting on rising and falling stocks, was out of vogue with investors. The pitch was uncompromising: take it or leave it.And yet, the duo ra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next up for shots: Kids under 12...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/24/health/covid-19-vaccines-kids-next-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Food and Drug Administration has given full approval to Pfizer's coronavirus vaccine for people age 16 and older. Approval for youths ages 12-15 is expected to follow soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS photographer killed after being left behind in retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/afghanistan-conflict-reuters-siddiqui/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danish Siddiqui was with soldiers on the front line of an Afghan Special Forces clash with the Taliban. New reporting, and his final photographs, cast light on his final hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD Expands Into Hormone-Therapy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/08/planned-parenthood-jumps-into-the-hormone-therapy-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The abortion group is swiftly becoming one of the nation’s largest providers of ‘gender affirming care,’ without counseling or doctor approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellphone catches fire on ALASKA jet upon landing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-3cee65159322ec431f1167807bf77717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATAC, Wash. (AP) — The cellphone of a passenger on an Alaska Airlines jet caught fire after the plane landed at the Seattle–Tacoma International Airport, forcing the crew to deploy evacuation slides to get everyone off, the carrier said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS CEO Blames Banks for Forcing 'Unfair' Porn Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/onlyfans-ceo-banks-forced-unfair-porn-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OnlyFans CEO Tim Stokely on Tuesday said the subscription platform's recent ban on porn is due to "unfair" treatment from banks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNHAPPY ENDING:  Cuomo EMMY rescinded...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824171514-giy9k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-CUOMO/EMMY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-International TV academy rescinds Cuomo's Emmy for COVID briefings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINBASE slammed after hackers drain accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/24/coinbase-slammed-for-terrible-customer-service-after-hackers-drain-user-accounts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers of the nation's largest cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase, say their accounts were taken over by criminals and the company's customer service is poor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Most Diverse Counties in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/slideshows/the-15-most-diverse-counties-in-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communities across the country are melting pots of racial and ethnic diversity, according to new Census Bureau data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONES LEGEND CHARLIE WATTS DEAD AT 80...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/15956054/rolling-stones-drummer-charlie-watts-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROLLING Stones drummer Charlie Watts has died aged 80. The music legend passed away just weeks after pulling out of the band’s US tour following an emergency heart operation. His publicist sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Grid Forecasts Record Power Demand... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-grid-forecasts-record-power-143030205.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Electricity demand in Texas is expected to climb to an all-time high as searing heat continues to grip the region. The National Weather Service issued a hazardous weather outlook for North and Central Texas on Tuesday because of hot and humid conditions that can make it feel like 107 degrees Fahrenheit (42 Celsius). Power consumption on the state’s main grid may surge to a record 75,094 megawatts in the hour ending at 6 p.m. local time, according to the Electric Reliability Counci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARNIVAL passenger who tested positive on cruise dies ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/carnival-passenger-who-tested-positive-for-coronavirus-on-cruise-dies/ar-AANGPQG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cruise line said it was unlikely the woman caught the virus on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says no end  before spring 2022 -- at earliest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-fauci-spring-2022-20210824-qzhyfahxmjgm7gh43omisyfrqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world-renowned infectious disease expert predicted the coming months will remain very difficult, with high caseloads and deaths especially in places with low vaccination rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk warns 'old world dying in blaze'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-sends-spacex-fans-24823480</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk confused and baffled his fans when he wrote out a message that fans speculated meant the end of the world. He appeared to allude to a 'war' looming on the Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican congressional candidate suing Candace Owens for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/politics/bs-md-pol-klacik-owens-lawsuit-20210823-wjt2fepudjcrfbu6wnjaktmpo4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Klacik, a former Maryland congressional candidate, is suing conservative commentator Candace Owens for $20 million in damages over an Instagram video Owens made in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Nightmare: If Something Happens to Feinstein...</title>
      <link>https://ckarchive.com/b/75u7h8hrzvd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ckarchive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;​View in Browser​ ​ ​ Welcome back to The Powers That Be, a private email about politics, media, and technology. I’m Peter Hamby, the host of Snap’s Good Luck America and a foun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN APPROVAL CRASHES TO 41%</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/08/24/afghanistan-woes-sink-bidens-approval-41-usa-today-suffolk-poll/8244854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For President Biden, the cost of the war's chaotic end has been steep. His overall job-approval rating is 41% approve versus 55% who disapprove.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROAD TO AIRPORT NOW BLOCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-taliban-have-blocked-the-road-leading-to-kabul-airport-for-non-foreigners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban have blocked the road leading to Kabul Airport, the terrorist group’s spokesman, Zabiullah Mujahid, has stated. The spokesperson added that from now on, only foreign nationals will be allowed to travel to the airport – the only way out of the country not involving crossing Taliban checkpoints. Mujahid called on Afghanis, who had flocked…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'zero-click' attack evades iPhone security protections...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2021/08/24/nso-pegasus-bahrain-iphone-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attacks circumvents Apple's new security feature, BlastDoor, built into all versions of iOS 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates run wild on Rikers amid staffing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/inmates-run-wild-on-rikers-island-amid-staffing-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates are running wild on Rikers Island amid a staffing crunch that’s left charges free to stab each other, answer phones and destroy equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire TX town closes with half affected by virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/24/texas-town-iraan-essentially-closes-covid/8253550002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraan, a small oilfield town in west Texas, has seen nearly half of the town's 1,200 people affected by COVID-19, and the school has shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems sped up recall to avoid crises. They're happening anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-sped-up-gavin-newsoms-recall-to-avoid-california-crises-theyre-happening-anyway/ar-AANFV20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once the recall effort against Gov. Gavin Newsom qualified for the ballot, Democrats who control statewide offices had a choice. They could delay the vote or speed it along. They chose to set an early recall election date, and changed state law in order to do so in late June, reasoning that things were looking up as the state re-opened and COVID-19 rates declined. Setting the date on Sept. 14 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO EVACUATION EXTENSION</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-taliban-demands-finishes-evacuations-24827965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban has said there will be no extension to the August 31 deadline for getting Americans out of Afghanistan, raising the possibility that thousands could be stuck in the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristol endorses McAuliffe in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569132-bill-kristol-endorses-mcauliffe-in-virginia-governors-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime conservative commentator and vocal critic of former President Trump Bill Kristol on Tuesday endorsed Democratic nominee Terry McAuliffe in the Virginia governor's race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican congressional candidate suing Candace Owens for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569130-former-gop-congressional-candidate-kimberly-klacik-suing-candace-owens-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Maryland GOP congressional candidate Kimberly Klacik has filed a defamation suit against conservative commentator Candace Owens, seeking $20 million in damages after she said the pundit publicly made false allegations about her that cost he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital has plate-smashing booth for stressed staff...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/delta-variant/1004073/oregon-hospital-has-plate-smashing-booth-for-doctors-and-nurses-stressed-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala flight delayed after potential health issue in Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/569133-harris-flight-delayed-after-potential-health-issue-in-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris's departure from Singapore on Tuesday was delayed for several hours after a report of an unexpected health issue in Hanoi, Vietnam, where she was scheduled to travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO EXTENSIONS FOR EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-taliban-a0f7cfd98704e6c2fca340324699a129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of the CIA met with the Taliban’s top political leader in Kabul, an official said Tuesday, as more reports emerged of abuses in areas held by the fighters, fueling concerns about Afghanistan's future and the fate of those racing to leave the country before the looming U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Ricans Live Longer Than Americans. What's Secret?</title>
      <link>http://brevnews.com/costa-ricans-live-longer-than-us-whats-the-secret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;brevnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Vaxxed Israel Crisis Is Dire Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ultra-vaccinated-israels-debacle-is-a-dire-warning-to-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t want to frighten you,” Israel’s COVID czar Dr. Salman Zarka told parliament this week. “But… unfortunately, the numbers don’t lie.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX  Exposes Dark Side of Bob Ross Painting Empire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-exposes-dark-side-bob-073857675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NetflixBob Ross: Happy Accidents, Betrayal &amp; Greed sounds like the title of a true-crime parody, promising a dark and gritty take on the life of one of America’s cheeriest—and most beloved—artistic figures. Nonetheless, there’s nothing jokey about Joshua Rofé’s Netflix documentary (Aug. 25), which serves as both a loving portrait of the landscape painter who inspired millions to pick up a brush, and a disheartening exposé of the various ways in which his work, and legacy, were exploited by the s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did Larry Elder Become Front-Runner in CA Gov Race?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/24/how-did-larry-elder-become-a-front-runner-in-californias-governor-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — For a generation, Larry Elder has been an AM radio fixture for millions of Californians, the voice they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All female' NFT exposed as founded -- by 3 men...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/nft-fame-lady-squad-all-female-women-created-fls-men-2021-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fame Lady Squad released the "first female avatar project of all time" this week, but it turned out it was all designed and founded by men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More destructive than first estimated...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824120238-hk0m2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-STORM/TENNESSEE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Tennessee flooding was more destructive than first estimated</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
