<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>School district cancels Dr. Seuss for 'racial undertones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/26/loudoun-county-schools-cancel-dr-seuss-racial-unde/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another day, another cancellation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER to test Covid vaccine on 5 year-olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2417145/pfizer-test-covid-vaccine-children-five-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFIZER is to start testing its Covid vaccine on children as young as five. The pharmaceutical company’s boss said it has already finished enrolling volunteers aged 12 to 15 and is now looking…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global defense spending hits new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/global-defense-spending-led-by-us-and-china-hits-new-high-1.663520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and China led the growth in global defense spending, which hit a new high in 2020 despite the economic stress brought on by the coronavirus pandemic, a report said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist behind golden Trump statue at CPAC says he made it in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/artist-says-gold-trump-statue-was-assembled-in-mexico-hits-back-at-golden-calf-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artist who created the already infamous Trump "golden calf" statue says it is not an "idol" but does concede it was made in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I WAS TRYING TO BE MENTOR'</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/27/cuomo-second-aide-sexual-harassment-accusations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times reported Saturday that former aide Charlotte Bennett, 25, says Cuomo harassed her last year while she was working as an executive assistant in his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBANY ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-andrew-cuomo-7fda294d42e92a2762fc7e7b9ee0cd57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A second former aide has come forward with sexual harassment allegations against New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, who responded with a statement Saturday saying he never made advances...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER CUOMO ACCUSER</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2420837/new-york-andrew-cuomo-accused-sex-harassment-second-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOVERNOR Andrew Cuomo has been accused of sexual harassment by another former employee less than a week after he was accused by sexual harassment by a former aide. Charlotte Bennett claimed the New…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga's dogs recovered safely...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/lady-gaga-s-dogs-returned-unharmed-n1259034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two French bulldogs were taken in a violent robbery, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOYCOTT RISK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-diversity-ava-duvernay-sterling-k-brown-judd-apatow-hfpa-no-black-members-timesupglobes-1234702414/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 10:11 PM: Battered again today by some of the biggest names in Hollywood for its stupefying lack of Black members, the Hollywood Foreign Press Association tonight responded by repeating a p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, travel, peace of mind. How life changing for fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/sex-travel-peace-of-mind-how-life-is-changing-for-some-of-the-fully-vaccinated/article_51a1566d-ba27-5a02-9724-14c9155908a5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dating during the pandemic is becoming less complicated and risky for attorney Shelley O'Connor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images reveal extent of damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/27/middleeast/us-syria-iran-airstrikes-analysis-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A resident of al-Bukamal, a city near the Syrian-Iraqi border, told CNN the explosions from US airstrikes targeting a compound the Pentagon said was used by Iranian-backed militia groups were unlike anything he had heard before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Rock' v. The Don: A serious comparison...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/540290-dwayne-the-rock-johnson-v-donald-trump-a-serious-comparison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson has that 'it' factor that Trump had in 2016, and his growing platform makes Trump’s look unsophisticated and outdated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Dog Used by Police Stirs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/digidog-a-robotic-dog-used-by-the-police-stirs-privacy-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were being held hostage in a Bronx apartment. They had been threatened at gunpoint, tied up and tortured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes may show early warnings for Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.iol.co.za/news/world/the-eyes-could-show-early-warnings-for-alzheimers-researchers-say-c0271978-4424-595c-992e-a79adf9bd84a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iol.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say a picture of your eye could assess your future risk of neurodegenerative disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Russia's mass arrests: Claims of beatings, threats and 'war' against rights monitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Inside-Russia-s-mass-arrests-Claims-of-beatings-15984774.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Authorities call it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiers defy death in descent of Yosemite's Half Dome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-eb713b3d3b2de28dd9a82b5ab72798b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK, Calif. (AP) — Two skiers navigated a thin layer of snow with no margin for error down the precipitous shoulder of Half Dome in Yosemite National Park and alternately skied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon wolf makes history on lengthy journey to California...</title>
      <link>https://defenders.org/newsroom/oregon-wolf-or-93-makes-history-traveling-californias-central-sierra-nevada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;defenders.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, a gray wolf from western Oregon dubbed OR-93 became the first collared wolf to explore the central Sierra region of California. According to the California Department of Fish and Wildlife (CDFW), OR-93, a former member of the White River Pack near Mt. Hood, has traveled farther south into the state than any known wild wolf in a century, a historic journey that highlights the importance of habitat connectivity and the dispersal ability of this iconic species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will AI get along with us?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/540821-will-artificial-intel-get-along-with-us-only-if-we-design-it-that-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People would be much more guarded with social media if they realized those platforms are actively profiling them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo wife to rat out cartel?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/27/el-chapos-wife-emma-coronel-aispuro-poised-to-snitch-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emma Coronel Aispuro went back to being a brunette for her mug shot last week. The glamorous beauty-queen wife of Mexico’s most notorious drug trafficker had last appeared in public as a blonde, he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing tension in Minneapolis as trial looms in Floyd death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-health-trials-coronavirus-pandemic-minneapolis-075d9b5f4a2a1f80d26cb33b77ca59b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Barbed wire and concrete barriers surround the courthouse where the former Minneapolis police officer charged with killing George Floyd will soon go on trial, a sign of the deep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plunging demand for tests may leave USA exposed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-b1c1f6fc83977830231c065625510e4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Just five weeks ago, Los Angeles County was conducting more than 350,000 weekly coronavirus tests, including at a massive drive-thru site at Dodger Stadium, as health workers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover ancient ceremonial carriage near Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-pompeii-idUKKBN2AR0E1?taid=603a67e6186e2a0001d275a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists have unearthed a unique ancient-Roman ceremonial carriage from a villa just outside Pompeii, the city buried in a volcanic eruption in 79 AD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>800-year-old prophecy predicts war?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/800-year-old-prophecy-predicts-23576016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ancient texts says the United States will be drawn into a conflict involving Iran and Saudi Arabia, with the fighting bringing "great strife and darkness into the world"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A road like no other, in peril like never before...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-road-like-no-other-in-peril-like-never-before-15984513.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GORDA, Calif. - Life here in this tiny town built on the continent-ending cliffs of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Beats Virus -- 150 Days After Being Admitted Hospital!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/02/26/isabel-pupo-coronavirus-south-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isabel Pupo was all smiles, just days after opening her eyes from a medically induced coma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue dog that nobody wanted saves life of new owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/steve-hartman-on-the-road-rescue-dog-2021-02-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Myers gave Sadie a chance. She saved his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINBASE Mafia Shows How Tight Circle Holds Sway Over Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinbase-mafia-shows-how-tight-a-circle-holds-sway-over-bitcoin/ar-BB1e4lQe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Coinbase Global Inc.’s filing to become a publicly-traded company provides a glimpse into the remarkably small circle of mostly men who command the incredibly lucrative digital landscape. This U.S.-based power list starts with Brian Armstrong, the now billionaire chief executive officer of Coinbase, and his co-founder, Fred Ehrsam, who went on to create Paradigm Operations. Fellow billionaire Fred Wilson of Union Square Ventures,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Why Bill Gates is now biggest farmland owner...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/27/why-bill-gates-is-now-the-us-biggest-farmland-owner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real reason billionaire Gates just became the biggest owner of farmland in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger -- The Man Who Refused to Bow...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/02/man-who-refused-bow/618156/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Kinzinger says he’ll fight to take his party back from Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sasse marches to own tune as GOP implodes around him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/27/ben-sasse-gop-471764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there's a model for how to successfully build a conservative GOP out of Trump's shadow, it might as well be the Nebraska Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper's Arrest Awakens Rage in Spanish Youth Chafing in Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/rappers-arrest-awakens-rage-in-spanish-youth-chafing-in-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA — It had all the markings of a free speech showdown: Pablo Hasél, a controversial Spanish rapper, had barricaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Baron and Bezos Remade WASH POST...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/how-marty-baron-and-jeff-bezos-remade-the-washington-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On July 30, 2013, Martin Baron left The Washington Post building and crossed 15th Street for an extremely rare happy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakout 'BORAT' star Maria Bakalova conquers Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maria-bakalova-sacha-baron-cohen-shootings-golden-globe-awards-bulgaria-f74d35197d8f38752698b4725d2063cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So what did YOU do at 5 a.m. after staying up all night for your prom? Maria Bakalova became a movie star. The 24-year-old actress has been telling the story of how she had a few free hours...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
