<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau strains to contain political scandal engulfing his family...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/24/trudeau-political-scandal-family-381002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving forward, Trudeau and Morneau may have to deal with more problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Michael Cohen released from federal prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/24/micheal-cohen-released-from-federal-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen was walked out of Otisville prison in Central New York shortly sometime after noon, his lawyer told the Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents dispatched to Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://ktiv.com/2020/07/24/us-agents-dispatched-to-seattle-to-protect-federal-buildings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktiv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory masks becoming rule amid Europe's virus uptick...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/mandatory-masks-becoming-rule-amid-122636738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New rules on wearing masks in England came into effect Friday, with people entering shops, banks and supermarkets now required to wear face coverings, while Romania reported a record for daily infections and France announced mandatory testing for arrivals from 16 countries, including the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS' star drops extremely loud F-bombs in fan-less stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/giants/article/Dodgers-Joc-Pederson-curse-F-bomb-empty-stadium-TV-15430777.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to professional sports leagues resuming without fans and crowd noise amid the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Trump could lose reelection in 100 days -- and USA is on edge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-could-lose-reelection-100-days-us-edge-014927857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cratering in the polls, canceling his showcase convention event, and struggling to land punches on his opponent, Donald Trump has only 100 days from Sunday to save his presidency -- and it's not going well. In the latest blow to momentum ahead of November 3, the president announced late Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica reopens -- but NOT TO AMERICANS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723231639-ub8sl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/COSTA RICA:Costa Rica to reopen two airports to tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia evicts Confederate monuments from state Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/899c05e1b9b8550bd7e1db30932dbe30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Virginia has removed from its iconic state capitol the busts and a statue honoring Confederate generals and officials. That includes a bronze statue of Gen. Robert E. Lee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK REPORT:  Dems favored to take back Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/cook-political-report-democrats-favored-to-take-back-senate-with-just-over-100-days-until-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the current political climate and just over 100 days until Election Day, Republicans are at risk of losing their Senate majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicated Chewing Gum Future Of Prescription Drugs?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/medicated-chewing-gum-future-prescription-drugs-robotic-mouth-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Bristol say medicated chewing gum is a very effective way of getting drugs into a patient's body. The problem is there's no proven method of testing how well gum releases medicine into the mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE WARNS:  'Do Not Underestimate Evil Genius Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/07/24/michael_moore_do_not_underestimate_the_evil_genius_that_is_donald_j_trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Moore warned Democrats not to get too excited and underestimate a Trump victory in 2020 in an interview on Joy Reid's new MSNBC program. Moore also encouraged Joe Biden to act as if he is currently the president and start holding a "Morning Meeting" and have fireside-type chats with Americans from his basement. if I were advising him, I would tell him just to start running the country right now, just act as if you are the president. That means nobody can assume the election is over. "I want to caution everyone, do not underestimate the evil genius that is Donald J. Trump," Moore warned. "There are many examples throughout history, whether it's Henry V facing the French on Saint Crispin's Day, they outnumbered him 4 to 1 and he was supposed to lose and he didn't. And or jump ahead to the 1995 NBA playoffs [ed. 1994], the Knicks are ahead with 15 seconds left, way ahead of the Indiana Pacers, and Reggie Miller scores eight points in nine seconds. With 15 seconds left." Reid and Moore also discussed their appearance on a 2016 episode of 'Real Time' with HBO host Bill Maher where the filmmaker predicted a Trump victory. "We've been fooled by polls before. Listen, Trump has got a number of tricks up his sleeve to suppress the vote, to try to postpone the election, blaming the coronavirus, to any of the number of things where he will try to weasel his way out of this," Moore said of the election. "And our side, and Joe Biden -- Joe Biden, I think, you know, honestly, if I were advising him, I would tell him just to start running the country right now, just act as if you are the president. That means nobody can assume the election is over." "Everybody's got to show up the vote and bring ten people with them, but right now every morning we could have a morning meeting with Joe Biden from the basement. The basement is fine. We want him safe, he's doing the smart thing and have the morning meeting with America. Tell us what we're going to do today to save this country. At night sit by the fireside and do what he does best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/refresh/AL082020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/150135_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems want to prevent swing voters from defecting back...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article244286797.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CANCELS REPUBLICAN CONVENTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/newslocalpolitics/trump-abruptly-cancels-republican-convention-in-jacksonville-its-not-the-right-time/ar-BB177hFy?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci gets security detail after threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article244460877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA Thought Police caution editors about using FOX as source...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/24/media/wikipedia-fox-news-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wikipedia community recently engaged in a spirited debate over whether Fox News is a reliable enough source to use as a citation in entries on the encyclopedia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF  TEXAS COAST... </title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-hanna-forms-and-heads-for-texas-coast/781953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Hurricane Douglas Weakening, But is Likely to Strike Hawaii Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-07-24-hurricane-douglas-hawaii-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on Douglas's journey to Hawaii this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSE CALL:  Mel Gibson was hospitalized for week with covid...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/mel-gibson-hospitalized-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gibson, 64, fell ill with the potentially deadly virus back in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big lead in polls shifts search...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-lead-polls-biden-shifts-110054292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many on Biden's team once felt he needed a running mate who'd generate excitement. Now, with his polling lead, a "do no harm" strategy gains ground. But pressure for a Black candidate mounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Deaths Set Record For 2nd Day In Row...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/24/coronavirus-at-a-glance-florida-breaks-record-for-single-day-increase-in-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest numbers and information you need to know at-a-glance as of 11 a.m. on July 24, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden VP selection down to Karen Bass or Tammy Duckworth?</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/congress/source-coelho-pushing-biden-to-pick-bass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order Requires Quarantine Upon Entering Massachusetts...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/24/coronavirus-massachusetts-governor-charlie-baker-update-friday-july-24-travel-order-fine-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new travel order says visitors and in-state residents returning home must fill out a "Massassachusetts Travel Form" and quarantine for 14 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Germans received neo-Nazi death threats. Now police under suspicion...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Prominent-Germans-received-neo-Nazi-death-15431323.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - When German comedian Idil Baydar heard last week that investigators suspect a police officer may have been involved in sending her neo-Nazi death threats, she was aghast.  She was especially distressed to learn that the suspected police link had been known for at least nine months and she had not been told. Instead, she had been informed that the investigation into the hate-filled text messages she received throughout 2019 was closed.  "I don't know who to trust or believe anymore," said the 45-year-old actress. "I am completely in shock."  Baydar is one of more than two dozen German public figures threatened over the past two years in a case that has cast a shadow over police since the outset. In 2018, it emerged that a police computer was used to access information on lawyer Seda Başay-Yıldız shortly before she received threats containing personal details.  Now, revelations that police computers in Frankfurt and Wiesbaden were also used pull data on Baydar and left-wing politician Janine Wissler have triggered uncomfortable questions for Germany about racism and far-right networks in its institutions.  It comes amid a flurry of public debate on issues such as racial profiling and systemic racism as the global Black Lives Matter movement increases scrutiny. Earlier this month reports of extremism within Germany's special forces led the defense minister to disband one combat unit and announce a restructuring.  While suspicions of a police role have not been confirmed, the scandal forced the police chief in the state of Hesse to resign this month. Meanwhile, each day brings reports of new threats, with a slew of left-wing and minority politicians, journalists and lawyers receiving new emails in recent days.  Pressure has mounted against regional Interior Minister Peter Beuth, who answered questions from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist claims possessed woman threw 4 men across room...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/exorcist-claims-possessed-woman-threw-22400635</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exorcist Bishop Plato Angelakis has claimed he witnessed a victim of demonic possession gain superhuman strength and throw four men across a room after speaking in a demonic language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumatran tiger cub born in Polish zoo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sumatran-tiger-cub-born-polish-zoo-135714320.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sumatran tiger -- a critically endangered species -- was born in a zoo in Poland, officials said on Friday. The female cub was born during the coronavirus lockdown on May 20 at the Wroclaw Zoo in the southwestern city by the same name, but news of her arrival was only made public now. &amp;quot;We were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOS:  Federal Officers Battle With Rioters in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/24/exclusive-videos-unlawful-assembly-portland-fires-federal-officers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An &amp;quot;unlawful assembly&amp;quot; was declared after a large, peaceful protest turned into another night of battling in front of the Federal Courthouse in Portland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Tops $1,900...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/commodities/spot-gold-tops-1900-first-time-2011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Reasons Election Day Could Be Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/24/2020-election-disaster-perfect-storm-372778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may think you know how bad Nov. 3 will be. But all signs point to something far, far worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbus statue in Chicago taken down under cover of darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8556221/Statue-Christopher-Columbus-removed-Chicagos-Grant-Park.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after news spread that Chicago mayor Lori Lightfoot had sanctioned the statue's removal, crews used a large crane to remove the monument from its pedestal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet freedom group alleges harassment by Trump administration...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/U-S-Internet-freedom-group-alleges-harassment-by-15431135.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Leaders of the Open Technology Fund accused the Trump administration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional poker player found dead with badly burnt body...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/sport/other-sports/professional-poker-player-susie-zhao-22408354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI has joined the investigation involving professional poker player Susie Zhao after her badly burned body was found in a Michigan parking lot earlier this month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death in Florida every 8 mins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-death-every-8-044632133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 has taken a heavy toll on Florida residents older than 65, who account for just 13% of the state&amp;#39;s coronavirus cases but 82% of the fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor forced to retire after 'slave' tweet found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/education/article244449237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ranked among worst countries to raise family?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/23/america-ranked-among-worst-countries-to-raise-a-family-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We get an “F” for family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Losing Luster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dollar-losing-luster-investors-line-052258429.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- After rocketing higher in March as the ultimate haven currency, the dollar is now headed for its worst month since the beginning of 2018, and many strategists see the sell-off continuing.Negative real rates in the U.S., the relentless spread of the coronavirus in America and a pickup in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Star of This $70 Million Sci-Fi Film Is Robot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/24/the-star-of-this-70-million-sci-fi-film-is-a-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strangest part of Matthew Helderman’s video call came when he bit into an apple. Or rather, what followed. “What</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Harvesting DNA From Millions. Is This Future of Policing?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/24/china-is-harvesting-dna-from-millions-of-people-is-this-the-future-of-policing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For several years now, the police and other authorities in China have been collecting across the country DNA samples from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Hurricane Douglas hurtling toward Hawaii with 130 mph max sustained winds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/240847.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks federal agents from arresting observers in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/847341576e44e4d9e717128db08faad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A federal judge specifically blocked U.S. agents from arresting or using physical force against journalists and legal observers at protests in Oregon's largest city where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA ORDERS USA TO CLOSE CONSULATE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5979db970a71ec5a0fdd3ba6ac92e03d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China ordered the United States on Friday to close its consulate in the western city of Chengdu, ratcheting up a diplomatic conflict at a time when relations have sunk to their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients will be 'sent home to die' if deemed too sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article244443257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx warns 11 major cities including Indianapolis, Pittsburgh and Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8554281/Dr-Birx-warns-11-major-cities-aggressive-steps-mitigate-COVID-outbreaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11 cities Dr Birx mentioned include: Baltimore, Cleveland, Columbus, Indianapolis, Las Vegas, Miami, Minneapolis, Nashville, New Orleans, Pittsburgh and St Louis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayors urge residents to wear masks --  at home!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/508836-two-florida-mayors-urge-residents-to-wear-masks-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Florida mayors who govern Miami and Miami-Dade County encouraged their residents on Thursday to wear masks inside to lower the transmission rate of COVID-19 between family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan and Harry file lawsuit over drone photos taken at LA pad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/harry-meghan-sue-unnamed-paparazzi-224159426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After settling in Los Angeles, the couple and their young child allege they have been harassed daily by eager photographers invading their privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Can Jump 26 Feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/virus-can-jump-26-feet-at-cold-meat-plants-filled-with-stale-air/ar-BB176xK5?ocid=uxcntrlbingtab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mel Gibson was hospitalized in April with covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1190803/mel-gibson-hospitalized-one-week-diagnosed-covid-19-april/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEL Gibson was hospitalized for one week back in April after he was diagnosed with COVID-19. The controversial actor was admitted in the United States after he tested positive for the illness. Mel&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci flattens his curve as baseball finally returns...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/23/dr-fauci-flattens-curve-straight-into-ground-on-opening-day-first-pitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His curve was a little too flat. White House coronavirus task force member and diehard baseball fan Dr. Anthony Fauci threw the first pitch at the long-awaited 2020 MLB season opener — as the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech CEO hearing on Hill 'likely' to be postponed...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/big-tech-ceo-hearing-is-likely-to-be-postponed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hearing, which was set to be held by the House Judiciary antitrust subcommittee, could be postponed to allow lawmakers to attend Rep. John Lewis' funeral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan and Harry file lawsuit over drone photos taken at LA pad...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-meghan-markle-prince-harry-22407680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filed at the LA County Superior Court, the complaint alleges unnamed photographers took drone shots of 14-month-old Archie at Meghan and Harry's Beverly Hills home during lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA ACTIVATES HEALTH CODES ON SMARTPHONES...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Summer-in-Beijing-Hot-and-oppressive-but-almost-15428177.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - All the signs of Beijing's infernal summer are in evidence. Men playing cards on the sidewalks are sporting their "Beijing bikinis," their shirts hoisted up over their beer bellies for better air flow, while young trendy types carry personal fans as they walk down the street.  People are cooking meat at outdoor restaurants or on little grills on the sidewalk. It's so hot that Beijingers - usually insistent on body-temperature beverages - are even drinking their beer cold.  It could almost be any other steamy July in any other year.  But even here, where life is almost back to normal after months of strict controls, the coronavirus remains a lingering menace, lurking behind the quotidian veneer.  Restaurants and malls are open, but to enter, customers have to activate a health code on their smartphones. The code tracks their movements and determines whether they have been to any risky places. Only those with green codes are allowed in. Many offices insist on green codes, too. A red code, or even an amber one, is the scarlet letter of 2020.  You can have concerns about privacy, or you can have a functioning life. You can't have both.  Security guards with temperature guns man the gates at supermarkets and residential compounds, pointing them at the wrists of every person who wants to enter. This is largely a formality, as the reading often does not reflect reality. This reporter has recorded temperatures in the low 80s on several occasions, yet was alive enough to walk through the gate.  Gyms are open, but only if they are above ground. Movie theaters on Monday turned the lights back on, but at 30 percent capacity and with no eating or drinking allowed. Beijing's main tourist attractions, such as the Forbidden City, require advance reservations, and masks are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANKEES AND NATIONALS ALL KNEEL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/23/yankees-nationals-take-a-knee-before-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every single member of the Washington Nationals and New York Yankees took a knee prior to the national anthem Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA TESTS ANTI-SATELLITE WEAPON IN SPACE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12206486/russia-has-secretly-tested-anti-satellite-weapon-in-space-us-space-command-says/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museums launch battle of the bums as curators pick artworks with best rear...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1189923/museums-bums-statues-artworks-peachiest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSEUMS have hit rock bottom — by trying to find the statues and artworks with the best bums. The challenge has gone worldwide after cheeky staff at the Yorkshire Museum were first to have a crack …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates warns MULTIPLE vaccine doses needed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1184945/bill-gates-vaccines-schools-closed-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILL Gates has warned that multiple doses of any coronavirus vaccine could be necessary as he slammed Donald Trump’s handling of the pandemic. Microsoft billionaire Gates said “serious …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE KARDASHIANS:  He will spill family secrets if they 'lock him up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1189095/kanye-west-kim-kardashian-family-secrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West is threatening to spill the Kardashian family secrets live on Twitter if wife Kim stages an intervention. Insiders say the rapper, who suffers from bipolar disorder told Kim he’ll “live …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE TEXAS COAST... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232046.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP08/refresh/EP082020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/204329_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FILMING RESUMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1173313/kim-kardashian-returns-to-filming-kuwtk-with-khloe-kardashian-and-tristan-thompson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a source, Kim Kardashian was professional in front of the cameras while filming Keeping Up With the Kardashians Wednesday, but "clearly had a lot on her mind."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Internal turmoil at FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/facebook-employee-leaks-show-they-feel-betrayed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the US heads toward a crucial and contentious presidential election, the world's largest social network is facing an unprecedented cultural crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  NO END IN SIGHT, PERFECT STORM...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-persisting-control-vaccine-c2fd6e17-8b26-46cf-9177-69d27c9a86ea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fauci says he's "never seen" such a wide spectrum of symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEAK LEVEL OF HOSPITALIZATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1286428078365765638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Live sports becoming video games...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/927132/pandemic-accelerating-video-gamification-sports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do you 'take me out with the crowd' when there's a global pandemic? By filling the stadium with people who can't get sick. Fox Sports announced Thursday that its broadcasts of Major League Baseball games this season will utilize 'cutting-edge' technology to populate the stands with 'virtual fans.' The Sims-like creations will wear their teams colors and thin out if the game is a blowout. They'll cheer, boo, and â€” abominably â€” even do the wave. If Fox's intention was to make empty stadiums less eerie, they've definitely failed. But its choice represents an even bigger shift in professional sports: the creep toward becoming more and more like video games. No fans? Not on FOX Sports. Thousands of virtual fans will attend FOXâ€™s MLB games this Saturday. pic.twitter.com/z9oQU0rYuC â€” FOX Sports (@FOXSports) July 23, 2020 Sports and video games have been in conversation with each other for decades; 1958's Tennis for Two, played on an oscilloscope, is considered one of the first video games ever. But while electronic games used to be more influenced by live sports, that relationship has shifted thanks to advances in television graphics, made possible in part by 'a new wave of high-resolution cameras and smart algorithms,' Fast Company reports. Since ESPN debuted in-game box scores in the mid-'90s, networks have tried to cram screens with as many angles and statistics as possible â€” much like the stat bars and camera toggles available in a video game. The push for electronic strike zones also pursues the mechanical perfection of a video game: a pitch either is or isn't a strike in the eyes of a computer, leaving no room for subjectivity or the delightful randomness of human error. The use of digital avatars in the place of human fans seems to take this to a Philip K. Dick extreme: Why involve real people at all, who might run onto the field, look bored on camera, or interfere with the game, when you can replace them with a sea of faces right out of MLB: The Show? Of course, there's an extreme beyond even digital fans: That the players themselves could eventually be replaced by algorithms, where stats are crunched in simulations, so no games need to be played at all (it would certainly save teams some money). That might sound laughably impossible â€” but hey, so would have a 60-game MLB season played in empty stadiums just six months ago. Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Orders Michael Cohen Released, Citing 'Retaliation' Over Upcoming Tell-All Book...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723150106-gksoi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/COHEN (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-U.S. judge finds Cohen target of retaliation, releases from prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial markets need to 'start thinking about blue wave'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/financial-markets-to-need-to-start-thinking-about-a-blue-wave-greg-valliere-113851176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How will financial markets receive a political blue wave in November? According to one strategist it’s time to start thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAY BALL! Masked men, empty parks, odd sounds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/62d86588e4926d68875a8cf0ce985746</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herb Vincent closes his eyes and drifts back a half-century, to his boyhood bedroom in North Little Rock, Arkansas. He’s 9, trying to stay awake deep into the night, the transistor radio tuned to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Naked women catch Key West hotel video voyeur in act...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/key-west-voyeur-652938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 23--A businessman arrested for surreptitiously filming two naked women in an adjoining Florida hotel room told police that he frequently engaged in such video voyeurism as he traveled across the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite U.S. demand, China refuses to commit to closing Houston consulate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/23/china-refuses-commit-close-houston-consulate-380220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top Communist Party official at the consulate said his office is operating normally today and will continue to do so "until further notice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaking into nursing homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article244401817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother says she got pregnant at 19 without EVER having sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-8553463/Woman-says-got-pregnant-19-year-old-virgin-without-having-sex.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samantha Lynn Isabel, 26, believes her first child was conceived when she and her boyfriend, Alex, were touching each other's genitals during foreplay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY delays 'MULAN' indefinitely; STAR WARS, AVATAR pushed back year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/23/disney-delays-mulan-indefinitely-star-wars-and-avatar-movies-pushed-back-a-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney is making some major changes to its release calendar that include displacing "Mulan" from its Aug. 21 release and pushing back the debuts of future Star Wars and Avatar by a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area worries about 'next 10 years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Japanese-Tea-Garden-opens-San-Francisco-15428654.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonoma County is considering fining people and businesses who violate the health order by not wearing masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine assigned to President's helicopter squadron infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/23/marine-one-helicopter-covid-positive-380444</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Marine assigned to the military helicopter squadron responsible for transporting the president has tested positive for Covid-19, a Marine Corps spokesperson told POLITICO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BIDEN +13 IN FL...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/23/poll-biden-lead-trump-florida-380369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shift comes as the state has suffered a surge in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States probe APPLE for potential consumer protection violation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/23/states-probe-apple-for-potential-consumer-protection-violation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is part of a multistate probe into Apple over a potential violations of a consumer protection law, according to a newly public document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle businesses looted, defaced with 'gentrifier' graffiti...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/23/seattle-businesses-looted-defaced-with-gentrifier-graffiti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters in Seattle busted out windows of a pot shop and scrawled “gentrifier” on it outside, according to a report. A group of 150 people gathered late Wednesday at Cal Anderson Park before busting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex life secrets WILL be made public...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12206248/ghislaine-maxwell-sex-life-secrets-released-pimp-plea-redacted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SECRETS of Ghislaine Maxwell’s sex life will be revealed ahead of her trial on sex trafficking charges, a New York judge has ruled. Lawyers for Maxwell had sought to keep documents from a 201…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMS RACE FEAR</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-tells-putin-hopes-to-avoid-us-russia-china-arms-race/ar-BB176TVw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Tyson returning to boxing for 8-round exhibition...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/former-heavyweight-champ-mike-tyson-to-return-to-boxing-to-face-roy-jones-in-an-8-round-exhibition-160530330.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The training videos that former undisputed heavyweight champion Mike Tyson has been releasing on social media weren’t just for show, it turns out. Yahoo Sports has learned from multiple sources that Tyson plans to return to boxing to face Roy Jones Jr. on Sept. 12 at Dignity Health Sports Park in Carson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BIDEN +13 IN FL...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/florida/release-detail?ReleaseID=3668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;79% In Florida Say Require Face Masks In Public, Coronavirus Handling Weighs On DeSantis, Trump Numbers, Quinnipiac University Florida Poll Finds; Biden Opens Up A Double-Digit Lead In 2020 Race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good vibrations? COVID quiet time soothes Earth's seismic shakes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723171317-0a82r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIBRATIONS (PIX):Good vibrations? COVID quiet time soothes Earth's seismic shakes</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
