<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Record-setting $11K blunt sold at Vegas pot dispensary...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegassun.com/news/2018/dec/29/paiutes-sell-most-expensive-pot-product-to-date-at/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegassun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A marijuana specialty product sold for a record price of $11,000 Friday night at a mega-dispensary on tribal land near downtown Las Vegas ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas manicurist killed trying to stop customer who didn't pay...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegassun.com/news/2018/dec/29/las-vegas-manicurist-killed-trying-to-stop-custome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegassun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A manicurist was run down, dragged and fatally injured Saturday afternoon by the vehicle of a customer who was trying to leave a central valley nail salon without paying ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi hires new top lawyer...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/the-man-who-could-impeach-trump-nancy-pelosi-hires-new-top-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker-designate Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., has picked a new guiding force for Democrats investigating and potentially impeaching President Trump when they take control of the House next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor exposed to Ebola brought to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/29/ebola-doctor-united-states-1076875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The physician was taken to a secure area at the University of Nebraska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel responds early in Supreme Court fight with foreign firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/28/mueller-probe-supreme-court-mystery-case-1076871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most details of the case remain under seal at the Supreme Court since the company asked for an emergency stay last week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CRIPPLES NEWSPAPERS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/computer-virus-hits-southern-california-newspapers-n953001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s likely that the issues will affect the process of printing and delivering the Sunday newspapers as well," the Los Angeles Times said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defends Rocky Tenure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/kids/other/outgoing-white-house-chief-of-staff-john-f-kelly-defends-his-rocky-tenure/ar-BBRBb1c?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE RETAILERS BAN CASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/retailers-ban-paper-cash-sweetgreen-dig-inn-starbucks-a94172f1-db08-466c-9647-c4b63f9b9b29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers have considered legislation to compel stores to accept paper money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP:  Florida school shooting voted top news story of 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/afs:Content:2712790004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The mass shooting at a Parkland, Florida, high school — which killed 17 students and staff, and sparked nationwide student-led marches for gun control — was the top news story of 2018, according to The Associated Press' annual poll of U.S. editors and news directors.  The No. 2 story was the investigation by special counsel Robert Mueller into whether Donald Trump's election campaign coordinated with Russia. It was one of several major stories — in a year jam-packed with dramatic developments — in which the U.S. president played a role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Franklin Graham says FACEBOOK ban was 'personal attack toward me'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/423233-franklin-graham-facebook-ban-was-personal-attack-toward-me</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelist Franklin Graham on Sunday accused Facebook of personally attacking him after the company banned him from the platform for 24 hours over a post he published in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Memoriam...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2018/12/celebrity-deaths-obituaries-rex-reed-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking back at a catastrophic year, 2019 has got to be better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative writer dies of swine flu at 26...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/28/conservative-writer-bre-payton-found-dead-at-26-in-san-diego/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 26-year-old political writer and TV commentator died suddenly on Friday, a day after being hospitalized with swine flu, her friends and employer said. Bre Payton, a staff writer at conservative n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Yellow vests' target French media...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/30/yellow-vests-target-french-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yellow vest protesters marched on the headquarters of leading French broadcasters Saturday, as small groups turned out in Paris and around France despite waning momentum for their movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Iranians found on U.K. beach as English Channel crossings mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/30/iranian-migrants-found-uk-beach-english-channel-cr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British officials say six Iranian men have been found on a beach in southeastern England as the number of migrants making risky crossings of the English Channel continues to mount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans Actors Want To Play James Bond...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trans-actors-we-would-be-proud-to-play-a-trans-james-bond</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A trans man Bond would establish trans men in entertainment, the way so many trans women, like Laverne Cox, already have [for trans women],” actor Scott Turner Schofield says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Brown: Climate change as serious as World War II...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/jerry-brown-climate-change-challenges-serious-those-faced-world-war-n952446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outgoing California Democratic governor joined "Meet the Press" for an in-depth discussion about climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists To Drop New Year's Eve Ball in Times Square...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5490488/new-years-eve-ball-drop-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global event honors free speech and free press</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Ex-Spy Pressured Manafort Over Debts...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5490169/paul-manafort-victor-boyarkin-debts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TIME investigation reveals a Russian ex-spy was a key link between Paul Manafort and a Putin ally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani rips Mueller: 'Time to put up or shut up'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/423194-giuliani-rips-mueller-its-time-to-put-up-or-shut-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's attorney Rudy Giuliani is seeking to put pressure on special counsel Robert Mueller to submit his report on whether the investigation into the Trump campaign and Russia has found collusion, saying Mueller should "put up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Pushes for Primacy in Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-pushes-for-primacy-in-space-11546171206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is poised to realize an ambitious mission to the far side of the Moon, the most immediate of many planned milestones in its effort to challenge America’s half-century long supremacy in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's March canceled over 'overwhelmingly white' concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/28/organizers-cancel-womens-march-being-too-white/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers of the Women’s March in Humboldt County, California, announced Friday that they have canceled the local Jan. 19 event because the marchers are overwhelmingly white.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defends Rocky Tenure...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-john-kelly-exit-interview-20181230-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John F. Kelly was supposed to be one of the “adults in the room” managing an impetuous President Trump. But as White House chief of staff, Kelly presided over some of the administration’s most controversial immigration and security policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FOREIGN ENTITY'</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cyberattack-by-foreign-entity-halts-deliveries-los-angeles-times-newspapers-1171996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Distribution of the West Coast editions of the Wall Street Journal and New York Times was also impacted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller, FBI examining Trump golf club's employment documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Investigators-examining-Trump-golf-club-s-13497806.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal and state investigators are scrutinizing the employment documents of immigrants without legal status who allegedly worked at President Donald Trump's golf club in New Jersey, according to their attorney. Anibal Romero, a Newark attorney who represents five undocumented immigrants who say they worked at the Trump National Golf Club in Bedminster, said in an interview Saturday that he met with investigators from the New Jersey state attorney general's office and two FBI agents in November, before the workers began to go public with their stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Spacey Seen in Public for First Time in Year...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/kevin-spacey-seen-public-after-sexual-assault-charge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey was spotted in public on Friday, days after being charged with felony sexual assault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CRIPPLES NEWSPAPERS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/78c2948b326f4baab79d61956fbfc831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A computer virus hit newspaper printing plants in Los Angeles and at Tribune Publishing newspapers across the country. Tribune Publishing said a computer virus disrupted production of the Chicago Tribune and its other newspapers, the Chicago Tribune reported. The print edition of the Chicago Tribune was published Saturday without paid death notices and classified ads, while in other markets a similarly slimmed-down version of the Saturday newspaper will be delivered on Sunday, the company said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  NKorea continues missile development...</title>
      <link>http://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0005450685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;the-japan-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea has continued its development of intercontinental ballistic missiles despite declaring a halt to launches, having conducted a missile-linked radio wave experiment early this month, it has been learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin New Year letter to Trump: Moscow open for dialogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-usa-dialogue/putin-in-new-year-letter-to-trump-says-moscow-is-open-for-dialogue-idUSKCN1OT07W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, in a New Year letter to his U.S. counterpart D...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FACEBOOK sorry for banning Franklin Graham...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/living/religion/article223714480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook banned Franklin Graham for 24 hours, the North Carolina evangelist posted. The social media giant described the 2016 post about Bruce Springsteen’s opposition to HB2, the bathroom bill, as hate speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside erotic New Year's Eve 'Illuminati Ball'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/29/inside-this-sexy-eyes-wide-shut-style-new-years-eve-bash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this day and age, risqué can be risky. But Cynthia von Buhler is bringing sexy back to NYC. The illustrator has thrown, by her own estimation, hundreds of over-the-top parties over almost three …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several Injured After Jet Bridge Collapse At BWI Airport...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/12/29/reports-of-jetway-collapse-at-bwi-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jetway has reportedly collapsed at Baltimore-Washington International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Original Woodstock site to host 50th anniversary concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/13cc53be5d4547d09ca5ded3c6b6ca16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHEL, N.Y. (AP) — A three-day music festival will be held in August 2019 at the original Woodstock concert site to mark the 50th anniversary of the historic event. The Bethel Woods Center for the Arts, a concert venue built on the original Woodstock site, announced Thursday that it will host the golden anniversary event Aug. 16-18. The center says performers will include "prominent and emerging artists spanning multiple genres and decades." The venue says talks by "leading futurists and retro-tech experts" will also be featured.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
