<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3473432/haiti-earthquake-huge-magnitude-7-quake-strikes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN EARTHQUAKE with a 5.8 magnitude shook Haiti on Saturday night – less than 24 hours after the country was hit by a massive 7.2 quake that claimed at least 304 lives. The 5.8 magnitude quake was m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTERSHOCKS RATTLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/magnitude-7-quake-strikes-western-haiti-usgs-2021-08-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 304 people died and hundreds were injured after a major earthquake struck southwestern Haiti on Saturday, authorities said, reducing churches, hotels, schools and homes to rubble in the latest tragedy to hit the impoverished Caribbean nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/pictureshow/2021/08/15/1027792264/photos-scenes-from-the-haiti-earthquake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say entire towns were destroyed and more than 300 people have died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROP STORM NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/14/1027707629/haiti-earthquake-strikes-magnitude</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People in the capital of Port-au-Prince felt the tremor and many rushed into the streets in fear. The U.S. Geological Survey predicts the death toll could reach into the thousands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Strangeness of Catholic Church's Latest Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-deep-strangeness-of-the-catholic-church-s-latest-scandal/ar-AANl655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outing of a top administrator of the nation’s conference of Catholic bishops as a regular Grindr user was clearly a story. But what kind?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILDINGS COLLAPSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-two-massive-magnitude-7-24759921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houses and churches were reduced to rubble as a major earthquake - bigger than the 2010 tremor that killed an estimated 300,000 - hit just west of Port-au-Prince, haiti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/haiti-earthquake-08-14-21/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7.2 magnitude earthquake struck near Haiti on Saturday morning. Follow here for the latest updates on Haiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHURCH CRUMBLES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/haiti-earthquake-7-2-magnitude-today-2021-08-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll rose to at least 304 after the 7.2 magnitude quake, which was felt in neighboring countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haiti-earthquake-live-search-survivors-083453052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the latest updates from recovery efforts in the Caribbean</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT GHANI LEAVES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210815135818-u91av</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 10, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 10-Taliban enter Afghan capital, official says President Ghani has left for Tajikistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAITI QUAKE HORROR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-haiti-earthquakes-e067bc2ba933fb40c6d98d34a41a7729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — A powerful magnitude 7.2 earthquake struck southwestern Haiti on Saturday, killing at least 304 people and injuring at least 1,800 others as buildings tumbled into rubble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How phone batteries create alien landscapes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210809-how-your-phone-battery-creates-striking-landscapes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a global hunt for lithium to power our phones and electric vehicles. BBC Future explores the distinctive terrain where the stuff is mined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GOLDMAN SACHS exploits 'woke values' for profit and power...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/14/how-companies-exploit-woke-values-to-pursue-profit-and-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big corporations exploit “woke values” to pursue their own profit and power, dishes a former Goldman Sachs employee in his new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Staffers Say Problems at 'Time's Up' Run Deeper...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/times-up-ex-staffers-say-problems-run-deeper-than-cuomo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revelations that the #MeToo organization consulted for Andrew Cuomo spurred open letters and furious op-eds. But former staffers say the situation is actually far more alarming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Yogurt a Day Keeps Alzheimer's Away? Gut Health Key To Preventing Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/yogurt-alzheimers-disease-probiotics-gut-health-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gut-boosting yogurts could help to ward off Alzheimer's disease, which opens the door to the development of probiotics that treat or even prevent dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSH TO EVACUATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/taliban-enters-kabul-u-s-evacuation-efforts-continue-n1276855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have a small batch of people leaving now as we speak, a majority of the staff are ready to leave," a U.S. official said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Preparing Plan for 3rd Dose, Perhaps By Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-preparing-plan-to-offer-vaccine-boosters-perhaps-by-fall/ar-AANjPWR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — With a stockpile of at least 100 million doses at the ready, Biden administration officials are developing a plan to start offering coronavirus booster shots to some Americans as early as this fall even as researchers continue to hotly debate whether extra shots are needed, according to people familiar with the effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400+ counties now minority white...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/diversity-majority-minority-white-american-census-bd181b53-f170-40b2-9913-dd43363e1aaf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Non-Hispanic, white Americans now make up less than half of residents in more than 400 counties — up from 340 counties in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of weedkilling robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/aug/14/weedkilling-robots-farming-pesticide-use-sustainable</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The makers of robot weeders say the machines can reduce pesticide use and be part of a more sustainable food system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta setting off alarm bells for airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Routes-COVID-variant-Delta-EU-Carribean-JFK-SFO-16385428.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weekly roundup of air travel and airport news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How international scam artists pulled off epic theft of Covid benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/easy-money-how-international-scam-artists-pulled-epic-theft-covid-n1276789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian mobsters, Chinese hackers and Nigerian scammers have used stolen identities to plunder tens of billions of dollars in pandemic aid, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic causing babies to develop differently...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/babies-born-in-covid-pandemic-show-reduced-cognitive-performance-study-676715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In infants, overall cognitive scores are significantly lower since the beginning of the coronavirus pandemic with young infants showing lower performance than infants born before January 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed, reporter attacked at protest at LA City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-police-coronavirus-pandemic-a41a3f36c80111cf8cc421293abd2d08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A man was stabbed and a reporter was attacked Saturday at a protest against vaccine mandates on the south lawn of Los Angeles' City Hall after a fight broke out between the protesters and counterprotesters, the Los Angeles Police Department and local media said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta bartender's kidnapping, death shocks city on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-investigation-underway-heavy-police-presence-in-se-atlanta/BHH7GA3I5ZFVFERELLRY5HCC54/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a city still reeling from the gruesome stabbing death of a woman walking her dog in Piedmont Park, Atlanta was once again stung by tragedy Friday morning when a woman was violently kidnapped outside her home and found shot to death hours later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest war: Were decades fighting worth it?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-afghanistan-8d6d6d9e1e7cddbd49caf0b52a40c2e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what 19-year-old Lance Cpl. William Bee felt flying into southern Afghanistan on Christmas Day 2001: purely lucky. The U.S. was hitting back at the al-Qaida plotters who had brought down the World Trade Center, and Bee found himself among the first Marines on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muhammad Ali's grandson wins first pro bout...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/sport/boxing/58220103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nico Ali Walsh pays tribute to his grandfather Muhammad Ali as he wins his debut professional bout wearing a pair of shorts he had given him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWAITS 'PEACEFUL TRANSFER'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/taliban-e1ed33fe0c665ee67ba132c51b8e32a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Taliban fighters entered the outskirts of the Afghan capital on Sunday and said they were awaiting a “peaceful transfer” of the city after promising not to take it by force, but panicked residents raced to the leave, with workers fleeing government offices and helicopters landing at the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Outsider' Buttigieg plays skillful inside game, positioning himself for future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/outsider-buttigieg-plays-a-skillful-inside-game-positioning-himself-for-the-future/ar-AANjOcY?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biking with Republicans. Tacos with AOC. Buttigieg is deftly using the infrastructure talks to quietly build a network, potentially laying the groundwork for his political future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Inherited Deal Cut By My Predecessor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/i-inherited-a-deal-cut-by-my-predecessor-biden-issues-statement-on-afghanistan-as-taliban-control-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden issued a statement on Sunday regarding the deteriorating situation in Afghanistan, reaffirming his administration’s plans and placing blame on the plan he “inherited from [his] predecessor,” former President Donald Trump, and the inability of the Afghan military to hold their own country. Biden began the statement by describing how he and his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN'S SPOILS OF WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9894251/Rampant-Taliban-ransack-palatial-home-Afghan-warlord-ally-General-Dostum.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurgents tightened their grip on Afghanistan on Saturday by capturing Mazar-e-Sharif - a large, heavily defended city in the north of the country - in a major setback for the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why conservatives depend on memes...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/08/why-the-left-cant-meme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Woke comedy' will never compete with the despair of the online Right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From hubris to humiliation:  America's warrior class contends with abject failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/from-hubris-to-humiliation-america-e2-80-99s-warrior-class-contends-with-the-abject-failure-of-its-afghanistan-project/ar-AANk1Z0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington’s policymakers reflect on the Afghan collapse after two decades of hollow nation-building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Daily Death Toll Nearly Doubles in Two Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-daily-death-toll-from-covid-19-almost-doubles-in-two-weeks/ar-AAMrNBT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news and guidance on the state of the COVID-19 pandemic across New England and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting lawsuits, federal government challenge DeSantis, Abbott bans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mounting-lawsuits-federal-government-challenge-desantis-abbott-bans-on-mask-mandates/ar-AANkmA5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican governors have argued it should be up to individuals to decide if they want to wear masks, which protect others against the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Newsom warns Dems to wake up!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/embattled-california-gov-newsom-facing-recall-election-says-it-s-time-for-democrats-to-wake-up/ar-AANk2mt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Republicans motivated, Newsom says the threat of the recall is real unless Democrats start to take the election seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Seniors Hospitalized With Covid as Much as in January...</title>
      <link>https://www.luxtimes.lu/en/world/pandemic-florida-seniors-hospitalised-with-covid-as-much-as-in-january-6117eed4de135b9236a47575</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.luxtimes.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of those hospitalised are unvaccinated, hospital chiefs say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel recalls envoy as Poland adopts law on WWII claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/8/14/israel-furious-as-poland-signs-law-to-limit-property-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel recalls its top diplomat to Poland after president approves bill curbing World War II-era restitution claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO 'RESPECT':  Critics Call Out Clichés in Aretha Franklin Biopic...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/08/13/respect-reviews-critics-weigh-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many critics are praising Jennifer Hudson's performance in Aretha Franklin biopic 'Respect,' but others are questioning the storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDERS 5,000 TROOPS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-increases-us-deployment-afghanistan-200126823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Saturday doubled down on his decision to withdraw US forces from Afghanistan despite the Taliban's rapid advances, but pledged to send more troops to evacuate civilians and warned the insurgents not to threaten that mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion, disappointment and anger...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/many-u-veterans-fall-afghanistan-110008966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retreat of U.S. troops and advance of the Taliban leave veterans of the Afghanistan war conflicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3CsZfNKbjGc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Behold Barack Antoinette...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/14/opinion/barack-obama-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He hated politics. But he loves post-politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDERS 1,000 TROOPS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-joe-biden-middle-east-evacuations-kabul-8ec855b3f943dafe80d3d3ca6b0953f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden authorized on Saturday an additional 1,000 U.S. troops for deployment to Afghanistan, raising to roughly 5,000 the number of U.S. troops to ensure what Biden called an “orderly and safe drawdown” of American and allied personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain flirts with record heat; 16 Italy cities on red alert...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-science-health-environment-and-nature-heat-waves-645440b90a8cfb48f9e728b28fe7408b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain endured its hottest day of the year Saturday, with temperatures topping 46 degrees Celsius (115 F), while authorities in Italy expanded the number of cities on red alert for health risks to 16 as a heat wave engulfed Southern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tap Dancing With Trump: Lindsey Graham Quest for Relevance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/tap-dancing-with-trump-lindsey-grahams-quest-for-relevance-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Graham’s moment, it seemed, came on the evening of Jan. 6. With crews still cleaning up the blood and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France sees fifth weekend of protests against Macron health pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210814-france-sees-fifth-weekend-of-protests-against-macron-covid-pass</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France sees fifth weekend of protests against Macron Covid pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YALE researchers say social media outrage machine has biggest influence on moderate groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90665826/yale-researchers-say-social-medias-outrage-machine-has-the-biggest-influence-on-moderate-groups</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tracking Twitter users over time, researchers found that those who racked up engagement after showing moral outrage were more likely to keep doing so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/fred-could-become-tropical-storm-as-it-aims-for-florida/999250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Rainstorm Fred threatens to restrengthen while bringing a wide variety of impacts to portions of Florida through the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Storm Intensifies; May Follow Similar Path...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2021-08-14-tropical-storm-grace-forms-south-florida-in-the-cone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Grace will soon bring gusty winds and heavy rain to the islands of the Caribbean. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As America exits, history repeats self...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/567790-as-america-exits-history-repeats-itself-in-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With so much going wrong in Afghanistan, now is hardly the time to be in any way optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Wall St Most Bullish on Stocks in Two Decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wall-street-most-bullish-stocks-121500623.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been two decades since Wall Street analysts were this upbeat.About 56% of all recommendations on S&amp;P 500 firms are listed as buys, the most since 2002. It’s one more data point that shows the extent of the euphoria sweeping markets after a blockbuster earnings season.While analysts are historically a bullish bunch, they’re turning even more optimistic in the face of relentless stock-market gains and corporate earnings that topped even the highest expectations. For all the con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militant Sweep Follows Years of Miscalculations...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/taliban-sweep-in-afghanistan-follows-years-of-u-s-miscalculations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden’s top advisers concede they were stunned by the rapid collapse of the Afghan army in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus claims more young as deaths climb yet again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-5e56dc3f817e3eaca1f48511c3be8549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A young mother had just celebrated her first wedding anniversary and was one of six members of a Jacksonville church to die over a 10-day span. Another Florida woman had just given birth to her first child, but was only able to hold the newborn girl for a few moments before dying.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
