<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Camp Took Almost Every Precaution. Majority of Kids Still Got It...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-summer-camp-took-almost-every-precaution-the-majority-of-kids-still-got-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 76 percent of young campers who were tested came back positive—an ominous sign as schools push to reopen by the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now wants EARLY election?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-makes-ominous-prediction-while-raging-against-mail-vote-this-is-going-to-be-the-greatest-election-disaster-in-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Actually, The Washington Post wrote a great article, of all groups," Trump said on Friday. "A week ago, The Washington Post wrote a great article that this is a disaster. This is going</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court overturns Boston Marathon bomber's death sentence...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2020/07/31/federal-appeals-court-overturns-boston-marathon-bomber-dzhokhar-tsarnaevs-death-sentence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen accused of being 'mastermind' behind TWITTER hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/hillsborough-county/tampa-teen-accused-of-being-mastermind-behind-twitter-hack-that-targeted-high-profile-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tampa teenager is in jail, accused of being the “mastermind” behind a hack on the social media website Twitter that caused limited access to the site and high-profile accounts, accord…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX set to bring NASA astronauts home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/31/tech/nasa-spacex-crew-dragon-mission-preview-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA astronauts Robert Behnken and Douglas Hurley, the first-ever astronauts to travel into orbit aboard a commercially developed spacecraft, are aiming to return to Earth this weekend — if an incoming hurricane doesn't delay those plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reopenings linked to politics not public health...</title>
      <link>https://www.brookings.edu/blog/brown-center-chalkboard/2020/07/29/school-reopening-plans-linked-to-politics-rather-than-public-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.brookings.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is partisanship playing a role in school reopening?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Warning Signs...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/31/gov-murphy-puts-new-jersey-on-notice-warns-residents-to-heed-coronavirus-guidelines-as-cases-spike-the-alarms-are-going-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey remains among the states with the lowest coronavirus positivity rates, but Gov. Phil Murphy said Friday that may change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer road trip? Quarantines crimping travelers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ee83aefdc086c7cc6710adc71a20774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Families trying to squeeze in a summer vacation before school starts better do some homework on COVID-19 restrictions before loading up the minivan. The web of state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient didn't recognize body after double transplant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/COVID-patient-didn-t-recognize-body-after-double-15447359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) - A Chicago woman who last month became the nation's first COVID-19 patient to undergo a double lung transplant said Thursday that she woke up days later, unaware about the surgery and unable to "recognize my body."  Mayra Ramirez said that before she fell ill she was an independent, active person who moved from North Carolina to Chicago in 2014 to work as a paralegal. She said she had an autoimmune condition, but was otherwise healthy. She had gone on a three-mile run shortly before becoming ill and heading for the hospital.  "I was told to hurry up (and) change," she said. "I was asked who would be making my medical decisions for me. That's when I told them it would be my mother and eldest sister who all live in North Carolina. I only had a couple minutes to contact them to let them know what was going on before I was intubated."  Ramirez, 28, spoke to the media on Thursday alongside Brian Kuhns, 62, of Lake Zurich, Illinois, who followed her as the second U.S. coronavirus patient to undergo a double transplant.  Ramirez underwent the lung transplant on June 5 at Northwestern Memorial Hospital in Chicago. She didn't wake up until mid-June.  "I looked at myself and couldn't recognize my body," she said. "I didn't have the cognitive ability to process what was going on. All I knew was that I wanted water."  Dr. Ankit Bharat, chief of thoracic surgery and surgical director of the Northwestern Medicine Lung Transplant Program, said Ramirez, who was on a ventilator, fought for her life for six weeks, with the virus completely destroying her lungs. Doctors would call Nohemi Romero, her mother in North Carolina, with updates.  Ramirez, sitting next to her mother during a news conference at the hospital, said her family made the trip to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Insiders Say Entertainment Boss Fostered Toxic Culture, Under Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/nbc-insiders-say-entertainment-boss-fostered-toxic-culture-under-investigation-1305307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former employees allege that NBC Entertainment chairman Paul Telegdy engaged in racist, sexist and homophobic behavior: "It was par for the course."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Order China's BYTEDANCE to Sell TIKTOK U.S. Operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-31/trump-to-order-china-s-bytedance-to-sell-tiktok-u-s-operations-kdaib6eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Republicans wants rapid testing available -- at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/510000-gop-leaders-wants-to-make-rapid-testing-available-at-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) said he is looking at options for Republicans to bring rapid testing to the Capitol that would be offered to members in both parties along with staff and reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors could lose hearing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/31/covid-19-survivors-may-lose-hearing-sense-of-smell-and-taste/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has already been established that some coronavirus survivors lose their sense of smell and taste — but doctors in Britain now warn that they can also lose their hearing, according to a report. E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to Seize Bolton Book Profits Without Trial?</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/us-seeks-to-seize-john-bolton-book-profits-without-a-trial/article_7670200f-2ea8-56d8-955a-a4e465390bc8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government asked a federal judge in Washington to rule in its favor without a trial as it seeks to seize the proceeds from former national security adviser John</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron salutes Kaepernick for inspiring NBA National Anthem demonstration...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/LeBron-James-salutes-Colin-Kaepernick-for-15448572.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KISSIMMEE, Fla. - After kneeling during the national anthem on the opening night of the NBA's bubble restart, LeBron James dedicated the coordinated social justice demonstration to former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick.  James, who led the Los Angeles Lakers past the Clippers at 103-101 at The Arena at Disney World on Thursday, said that Kaepernick "taught me a lot" about the protest issue. Kaepernick, once a star quarterback with the San Francisco 49ers, has not played in the NFL since he began protesting police brutality by taking a knee during the national anthem in 2016.  "I hope we made Kaep proud," James said. "I hope we continue to make Kaep proud every single day. I hope I make him proud on how I live my life, not only out on the basketball floor but off the floor."  The Lakers and Clippers donned "Black Lives Matter" shirts and locked arms before their contest in a unified demonstration. Every player on both teams participated, as did the coaches and referees. A similar demonstration took place involving members of the Utah Jazz and New Orleans Pelicans earlier Thursday.  The 35-year-old James, who has been outspoken on political issues dating back to Trayvon Martin and Eric Garner, called for the Louisville police officers who shot Breonna Taylor to be arrested last week. After praising Rep. John Lewis recently for teaching him to "never be afraid of conflict, good conflict, positive conflict that can create change," James said he appreciated Kaepernick's willingness to take a polarizing stand and to clearly state his motives, even when critics suggested that kneeling was disrespectful to the military or un-American.  "Kaep was someone who stood up when times weren't comfortable, when people didn't understand, when people refused to listen to what he was saying," James said. "If you go back and listen to his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers make wills, retire, plan strikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2020/jul/31/teachers-school-reopening-in-person-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators, worried about the potentially deadly risks they are being forced to take, say proper protections have not been implemented</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Sentiment Sinks into Deep Funk...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2020/07/31/summertime-blues-u-s-consumer-sentiment-sinks-deeper-into-coronavirus-resurgence-funk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer sentiment continued to slide downward in late July, with both the current conditions and expectations gauges declining. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH EAST COAST</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/isaias-explodes-into-hurricane-to-eye-us-east-coast/786335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Alan Parker dead...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/alan-parker-dies-director-of-bugsy-malone-midnight-express-evita-was-76-1203000762/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Alan Parker, a towering figure in the UK industry, passed away this morning following a lengthy illness, the British Film Institute has confirmed. He was 76. Two-time Oscar nominee Parker…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced microchip to revolutionize commercial, weapons tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/30/tachyum-prodigy-universal-processor-microchip-revo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An energy-efficient microchip under development combines different types of processors into one chip and is expected to revolutionize commercial and defense technology, the advanced semiconductor’s inventor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: 'NO END IN SIGHT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1233195/fauci-covid-continue-for-some-time-disagreement-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTHONY Fauci said the COVID-19 crisis will “continue for some time” in latest disagreement with Trump, who said it would “disappear.” On Friday, Fauci, CDC boss Robert Redf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICH GET RICHER DURING COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1232880/amazon-facebook-apple-profit-coronavirus-quarter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON sales have jumped by 40 percent, Facebook’s profit has increased by 98 percent and Apple has posted more than $11billion profit in the last quarter. The companies have all seen a rise …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Algorithms Struggle to Detect Faces Under Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/07/facial-recognition-algorithms-struggle-detect-faces-under-masks-nist-study-finds/167303/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Halts Ad Spending While It Reviews Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-campaign-halts-ad-spending-while-it-reviews-strategy/ar-BB17q4ET</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Owners Leaning on Credit Cards to Survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/small-business-owners-are-leaning-on-credit-cards-to-survive/ar-BB17q2Mg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 men killed, woman injured in baseball bat attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2020/07/31/2-men-killed-woman-injured-in-baseball-bat-attack-at-windermere-home-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were beaten to death and a woman was seriously injured late Thursday during an attack at a home in a gated Windermere community while a 10-year-old boy called authorities while hiding in a bathroom, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH EAST COAST</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/isaias-explodes-into-hurricane-to-eye-us-east-coast/785580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Street Corners Overflowing With Garbage After Sanitation Dept Budget Slashed...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/trash-collection-nyc-sanitation-department-budget-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sanitation commissioner says curbside collection service has stayed the same, but people are leaving out more trash than usual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deal with it'... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deal-epstein-told-maxwell-unsealed-emails-150325713.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York court has unsealed emails revealing that disgraced late financier Jeffrey Epstein tried to reassure accused sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell by telling her she had "done nothing wrong." "You have done nothing wrong and I would urge you to start acting like it," Epstein</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to invest $10 billion in space-based internet system...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-invest-10-bn-space-based-internet-system-143020830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon says it will invest $10 billion for its planned space-based internet delivery system after winning US regulatory approval to deploy more than 3,000 low-orbit satellites. The US tech giant said on Thursday it is moving forward with its Project Kuiper, one of several systems planned to bring internet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAHAMAS BRACES...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200731144415-rvcis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-ISAIAS/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Hurricane Isaias heads toward Florida with 75-mph winds -Hurricane Center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami-Dade Mayor Urges Residents To Prep For Hurricane; All COVID-19 Testing Sites Shut Down...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/31/miami-dade-mayor-carlos-gimenez-urges-residents-prepare-impacts-hurricane-isaias/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade is preparing for possible impacts from Hurricane Isaias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President faces rare rebuke from GOP for floating election delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08c1c9bb58ecb5392e2e59a4161233b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump repeatedly tests the Republican Party's limits on issues including race, trade and immigration. Now he has struck a boundary. GOP officials from New...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPECTED CAT 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-hurricane-isaias-florida-update-20200731-5g7pveljzjdcppbzmd64s35jim-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hurricane watch was issued for part of the South Florida coast, as Hurricane Isaias was projected to reach Category 2 strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partisan clash at start of hearing with Fauci...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-fauci/partisan-clash-at-start-of-u-s-house-coronavirus-hearing-with-fauci-idUSKCN24W1GS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional Republicans and Democrats clashed about whether the Trump administration had a national strategy to respond to the coronavirus pandemic at the start of a hearing featuring Dr. Anthony Fauci, the United States' top infectious disease expert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist recalls most disturbing case: Yellow snake-like eyes, contorted body...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/yellow-snake-like-eyes-contorted-22439624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Reverend Bill Bean has been a practising exorcist since 2013 and told Daily Star Online about the chilling details of one particular demonic possession</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDINALS Game Postponed After 'Multiple' Players Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/cardinals-have-positive-coronavirus-tests-fridays-game-against-brewers-postponed-per-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cardinals are reportedly self-isolating at their hotel following multiple positive tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Nevada Sportsbooks Suffer First Monthly Loss Since '13...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/general/news/nevada-sportsbooks-suffer-first-monthly-net-loss-since-2013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada sportsbooks lost $483,000 in June</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for fourth straight day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200731134711-omuu8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (URGENT):Florida reports record increase in COVID-19 deaths for fourth day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Lost Penis Now Has New One Growing On His Arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_uk/article/akz4mp/man-lose-penis-grow-arm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The father of two was "completely gutted" when his penis fell off due to an infection, but is excited to see his new one grafted to his groin and "ultimately used for what it was built for".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face of God? Archaeologist claims to find 10th cent. BCE graven images of Yahweh...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/face-of-god-archaeologist-claims-to-find-10th-cent-bce-graven-images-of-yahweh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hebrew U Prof. Yosef Garfinkel asserts small male figurines discovered at digs near Jerusalem are an image of the biblical God; other experts angrily dismiss theory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did CIA Torture Undercover DEA Agent for Mexican Drug Cartel?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/did-the-cia-torture-an-undercover-dea-agent-for-a-mexican-drug-cartel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Amazon docuseries “The Last Narc” contains several eye-opening claims—including that the CIA may have helped in the killing of undercover DEA agent Enrique “Kiki” Camarena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryan Singer's Traumatic 'X-MEN' Set: Movie Created Monster...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/bryan-singers-traumatic-x-men-set-movie-created-a-monster-1305081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director's auteur style changed Hollywood's approach to superhero movies forever, but his on-set tantrums, a cast mutiny and, later, allegations of sexual abuse have left a tarnished legacy as the franchise turns 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Lincoln Project video imagines what it's like to wake up from coma in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/928582/new-lincoln-project-video-imagines-what-like-wake-from-coma-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you've ever wondered what it would be like to wake up in 2020 after being in a coma for nearly four years, the Lincoln Project has you covered. The Lincoln Project, founded by Republicans who do not want to see President Trump re-elected, released its latest ad, 'Wake Up,' on Thursday. It opens with a man in a hospital bed being greeted by his family, who let him know he was in a car accident and has been in a coma for more than three years. 'Did I miss anything interesting?' he asks his masked family. A proud Trump voter, he starts peppering his Republican family with questions, like how did the president get Mexico to pay for his border wall? They catch him up to speed on about 0.01 percent of what has happened over the last few years, putting their own positive spin on the impeachment, the coronavirus pandemic, the Stormy Daniels saga, Trump throwing paper towels in Puerto Rico, and the economy. The man's reaction, while extreme, also feels pretty relatable. Watch the video below. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Best argument against Kamala for VP...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/928426/best-argument-against-kamala-harris-vp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) is reportedly the frontrunner to be picked as Joe Biden's running mate. At a time of close attention to racial justice issues, the first Black woman vice president would be a marked symbolic advance. However, there is another side to Harris' record on this question. Alex Sammon examined documents from Harris' tenure as California attorney general for The American Prospect, and found that she disobeyed for years a Supreme Court order to reduce the extreme overcrowding in the state's prisons. Harris took office in 2011, and in May that year the court ruled the state's packed prisons â€” which had previously reached 200 percent of their design capacity â€” were a violation of the Eighth Amendment. They instructed the state to cut capacity to 167 percent by the end of 2011, to 137.5 percent by June 2013, and appointed a 3-judge oversight panel. Harris refused. The state made little progress in 2011, and in 2012 appealed to get the final figure raised to 145 percent (which was denied). By April 2013 the state was still 9,636 prisoners over the cap, and the oversight board recommended extending 'good time' credits to nonviolent offenders. Harris's office fought tooth and nail against this proposal. The judges found their arguments so 'continually equivocated regarding the facts and the law' that they nearly held the state in contempt of court. Eventually, in 2014, Harris gave in and the prison population was duly reduced. This stubborn foot-dragging to keep nonviolent, low-risk offenders in grossly overcrowded prisons bears a striking contrast with Harris's decision not to prosecute Steven Mnuchin (now secretary of the Treasury) for illegal foreclosures when he was head of OneWest Bank. As David Dayen reported at The Intercept, California prosecutors wrote a memo in 2013 describing how they 'uncovered evidence suggestive of widespread misconduct,' including 1,000 alleged legal violations in just a sample of OneWest loans. They recommended Harris file charges, but she declined to do so. So on the one hand, Harris went to the mat to keep thousands of nonviolent offenders behind bars. On the other, she would not prosecute a rich, well-connected person even when her own staffers found 1,000 alleged crimes. It's not a great fit for a time when the rampant injustice in American police departments and prisons has become a first-rank political issue. Ryan Cooper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC THREAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/nyc-entire-tri-state-in-cone-of-concern-next-week-as-hurricane-isaias-eyes-bahamas-friday/2544398/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire tri-state area, including New York City, is in the cone of concern for potential impacts from Hurricane Isaias, the category 1 storm that is expected to pound the Bahamas later Friday before turning slowly toward the U.S. East Coast. As of NOAA’s 8 a.m. update, it was currently about 30 miles northwest of Great Inagua Island with maximum…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car of future more like LEGO set than Bond ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90534847/why-the-car-of-the-future-is-more-like-a-lego-set-than-a-bond-ride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Electric. Modular. And pretty much whatever you want it to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping lions, terrible pain: New world without tourism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9439258ed4ba433ec9266d3fc9a7d2fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — With no American visitors to show around the D-Day beaches or the Loire Valley’s chateaux, and no work on the immediate horizon, Paris tour guide Linda Zenou frets about how she’ll...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They're not the first...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/They-were-arrested-and-jailed-for-breaking-a-15448411.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After he tested positive for the coronavirus this month, Jose Freire Interian received strict orders to quarantine at his home in Key West, Fla. With infections exploding across the state, the sick 24-year-old was not to leave his bungalow and risk spreading the virus any further.  But on Wednesday, police showed up to his door, demanding that he and his wife leave their house - in handcuffs.  "I asked them, 'Why?' I was in shock," he told the Associated Press. "Why am I getting arrested for? It was unfair."  Officials allege that Freire and Yohana Gonzalez, 26, repeatedly ignored the quarantine orders - going to walk their dog, shop for groceries, and get their car washed - and had been caught on tape.  On Thursday, the couple was taken to the Stock Island Detention Center on two second-degree misdemeanor charges: breaking quarantine during a public health emergency and violating emergency management.  Authorities believe Freire and Gonzalez are the first people to be arrested for such an offense in Monroe County, and perhaps all of Florida, since the start of the coronavirus outbreak. But nationwide, they are hardly the only ones whose lax adherence to the rules has landed them in jail.  As the pandemic has spread across the United States, killing more than 148,000 people to date, police have on occasion locked up possible vectors of disease - those who are sick, or irresponsible, or both - to ensure the virus does not spread even further.  Earlier this month, a Kentucky woman and her husband were placed on house arrest after she refused to sign papers agreeing to quarantine herself. A man from New York was detained in South Carolina after he was discovered walking around in a hospital gown, just days after his trip down.  Hawaii, in particular, has taken a relentless...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Marine dead, 8 missing after training 'mishap' off California coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/one-marine-dead-8-missing-after-training-mishap-california-coast-n1235440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We are deeply saddened by this tragic incident,” said Col. Christopher Bronzi, commanding officer for the 15th Marine Expeditionary Unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health of Ruth Bader Ginsburg fuels anxiety, preparations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/health-us-supreme-court-justice-ginsburg-fuels-anxiety-031823466.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, a darling of the US left and an increasingly frail octogenarian, is taking center stage ahead of this year's presidential election, with the Supreme Court's balance hanging on her seemingly faltering health. Ginsburg's liver cancer -- and recent repeat trips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji records first death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/enormous-tragedy-fiji-records-first-covid-19-death-064837607.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiji announced its first coronavirus death Friday, but health officials assured people in the Pacific island nation that it was not the precursor to a major outbreak. Health Minister Ifereimi Waqainabete said the victim was a 66-year-old man who tested positive after returning from India, where he had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM postpones next stage of lockdown lifting due to rising infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200731104059-11er5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-POSTPONE (URGENT):UK PM Johnson postpones next stage of lockdown lifting due to rising COVID infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Seeks to Seize Bolton Book Profits Without Trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/us-law-week/u-s-seeks-to-seize-john-bolton-book-profits-without-a-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government asked a federal judge in Washington to rule in its favor without a trial as it seeks to seize the proceeds from former National Security Advisor John Bolton’s tell-all memoir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZ: FACEBOOK, GOOGLE Told They Must Pay Media For News...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-google-told-must-pay-034708811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Australia’s government has ordered Facebook Inc. and Alphabet Inc.’s Google to share revenue generated from news articles, adding to growing global regulatory and political pushback against the digital giants.The two companies will have to negotiate with traditional media on remuneration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond Yields Sending Scary Signal on Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bond-yields-sending-scary-signal-100003918.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- There is no shortage of investors shrugging off the latest leg lower in U.S. Treasury bond yields, saying heavy central bank involvement in this part of the financial market make such moves less of a signal that the economy or that equities are headed for trouble. That interpretation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans, White House at Odds Over Kansas Senate Race...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/30/republicans-and-white-house-at-odds-over-kansas-senate-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As the Kansas Senate primary barrels to a close, tensions are rising between Senate Republicans and the White</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12274877/bill-clinton-flew-to-jeffrey-epsteins-orgy-island-with-two-young-girls-bombshell-ghislaine-maxwell-docs-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER president Bill Clinton once flew to Jeffrey Epstein’s “orgy” island with “two young girls”, bombshell legal papers claim. The news was revealed after a trove of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trained sex slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jul/31/ghislaine-maxwell-underage-girls-sex-jeffrey-epstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsealed testimony from 2015 case reveals series of claims about British socialite’s role in Epstein sex-trafficking ring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court docs detail Maxwell's 'constant' orgies with young girls on Epstein island...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/31/ghislaine-maxwell-had-continuous-sex-with-young-girls-on-epstein-island/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein and his alleged madam Ghislaine Maxwell used his private Caribbean island to host “constant” orgies and once flew in a group of European models to fulfill their sexual f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAHAMAS BRACES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db2517c2ff9ef9597a49cb57524cdbc9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — New Hurricane Isaias kept on a path early Friday expected to take it to the U.S. East Coast by the weekend as it approached the Bahamas, parts of which are still...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PO150o2pNw0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA FORECAST: HURRICANE?</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EeOPU8jU0AIC6sA?format=jpg&amp;name=900x900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingraham dethrones Maddow as most-watched female cable host...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/laura-ingraham-sprints-past-rachel-maddow-to-become-most-watched-female-cable-news-host  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL players kneel during anthem as NBA restarts...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/sports/orlando-magic/os-sp-nba-players-kneel-national-anthem-20200730-qkkvbcpsmze53izzljq7iw4gj4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All players competing in the first game of the NBA restart took a knee and locked arms during a recording of the national anthem Thursday night at ESPN Wide World of Sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was hospitalized less than two weeks after attending MAGA rally in Tulsa...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/30/herman-cain-dead-dies-74-sick-covid-19-attending-trump-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herman Cain, once a GOP presidential hopeful, died after battling COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Vaccine distribution will be 'joint venture' between CDC, Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/30/coronavirus-vaccine-distribution-388904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan breaks with the longstanding precedent that CDC distributes vaccines during major outbreaks through a centralized ordering system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Secrets, From Sex to Pets to Celeb Bad Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/technology/eight-shocking-secrets-i-learned-while-working-on-private-jets/ar-BB17lXlV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worth even more the day after Congressional grilling!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/a-day-after-congress-grilling-big-tech-stocks-add-250-billion/ar-BB17o6e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP PLUNGES RECORD 32.9%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/economy-suffers-titanic-329-plunge-in-2nd-quarter-gdp-shows-and-points-to-drawn-out-recovery-2020-07-30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An economy badly battered by the coronavirus shrank at a record 32.9% pace in the second quarter, underscoring just how big a hole the U.S. finds itself in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix to break record for its hottest month!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Phoenix-to-break-record-for-its-hottest-month-15447006.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unforgiving heat has baked Phoenix this month, not only scorching the afternoons but staying hot at night, more often than not above 90 degrees round the clock. Such unforgiving heat poses public health risks and could be a sign of things to come as climate change leads to a hotter, drier Southwest.  Thursday's low temperature stayed above 90 degrees in Phoenix for the 15th time this month. The count of exceptionally hot nights has obliterated the previous July record of 11 set in 2006. Assuming that the temperature does not drop below 90 before midnight Thursday, the count will match the most such hot nights in Phoenix for any year on record, with much summer heat still to come.  Low temperatures this month have been the warmest recorded for the city, where weather data began in the 1800s. The July average temperature for Phoenix of 98.6 degrees is also the hottest on record for any month.  With an excessive heat warning in effect through Saturday, and temperatures expected to top 110 into the middle of next week, the city probably will see its hottest recorded month.  The heat is in large part due to a strong area of high pressure, also referred to as a heat dome, parked over the region for much of the month.  The hottest major city in the country, Phoenix averages about 175 days at or above 90 degrees and 110 days at or above 100, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA).  But it's a dry heat; such an arid atmosphere tends to allow temperatures to cool off at night. Until recently.  Ninety-degree lows were almost unheard of in Phoenix before the 1970s, but then the city started seeing about one to two a year in the 1980s and '90s. Since 2000, such occurrences have increased in frequency.  In the early 2000s the 30-year average was still...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA FORECAST: HURRICANE?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-isaias-to-eye-florida-us-east-coast/785580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA THURSDAY:  1,529 COVID DEATHS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1288970515344842753?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sales soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730202918-jcjn9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON.COM-RESULTS/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Amazon posts biggest profit ever at height of pandemic in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS REJECT</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730180310-sef8v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/DELAY (UPDATE 8, PIX):UPDATE 8-Trump floats election delay, congressional Republicans reject idea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court lets Michael Cohen publish book while sentenced at home...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730174309-vif6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/COHEN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. lets ex-Trump lawyer Michael Cohen publish book while serving sentence at home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for third straight day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f69d7f7b08fb036647880ae4874a5dc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Florida tallied on Thursday a new record high in daily confirmed COVID-19 deaths for the third straight day as the state faces pressure to outline new measures to combat the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd virus surge hits plateau?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3081a60a6abf62effa2e6030556ee30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — While deaths from the coronavirus in the U.S. are mounting rapidly, public health experts are seeing a flicker of good news: The second surge of confirmed cases appears to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FLOATS ELECTION DELAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d203eaa406dc5e7362dfa9e33522195e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump, lagging in the polls and grappling with deepening economic and public health crises, on Thursday floated the startling idea of delaying the Nov. 3...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS SPIKE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1878e580f5acd2c0305e5236c4e3197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The coronavirus pandemic sent the U.S. economy plunging by a record-shattering 32.9% annual rate last quarter and is still inflicting damage across the country, squeezing already...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERMAN CAIN DEAD FROM COVID...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8173fe14f7cf7095ced3b55fdc65581e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Herman Cain, former Republican presidential candidate and former CEO of a major pizza chain who went on to become an ardent supporter of President Donald Trump, has died of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Music Lessons Don't Make Children Smarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/music-lessons-dont-make-children-smarter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors declare that “teaching music with the sole intent of enhancing a child’s cognitive or academic skills may be pointless.” LONDON — Parents who think guitar or piano lessons will help their child’s academic performance may end up singing the blues themselves, according to a surprising new study. Researchers from both Japan and England conclude…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deleted Biden video sets off crisis at VOICE OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/30/deleted-biden-video-sets-off-a-crisis-at-voice-of-america-388571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The taxpayer-funded outlet is grappling with the fallout from a video post deemed too favorable to the former vice president, setting off recriminations and suspicion amid a shakeup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA FORECAST: HURRICANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/302054.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen DeGeneres Addresses 'Toxic Work Culture' Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ellen-degeneres-addresses-workplace-allegations-changes-forthcoming-staff-letter-1305189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the steps to change a workplace environment under fire, two sources tell The Hollywood Reporter that producer Ed Glavin will soon be out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will she be canceled?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/30/will-ellen-degeneres-become-a-canceled-celebrity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s faced major backlash in recent months, and her show is under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton ripped for remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theroot.com/will-someone-come-get-bill-clinton-he-just-shaded-stok-1844561440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theroot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how on beat they seem during the “Electric Slide” or how good their blaccent may be, there is a reason not every white person can come to the proverbial Black cookout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Why Trump Might Quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/30/why-trump-might-quit-387681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is logic behind saying to hell with reelection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court lets Michael Cohen publish book while sentenced at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/court-lets-ex-trump-lawyer-cohen-publish-book-while-sentenced-at-home-636989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK reports massive revenue growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/facebook-fb-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has seen an increase in user engagement as a result of the coronavirus, but has also endured an ad boycott that may crimp revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE blowout; Sales up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/apple-aapl-earnings-q3-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple reported a historically strong quarter for the company on Thursday, including $59.7 billion in revenue and double-digit growth in its products and services segments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sales soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/30/amazon-amzn-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company beat on both the top and bottom lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study finds higher viral load in young children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/30/health/children-coronavirus-viral-load-transmission-study-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children younger than 5 have between 10 and 100 times more genetic material from the novel coronavirus in their noses compared to older children and to adults, according to a small study published Thursday in the journal JAMA Pediatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: 92-Year-Old Woman With Dementia Sexually Assaulted In Home...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/stockton-woman-92-assaulted-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Joaquin County Sheriff deputies arrested James Lee Coose Wednesday for the attack a day earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama delivers eulogy at funeral with Presidents Bush, Clinton in attendance...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/30/barack-obama-delivers-eulogy-at-rep-john-lewis-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama is delivering the eulogy at civil rights icon Rep. John Lewis’ funeral Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY authorities break up alleged sex party...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/york-authorities-break-alleged-sex-party-crackdown-large/story?id=71948681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheriff's deputies in New York City recently broke up a sex party in Midtown.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
