<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brady assistant said to be job hunting -- fueling retirement rumors...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/01/28/tom-brady-retiring-assistant-said-to-be-looking-for-a-new-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady’s longtime assistant Ben Rawitz has been talking to other top quarterbacks about work — prompting even more speculation that the star athlete is going to retire. Page Six has been t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rules put Djokovic at risk of missing French Open...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-health-french-open-74b9b748bb0ee88e52c4f4ca59f0a46c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France is tightening its vaccination rules in a way that could put Novak Djokovic at risk of missing the French Open. From Feb. 15, anyone who is not vaccinated against the coronavirus will need to show proof they tested positive for COVID-19 within the previous four months — down from the current six-month window — in order to enter sports venues in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Targeting Election Lies Mulled by Washington Lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2022-01-28/bill-targeting-election-lies-mulled-by-washington-lawmakers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Gov. Jay Inslee is urging state lawmakers to approve a bill that would make it a crime for elected officials or candidates to knowingly lie about election outcomes if those claims result in violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus-sniffing dogs on tour with METALLICA, BLACK KEYS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/28/covid-sniffing-dogs-living-on-tour-with-metallica-black-keys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But has Snoop Dogg booked them yet? A pack of trained canines are living the rock ’n’ roll life — touring with the likes of Metallica and the Black Keys in an effort to keep the musicians and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Spending Drops With Inflation Hitting 40-Year High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-spending-drops-inflation-135649366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. inflation-adjusted consumer spending fell last month by the most since February, suggesting that Americans tempered their outlays amid the latest Covid-19 wave and the fastest inflation in nearly 40 years.Most Read from BloombergApple to Rival Square by Turning iPhones Into Payment TerminalsHow a Fox News Interview Threw the Antiwork Subreddit Into ChaosCrypto Secrecy Makes DeFi a Financial Felon’s WonderlandStocks Drop in Roller-Coaster Ride for Wall Street: Markets WrapMega</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists urge athletes to speak out at Beijing Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-sports-beijing-xi-jinping-2020-tokyo-olympics-879330e41869afcc81bfd5473fca56e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Human rights activists issued a call to action against the Beijing Olympics on Friday, imploring athletes and sponsors to speak out against what they call the “genocide games.” Speaking at an online press conference organized by the rights group Human Rights Watch, activists representing Chinese dissidents and the minority Uyghur and Tibetan populations urged international attendants to voice their opposition to China's hosting of the Games, which begin next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia loses million people in historic population fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220128-russia-loses-a-million-people-in-historic-population-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's population declined by more than one million people in 2021, the statistics agency Rosstat reported Friday, a historic drop not seen since the collapse of the Soviet Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are so many San Franciscans moving to Montana?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/sf/article/Data-shows-that-Montana-has-surged-in-popularity-16811723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana saw the largest pandemic spike in movers from San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China county tells 'leftover' women to marry unemployed men...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/economy/china-economy/article/3165120/china-population-county-sparks-uproar-telling-leftover-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yihuang county in Jiangxi province is offering women a host of sweeteners to encourage them to marry, the latest effort by a local government to address China’s declining birth rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Secretly Bought Spyware, Explored Hacking US Phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/28/world/middleeast/israel-pegasus-spyware.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel used the NSO Group’s software as a tool of diplomacy. The F.B.I. wanted it for domestic surveillance. Then everything soured. Here are highlights of a New York Times Magazine investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for World's Most Powerful Cyberweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-battle-for-the-world-s-most-powerful-cyberweapon/ar-AATex5P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Adams' war against crime sparks unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/28/adams-nypd-crime-00002011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA net neutrality law upheld...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-california-telecommunications-jerry-brown-2db073ce6d11c7274fd9c6291d3c411b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court has upheld California’s net neutrality law , rejecting an attempt by telecommunications industry groups to prevent the state from enforcing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside look at how 1 person can control swarm of 130 robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.popsci.com/technology/drone-swarm-control-virtual-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popsci.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usually, one person controls one drone. In this case, virtual reality and artificial intelligence allowed one person to direct a large swarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Becomes Contagious -- Among Clams...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/contagious-cancer-spreading-clams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contagious cancers, surprisingly, aren't actually unheard of. Scientists have documented these diseases in dogs, Tasmanian devils, and various bivalves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiker falls hundreds of feet to death while taking selfie...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-21-year-old-hiker-fell-hundreds-of-feet-to-his-16812838.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Jacobson, a 21-year-old hiker from Arizona, was high up in the Superstition...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA School Calls Cops on Unvaccinated Teens...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/28/this-l-a-school-called-the-cops-on-unvaccinated-teens-who-showed-up-for-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When 15-year-old Ellah Nahum and a few other unvaccinated students showed up at Los Angeles' New West Charter School on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swastikas spray painted on DC's Union Station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-amtrak-93eb06b8c1b3ee22030314c8993b103b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Vandals spray-painted dozens of swastikas on the outside of Union Station, the central hub for regional train transportation in the nation's capital. The graffiti was discovered Friday, a day after International Holocaust Remembrance Day, with crude Nazi symbols painted on columns across the front of the massive building and several clustered around the escalator entrance to the underground D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide hotline shares data with for-profit spinoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/28/suicide-hotline-silicon-valley-privacy-debates-00002617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusionment of a Young Presidential Official...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-political-scene/the-disillusionment-of-a-young-biden-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrea Flores’s efforts to roll back Trump’s immigration policies faced opposition inside and outside the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carville's advice to Dems:   'Just win some godd*mn elections'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/22893113/james-carville-joe-manchin-biden-democratic-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Carville on why Manchin is actually good, Sinema less so, and why 2022 isn’t quite hopeless yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber-War Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nd9x/ukraine-russia-invasion-belarus-railway-hack-cyber-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An apparent hack of the railway network in Russia’s ally Belarus hints at the prospect of a massive new wave of cyber warfare over Ukraine, security officials told VICE World News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'A boom, then monster sound'...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/local/city/2022/01/28/pittsburgh-bridge-collapse-forbes-braddock-avenue-point-breeze-squirrel-hill/stories/202201280075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were transported to a hospital with non-life-threatening injuries, Pittsburgh fire Chief Darryl Jones said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ambassador warns of 'military conflict' over Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/28/1076246311/chinas-ambassador-to-the-u-s-warns-of-military-conflict-over-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first one-on-one interview since assuming his post in Washington, D.C., last July, Ambassador Qin Gang has an unusually blunt message for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly center closes due to 'threats' from border rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/border-butterfly-center-closed-hidalgo-texas-16811253.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The butterfly facility will be closed throughout the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-described 'Freedom Convoy' of anti-vax Canadian truckers due to arrive in Ottawa...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-self-described-e2-80-98freedom-convoy-e2-80-99-of-anti-vaccine-canadian-truckers-is-due-to-arrive-in-ottawa/ar-AATeYnj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple recovering from covid couldn't smell smoke when house caught fire. Toddler saved family...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-couple-recovering-from-covid-couldn-e2-80-99t-smell-the-smoke-when-their-house-caught-fire-their-toddler-saved-the-family/ar-AATeA1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next normal: States will recognize multiparent families...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-the-next-normal-states-will-recognize-multiparent-families/ar-AATeJiz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies in 'happy ending' massage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/british-man-70-dies-inside-26078822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrived at the 'Lovely Massage' shop in the Bang Lamung district of Pattaya City to find Robert John Swain, 70, had died at the scene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars, bus left teetering...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10452285/Bridge-collapse-Pittsburgh-hours-President-Biden-set-visit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers formed a human chain to rescue four people from a commuter bus left dangling off the edge of a collapsed bridge in Pittsburgh early Friday - hours before Biden's scheduled visit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the $128 million heist that shocked the world...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/dresden-green-vault-heist-trial-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took at least nine hard blows from an ax to smash the glass case in Dresden's historic Green Vault. Once the glass shattered, the two masked thieves grabbed 21 priceless diamond-studded artifacts and disappeared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images of Navy's newest US stealth fighters crashing into sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/28/asia/us-navy-f-35-crash-photos-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images have emerged of a US Navy F-35C stealth fighter crashing into the South China Sea earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't create panic, Zelensky tells West...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60174684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Volodymyr Zelensky says warnings of a Russian invasion are putting the economy at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOYOTA heading to moon with cruiser, robotic arms, dreams...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/space-exploration-technology-science-business-robotics-43addff6ee72bc7cf3b2bfcf9f3ab570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Toyota is working with Japan's space agency on a vehicle to explore the lunar surface, with ambitions to help people live on the moon by 2040 and then go live on Mars, company officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov tells Bette Midler to kiss dog's 'hiney' -- and shows it...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-oddities-bette-midler-west-virginia-joe-manchin-f791d896f56707884d1ad7effbe99ffa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — Gov. Jim Justice has a message for singer and actress Bette Midler, who called West Virginians “poor, illiterate and strung out” in a tweet after Sen. Joe Manchin refused to support President Joe Biden’s Build Back Better Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaun White aims for last snowboarding medal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/winter-olympics/shaun-white-hopes-for-one-final-olympics-he-can-be-shaun-white-again/ar-AATeUCs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant man emoji coming to iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10451689/Apple-adopts-latest-emoji-including-pregnant-MAN.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's own designs for the new emojis are already available in a beta test of iOS 15.4 released on Thursday prior to its full release in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/28/winter-storm-set-to-snarl-northeast-air-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JetBlue cancelled more than 300 flights scheduled for Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'JANET,' star famous for privacy lives up to reputation...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/In-Janet-Jackson-a-star-famous-for-her-privacy-16812895.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the start of the new year, few documentaries were as widely anticipated as "Janet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Le Pen family feud looms ahead of French election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220128-new-le-pen-family-feud-looms-ahead-of-french-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right leader Marine Le Pen spoke of her shock and pain on Friday after her niece suggested she would back a rival in this year's presidential election, in what would be a heavy personal an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Confirms Will Team Up With Russia to Explore Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-confirms-it-will-team-up-with-russia-to-explore-the-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Confirms It Will Team Up With Russia to Explore the Moon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Is Jeffrey Epstein's Money Going?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/28/where-is-jeffrey-epsteins-money-going/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Jeffrey Epstein died, he left behind an estate with an estimated value of $600 million. There were vast financial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightfoot Promised to Change Chicago. Crises Keep Piling Up...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/28/lori-lightfoot-promised-to-change-chicago-crises-keep-piling-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Days into a dispute between Mayor Lori Lightfoot and the Chicago Teachers Union, labor leaders outlined what they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human chain formed to help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-pittsburgh-bridge-collapses-b91476e4d1dc1c7839bd0c39e7be186e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — A two-lane bridge collapsed in Pittsburgh early Friday, prompting rescuers to rappel nearly 150 feet (46 meters) while others formed a human chain to help rescue multiple people from a dangling bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Fed inflation gauge rises 4.9%; Fastest since 1983...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/28/key-fed-inflation-gauge-rises-4point9percent-from-a-year-ago-fastest-gain-since-1983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Specific Blood Proteins Determine Longevity?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/blood-proteins-living-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors identified two proteins that show "significant negative effects across various aging measures."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh bridge collapses on day Biden visits city to talk infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/pittsburgh-bridge-collapses-on-day-biden-to-visit-city-to-talk-infrastructure/ar-AATeX5u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They were fined for breaking rules. They say PM should be punished, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/They-were-fined-for-breaking-U-K-lockdown-rules-16809535.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - After the death of a close friend, Kieron McArdle was struggling, and three...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36" inches Long Island?</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-new-york-snow-storm-weather-20220127-p54i3pruebc2diusfkirbps6ya-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long Island will likely be buried in snow by Saturday and the boroughs could be battered as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Bennett says Netanyahu 'threatened' him over govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220128-israel-s-bennett-says-netanyahu-threatened-him-over-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said his predecessor Benjamin Netanyahu "threatened" him last year when he was fighting to unseat the veteran leader, in an interview published Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks slip as market set to wrap up wild week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/27/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-new.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major averages have experienced outsized intraday swings each day this week as investors continued to digest the Federal Reserve's pivot to tighter policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Boston?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/bostons-blizzard-could-be-biggest-in-january/1132147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston is no stranger to big snowstorms, but Beantown's first blizzard since 2018 could end up being the biggest on record for the month of January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIZZARD '22</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2022-01-27-winter-storm-kenan-east-coast-snowstorm-noreaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strong storm will develop, but some key forecast details are still uncertain. Here's our latest thinking. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge may suspend mustang roundup in Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-environment-and-nature-nevada-reno-horses-9bef18eb567b9a445574a470a596b383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — A federal judge is considering temporarily suspending the capture of wild horses in Nevada where their advocates say the federal government is “needlessly and recklessly” killing free-roaming mustangs in violation of U.S.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
