<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Variant risk to Biden promise of swift comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/delta-variant-poses-major-risk-to-biden-e2-80-99s-promises-of-swift-economic-comeback/ar-AAMlVrZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House had expected the economy to roar in 2021, but the growing number of cases has raised concerns about a setback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly spider venom could help heart attack victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/deadly-spider-e2-80-99s-venom-could-someday-help-heart-attack-victims-australian-scientists-say/ar-AAMlrp0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in Australia, home to some of the most poisonous creatures on Earth, have made a discovery about spider venom that eventually could lead to a new class of drugs to help heart attack victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia man ties bedsheets together to escape 4th floor hotel quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210720074525-vvju0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA-ESCAPE (PIX):Australia man ties bedsheets together to escape 4th floor hotel quarantine - police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yield Plunge Stirs Thoughts of 1% Treasuries...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/long-term-treasury-yields-plunge-134445715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Long-term Treasury rates tumbled to the lowest levels in months on Monday as the spread of the delta coronavirus variant called into question optimistic assumptions about economic recovery, also touching off a global stock market slump.Market-implied expectations for a Federal Reserve rate increase were pushed further into the future amid stronger-than-normal debt-market volumes, and the rally in bonds drove benchmark 10-year yields down as much as 12 basis points to 1.17% on Mond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLION DOLLAR VIEWS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3310172/blue-origins-new-shepard-rocket-bezos-launch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS BLUE Origin’s 60ft New Shepard rocket readies for launch its founder Jeff Bezos has guaranteed those on board will have the best views possible. The capsule – which is entirely autom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH'S RICHEST MAN SET TO LEAVE PLANET!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-magnate-bezos-ready-ride-011406157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealthiest man on the planet Jeff Bezos will ride his own rocket to outer space on Tuesday, a key moment for a fledgling industry seeking to make the final frontier accessible to elite tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mandates make a return -- along with controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mask-mandates-make-a-return-along-with-controversy/ar-AAMkFmO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing calls to reinstate mask mandates have renewed their status as a cultural and health flashpoint a year and a half after the virus landed in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL Menu Hit Hard By Nationwide Shortages Of Ingredients...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/taco-bell-menu-ingredients-shortage-chicken-beef-lettuce-tortillas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chain cites "transportation delays happening throughout most of the industry" as reason why its eateries are out of some items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Employers CAN Fire You for Not Getting Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.worth.com/vaccine-workplace-employers-legal-questions-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.worth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worth sat down with Domenique Camacho Moran, a partner at Farrell Fritz, to discuss the legal questions associated with going back to the office coming off a global pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer creates wedding dress made entirely from dumped face-masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3313195/wedding-dress-made-from-dumped-face-masks/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DESIGNER has created a wedding dress made entirely from dumped face-masks – as all wedding restrictions were lifted. Designer Tom Silverwood stitched together material from 1,500 masks to create …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside BLUE ORIGIN craft where everyone gets window seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3310172/blue-origins-new-shepard-rocket-bezos-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS BLUE Origin’s 60ft New Shepard rocket readies for launch its founder Jeff Bezos has guaranteed those on board will have the best views possible. The capsule – which is entirely autom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems propose requiring women to register for military draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/19/senate-democrats-propose-women-military-drafts-500153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Armed Services Chair Jack Reed has proposed changing draft registration requirements to include all Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat Wave Bakes Rockies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/heat-wave-bakes-the-northern-rockies/ar-AAMjywt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A summer of unrelenting heat in the western United States and Canada hit the Northern Rockies this weekend, where temperatures reached the upper 90s and lower 100s with a heat wave that is expected to peak on Monday but ease only slightly through the week. It was the fourth major heat wave to afflict parts of the West since early June, bringing dangerously hot temperatures and helping fuel the deepening drought and exploding wildfires across the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Firm paid top Biden adviser...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9801185/Israeli-firm-Pegasus-spyware-paid-Biden-adviser-Anita-Dunn-PR-advice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NSO, the private Israeli firm behind the controversial spyware Pegasus, had previously launched a public relations crusade led by Anita Dunn's PR firm SKDKnickerbocker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Washington power brokers gained...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/How-Washington-power-brokers-gained-from-NSO-s-16324343.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli surveillance giant NSO Group and companies linked to it or its founders have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady expected at White House Tuesday...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/weei/sports/patriots/nfl-rumors-tom-brady-will-visit-white-house-tuesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tampa Bay Buccaneers quarterback Tom Brady will attend the White House ceremony on Tuesday when he and his teammates will be honored for their Super Bowl win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peyton, Eli Manning to call ESPN alternative 'Monday Night Football' broadcast...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/19/peyton-manning-eli-manning-to-call-alternative-mnf-for-espn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you ready for some Mannings on Monday Night?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear mauls circus trainer twice in front of horrified crowd...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/19/circus-trainer-mauled-twice-by-bear-in-front-of-crowd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the attack, the circus had promised “an unforgettable large-scale performance with a wide variety of animals” to “surprise every city in Russia.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Drought Could Shutter CA Hydroelectric Power Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93yz73/extreme-drought-could-shut-down-a-hydroelectric-power-plant-in-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change is coming for renewable energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters will decide if Mainers have constitutional right to food...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2021/07/18/voters-will-decide-if-mainers-have-a-constitutional-right-to-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Legislature approved the proposal by a two-thirds margin, but some critics worry that embedding the language in the Maine Constitution could have unintended consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Beds Are Germ-Filled Petri Dish...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/your-bed-germ-filled-petri-dish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the sweat, saliva, dandruff, and dead skins cells people leave behind after a night's sleep is just the tip of the iceberg when it comes to a less-than-cleanly bed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX quietly implemented vax passport while top personalities attack them...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/19/media/fox-vaccine-passport/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson has called the idea of vaccine passports the medical equivalent of "Jim Crow" laws. And other Fox News personalities have spent months both trafficking in anti-vaccine rhetoric and assailing the concept of showing proof of vaccination status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Movement to Raise 'Free Range' Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/life-culture/kids-family/2021/07/12/creator-of-free-range-kids-updates-call-to-give-kids-more-independence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The book and movement that urged parents to give kids some breathing room adds chapters on anxiety and a call to educators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player Comes Out As Gay And Makes NHL History...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/19/1017915128/luke-prokop-becomes-the-first-nhl-player-under-contract-to-come-out-as-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-year-old prospect for the Nashville Predators is the first NHL player, active or retired, to come out. "Living my authentic life will allow me to bring my whole self to the rink," Prokop said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET GOES PSYCHEDELIC...</title>
      <link>https://seekingalpha.com/news/3716128-interest-in-shroom-stocks-rises-as-investors-see-potential-of-psychedelics-as-therapy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;seekingalpha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magic mushrooms, LSD, and MDMA, once thought to be purely recreational drugs, are under investigation by many publicly traded companies as potential psychedelic treatments for a host...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to open border Aug. 9 to fully jabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/19/canada-reopen-border-500158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major unanswered question is how and when the Biden administration will peel back its own measures at the shared border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Border Tax Proposed by Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/carbon-border-tax-is-proposed-by-democrats/ar-AAMkeDY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' Warns FL Boaters Planning Flotilla To Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/19/homeland-security-warning-florida-boaters-trip-cuba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Homeland Security has issued a warning to South Florida boaters planning to take part in a flotilla to Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry writing explosive memoir about royal family life...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/19/prince-harry-writing-an-explosive-memoir-about-royal-family-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry has been secretly writing a memoir for nearly a year, and he’s sold it to Penguin Random House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ declined to prosecute Wilbur Ross...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/19/doj-declined-to-prosecute-wilbur-ross-over-census-citizenship-question-testimony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOJ declined to prosecute Wilbur Ross despite a watchdog finding that he made misrepresentations to Congress about adding a census citizenship questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fish hooked on meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210716-why-fish-are-becoming-addicted-to-illegal-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trout enjoy water that contains methamphetamine – could this lead to them loitering around sewage pipes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Shows on CW Network Pull 0.0 Rating...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/dead-pixels-premiere-ratings-the-cw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CW's "Dead Pixels" Season 2 premiere was dead on arrival. The show returned to The CW last night with a 0.0 rating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google ADMITS employees listen to your conversations without you knowing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3304811/google-admits-recording-converstations-assistant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE allegedly admitted to listening to conversations recorded by Google Assistant even without a user’s “Hey Google” trigger. The tech giant made the admission during a closed-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Rejects Calls to Dial Down UK Isolation App...</title>
      <link>https://businesshala.com/boris-johnson-rejects-calls-to-dial-down-u-k-s-covid-isolation-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businesshala.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Businesshala) - The UK government will not change settings on the COVID-19 mobile phone app, forcing hundreds of thousands of people to isolate at home,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Socialism Boom: Emboldened Leftists Agitate for Radical Change...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywoods-socialism-reboot-1234982568/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chants are beginning in front of the Chateau Marmont. It’s the evening of June 25 and masked protesters are marching on the sidewalk outside the legendary Hollywood hangout, which has bee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK's $1.6 Billion Bid to 'Save Journalism': Secret Deals, Favored Partners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/inside-facebooks-1-6b-bid-to-save-journalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside Facebook's $1.6 billion bid to save journalism: Secret deals, favored partners but few actual details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMASK NYC?</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-councilman-wants-mask-mandate-reinstated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿With COVID-19 cases climbing in all 50 states, New York City Councilman Mark Levine, who chairs the Health Committee, is calling for the indoor mask mandate to be reinstated even for the vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leyna Bloom is SPORTS ILLUSTRATED SWIMSUIT first trans cover star...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/19/leyna-bloom-is-sports-illustrated-swims-first-transgender-cover-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The world is changing and people need to see the fact that, wow, this is the beginning of it,” she told us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti acting PM to step down amid post-assassination leadership dispute...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haitis-acting-prime-minister-step-140646239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti's acting Prime Minister Claude Joseph told the Washington Post on Monday that he will step down from the role, which had seen him serve as de facto leader of Haiti in the wake of President Jovenel Moïse's assassination earlier this month.Why it matters: Joseph's decision to step down, which he said was “for the good of the nation," may resolve the leadership crisis set off by Moïse's death.Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free.Joseph will be succeeded b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is aging disease? Treating it like one could be worth trillions, study says...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/life-culture/2021/07/13/is-aging-a-disease-treating-it-like-one-could-save-us-trillions-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investing in healthy aging — rather than fighting specific diseases — could have an economic value worth trillions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five people shot, including ambulance crew, in AZ attack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/563652-five-people-shot-including-ambulance-crew-in-arizona-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of attacks on paramedics, firefighters and police on Sunday left 5 people shot, several children missing and one person dead in Tucson, Ariz.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA spike hits alarming levels, with 10,000 infected in week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-county-coronavirus-spike-hits-120023795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County coronavirus spike hits alarming levels as the Delta variant hits the unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Levitating' hyperloop will travel 670mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3308608/hyperloop-commuters-cities-minutes-levitation-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HYPERLOOP systems will move as many people as a 30-lane highway between cities in minutes, according to Virgin Hyperloop’s chief. Speaking to Reuters on Monday, Josh Giegel said the upcoming …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tornado' of mosquitos blot out sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3309746/mosquitoes-swarm-in-east-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“TORNADOES” of sex-starved mosquitoes have blotted out the sun in east Russia as they gather for mating season. The swarm is one of the worst yet in the region. Fast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China threatens to nuke Japan if intervenes in Taiwan conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3308916/china-threatens-to-nuke-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA is threatening to NUKE Japan on the eve of the Olympics if it intervenes in conflict with Taiwan, it has been revealed in a new video. The communist republic said that it would declare “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Iran launched stealth missile boat?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/has-iran-launched-a-new-stealthy-missile-boat-674310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Iranian ship is one of several under construction that will be called the Shahed Soleimani class of stealth ships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS REBOUND SPOOKS STOCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/18/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks dropped aggressively on Monday amid concerns about a flare-up in Covid cases slowing economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drag Queens Navigating One of Most Dangerous Culture Wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvz5ed/the-drag-queens-navigating-one-of-europes-most-dangerous-culture-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drag scene in Hungary is popular and vibrant. But animosity whipped up by the nationalist government and a supportive press is taking its toll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths up 25% from two weeks ago; Cases rising in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/07/19/covid-vaccine-variant-mask-restrictions-hospitalizations/8008947002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More experts are calling for vaccinated people to mask up as COVID surges around the country. Live COVID news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branding the left: AOC makes push into political merch...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/branding-us-left-aoc-makes-push-into-political-merchandise-2021-07-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez became one of America's most prominent progressive Democrats with her calls to tax the wealthy and spend heavily to fight climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing buying up American farms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/19/china-buying-us-farms-foreign-purchase-499893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bipartisan pressure is building to stop foreign nationals from purchasing American farm operations and receiving taxpayer subsidies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Kristof Exploring Run for Oregon Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.wweek.com/news/state/2021/07/18/new-york-times-columnist-nicholas-kristof-is-exploring-a-run-for-oregon-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says successfully tested hypersonic missile praised by Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-conducts-ship-based-hypersonic-missile-test-ifax-cites-defence-ministry-2021-07-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia said on Monday it had successfully tested a Tsirkon(Zircon) hypersonic cruise missile, a weapon President Vladimir Putin has touted as part of a new generation of missile systems without equal in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiet and secretive BLUE ORIGIN hopes to start new chapter with flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/quiet-and-secretive-blue-origin-hopes-to-start-new-chapter-with-jeff-bezos-s-space-flight/ar-AAMiims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos has said Blue Origin is "the most important work I am doing." Tuesday, he'll launch to space on the company's New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Agrees With Critics of 'Joyrides'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jeff-bezos-agrees-with-critics-of-billionaire-joyrides-to-space-theyre-largely-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos defended himself from critics who argue that billionaire tycoons would be better off focusing on Earth's problems, rather than traveling to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMORROW: SPACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9796123/Jeff-Bezos-fly-space-TOMORROW-Blue-Origin-New-Shepherd-rocket.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This will be the first human flight launched by Jeff Bezos owned space company, Blue Origin, and will take place out of their spaceport Launch Site One in Van Horn, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador 'House of Horrors' killings shock nation numbed to violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210719094736-vc7av</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL SALVADOR-VIOLENCE/ (PIX):El Salvador 'House of Horrors' killings shock nation numbed to violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive and mysterious, 100-pound fish washes ashore. Scientists hope to learn secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/massive-and-mysterious-a-100-pound-fish-washed-ashore-scientists-hope-to-learn-its-secrets/ar-AAMiDBz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Seaside Aquarium official said the 3½-foot, 100-pound opah is the first she’s seen on local beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US GYMNAST POSITIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9802439/US-womens-gymnast-tests-positive-Covid-training-four-days-Tokyo-opening-ceremony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of the US women's gymnastics team tested positive for the coronavirus while training for the 2021 Olympics in Narita, 35 miles east of Tokyo. She is between the ages of 10 and 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales of Vegan Bacon on Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/as-more-vegan-bacon-brands-hit-the-market-sales-are-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of Vegan Bacon Are On the Rise as More Brands Hit the Market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Challenges Chinese Warship in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/philippines-challenges-chinese-warship-in-south-china-sea-083314946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philippines Coast Guard said it drove away a Chinese warship in the South China Sea, in another sign of tension between the two nations in the disputed waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Allies Blame Chinese Govt for MICROSOFT Hack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/microsoft-exchange-hack-biden-china-d533f5361cbc3374fdea58d3fb059f35</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Monday blamed China for a hack of Microsoft Exchange email server software that compromised tens of thousands of computers around the world earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
