<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SKIPS BIDEN INAUGURATION IN WAR-TORN CAPITAL...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-leaves-white-house-skipping-131813594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump left the White House for the final time on Wednesday, heading by helicopter to a nearby military base where he will fly to Florida, skipping the inauguration of successor Joe Biden in an extraordinary break with tradition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backers getting hit with one-star online reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Some-Trump-backers-are-getting-hit-with-one-star-15883997.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let's say you're in the market for a new pillow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated Amazon villagers tackle with faith potions...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/covid-19-frustrated-amazon-villagers-tackle-virus-faith-potions-13999324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote Amazon village communities, feeling abandoned by the state, are turning to religion and traditional remedies for protection in the COVID-19 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay American couple to be deported after calling Bali 'queer friendly'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gay-us-couple-deported-calling-094828314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gay American couple is being deported from Bali after viral tweets that called the Indonesian resort island "queer friendly".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKIPS BIDEN INAUGURATION IN WAR-TORN CAPITAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-politics-district-of-columbia-coronavirus-pandemic-0a49b6d8b3c9904d88d5bccfd854ab25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Joe Biden's presidential inauguration (all times local): 8:15 a.m. Donald Trump has left the White House for the final time as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese scientists have key to delaying aging?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinese-scientists-may-key-delaying-044936672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in Beijing may be one step closer to having the answer to living longer and reversing the effects of ageing. A group of biologists at the Chinese Academy of Sciences say they have developed a world-first new gene therapy and have been running tests on mice. It involved screening around 10,000 genes in search of particularly strong drivers of cellular ageing. They identified 100 genes in that pool, but the one that really stood out was the kat7. They then inactivated that kat7 gene in the livers of mice, Professor Qu Jing explained some of their findings: "These mice show after six to eight months, they show overall improved appearance and grip strength and most importantly they have extended lifespan for about 25%." Kat7 is one of tens of thousands of genes found in the cells of mammals. The scientists also tested the function of the gene in human stem cells, human liver cells and more. So far there have been no side effects of cellular toxicity. Despite this, the method still has a long way to go from being ready for human trials and will require a lot of funding and much more research. "In the end we do hope that we can find a way to delay ageing even by a very minor percentage we want to delay the human ageing in the future." For now, there's no final answer to cheating death, but the scientists plan on testing the function of kat7 in other cell types of humans and other organs of mice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE UPDATES: INAUGURATION DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/joe-biden-inauguration-2021-01-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and Harris will take the oath of office and assume power at noon, in an inauguration ceremony unlike any in American history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?507998-1/presidential-inauguration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;C-SPAN coverage of the swearing-in ceremonies and related events for the inauguration of Joe Biden as president and Kamala Harris as vice president of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Shortage Puts Americans on Road in Search of Shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/vaccine-shortage-puts-americans-on-the-road-in-search-of-shots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine Shortage Puts Americans on the Road in Search of Shots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel buys $18M estate in Miami...</title>
      <link>http://usa-newsposts.com/2021/01/20/peter-thiel-bought-an-18-million-island-estate-in-miami-that-was-once-featured-on-mtvs-the-real-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;usa-newsposts.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team fears rocky transition may have revealed only 'tip of iceberg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/20/biden-staff-takeover-government-460600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials recognize some of their priorities will be sidelined by the need to fix bureaucratic messes they aren’t even aware of yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Plans Sweeping Executive Orders to Unwind Trump Legacy on Day One...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-plans-sweeping-executive-orders-to-unwind-trump-legacy-on-day-one/ar-BB1cV2jc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President-elect Joe Biden plans to begin immediately unwinding President Donald Trump’s policies on immigration, climate and other issues on Wednesday with at least 15 executive actions, including moves to reverse U.S. withdrawals from the Paris Agreement and the World Health Organization, and stop construction of a border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Dawn of an Era. The Nation is Exhausted...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/19/he-was-just-everywhere-a-tired-country-after-four-years-of-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH — For four years, David Betras has been unable to escape Donald J. Trump. The president has visited Youngstown,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel buys $18M estate in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://buzzwind.com/peter-thiel-bought-18m-miami-estate-featured-on-mtvs-the-real-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buzzwind.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Pardons for Self, Family?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/can-trump-really-issue-secret-pardons-for-himself-and-his-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and his family were not among the 143 11th-hour pardons issued shortly after midnight on Trump's last day in office, leading many to fret that he could still issue secret "po</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revokes 'Swamp-Draining' Lobbying Ban for Former Aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-revokes-ethics-order-barring-former-aides-lobbying-82628c48-c840-4566-833e-c439272b5f6e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He signed the order into law eight days after he took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces tall order in uniting polarized nation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/534922-biden-faces-tall-order-in-uniting-polarized-nation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden, who will take the oath of office on Wednesday as the 46th president in U.S. history, is vowing to succeed where his recent predecessors failed: uniting this fractured country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans voice anguish and hope as Biden prepares to take office...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pre-inaugural-snapshot-americans-voice-011343293.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American presidential inaugurations have often come against the backdrop of momentous events — the Civil War, the Great Depression, the war in Vietnam, the civil rights era. For Biden, the burdens are great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators already have The Don's tax records...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2021/01/20/trump-investigations-legal-inaugeration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Biden's inauguration, Trump faces the prospect of looming investigations into his finances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-capitol-siege-donald-trump-michael-pence-ad718c0048c341d0044c4709fb23c8dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump will walk out of the White House and board Marine One for the last time as president Wednesday morning, leaving behind a legacy of chaos and tumult and a nation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON discussed posing as troops to infiltrate Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/01/19/qanon-adherents-discussed-posing-as-troops-to-infiltrate-inauguration-fbi-briefing-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report, a copy of which was obtained by The Washington Post, did not identify specific plots to attack Wednesday’s inaugural events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON GETS ONE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ap-top-news-pardons-and-commutations-66c82f25134735e742b2501c118723bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is expected to pardon his former chief strategist, Steve Bannon, as part of a flurry of last-minute clemency action that appeared to be still in flux in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasingly militant 'PARLER refugees' and anxious QAnon adherents prep for doomsday...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/internet/increasingly-militant-parler-refugees-anxious-qanon-adherents-prep-doomsday-n1254775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QAnon followers have become more divorced from reality since the Capitol riots as some are targeted by extremists who try to radicalize them further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier Allegedly Conspired to Plot Attacks on 9/11 Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/u-s-soldier-allegedly-conspired-to-plot-attacks-on-9-11-memorial-sources-say/2837595/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. soldier is facing charges he communicated with someone he thought was a member of ISIS to plan attacks on New York City landmarks — including the 9/11 Memorial in Manhattan — and provide tactical military advice to terrorists, federal officials said Tuesday. Cole James Bridges, 20, of Stow, Ohio, is charged with attempted material support for terror and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA approves Iowa airport's virus screenings, possible model for others...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/FAA-approves-Iowa-airport-s-virus-screenings-a-15882921.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airport in Cedar Rapids, Iowa, plans next week to begin screening passengers for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump stock performance falls short of Obama, Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/534881-trump-stock-performance-falls-short-of-obama-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is closing out his time in office with a significant increase in the stock market, but has fallen short of stock gains seen under predecessors former Presidents Obama and Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Wide Web inventor opposes Australia's news payment plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-wide-inventor-opposes-australias-002230464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Wide Web inventor Tim Berners-Lee says Australia's plan to force digital giants to pay media outlets for news content is "unworkable" and undermines a "fundamental principle" of the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE to release new Kamala Harris cover after controversy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vogue-release-kamala-harris-cover-230022576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vogue will publish a limited edition of its latest issue featuring a different photo of Vice-President-elect Kamala Harris after the original cover image sparked controversy, the magazine said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald, supporters will find life different at extreme corners of Web ...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-supporters-will-find-life-different-at-15883004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump will leave the White House on Wednesday as a man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: FOXNEWS Launches 'Purge' to 'Get Rid of Real Journalists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-launches-purge-to-get-rid-of-real-journalists </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says Trump provoked Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mcconnell-trump-fed-lies-to-mob-36871d68df56a10be1c46ed364ad6de6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate Republican leader Mitch McConnell on Tuesday explicitly blamed President Donald Trump for the deadly riot at the Capitol, saying the mob was “fed lies” and that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAREWELL ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/01/19/trump-stresses-economy-foreign-policy-farewell-address-nation/4217614001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump criticized attacks on the U.S. Capitol and touted his economic record in his farewell remarks to Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missteps, Mystery and, in the End, Absence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/19/us/politics/melania-trump-legacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When she leaves Washington on Inauguration Day, Mrs. Trump will be remembered as the first lady who arrived at the White House late and checked out early.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mahomes Remains In Concussion Protocol, Expected To Practice...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/patrick-mahomes-remains-in-concussion-protocol-but-is-reportedly-expected-to-practice-wednesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's still too early to say if Mahomes will play in Sunday's AFC Championship game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commutes sentence of Snoop Dogg pal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/19/trump-commutes-sentence-of-snoop-dogg-pal-michael-harry-o-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday commuted the prison sentence of Death Row Records’ co-founder Michael “Harry O” Harris for attempted murder and cocaine trafficking, a friend who advoca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFUSES government jet to bring to DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9164707/Biden-cries-leaves-Delaware-fsaying-Beau-introducing-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An emotional President-elect Joe Biden said goodbye to his home state of Delaware one day before he's sworn in as the 46th president of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald's snub of predecessor historic in its magnitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/politics/trump-biden-inauguration-snub/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the morning of January 20, Donald Trump and Melania Trump will depart the White House as President and first lady, but they will not invite their incoming counterparts, Joe and Jill Biden, inside before they do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Steak? Lab-Grown Meat With Better Taste,Made-To-Order Marbling...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/perfect-steak-lab-grown-meat-better-taste-made-to-order-marbling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Consumers will be able to buy meat with whatever percentage of fat they like - just like they do with milk," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence to skip sendoff!</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/news/politics-election/mike-pence-wont-attend-trumps-presidential-sendoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Vice President Mike Pence is among those who will not be attending President Donald Trump’s sendoff event at Joint Base Andrews. A person familiar with Pence’s schedule cited “logistical challenges” in getting from the air base to President-elect Joe Biden’s inauguration ceremonies on Wednesday. The person spoke on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossil reveals how dinosaurs peed, pooped and had sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/19/world/dinosaur-fossil-sex-study-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know a lot about dinosaurs -- what they looked like, what they ate and what killed them off -- but no fossils have definitively preserved two dinosaurs in the act of mating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: FOXNEWS Launches 'Purge' to 'Get Rid of Real Journalists'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/fox-news-launches-purge-rid-211350787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Photos GettyFox News on Tuesday fired the political editor who was tasked with defending the network’s election night decisions that especially angered President Donald Trump and his allies.Politics editor Chris Stirewalt’s exit from the network coincided with the sacking of at least 16 digital editorial staffers, including senior editors. People familiar with the situation said the layoffs—a “blood bath,” as multiple Fox News insiders described it—were perpetrated by Porter Berry, the Sean Hannity crony now in charge of remaking Fox’s digital properties in the image of its right-wing opinion programming.In addition to Stirewalt—the Fox News “nerd” responsible for the accurate election-night projection for Joe Biden to win Arizona, which angered much of the network’s MAGA viewership and led to the rise of an even more obsequious, pro-Trump alternative in Newsmax—sources confirmed that long-time digital editors and reporters, some of whom had been with Fox for a decade or more, were among those laid off.“Fuck this,” one particularly despondent current Fox News staffer remarked to The Daily Beast.Officially, the network claimed the layoffs are merely part of a “restructuring” initiative. “As we conclude the 2020 election cycle, Fox News Digital has realigned its business and reporting structure to meet the demands of this new era,” a spokesperson said in a statement. “We are confident these changes will ensure the platform continues to deliver breakthrough reporting and insightful analysis surrounding major issues, both stateside and abroad.”But a dozen current and recently departed Fox News employees who spoke with The Daily Beast all said the “purge”—as a few characterized it—was part of the network’s larger effort to pivot its website from straight-news reporting to right-wing opinion content in the mold of Fox’s primetime programming.“There is a concerted effort to get rid of real journalists,” said one recently departed Fox staffer. “They laid capable people off who were actual journalists and not blind followers.”Others said it was an attempt to silence leakers from speaking to outside media about the changes being instituted by Porter Berry, a former producer for Hannity and Bill O’Reilly, who recently transitioned from the TV side to running Fox’s digital properties.“Porter’s uncomfortable around and is suspicious of experienced editors,” one Fox News insider remarked to The Daily Beast. “They make him feel inept because his background is entirely in TV.”“Porter is at the helm,” declared one current employee of the layoffs, while a recently departed staffer said: “This is all Porter. Both an ideological purge and a purge of people he was threatened by.”Even before this round of layoffs, Berry’s management and editorial style had resulted in the departures of several key employees, such as Jason Ehrich, former executive vice president of audience development and strategic partnerships, and Greg Wilson, the former managing editor of the Fox News website, among others.As The Daily Beast reported, Berry’s influence over the network’s online properties has raised eyebrows among staffers, largely because he continues to act as a “shadow executive producer” for Hannity—yet another sign of the increasingly blurred lines at Fox between the network’s right-wing opinion commentary and its so-called news division.The ouster of Stirewalt came months after he oversaw the Fox decision desk’s early (and accurate) election-night projection of Joe Biden winning Arizona’s votes. The on-air call immediately infuriated President Donald Trump, as such a projection by his then-favorite network inhibited his plans to prematurely declare victory that evening. “Jared, you call the Murdochs! Jason, you call Sammon and Hemmer!” Axios reported Trump shouting that night at his son-in-law Jared Kushner and top adviser Jason Miller.Immediately following the Arizona call, which has been linked to angry Trump fans abandoning the network for even more fact-free, right-wing outlets like Newsmax, Stirewalt was repeatedly grilled on-air over the projection and asked whether his team would reverse its call. “Not that I see,” Stirewalt said, standing by decision desk director Arnon Mishkin’s analysis.While the network’s pro-Trump opinion hosts openly undermined the decision desk and political team’s Arizona call, parroting the Trump campaign’s complaints, Stirewalt refused to reverse course while also throwing cold water on the president’s bogus claims of widespread voter fraud.“Lawsuits, schmawsuits,” he said the day after the election. “We haven’t seen any evidence yet that there’s anything wrong.”Though the network never backed off its Arizona call, and followed other major news outlets in calling the entire election for Biden days later, Stirewalt soon apparently found himself on the outs at Fox News.Despite having been a regular on-air presence for years—including playing a pivotal role in the Fox’s 2012 election night drama in which he was forced to go on-air to defend effectively calling the election for Barack Obama—Stirewalt did not make a single network appearance after November 16.Stirewalt’s final contribution for Fox News was a Monday afternoon digital post, titled “Put that in your Hot Pocket.”—Maxwell Tani, Justin Baragona, and Andrew Kirell contributed additional reporting. Diana Falzone was an on-camera and digital reporter for FoxNews.com from 2012 to 2018. In May 2017, she filed a gender discrimination and disability lawsuit against the network and settled, and left the company in March 2018.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monarch butterfly population moves closer to extinction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/insects-immigration-butterflies-california-d74874fe777b57edce510b0e716b6f34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The number of western monarch butterflies wintering along the California coast has plummeted precipitously to a record low, putting the orange-and-black insects closer to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawley to delay swift confirmation of 'Homeland' pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/19/alejandro-mayorkas-confirmation-hearing-460256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Missouri Republican will object to swift consideration of Alejandro Mayorkas' nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Scientist Charged With Secretly Working For Tehran...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/01/19/kaveh-lotfolah-afrasiabi-iran-arrest-watertown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A political scientist and author from Watertown is accused of secretly working for the Iranian government while here in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: IRS may have paid $57 million in error for Trump tax break...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/19/irs-may-have-given-millions-in-error-for-20percent-qbi-tax-deduction-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials may have granted a 20% QBI — or "pass through" — tax deduction in error to nearly 13,000 business owners, according to an IRS watchdog report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Kraken' back on its leash: GA lawsuit withdrawn...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/election/kraken-back-on-its-leash-georgia-lawsuit-withdrawn/4TMB45RUBVDPVFMF7M2OMJ2UCQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The â€œkrakenâ€� is back on its leash and licking its wounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Talked out of pardoning kids, Republican lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/19/politics/trump-self-pardon-warning/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump received an unsettling warning on his final Saturday night in the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President-elect tears up during emotional farewell speech in DE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/19/joe-biden-tears-up-as-he-delivers-farewell-speech-in-delaware/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden became teary-eyed on Tuesday afternoon as he delivered a speech thanking his staff and honoring his late son Beau Biden, saying it should have been Beau who was about to be sworn in as th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big plans, big problems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-philadelphia-aa7d5101f28c4792ccd4752795d0b968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — It's hardly the grand entrance Joe Biden might have dreamed of. The president-elect is arriving in the nation's capital Tuesday, ready to assume power as the nation reels...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 mayors pushing for guaranteed income...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/19/the-mayors-piloting-guaranteed-income-programs-across-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayors across the country are giving out thousands of dollars in guaranteed income pilot programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Fauci says PFIZER first dose less effective than indicated...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/19/nachman-ash-says-pfizers-first-dose-less-effective-than-indicated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single dose of Pfizer’s vaccine may be less effective than the drugmaker had indicated, Israel’s COVID-19 czar has warned. Nachman Ash — Israel’s equivalent of Dr. Anthony…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK sees record deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210119-uk-sees-record-deaths-as-virus-variants-deepen-global-concern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK sees record deaths as virus variants deepen global concern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders more Ghislaine records released -- minus salacious details...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article248600605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Tuesday ordered the unsealing and release of dozens of documents in a now-settled civil suit involving Ghislaine Maxwell, the jailed and accused co-conspirator of the sex offender Jeffrey Epstein, but afforded the longtime Epstein associate a measure of privacy by ruling that salacious portions of testimony about her sex life swill remain private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAND FINALE:  100 PARDONS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-capitol-siege-politics-84f1a283e988dc8c231d064c9cba08eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump was expected to spend his last full day in office issuing a flurry of pardons and bidding farewell to the American public from a near-deserted White House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAKE:  What Biden era feels like six months in...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/01/19/america-six-months-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stolid daily rhythms of the new presidency have been established, and governing has assumed the assured — and reassuring — calm and dignity befitting the world’s indispensable nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mob Was Fed Lies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/mitch-mcconnell-blames-trump-for-insurrection-the-mob-was-fed-lies-provoked-by-the-president-and-other-powerful-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitch McConnell blamed President Trump's "lies" for provoking the mob of Trump supporters that engaged in a deadly insurrection on the capital building last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Melania leaving office as least popular first lady ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/19/politics/melania-trump-analysis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much has been written about President Donald Trump's historically low popularity ratings as he leaves office. But the tarnish on the Trump brand goes beyond the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says Trump provoked Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mcconnell-capitol-riots-trump-impeachment-7129d841-f306-4f3a-8f58-3b97f05670c5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McConnell has not yet signaled how he will vote in Trump's impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of millions stick by him...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lowest-moment-trumps-presidency-tens-100050172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the U.S. Capitol insurrection, President Trump has suffered greater losses in support than ever before. Still, his popularity among his base is unwavering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebration of democracy clouded by fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/celebration-democracy-clouded-fear-140059295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Normally, presidential inaugurations are a constitutional Mardi Gras, but deadly threats have left the nation's capital in a state of suspicion and anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand sold itself as a paradise covid retreat. No one came...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/lifestyle/destination-of-the-week/thailand-sold-itself-as-a-paradise-covid-retreat-no-one-came-7151362/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of interest is adding pressure on Thai policy makers, who have struggled to accommodate both industry players calling for relaxed quarantine rules and public-health experts warning against putting people in danger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Morning Joe' Warns About Future Revolts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-stupidity-morning-joe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American democracy remains threatened if social media sites remain unchecked, Joe Scarborough says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gets 43-Year Prison Sentence For Insulting Thai King...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/woman-43-year-prison-sentence-insulting-thailand-monarchy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former civil servant posted audio clips to Facebook and YouTube with comments deemed critical of the monarchy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell, McCarthy skip sendoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-leaders-biden-church-skip-trump-departure-75c20557-3968-4815-8f0c-e6d1ff46704e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They'll instead attend a Catholic service with Presdient-elect Biden at 8:45am.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing 2 Masks  Better Than 1; BUT 3 MAY GO TOO FAR...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/01/19/doubling-up-face-masks-creates-obstacle-course-covid-colorado-doctor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wearing a mask provides protection against COVID-19 both for the person wearing the mask and those around them. Now we're hearing wearing two masks may offer even more protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  US B-52 nuke bombers fly over Middle East as Iran stages massive war games...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2166652/american-b52-bomber-middle-east-iran-crush-aggressors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has promised to “crush its aggressors” after US B-52H Stratofortress bombers flew over the Middle East in a show of military strength. The “presence patrol” mission too…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How First Day of Presidency Foreshadowed The Years to Come...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/01/19/trump-2017-inauguration-presidency-460248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Behind the scenes at the last inauguration—as remembered by the Obama and Trump aides who were there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALM BEACH ANGST</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-mar-a-lago-neighbors-palm-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's neighbors recently sent a letter to town leaders, citing a 1993 agreement they say prohibits anyone from living permanently on the property because it is a social club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  LOWEST RATED PRESIDENCY</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/328637/last-trump-job-approval-average-record-low.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's last job approval rating is a personal low 34%. He averaged 41% job approval in office, a record low by four points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin marks Orthodox Epiphany with icy dip...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210119144500-nptfp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RELIGION-EPIPHANY/PUTIN (PIX, TV):Russia's Putin marks Orthodox Epiphany with icy dip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves White House as he came in: Isolated and unpredictable...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article248535105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his final days in office, Donald Trump found friends and political allies in short supply following the deadly Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next TESLA? Investors Bet Big on RIVIAN...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/19/rivian-has-been-a-tortoise-to-teslas-hare-can-it-catch-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLYMOUTH, Mich. — It’s hard to imagine any company matching Tesla’s rocket-like rise. But if any electric car start-up could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, GOP leaders will attend church before inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-gop-leaders-will-attend-church-before-inauguration/ar-BB1cTrsx?ocid=Peregrine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President-elect Joe Biden has invited top Republican and Democratic congressional leaders to a bipartisan prayer session at church early Wednesday hours before his inauguration, people familiar with the plans said. "Yes I can confirm" that top Senate Republican Mitch McConnell will join Biden, who was a longtime colleague in the US Senate, at the church, a person knowledgeable of McConnell's plans told AFP Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON discussed posing as troops to infiltrate National Guard...</title>
      <link>ttps://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/01/19/qanon-adherents-discussed-posing-as-troops-to-infiltrate-inauguration-fbi-briefing-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Hottest Housing Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.zillow.com/research/zillow-hottest-markets-2021-28667/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zillow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austin and a lineup of sunny, affordable metro areas are most likely to outperform the nation in home value growth in 2021, according to experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence 'man without a home'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/01/19/mike-pences-future-chances-running-president-hurt-trump/6640990002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After four years of steadfast loyalty to Trump, Pence is said to be open to a 2024 run, but his rift with the president may close off that option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revving up electric car industry, firm develops 5-min-charge battery...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/revving-up-electric-car-industry-israeli-firm-develops-5-minute-charge-battery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herzliya-based startup StoreDot unveils solution for main obstacle to widespread use of electric vehicles, but it requires major upgrades to charging stations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to hold Covid rule breakers in refugee camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13773701/germany-covid-rule-breakers-refugee-camps-mutant-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY’S worst Covid rule breakers will be held in detention centres under new proposals being drawn up by a number of state governments. The move forms part of the country’s efforts t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Was Fired From TACO BELL for Being in Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lonna-wells-was-fired-from-taco-bell-for-being-in-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her sex work on pause during the pandemic, Lonna Wells was earning money for her family at Taco Bell. But she was fired when a customer complained. Now she’s speaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Bracing for Dangerous Times...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/01/how-secret-service-plans-protect-joe-biden-now/617726/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any chance of a normal security environment for the president-elect evaporated during the Capitol siege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 HOURS</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-era-s-battles-over-truth-will-outlast-his-15879674.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump stands as a singular figure in American history for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to propose major immigration legislation this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-to-propose-major-immigration-legislation-15880225.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President-elect Joe Biden propose major changes to the nation's immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican support for convicting Trump in Senate growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/19/republican-support-convicting-trump-growing-460247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 20 percent of Republicans said they “strongly” or “somewhat” approved of a Senate conviction in the latest poll, conducted between Jan. 15-17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon deploys hundreds of active-duty soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/18/pentagon-deploys-troops-inauguration-security-460203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personnel will support enhanced security measures related to the event, as local law enforcement continues to track threats of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds file conspiracy charge against Oath Keeper leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-files-conspiracy-charge-against-oath-keeper-leader-in-alleged-plot-against-the-capitol/ar-BB1cT81o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI says Thomas Caldwell of Virginia scouted lodging and recruited self-styled militia members before “storming the castle.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many paths ahead for ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/citizen-trump-the-many-paths-ahead-for-the-ex-president/ar-BB1cR7gW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump leaves the White House as the most controversial president in modern history. So what now?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FOR SELF, FAMILY?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/breaking-trump-reportedly-will-not-pardon-himself-or-his-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is set to issue a slew of pardons in the final hours of his term. But none, reportedly, will go to his family. And he will not pardon himself either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Going to Church with Biden Ahead of Inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/just-in-mitch-mcconnell-going-to-church-with-joe-biden-ahead-of-inauguration-at-bidens-invitation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has learned that Joe Biden's outreach to Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell will begin with the two of them attending church before inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast, Trailed by Pandemic, Joblessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/trump-leaves-town-an-outcast-trailed-by-covid-19-pandemic-joblessness-101611047742915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last president who chose not to attend his successor’s inauguration was Andrew Johnson in 1869, another impeached leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof vests and gas masks: Journalists prep...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/media/journalists-inauguration-preparation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of December, Los Angeles Times Washington Bureau Chief Kimbriell Kelly was looking at getting Moleskine notebooks as gifts for her staff. A couple weeks later, she was procuring goods of a decidedly different kind: gas masks, helmets and body armor for LA Times staff members who will be attending Wednesday's inauguration of President-elect Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St has new top cop. And Elizabeth Warren is big fan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/economy/biden-wall-street-gensler-sec-elizabeth-warren/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new sheriff is coming to Wall Street -- and, for a change, he's not a friendly face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAND FINALE:  100 PARDONS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/17/politics/trump-pardons-expected/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is preparing to issue around 100 pardons and commutations on his final full day in office Tuesday, according to three people familiar with the matter, a major batch of clemency actions that includes white collar criminals, high-profile rappers and others but -- as of now -- is not expected to include Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie mural defaced in DC; Cops investigating as hate crime...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/01/bernie-sanders-mural-defaced-in-dc-police-investigating-as-hate-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mural of Independent Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders was defaced near Navy Yard in Southeast D.C., and it’s being investigated as a hate crime, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused of trying to sell Pelosi laptop to Russians arrested...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/534727-woman-accused-of-trying-to-sell-pelosi-laptop-to-russians-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who the FBI says took a laptop belonging to Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) during the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol and tried to sell it to Russians has been arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  Give me something. Give me hope. Give me Xanax...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/topic/trumpism-toxic-debate-matt-labash-chris-buskirk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if I told you I disliked the ‘uniparty’ and Trump? In the binary world that is Trumpism (us vs them typifies all cults), it’s impossible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemalan security forces break up US-bound migrant caravan ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guatemalan-security-forces-break-us-194807999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guatemalan security forces on Monday broke up a caravan of some 4,000 Honduran migrants trying to reach the United States on a journey of thousands of kilometers through Central America on foot, AFP reporters witnessed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An inauguration like no other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-concerns-razor-wire-no-014358732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With war-zone-like security, no crowds and coronavirus distancing for guests, Joe Biden's swearing-in as the 46th US president will be a muted affair unlike any previous inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cinderella story for a dog': Joe's shelter pet gives adoption trend boost...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cinderella-story-dog-bidens-shelter-130045525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major, a German shepherd, will become the first White House shelter dog. The pandemic has fueled pet adoptions, "one of the few silver linings to COVID," one animal rescue official says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Field of Flags'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-inaugurated-amid-high-security-052251407.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers for President-elect Joe Biden's inauguration on Wednesday finished setting up about 200,000 flags on Monday, representing the American people who cannot travel to the inauguration amid a worsening coronavirus pandemic and extraordinary security precautions. The flags represent all of the states and U.S. territories, and they also are meant to honor the 400,000 Americans who will have officially died from COVID-19 by the time Biden is sworn in.Embed from Getty ImagesEmbed from Getty ImagesEmbed from Getty ImagesThe Presidential Inaugural Committee highlighted the "Field of Flags" on Monday night, with 56 pillars of light — one for each of the 50 states and six U.S. territories — beamed into the air for 46 second, a reference to Biden becoming the 46th U.S. president.Embed from Getty ImagesBiden arrives in Washington for his inauguration on Tuesday, and he and incoming first lady Jill Biden will spend Tuesday night at Blair House, near the White House. Outgoing President Trump plans to leave the White House on Wednesday morning, making him the first president since Andrew Johnson — the first impeached president — to skip the inauguration of his successor. Trump has made no public appearances in six days.Biden and Vice President-elect Kamala Harris, who resigned as a U.S. senator on Monday, volunteered in service events to honor Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. on Monday. They will take part in a memorial at the reflecting pool near the Lincoln Memorial on Tuesday to honor the Americans who lost their lives to COVID-19.More stories from theweek.com 5 more scathing cartoons about Trump's 2nd impeachment Melania Trump released a farewell video. So did Colbert's Late Show Melania Trump. Stephen Colbert has theories about Trump's conspiratorial 'pillow talk' with MyPillow's Mike Lindell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After allergic reactions, CA pauses use of MODERNA doses...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/after-allergic-reactions-at-1-clinic-california-pauses-use-of-more-than-330k-doses-of-moderna-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After several people had apparent allergic reactions at one California clinic, state health officials on Sunday told providers across the state to pause administering doses from one COVID-19 vaccin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army working on Frankenbots with living tissue...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/defense-main/2021/01/army-is-working-on-frankenbots-with-living-tissue-to-better-robot-capabilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robots may have better stability and flexibility by taking advantage of living muscles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cremation limits lifted in LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/health/as-bodies-pile-up-cremation-limits-lifted-in-los-angeles-county/9762002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death rate during the COVID-19 pandemic is so high in LA County that officials are lifting environmental limits on cremations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police recover 500-year-old stolen copy of da Vinci's 'MUNDI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/salvator-mundi-leonardo-da-vinci-copy-found/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under concussion protocols, decision on Mahomes' status out of CHIEFS' hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Under-NFL-s-concussion-protocols-decision-on-15881157.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major betting implications...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/19/patrick-mahomes-mystery-has-major-nfl-betting-implications/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
