<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>It used to feel that life hung in balance during US-Russia summits. No longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/jun/17/us-russia-summit-china-biden-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of China puts any decisions made at Biden’s meeting with Putin into perspective, says Guardian columnist Martin Kettle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE INCREASES TO DROP MASK MANDATE ON PLANES...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/06/17/senators-running-out-of-patience-on-mask-mandate-for-travelers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican senators expressed mounting impatience with the federal mask mandate for travelers as restrictions are lifted elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTORIA'S SECRET ditches supermodels and replaces them with 'diverse high-achievers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3101328/victorias-secret-megan-rapinoe-priyanka-chopra-catwalk-angels-models/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICTORIA’S Secret has announced it is ditching its “Angels” supermodels to redefine sexy with “diverse high-achievers” like Megan Rapinoe. The lingerie brand announced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook claims GOOGLE Android system littered with bad, dangerous software...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3102068/android-worse-dangerous-iphone-apple-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE boss Tim Cook has made a subtle dig at Google, claiming that the firm’s Android operating system is littered with dodgy software. In an interview yesterday, the 60-year-old said that An…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines pressure for less restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/fully-vaccinated-people-uk-could-be-allowed-travel-amber-list-countries-the-2021-06-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain is considering easing travel rules for double vaccinated people, a move that would placate airlines which have launched legal action against the government's curbs on trips abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-heatwave peaking in West, breaking records and intensifying drought, fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/mega-heat-wave-is-peaking-in-the-west-breaking-records-and-intensifying-drought-fires/ar-AAL9n9s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change has made the situation worse, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City to use sirens to start nightly curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlantic-city-to-use-sirens-mark-10-pm-juvenile-curfew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens soon will sound each night in Atlantic City at 10 p.m., marking the arrival of a juvenile curfew prohibiting those under 18 from being on the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Juneteenth, Federal Employees Now Get 44 Paid Days Off Each Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/06/17/with-juneteenth-federal-employees-now-get-44-paid-days-off-on-average/?sh=2acdecf83477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This makes 44 paid days off for the average federal employee annually, which is nearly nine full weeks of paid-time off each year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK infections climb to highest since Feb...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/uk-coronavirus-infections-4-month-high-34d7d30b-8120-409a-ba96-e4999623ef93.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta variant continues to spread across the U.K. and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-2 DECISION</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-spares-obamacare-gop-challenge-n1271140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of Trump's three appointees, Brett Kavanaugh and Amy Coney Barrett, joined the majority opinion, while the third, Neil Gorsuch, dissented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Secretly Harboring Top China Official?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rumors-of-u-s-secretly-harboring-top-china-official-swirl/ar-AAL9Tb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese-language anti-communist media and Twitter are abuzz this week with rumors that a vice minister of State Security, Dong Jingwei defected in mid-February, flying from Hong Kong to the United States with his daughter, Dong Yang. Dong Jingwei supposedly gave the U.S. information about the Wuhan Institute of Virology that changed the stance of the Biden Administration concerning the origins of the COVID-19 pandemic. Dong is, or was, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing launches astronauts to new space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-launches-first-astronauts-to-its-new-space-station-as-race-with-us-heats-up/ar-AAL8h0w </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES KEEP OBAMACARE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/17/obamacare-survives-after-supreme-court-rejects-latest-republican-challenge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court ruled against Texas and other Republican-led states seeking to strike down the Affordable Care Act in its latest high court test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcia could be first cigarette-smoking winner since '65...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/17/kathryn-garcia-could-be-first-cigarette-smoking-nyc-mayor-since-65/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Sanitation Commissioner and mayoral candidate Kathryn Garcia could be City Hall’s first smoker-in-residence since Mayor Robert Wagner left office in 1965.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEARS Eyeing Move Out Of Chicago?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/bears-eyeing-possible-move-out-of-downtown-chicago-to-suburb-that-sits-35-miles-away-from-soldier-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bears could be leaving Soldier Field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza after Hamas fires incendiary balloons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/west-bank-israel-middle-east-health-3619c2694df63cc92bdec9cce2e69493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel launched airstrikes on the Gaza Strip late Thursday for a second time since a shaky cease-fire ended last month's 11-day war. The strikes came after activists mobilized by Gaza's militant Hamas rulers launched incendiary balloons into Israel for a third straight day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis gun-waving couple plead guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/st-louis-gun-waving-couple-plead-guilty-to-misdemeanor-charges/article_5b02e25b-0034-58a3-8181-f0a724ffa323.html#tracking-source=home-top-story-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark McCloskey on Thursday pleaded guilty to fourth-degree assault. Patricia McCloskey pleaded to second-degree harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists still puzzling over deaths of DC birds...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2021/06/scientists-still-puzzling-over-deaths-of-birds-in-dc-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ornithologist at the Smithsonian said that experts are still trying to figure out what’s behind a “mortality event” that’s been plaguing birds in the D.C. area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MSNBC WON'T RECOGNIZE NEW UNION...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/559028-msnbc-says-it-wont-voluntarily-recognize-new-union-effort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 200-plus MSNBC workers are forming a union, but the network, known for its progressive politics, said it won’t recognize the effort until a majority of workers vote in a secret ballot election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops resign en masse from Portland crowd control unit...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2021/06/officers-sergeants-with-portlands-rapid-response-team-resign-from-the-specialized-crowd-control-unit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers who serve on the Portland Police Bureau’s specialized crowd control unit, known as the Rapid Response Team, voted to resign from the team during a meeting Wednesday night, a police lieutenant and the mayor's office confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUND:  New fossils of largest land mammals ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/new-fossils-giant-rhinos-largest-land-mammals-ever-are-found-china-rcna1213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fossils from two giant rhinos dating back about 22 million years have been unearthed in China, according to a study published Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Campaign Trail With Andrew Giuliani...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/andrew-giuliani-new-york-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Son of Rudy is working out his father issues on the road to Albany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian ships once believed to be headed toward Venezuela change course...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/17/iran-ships-venezuela-495013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People familiar with the matter believe diplomatic efforts may have made a difference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform could soon track troops' body signals -- and tell if sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/06/17/your-uniform-could-soon-track-your-bodys-signals-and-tell-you-if-youre-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who collected hospital's bodies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wasnt-just-anyone-collected-bodies-120029485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man collecting the Loma Linda hospital's COVID victims was all but invisible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race-Based Bailouts In Stimulus Face Legal Setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/courts/race-based-bailouts-in-covid-stimulus-bill-face-legal-setbacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative legal groups are challenging the racially driven repayment programs Democrats included in their $1.9 trillion coronavirus relief act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Death Valley Hits 129 Degrees -- 6 Shy Of Record!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/17/death-valley-national-park-129-degrees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death Valley National Park officials have been warning visitors that daytime highs could reach 128 degrees at some point during this week’s heat wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian regions make jabs mandatory for many...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-coronavirus-pandemic-business-government-and-politics-d426c8260fb7a69e51bf84a4ad4c54f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Authorities in four Russian regions have made coronavirus vaccines mandatory this week for workers in retail, education and other service sectors, part of an effort to boost the country's low immunization rates as COVID-19 infections continue to soar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver charged in deadly crash reportedly was having sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Driver-charged-in-deadly-crash-reportedly-was-16253836.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — A man charged with barreling his pickup truck into a San Jose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis offers Florida police to help Texas, Arizona enforce border?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article252170028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis said Wednesday that Florida law-enforcement officers will go to Texas and Arizona to help with border control, as Florida continues to challenge the Biden administration in federal court about immigration enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran mansion sells for record $43.5M!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mansion-in-pacific-heights-sets-record-for-most-expensive-house-sold-in-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11,000-square-foot home was built in 1931, by the heirs to the Hills Bros. Coffee fortune, and has stunning views of the bay and the Golden Gate Bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Audio of Sen. Manchin Provides Rare Glimpse of Dealmaking...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/06/16/joe-manchin-leaked-billionaire-donors-no-labels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manchin urged big-money donors with No Labels to talk to Sen. Roy Blunt about flipping his vote on the commission in order to save the filibuster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Furor rages over FDA approval of controversial Alzheimer's drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/furor-rages-over-fda-approval-of-controversial-alzheimer-e2-80-99s-drug/ar-AAL8Ybg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For days, critics have blasted the approval in opinion columns and tweets, saying there is insufficient evidence of efficacy. Supporters have expressed confidence the drug, Aduhelm, will help patients stay in the earliest stages of the disease longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin lavishes post-summit praise on Biden, says media have U.S. leader wrong...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210617125641-bev96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/PUTIN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Putin lavishes post-summit praise on Biden, says media have U.S. leader wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill to Treat Covid? USA Betting on It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/17/a-pill-to-treat-covid-19-the-u-s-is-betting-on-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government will invest $3.2 billion to develop antiviral pills for Covid-19, the Department of Health and Human Services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opioids rip through workforce, with deaths at record level...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2021/06/17/opioids-rip-through-u-s-workforce-with-deaths-at-record-level/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opioids are behind about three-fourths of the overdoses, according to Wednesday’s data from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In mental health crises, 911 call brings mixed team of helpers -- maybe no cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/in-mental-health-crises-a-911-call-now-brings-a-mixed-team-of-helpers-and-maybe-no-cops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More communities are creating teams of health care providers to respond to mental health crises instead of cops, a shift propelled by nationwide demonstrations against police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admits on FOXNEWS: 'We didn't win' election...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article252177178.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I want this guy to go out and do well for our country,” Trump said of Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose mandates videotaping of all gun purchases...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/city-of-san-jose-mandates-videotaping-of-all-gun-purchases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose officials have passed a new gun law that requires retailers to video-record all firearm purchases, becoming the largest city in California with such a rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules for Catholic group in LGBT rights dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/17/supreme-court-sides-with-catholic-adoption-agency-that-refuses-to-work-with-lgbt-couples.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging process unstoppable, finds unprecedented study...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/17/ageing-process-is-irreversible-finds-unprecedented-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research suggests humans cannot slow the rate at which they get older because of biological constraints</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cotton plantations, non-consensual kisses: DISNEY embroiled in culture wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/jun/16/how-disney-became-embroiled-in-the-culture-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has been addressing its historical racism and sexism, adding disclaimers to films and altering theme park rides. But these moves have stirred contempt as well as approval</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film Argues Whitey Bulger Was Victim of FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-new-film-argues-notorious-gangster-whitey-bulger-was-a-victim-of-the-fbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though he was found to be involved in *at least* 11 murders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenes From NYC's Surreal, Unpredictable Mayor Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/17/new-york-mayoral-race-democratic-candidates-photoes-494422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photographs from the final stretch of a surreal race to lead the country’s biggest city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In secret recording, Florida Republican threatens to send Russian-Ukrainian 'hit squad' after rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/17/secret-recording-florida-republican-threat-hit-squad-494976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I really don't want to have to end anybody's life for the good of the people of the United States of America. ... But if it needs to be done, it needs to be done," William Braddock says in the clip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half millennials wish had chosen different career path...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/17/nearly-half-of-older-millennials-wish-theyd-chosen-a-different-career.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older millennials across the country share what they'd do differently in their career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit says PORNHUB profited from videos posted without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pornhub-lawsuit-nonconsensual-videos-child-abuse-imagery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An underage girl's private video for her high school boyfriend. A woman's alleged rape while drugged by her husband. The lawsuit alleges Pornhub exploited nonconsensual video uploads — including child abuse imagery — for profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women between 18 and 50 should NOT drink AT ALL?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15298698/women-childbearing-age-not-drink-who/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD Health Organisation bosses want to ban half of women from drinking. They suggest no booze for those of “childbearing age”. The barmy diktat means any woman aged between 18 and their early 50s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 1 In 4 Couples Opt To Never Have Children -- Just As Happy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/quarter-of-adults-child-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite this growing trend towards "child-free" relationships, researchers find these couples are just as happy as those who have children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Cuban 'Hit' by Titan Crypto Crash As Coin's Price Falls to Near Zero...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mark-cuban-hit-titan-crypto-crash-price-near-zero-1601481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The token, linked to the Iron Finance stablecoin project, plummeted on Wednesday in what one investor said was a panic sell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: What Happened When 3,000-Person Village in El Salvador Became 'Bitcoin Beach'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/what-happened-when-a-3000-person-village-in-el-salvador-became-e2-80-9cbitcoin-beach-e2-80-9d/ar-AAL7dqR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador's president says the village of El Zonte shows Bitcoin as legal tender can work. The truth is more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking numbers behind Lake Mead drought crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/17/us/lake-mead-drought-water-shortage-climate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lake Mead reservoir is poised to become the focal point of one of the country's most significant climate crises: water shortages in the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON asks social media platforms to help curb fake reviews...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/558893-amazon-asks-social-media-platforms-to-help-curb-fake-reviews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon on Wednesday asked social media companies to help it tackle fake product reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrutiny mounts on MICROSOFT surveillance tech...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/558890-exclusive-scrutiny-mounts-on-microsofts-surveillance-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft is facing new pressure from investors over its development and sale of surveillance technologies to law enforcement and its efforts to shape the policies regulating their deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Wolff book on Trump's last days as president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-michael-wolff-business-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-103209c1e8888ab585c3a64a6eb9731b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The author of “Fire and Fury,” the million-seller from 2018  that helped launched the wave of inside accounts of the Trump White House, will have a last take coming out next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Jumps Into Lake, Saves Fawn From Drowning! Deer Returns Next Morning To 'Thank'...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/goldendoodle-rescues-fawn-from-drowning-in-virginia-lake-67712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Not sure how the fawn got out there but Harley obviously didn't ask why, he just jumped into action," said Ralph Dorn, 62, of Culpeper, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadal pulls out of Wimbledon and Tokyo Olympics; Pressure on body...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/17/tennis/rafael-nadal-withdraws-from-wimbledon-and-tokyo-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rafael Nadal has announced he is pulling out of Wimbledon and the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cloud of dust sweeps across Atlantic, heads toward USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/massive-cloud-saharan-dust-sweeps-over-atlantic-toward-us/963897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's "dust season," according to an AccuWeather hurricane expert, and even though a repeat of last year's "Godzilla dust cloud" is not projected, some areas of the U.S. could soon see more vivid sunsets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gulf Tropical System Could Drench Rain-Fatigued Regions...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2021-06-16-gulf-tropical-depression-louisiana-mississippi-valley-rain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More rain is ahead for parts of the already-soaked Gulf Coast and lower Mississippi Valley. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell jail cell flooded with raw sewage, filing says...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-jail-cell-flooded-183300793.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — Ghislaine Maxwell’s cell in a Brooklyn federal jail was “permeated” with raw sewage last week, according to a new court filing. Bobbi Sternheim, an attorney for the British socialite accused of grooming and abusing underage girls, included the sewage leak in her latest list of complaints about conditions at the Metropolitan Detention Center in Sunset Park. “Last week, raw sewage ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims roiling insurance industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ransomware-claims-are-roiling-an-entire-segment-of-the-insurance-industry/ar-AAL8Qpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyber insurance carriers are raising premiums and limiting coverage in the face of severe ransomware attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's 'Dr. Fauci' Damps Olympic Mood With Call to Ban Fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/japan-s-dr-fauci-damps-olympic-mood-with-call-to-ban-fans/ar-AAL7IeB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Shigeru Omi may invite comparisons to Anthony Fauci, Japan’s top Covid-19 adviser has shown little of his American counterpart’s flair for challenging politicians. That is, until he started suggesting banning spectators from the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No apology: Tavis Smiley makes comeback bid after PBS firing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tavis-smiley-business-lifestyle-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-c6d75e1491e93c96a7f0e64afcbb78c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Three years after workplace misconduct allegations cost veteran TV and radio talk-show host Tavis Smiley his job and a national forum, he’s ending his silence. Smiley, who continues to deny the claims of unwanted sexual behavior that led PBS to drop his long-running show, is attempting to rebound with the purchase of a Los Angeles radio station that will offer a Black and progressive perspective on the city and nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China disease expert says COVID origins probe should shift to USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210617012947-lpli3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONOVIRUS/US-CHINA:China disease expert says COVID-19 origins probe should shift to U.S.- Global Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustbusting Kicks Into Higher Gear...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/17/trustbusting-kicks-into-higher-gear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking up The Department of Justice yesterday filed its first antitrust action since President Biden took office, to block the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editors of Hong Kong paper arrested under security law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hong-kong-arrests-business-97e0fbed611073be258763dcf80c4b7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Hong Kong police used a sweeping national security law Thursday to arrest five editors and executives of a pro-democracy newspaper on charges of colluding with foreign powers — the first time the legislation has been used against the press in yet another sign of an intensifying crackdown by Chinese authorities in the city long known for its freedoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo snubbed COCA-COLA. Company's market value fell $4 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cristiano-ronaldo-coca-cola-market-value/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the end of Ronaldo's press conference, Coca-Cola's shares had already started falling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race for Global Tax Revolution Faces Hurdles in Final Stretch...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-tax-report/race-for-a-global-tax-revolution-faces-hurdles-in-final-stretch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s richest nations have set the stage for a revolution in corporate taxation, but they still have their work cut out to actually achieve that overhaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rattles Rate-Hike Saber as Price Pressures Surprise...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-officials-rattle-rate-hike-233000891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.Federal Reserve officials have said for months that price increases are temporary. On Wednesday, they weren’t so sure.“Is there a risk that inflation will be higher than we think? Yes,” Chair Jerome Powell told a press conference. He spoke after financial markets were taken by surprise when policy makers signaled they expect to make not one, but two, hikes to interest rates in 2023 from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Residence in Orbit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/17/as-astronauts-dock-china-takes-up-long-term-residence-in-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Chinese astronauts docked with the country’s still-under-construction space station on Thursday, beginning what their government expects will be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden drew line on Putin. Now it's Russian's move...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/biden-drew-line-putin-now-it-s-russian-s-move-n1271093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Biden turned the page from the Trump years. It's up to Putin to decide whether to abide by international norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abbott launches TX border wall project with $250 million 'down payment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/abbott-texas-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott on Wednesday formally announced that Texas will build its own border wall, as he accused the Biden administration of abandoning its responsibility to protect the southern U.S. border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline, bank sites go down in another major internet failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/17/tech/airlines-website-outage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines, United Airlines, banks and trading platforms suffered brief website outages after a key piece of internet infrastructure failed, sparking the second major interruption of the past 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed moves up timeline for rate hikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/16/fed-holds-rates-steady-but-raises-inflation-expectations-sharply-and-makes-no-mention-of-taper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the central bank gave no indication as to when it will begin cutting back on its aggressive bond-buying program.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
