<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Logs renew concern about security of Trump communications... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Phone-logs-in-impeachment-report-renew-concern-14885944.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump has routinely communicated with his personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani and other individuals speaking on cellphones vulnerable to monitoring by Russian and other foreign intelligence services, current and former U.S. officials said.  Phone records released this week by the House Intelligence Committee revealed extensive communications among Giuliani, unidentified individuals at the White House and others involved in the campaign to pressure Ukraine, with no indication that those calls were encrypted or otherwise shielded from foreign surveillance.  The revelations raise the possibility that Moscow was able to learn about aspects of Trump's attempt to get Ukraine to investigate a political rival months before that effort was exposed by a whistleblower report and the impeachment inquiry, officials said.  Trump is not identified by name in the House phone records, but investigators said they suspect he may be a person with a blocked number listed as "-1" in the files. And administration officials said separately that Trump has communicated regularly with Giuliani on unsecured lines.  "It happened all the time," said one former White House official, who noted that Giuliani had a range of foreign clients.  The disclosures provide fresh evidence suggesting that the president continues to defy the security guidance urged by his own aides and followed by previous incumbents - a stance that is particularly remarkable given Trump's attacks on Hillary Clinton in the 2016 presidential campaign for her use of a private email account while she served as secretary of state.  The connection to the Ukraine campaign is also troubling because of how Moscow could exploit knowledge that Trump was secretly engaged in efforts to extract political favors from the government in Kyiv.  Insight into Giuliani's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyongyang raises 'dotard' spectre as deadline looms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pyongyang-raises-dotard-spectre-deadline-looms-021434241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea has threatened to resume referring to US president Donald Trump as a "dotard", raising the prospect of a return to a war of words with a negotiating deadline approaching. Pyongyang has set Washington an end-of-year time limit to offer it new concessions in deadlocked nuclear negotiations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz survivor fears rise of anti-Semitism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/auschwitz-survivor-fears-rise-anti-semitism-013914324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As German Chancellor Angela Merkel visits Auschwitz for the first time on Friday, 96-year-old survivor Frederick Terna will be at home in New York worrying about a resurgence of anti-Semitism. Terna, in America since 1952, isn't trying to be "the conscience of the world," but said he is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO OKs Watergate series...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amid-impeachment-turmoil-hbo-oks-watergate-series-224349842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US cable channel HBO on Thursday green-lit the production of a new limited series based on the Watergate scandal that brought down President Richard Nixon, starring Woody Harrelson and Justin Theroux. The announcement comes as Washington is again in the throes of an impeachment inquiry against US President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest ever IPO!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9c0e7a81fc56f26da031f5e98cbe2fb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Saudi Arabia's state-owned oil company Aramco on Thursday set a share price for its IPO — expected to be the biggest ever — that puts the value of the company at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP:  'ONCE UPON A TIME... IN HOLLYWOOD' BEST OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0ec356ee3fa4dcdd71683d966cb4f5ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Associated Press Film Writers Lindsey Bahr and Jake Coyle name their choices for the best films of 2019. LINDSEY BAHR 1. “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood": Quentin Tarantino’s movie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden finally finds media buzz with viral Trump video, voter spat!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191205205818-3rgtc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/BIDEN (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Biden finally finds social media buzz with viral Trump video, voter spat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC CLASH</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191205192711-exwzb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Pelosi pursues articles of impeachment against Trump, says democracy at stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Deemed Obstructing Congress an Impeachable Offense...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/brett-kavanaugh-wrote-that-hiding-evidence-from-congress-is-an-impeachable-offense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back when he worked for Ken Starr, the future justice had no tolerance for anything that could be construed as obstructing Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge waves and disease turn Marshall Islands into 'war zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/12/05/breaking-news/huge-waves-and-disease-turn-marshall-islands-into-war-zone-health-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court confronts homeless crisis and whether there's a right to sleep on sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-confronts-homeless-crisis-and-whether-theres-a-right-to-sleep-on-the-sidewalk/ar-BBXPhbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tells jury he's worth $20 billion but short on cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/musk-tells-jury-hes-worth-dollar20-billion-but-is-short-on-cash/ar-BBXLEXF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal gold flowing through Miami is 'direct threat' to national security, Rubio says...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article238048869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL LITE:  Rent clothes at hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/05/rent-the-runway-partners-with-w-hotels-so-you-can-pack-lighter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rent the Runway is hoping to make packing for your vacation a little less painful. It has teamed up with Marriott International's W Hotels' brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Wonder If Schiff Has Their Phone Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/12/05/some-journalists-wonder-if-schiff-has-their-phone-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some journalists are beginning to worry that their phone records may have been caught up in snooping conducted by Rep. Adam Schiff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rep. Says Could Impeach 'More Than Once'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/12/05/dem-rep-green-no-limit-to-how-many-times-we-can-try-to-impeach-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday on C-SPAN, Rep. Al Green (D-TX) discussed impeachment, saying "there is no limit" to how many times the House and Senate can try to impeach | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT QUICKLY</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-says-house-draft-impeachment-142150991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Speaker Nancy Pelosi set the House in motion toward a historic vote to impeach President Donald Trump on a rapid timetable that could bring the process to conclusion before the Christmas holiday.She directed the heads of the House committees that have been investigating the president to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Epstein Was Blackmailing Political Figures...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/russia-israel-and-saudi-arabia-jeffrey-epstein-found-a-niche-blackmailing-american-and-other-d3499f4f60dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shameless pedophile Jeffrey Epstein inherited his espionage business from ex-girlfriend Ghislaine Maxwell, whose father British media…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI ARAMCO to Lead Elite $1 Trillion-Plus Club After IPO...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/saudi-aramco-lead-elite-1-212655557.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It seems like only yesterday equity investors had pegged $1 trillion as the dividing line between run-of-the-mill large cap companies and freakishly huge ones. Saudi Aramco just took things to a whole new level.The oil producer’s initial public offering Thursday valued the company at $1.7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER reports more than 3,000 sex assaults...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f71b1d1292e8d0d0f5d232039bfd77f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Uber, as part of along anticipated safety report, revealed that more than 3,000 sexual assaults were reported during its U.S. rides in 2018. That figure includes 229...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew's Ex-Girlfriends Speak...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2019-12-7/naughty-nights-with-randy-andy </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian agents planned hit from assassins' lairs in French Alps, say intel officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/russian-agents-planned-hits-assassins-lairs-french-alps-say-intel-n1096576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western intelligence agencies tracked up to 15 members of Russia's military intelligence agency, the GRU, including 2 who poisoned a defector in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani in Kyiv; Ukraine Officials Steer Clear...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/giuliani-is-in-kyiv-and-ukrainian-officials-are-steering-clear/ar-BBXPefu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellphone-linked face injuries on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/phone-cheek-spike-seen-cellphone-linked-face-injuries/3Qf1DnKfQ9W6NLBRlK1omJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some injuries were caused by phones themselves, including people getting hit by a thrown phone. But Paskhover said many were caused by distracted use, including texting while walking, tripping and landing face-down on the sidewalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS Driver Carjacked In Miami, Held Hostage During Wild Police Chase, Shootout...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/05/coral-gables-police-investigating-armed-robbery-miracle-mile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pursuit of a carjacked UPS truck involving several police agencies through South Florida streets ended Thursday afternoon in Miramar with an exchange of gunfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MCCLATCHY Fears 'Ghost Papers'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mcclatchy-goes-digital-ward-off-120029475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- When I interviewed Craig Forman, the chief executive officer of McClatchy Co., last week, shares of the regional newspaper chain stood at 39 cents. Like its peers, it has struggled as print advertising has dwindled and subscribers have abandoned ship. Last month, the company said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: WE WILL IMPEACH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/05/pelosi-asks-house-judiciary-committee-to-proceed-with-articles-of-impeachment-against-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The president's actions have seriously violated the Constitution," Pelosi says at a news conference on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is LeBron's Teen Son Second Coming Of NBA's King?</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2019/12/05/lebron-james-son-bronny-identical-dunk-comparison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James is playing at an MVP level in the early stages of the 2019-2020 season and if it [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish politician makes 'gun' gesture at Trump's back...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/05/polish-politician-makes-what-appears-to-be-gun-gesture-at-trumps-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish politician Donald Tusk on Thursday tweeted a photo of him pointing a pair of fingers toward President Trump’s back, a gesture some alarmed Twitter users likened to a gun. “Despit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG, the company, fixes 'glitch' sending users to candidate site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-company-fixes-glitch-sending-users-candidate-213309556.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We've updated that function to go to (Michael Bloomberg's) bio page just like anyone else," said Bloomberg LP spokesman Ty Trippet in a tweet to an FT journalist. Before he launched his presidential run, the feature was used to direct users to Michael Bloomberg's philanthropy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK rejects ISIS 'defeated' claim...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/uk-armed-forces-head-rejects-trumps-claim-islamic-state-has-been-defeated-11879124</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Sir Nicholas Carter has also said Syria is a "tinderbox that could very easily ignite a wider conflagration".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details on drug that may slow Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/new-details-emerge-drug-may-slow-alzheimer-s-disease-n1096561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excitement and skepticism have surrounded the drug since its developers stopped studies earlier this year because it didn't seem to be working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia govt secretly prosecuting citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-12-05/witness-j-how-can-a-trial-be-kept-secret/11739288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public is in the dark about how secret trials can happen. So too is the legal profession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York's 'island of the dead' to welcome more living...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/yorks-island-dead-welcome-more-living-014616727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A once off-limits, eroding island in New York where more than a million people are buried in unmarked mass graves dug by prisoners is about to become more accessible. For 150 years, unclaimed bodies, the poor, still-born children and AIDS victims have been laid to rest on the mile-long Hart Island,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West to Let Roads, Homes Be Swallowed Up By Rising Sea...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/04/florida-keys-officials-roads-homes-lost-sea-level-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are troubled waters on the horizon for the Florida Keys. Monroe County made a shocking announcement Wednesday that some roads and homes may be surrendered to the sea. It's all because of sea level rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Challenges Voter to 'IQ Test', Push-Up Contest After Asked About Son...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/nidhiprakash/joe-biden-iq-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You're a damn liar," Biden told a man at a campaign event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're a damn liar'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/473226-biden-gets-in-testy-exchange-in-iowa-youre-a-damn-liar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Thursday got in a tense back-and-forth with an audience member during an Iowa campaign stop after the man claimed the former vice president sent his son Hunter Biden to work for an energy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rep. Says Could Impeach 'More Than Once'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/05/al-green-impeach-trump-more-than-once/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Texas Rep. Al Green on Thursday said that House Democrats could impeach President Donald Trump multiple times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Kap Workout Leads To NFL Contract -- For Receiver Who Caught Passes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/colin-kaepernicks-november-workout-produces-its-first-nfl-signing-but-not-for-the-quarterback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One player involved in Colin Kaepernick's November workout has signed an NFL deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA news helicopter struck by suspected drone...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/05/us/helicopter-drone-emergency-landing-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The object ripped a hole through the helicopter's tail and dented and scratched the craft in other spots -- damage too severe to be caused by a bird, crew said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500,000 march against Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/dec/05/anti-macron-protests-held-in-france-with-strikes-set-to-continue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transport workers bring country to standstill amid anger over pension changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign ad features foreign leaders 'laughing' at Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/5/joe-biden-campaign-cuts-digital-ad-featuring-forei/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden’s presidential campaign released a digital ad Wednesday evening that includes the now-infamous footage of world leaders appearing to mock President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  BERNIE TOPS IN CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-12-05/democrats-2020-race-california-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg rise in a poll of California Democratic primary voters. Mike Bloomberg is the most unpopular candidate in the field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS:  80 Miles Of New Border Wall To Be Completed By 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-border-wall-construction-underway-for-the-first-stretch-built-under-president-trump-2019-12-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In total, Congress has approved nearly $1.4 billion to repair, replace or build new wall along the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk's 'Pedo Guy' Trial Shows Depth, Danger of His Own Mythos...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/12/elon-musk-pedo-guy-trial-mythos-depth-danger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big problem with this wealth-fueled Elon Musk mythos is that Elon Musk is also susceptible to its spell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASONS BEATINGS: Video Shows BARNEY'S Employees Brawl With Shoplifters...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/12/05/caught-on-camera-barneys-employees-brawl-with-pair-suspected-of-shoplifting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said employees confronted two people who allegedly stole merchandise from the store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muhammad makes list of 10 most popular baby names in USA for the first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10489360/muhammad-popular-baby-names-united-states-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE most popular baby names this year have been revealed with Muhammad making the top ten list for the first time in the US. According to BabyCenter’s list of 100 most popular baby names for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napolitano Predicts Will Testify Under Oath in Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-napolitano-predicts-trump-will-testify-under-oath-in-impeachment-trial-with-200-million-people-watching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News analyst Andrew Napolitano told America's Newsroom that he believes President Donald Trump will testify in the now-likely impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Nye Science Guy Headed to Trial Against DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/bill-nye-science-guy-headed-trial-disney-1259788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles judge trims Nye's profits lawsuit, but will allow the TV star to pursue punitive damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar quietly gaining momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/politics/elections/ct-amy-klobuchar-iowa-2020-presidential-race-20191204-5cqtk5qhazgahk73hdtyojzqpe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when many Democratic presidential candidates are stagnating in the polls and struggling to keep their campaigns financially afloat, Minnesota U.S. Sen. Amy Klobuchar’s operation is growing. She is one of just six candidates who has qualified for the December debate and is in the midst of doubling her Iowa campaign offices to more than 20, doubling her paid staff in New Hampshire and has hired up in the other early states of Nevada and South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal lawyer to be charged with graft in new woes for Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lawyer-charged-graft-woes-netanyahu-153616993.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's state prosecutor said Thursday he intends to charge the personal lawyer of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu with money-laundering in the state's purchase of submarines from German firm Thyssenkrupp. Netanyahu has in the past been questioned as a witness in the case but was not considered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' Ride Breaks Down Minutes After Opening...</title>
      <link>http://www.brevardtimes.com/2019/12/star-wars-rise-of-the-resistance-ride-breaks-down-minutes-afte-opening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.brevardtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE BUENA VISTA, Florida – The Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance ride broke down just minutes after opening today as part of Disney’s $1 billion Star Wars: Galaxy’s Edge expansion …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NIGHT OF HOPE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/12/05/kanye-west-joel-osteen-yankee-stadium-choir-americas-night-of-hope-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ye and Joel are hitting the road together, for one stop anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Mannequin Vaginas, Evil Babies: Inside Most Grotesque Movie of Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/in-fabric-is-the-most-gorgeously-grotesque-movie-of-the-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrealist master Peter Strickland (“The Duke of Burgundy”) is back with “In Fabric,” a gory ode to Dario Argento about a cursed red dress that has to be seen to be believed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery at Center of Solar System; Spacecraft Reaches Sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/12/parker-solar-probe-nasa-sun/602962/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spacecraft has finally gotten close enough to the sun to gather clues about some lingering questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Can't Last 4 Hours With Family Over Holidays...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/breaking-point-average-person-cant-last-four-hours-with-their-family-over-the-holidays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holidays are supposed to be a time to come together with family and celebrate, but a new survey finds that most Americans can barely get through an evening with their family before needing a break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot to be based on singer after sensational AI agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-based-russian-singer-21033186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anna Pletnyova has reportedly agreed to use her image as a prototype for a new South Korean doll after striking a deal with a company that produces erotic humanoid models</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Mother Upset With Son's Haircut Slams Car Into Barber Shop...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/12/04/mother-upset-with-kids-haircut-slams-car-into-antioch-barber-witnesses-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antioch police are searching for a woman who witnesses say intentionally drove her car into a barber after she was reportedly dissatisfied with the haircut he gave her son, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our democracy is at stake'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ea344e9bf24d8a8b64c20a305c14305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi announced Thursday that the House is moving forward to draft articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump. ‘’Our democracy is what is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Punches MCDONALD'S Workers Over Wrong Order...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/utah-mcdonalds-rage-801954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 5--Two McDonald’s employees were assaulted by an irate customer who claimed that the workers botched his order, according to Utah police. Investigators say Victor Jimmy Castro placed an ord</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea: 'very dangerous challenge' if Trump calls Kim 'Rocket Man' again...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/north-korea-very-dangerous-challenge-if-trump-calls-kim-rocket-man-again-idUSKBN1Y91L0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should U.S. President Donald Trump call North Korean leader Kim Jong Un "Ro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: DO IT FAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-challenges-do-nothing-democrats-if-you-are-going-to-impeach-me-do-it-now-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump returned from a shortened trip to the UK-based NATO summit amidst an ongoing Congressional impeachment inquiry threating his administration and issued an interesting challenge t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Releases Ad Showing World Leaders Laughing at Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/joe-biden-twists-the-knife-with-viral-video-showing-the-world-is-laughing-at-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President and Democratic presidential frontrunner Joe Biden capitalized on President Donald Trump's overseas trip by releasing a video mashup showing world leaders "laughing at P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE WEST AND JOEL OSTEEN TO TAKE OVER YANKEE STADIUM...</title>
      <link>https://thesource.com/2019/12/05/kanye-west-and-joel-osteen-to-take-over-yankee-stadium-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesource.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a confirmed report from TMZ, Kanye West and Joel Osteen are going to o one bigger than Lakewood Church. The best part is that the date is already set; May 2, 2020 Joel and Ye are set to takeover the home of the Bronx Bombers. The event is an installment of Osteen’s “America’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMAC in the DARQ: Tech trends shaping 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/smac-darq-tech-trends-shaping-2020-042708248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or will the world unify against Big Tech's privacy-busting, tax-avoiding practices? Apple has yet to launch a compatible phone, unlike rivals including Samsung. The rollout should quicken next year as more countries install base stations and networking equipment -- although US President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian faints during whipping for Sharia-banned sex...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indonesian-faints-during-whipping-sharia-banned-sex-103819011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite international condemnation, public flogging is common for a range of offences banned under local Islamic law in the conservative Aceh region on Sumatra island, including gambling, drinking alcohol, and having gay or pre-marital sex. Aceh is the only region in Indonesia, the world's biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 hours in the shadow of Mexico's violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/24-hours-shadow-mexicos-violence-030820490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mexico struggles to stop the bloodshed unleashed by its "drug wars," the violence casts a long shadow over ordinary life for many Mexicans. Everything in Ciudad Juarez is extreme: the arid climate of the Chihuahuan desert, the stark contrasts of the US-Mexican border, the violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France shuts down: Mass strike hits trains, Eiffel Tower...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a90ae89bba844a729e2d0ea894b11294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Eiffel Tower shut down, France’s vaunted high-speed trains stood still and teachers walked off the job as unions launched nationwide strikes and protests Thursday over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi to discuss 'status of inquiry'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473135-pelosi-to-discuss-status-of-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) will deliver a statement on the “status of impeachment inquiry” into President Trump at 9 a.m., her office announced early Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quiet Return of Bruce Weber and Mario Testino...</title>
      <link>https://businessglitz.com/us/the-quiet-return-of-bruce-weber-and-mario-testino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businessglitz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Showdown of NFL next generation QBs: Jackson vs Allen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f333c12f27773587f0c76a3b31bfb045</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORCHARD PARK, N.Y. (AP) — It's easy to forgive Ravens coach John Harbaugh for forgetting this weekend's showdown of two of the AFC's more dynamic quarterbacks won't be the first meeting between...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK MORRIS:  SHE'LL WAIT FOR BIDEN TO DROP OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/former-bill-clinton-adviser-hillary-feels-god-put-her-on-earth-to-be-president-but-one-thing-is-keeping-her-from-running-2019-10-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick Morris went on the John Catsimatidis’s radio show to talk about the likelihood of Hillary Clinton running for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10472853/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10472853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
