<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PHOTO:  Bill Clinton receives neck massage from Jeffrey Epstein victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8639501/Bill-Clinton-smiles-receiving-neck-massage-Jeffrey-Epstein-victim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton is seen in photos sitting comfortably and smiling as Chauntae Davies, 22, rubs her hands into his shoulders. They were on a trip with Jeffrey Epstein to Africa in September of 2002.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New accuser says Cuba Gooding Jr. raped her...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/08/18/new-accuser-says-cuba-gooding-jr-raped-her-in-soho-hotel-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gooding has is currently facing a criminal trial on six misdemeanor counts of sexual abuse and forcible touching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA's Next Foe: One of Their Own...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/18/the-n-r-a-and-wayne-lapierres-next-foe-one-of-their-own/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this month, the National Rifle Association was sued by the New York attorney general, who is seeking to dissolve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEWERSHIP SHRINKS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/nbc-abc-monday-tv-ratings-2020-democratic-national-convention-1203016422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Democrats and Republicans rallying against Trump’s handling of the pandemic to the emotional moment of silence for George Floyd to Michelle Obama’s memorable “It is what it i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton to Address Party That Left Him Behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-bill-clinton-a-chance-to-address-a-party-that-has-left-him-behind/ar-BB185P2j?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhinged TWITTER meltdown shows she drew blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-trump-e2-80-99s-unhinged-twitter-meltdown-shows-michelle-obama-drew-blood/ar-BB186t8o?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O ROASTS AND GAGS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michelle-obama-condemns-trump-in-blistering-dnc-speech-if-you-think-things-cannot-possibly-get-worse-trust-me-they-can</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former First Lady Michelle Obama tore into President Donald Trump in her DNC convention speech Monday night for being divisive and lacking empathy during his first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea 'has 60 nukes and 5,000 tones of chemical weapons'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/north-korea-60-nuclear-weapons-22541908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Department of the Army released the report last month, and some sections warned that North Korea may be able to obtain 100 nuclear weapons by the end of this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tavis Smiley ordered to pay PBS $2.6M for sexual misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/biz/news/tavis-smiley-ordered-to-pay-pbs-2-6-million-for-workplace-affairs-1234737603/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has ordered TV host Tavis Smiley to pay $2.6 million to the Public Broadcasting Service for having multiple affairs with his subordinates. A Washington, D.C., jury found in March that Smile…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIANNE WILLIAMSON:  'Like binge watching a MARRIOTT commercial'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/512490-marianne-williamson-democratic-convention-like-binge-watching-a-marriott</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Marianne Williamson on Tuesday criticized the first night of the Democratic National Convention, which she said was “like binge watching a Marriott commercial.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 111 Days In 4 Hospitals, 33-Year-Old 'Miracle Patient' Goes Home...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/17/coronavirus-miracle-patient-tito-velasquez-northwell-stern-family-center-of-rehabilitation-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He spent more than three months in multiple hospitals battling COVID-19. But on Monday, a Valley Stream man in his 30s was discharged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers Can Now Buy Marijuana From Vending Machines In Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/08/18/cannabis-customers-can-buy-marijuana-vending-machines-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now four pot vending machines operating at one location in Pueblo -- and there are plans to install one at a dispensary in Aurora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postmaster general to appear before Senate over mail delays...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26926bf85cae5175fbd920efb534ef84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Backlash mounting, President Donald Trump's embattled Postmaster General Louis DeJoy will appear Friday before the Senate to testify on mail delivery delays and service changes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort was 'grave counterintelligence threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/08/18/senate-details-paul-manafort-ties-russian-intel-officer-kilimnik/3390437001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort's "proximity to Trump created opportunities for Russian intelligence services to exert influence over, and acquire confidential information on, the Trump campaign."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France makes masks compulsory at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/france-makes-masks-compulsory-at-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extensive web of contacts between Trump campaign advisers and  govt officials... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/18/us/politics/senate-intelligence-russian-interference-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nearly 1,000-page report confirmed the special counsel’s findings at a moment when President Trump’s allies have sought to undermine that inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC orders hotels to ban some travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/cuomo-to-update-quarantine-list-as-new-york-virus-numbers-remain-in-check/2572422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio doubled down on his commitment to protect the five boroughs from travel-linked virus surges Tuesday, ordering hotels and short-term rentals to require travelers complete quarantine forms before they get access to rooms. Fines will be issued starting this week for failure to comply. De Blasio also urged New Yorkers to avoid hotspot state…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry and Markle Pitching Top-Secret Project to Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/prince-harry-meghan-markle-pitch-meetings-tv-project-1234734074/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever since Prince Harry and Meghan Markle moved to California earlier this year, rumors have swirled that they had a plan to gain a foothold in Hollywood. They now seem to be taking steps to do tha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Warns Spike Leaves No Room to Ease Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-rules-easing-coronavirus-rules-152025366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel warned on Tuesday there could be no further relaxation of coronavirus restrictions while Germany grapples with a surge in new infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel warns Hamas of war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israeli-planes-bomb-gaza-egyptians-053658998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel warned Hamas Tuesday it was risking &amp;quot;war&amp;quot; by failing to stop incendiary balloon attacks from Gaza, as fuel shortages in the Palestinian enclave caused by Israel&amp;#39;s blockade caused widespread blackouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VIRTUAL DNC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de0107b02c0373105b86d5c4d3d9a302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michelle Obama delivered a passionate condemnation of President Donald Trump during the opening night of the Democratic National Convention, declaring him “in over his head” and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate snow rains down on Swiss town!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/879a16ca4c343a8877c787c06beca1f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Residents of a Swiss town got a bit of a shock when it started snowing particles of a fine cocoa powder after the ventilation system at a chocolate factory malfunctioned. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate panel concludes Russia interfered in 2016 election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e833a62e9492f6a66624b7920cc846a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump campaign's interactions with Russian intelligence services during the 2016 presidential election posed a “grave” counterintelligence threat, a Senate panel concluded...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhinged TWITTER meltdown shows she drew blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2020/08/18/trumps-unhinged-twitter-meltdown-shows-michelle-obama-drew-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has no response, because Michelle Obama's searing indictment is correct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows true extent of horrifying lab tests on terrified monkeys...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/cruel-footage-monkeys-being-force-22540514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant monkeys became booze, nicotine and junk food addicts in "cruel" lab experiments at the Oregon National Primate Research Center with the full horrors of the experiments not revealed until now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postmaster General agrees to testify amid fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/18/politics/louis-dejoy-senate-testify/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Postmaster General Louis DeJoy will testify before the Republican-led Senate Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs Committee on Friday, the committee announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Warns Spike Leaves No Room to Ease Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-18/merkel-warns-pandemic-threat-leaves-no-room-to-ease-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketers, Media Outlets Feud Over Billions of Dollars in Advertising...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/biz/news/madison-avenue-marketers-media-feud-advertising-1234737422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last sheriff of New York’s Madison Avenue spends most of his time in the middle of the country. Rino Scanzoni used to help put together deals for some of the advertising industry’s biggest heav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark to Make Banks, Rich Fund Early Retirement Plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-international/denmark-to-make-banks-the-rich-fund-its-early-retirement-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark’s Social Democrat-led government drew the ire of the country’s financial industry by unveiling 3 billion kroner ($480 million) worth of additional taxes to fund early retirement for certain categories of workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to pardon Susan B. Anthony over 1872 voting arrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0bc7c76b965205e136e05277911bb2a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As controversy swirls over mail-in voting in this year’s election, President Donald Trump said Tuesday he will pardon Susan B. Anthony, a women's suffrage leader arrested for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent public toilets installed in Tokyo parks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/18/loo-with-a-view-transparent-public-toilets-installed-in-tokyo-parks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amenities designed so prospective users can inspect their cleanliness from the outside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: S&amp;P 500 rises to new record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/17/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Tuesday as the S&amp;P 500 tried once again to exceed its previous record close set in February before the coronavirus hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Wallace: She flayed, sliced and diced...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/512474-foxs-chris-wallace-lauds-michelle-obama-convention-speech-really-flayed-sliced</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran Fox News anchor Chris Wallace praised former first lady Michelle Obama's virtual speech at the Democratic National Convention late Monday, with the "Fox News Sunday" host stating that she "really flayed, sliced and diced" President Tr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump erupts at takedown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-erupts-angrily-michelle-obamas-124758798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump erupted angrily Tuesday after former first lady Michelle Obama said he was &amp;quot;in over his head&amp;quot; in a blistering speech at the Democratic convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's first cyborg' to become part-robot to tackle motor neurone disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/12430732/cyborg-peter-scott-morgan-robot-motor-neuron-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TERMINALLY-ILL scientist is on a mission to become the world’s first cyborg in a bid to combat his muscle wasting disease. Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, 62, wants to enhance his deteriorating body…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scary War Game Over Taiwan That USA Loses Again and Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearinvestigations.com/articles/2020/08/17/the_scary_war_game_over_taiwan_that_the_us_loses_again_and_again_124836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearinvestigations.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above, a Taiwanese soldier during drills aimed at deterring China. U.S. war-game simulations show pushing back a Chinese invasion is a grim prospect. By Richard Bernstein,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam has been collapsing for years. Now it's paying price...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/amsterdam-collapsing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the recent Covid-19 restrictions have relieved the Dutch capital from the more superficial blight of overtourism, it seems Amsterdam has a more pressing existential crisis. It's in danger of crumbling into the water it's built upon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War against dollar heating up...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-dollar-euro-value-reserve-currency-918a7a7c-b974-42e2-b1f0-dcbcdbb7b929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things may actually be different this time for its status as the world's reserve currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coin shortage hits retailers, laundromats, tooth fairy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a06b0341ff8c9a53582d953ac8c02971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national coin shortage has been an unusual side effect of the pandemic. Among its victims? Retailers, laundromats and even the tooth fairy. The Federal Reserve announced in June that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE rallies YOUTUBErs against Oz news payment plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200818-google-rallies-youtubers-against-australian-news-payment-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google rallies YouTubers against Australian news payment plan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Spain. Super-Yachts Flocking to Croatia, Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/hasta-luego-spain-super-yachts-now-flock-to-croatia-and-turkey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Spain. Super-Yachts Are Flocking to Croatia and Turkey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More infectious mutation may be 'good thing', says disease expert...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200818024342-3xads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MUTATION (UPDATE 1, TV):UPDATE 1-More infectious coronavirus mutation may be 'a good thing', says disease expert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Bill Clinton, Chance to Address Party That Left Him Behind...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/18/for-bill-clinton-a-chance-to-address-a-party-that-has-left-him-behind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton was a prime-time star when Democrats gathered in 2012 to nominate President Barack Obama for a second term,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Tracking Vast, Growing Anomaly in Earth's Magnetic Field...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/nasa-is-tracking-the-mysterious-evolving-anomaly-in-earth-s-magnetic-field</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is actively monitoring a strange anomaly in Earth's magnetic field: a giant region of lower magnetic intensity in the skies above the planet, stretching out between South America and southwest Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-minute power walk decreases chance of death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8635361/Exercise-Turning-12-minute-stroll-7-minute-power-walk-daily-lowers-risk-early-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts led from Cambridge used fitness tracker data to show that, when it comes to longevity, it's not how much exercise you get but the intensity that matters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nhl9QoXAB34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders addressed Democrats on Aug. 17 during the first night of the Democratic National Convention. Kasich ran for the Republican presid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_jmm2NLLeQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Ohio Republican Gov. John Kasich addressed Democrats on Aug. 17 during the first night of the Democratic National Convention. Kasich ran for the Repub...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speeches lasted just couple of minutes or less...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democratic-convention-opens-with-virtual-speakers-15491262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats kicked off their virtual nominating convention Monday with a focused denunciation of President Donald Trump, showcasing dozens of testimonials that culminated in lancing criticism from former first lady Michelle Obama, who cast Trump as incapable of meeting America's needs and said Joe Biden would usher in racial justice and ease the coronavirus pandemic.  In the centerpiece speech of the night, a searing indictment of her husband Barack Obama's successor, Michelle Obama declared that Trump has mishandled the pandemic and failed to respond to outcries over the deaths of Black Americans. She warned that the nation would suffer more if he is elected to a second term.  "Let me be as honest and clear as I possibly can: Donald Trump is the wrong president for our country. He has had more than enough time to prove that he can do the job, but he is clearly in over his head. He cannot meet this moment. He simply cannot be who we need him to be for us," she said, before quoting a line Trump used about covid-19 deaths in a recent interview: "It is what it is."  Obama spoke passionately about protests against police brutality this year - and Trump's declaration that those in the streets were anarchists.  "Here at home as George Floyd, Breonna Taylor and a never-ending list of innocent people of color continue to be murdered, stating the simple fact that a Black life matters is still met with derision from the nation's highest office," Obama said, wearing a necklace that read "Vote."  Earlier in the night, the brother of Floyd, who was killed while pleading for air as a Minneapolis police officer knelt on him, appeared to ask for a moment of silence to commemorate those who have died as a result of police misconduct.  "It is up to us to carry on the fight for justice," Philonise Floyd said, without making an overt call for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE:  MIXED MESSAGES IN CHAOTIC CONVENTION...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/columns/chaotic-democratic-national-convention-1234738294/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meg Whitman spoke for only a fleeting segment of Monday night’s opening of the Democratic National Convention. And yet the Quibi corporate leader and Republican politician’s presence seemed emblema…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Michelle steals the show, too bad it's Joe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/17/michelle-obama-breathes-life-into-listless-dnc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama brought a breath of life to the Democratic National Convention Monday after nearly two hours of brief, bleak speeches and videos, taking aim at President Trump as she urged Americans…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party promises Biden and Harris will be live, NOT pretaped...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-convention-season-set-begin-201227357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Democrats opened their nominating convention Monday with a show of unity behind Joe Biden and former first lady Michelle Obama delivering a scathing rebuke of Donald Trump as she urged voters to reject his politics of &amp;#39;division.&amp;#39;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention Kicks Off With Hollywood Help...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/democratic-convention-review-night-1-joe-biden-michelle-obama-eva-longoria-sean-hannity-donald-trump-dnc-1203016023/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only thing missing from the opening night of the Democratic National Convention on Monday were the Rolling Stones and Barack Obama – and the former POTUS is coming later this week. Other than a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKOUT FOR MILLIONS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/78364b669c0a714d2ca7107886510f5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Widespread blackouts to reduce pressure on the electric grid were averted Monday night after regulators warned earlier in the day that they would not have enough power to meet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CILLIZZA:  Hits and misses from Night 1...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2020/08/17/politics/democrats-analysis-best-worst-dnc/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first night of the 2020 Democratic National Convention is in the books.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The only way we are going to lose is if election rigged'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/08/17/trump_the_only_way_we_lose_the_election_is_if_the_election_is_rigged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump at a campaign-style event in Oshkosh, Wisconsin on Monday: "So, we have to win the election. We can't play games. Get out and vote. Do those beautiful absentee ballots or just make sure your vote gets counted. Make sure, because the only way we're going to lose this election is if the election is rigged. Remember that. It's the only way we're going to lose this election... This is more than this election. That's a big statement. The only way they're going to win is that way, and we can't let that happen. And, you know, our post office, we're going to make our post office great. It's been a disaster for many years. We're going to take care of the men and women in the post office, and we're going to make it great. Right now, it's a laughingstock."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE:  'Nero Fiddled While Rome Burned, Trump Golfs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/08/17/bernie_sanders_nero_fiddled_while_rome_burned_trump_golfs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders speaks at the 2020 Democratic Convention. Sanders says that "by rejecting science," President Trump has "put our lives and health in jeopardy" and "fanned this pandemic." "Ideas that were once considered radical only a few years ago are now considered mainstream," Sanders said.  "My friends, the price of failure us just too great to imagine," Sanders said about the Biden/Harris ticket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resembles an online awards show... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/no-applause-no-crowds-democrats-begin-a-most-unusual-convention/ar-BB184YW3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O ROASTS TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michelle-obama-condemns-trump-in-blistering-dnc-speech-if-you-think-things-cannot-possibly-get-worse-trust-me-they-can/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former First Lady Michelle Obama tore into President Donald Trump in her DNC convention speech Monday night for being divisive and lacking empathy during his first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KASICH:  America at Crossroads...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/america-is-at-a-crossroads-john-kasich-delivers-dnc-speech-from-literal-crossroads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Ohio Governor and 2012 Republican presidential candidate John Kasich delivered his DNC speech at a literal crossroads on Monday night -- calling for all Americans, regardless of party, to suppo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subtle handoff for 78-year-old senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/We-have-a-come-a-very-long-way-Bernie-Sanders-15490156.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few people saw the beginning of Sen. Bernie Sanders's journey in presidential politics as a major moment - including Sanders himself.  "Let me just make a brief comment," the Vermont independent said as he spoke to a small group of reporters outside the Capitol in April 2015. "We don't have an endless amount of time."  Since then, everything and nothing has changed.  "We have come a very long way in five years," Sanders said in an interview Sunday, chuckling as he recalled his modest start, which focused on the power of the "billionaire class."  Sanders's address at the Democratic National Convention on Monday night effectively closed an improbable odyssey - two bids for the White House that together formed the backbone of a new, insurgent liberal movement.  Sanders nodded to his success in lifting his previously fringe calls for Medicare-for-all, free college tuition and a chastening of the nation's financial elite to the fore of a Democratic Party that had been drifting toward more-centrist views.  "Many of the ideas we fought for, that just a few years ago were considered radical, are now mainstream," Sanders said in his address, speaking from Burlington, Vt.  He cast President Donald Trump as a historic failure - a "threat to our democracy" who is "leading us down the path of authoritarianism."  "Nero fiddled while Rome burned," Sanders said. "Trump golfs. His actions fanned this pandemic, resulting in over 170,000 deaths and a nation still unprepared to protect its people."  Any bitterness about his defeat in the primary to presumptive nominee Joe Biden was absent. This phase of his revolution was televised and unified, with Sanders urging his supporters to back Biden.  "My friends, I say to you, to everyone who supported other candidates in the primary and to those who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT IS WHAT IT IS'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/democratic-national-convention-2020-michelle-obama-night-one/#post-update-f6b259ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If we have any hope of ending this chaos, we have got to vote for Joe Biden like our lives depend on it," the former first lady said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Sued Over Warning Labels on Anti-Vaccine Posts...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-sued-over-warning-labels-232117077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc.’s practice of putting fact-checking warning labels on anti-vaccination posts triggered a lawsuit accusing the social media company of censorship.Children’s Health Defense, a nonprofit advocacy group led by Robert F. Kennedy Jr., filed the complaint Monday in federal court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/convention/?party=dnc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follows People Who Move Out of State...</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/section-2/california-dems-wealth-tax-follows-people-who-move-out-of-the-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force One nearly hit by small drone, witnesses say...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/35763/air-force-one-just-had-a-near-miss-with-a-drone-according-to-reporter-onboard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The C-32A was descending into Andrews Air Force Base when the incident supposedly took place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIZZA HUT files for bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pizza-hut-files-bankruptcy-300-restaurants-mostly-dine-in-locations-to-close</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Leawood, Kansas, company filed for bankruptcy protection last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  'ELLEN' FIRES TOP PRODUCERS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/ellen-degeneres-producers-ed-glavin-jonathan-norman-glavin-kevin-leman-jonathan-norman-1234737854/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Ellen DeGeneres Show” has overhauled its senior production team in the wake of accusations of racial insensitivity, sexual misconduct and other problems in the work environment at the long-run…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says coronavirus is 'God testing me'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/931752/trump-says-coronavirus-god-testing-build-economy-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday blasted his likely presidential challenger former Vice President Joe Biden during a speech in Manakato, Minnesota, saying he'd 'abolish the American way of life' en route to turning the U.S. into a 'very boring socialist country that will go to hell.' He then had a go at Biden's running mate, Sen. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.), for co-sponsoring a 'socialist takeover of health care.' The president also joked the coronavirus pandemic was 'God testing me' to rebuild the U.S. economy a second time. He zeroed in on New Zealand, a country which, to Trump's apparent chagrin, has won praise for containing the virus. Recently, though, New Zealand has had a flare-up, and Trump made sure the crowd in Minnesota knew about it. While New Zealanders are certainly concerned about the virus resurfacing after several months, just nine new infections were reported Monday, far lower than the average daily number of cases in the United States, which Trump maintains has handled the pandemic with aplomb. 'All of a sudden a lot of the places they were using to hold up, they are having a big surge ... New Zealand, you see what's going on in New Zealand' -- New Zealand had nine (9!) new Covid cases today. The US had more than 42,000. The outbreaks are not comparable. pic.twitter.com/T8ugmKK6aa â€” Aaron Rupar (@atrupar) August 17, 2020 The speech also included a defense of the Minneapolis Police Department, which has come under fire in the wake of the killing of George Floyd, and criticism of the Minneapolis protests. 'The city was ablaze,' he lamented. Tim O'Donnell Trump says this of Minneapolis cops: 'The police department is very good but they were told you can't do anything. They have to be able to do what they do very well.' (Recall that people were protesting in Mpls after George Floyd was killed by a cop.) pic.twitter.com/nQJZp9P3a0 â€” Aaron Rupar (@atrupar) August 17, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The only way we are going to lose this election is if the election is rigged'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/512424-trump-the-only-way-we-are-going-to-lose-this-election-is-if-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday further cast doubt on the U.S. election process, claiming falsely that the only way he would lose in November is if the election is “rigged.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS announce plans to have fans at NFL season-opener...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/when-the-chiefs-host-the-texans-to-kick-off-the-2020-nfl-season-over-15000-fans-could-be-in-attendance-221846644.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chiefs said Monday that Arrowhead will be capped at 22 percent capacity to open the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems kick off DNC  -- unified... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd1ec0b8c19b4d942972b6de5379857d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ohio’s former Gov. John Kasich, a Republican presidential contender four years ago, joined Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders, a self-described democratic socialist, on Monday in calling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O READY FOR HER CLOSE-UP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/105dedebd16d3fd28e9c23e85ed479bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Michelle Obama will call Joe Biden a “profoundly decent man” who will “tell the truth and trust science" in her Monday night convention speech, seeking to draw a sharp contrast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARRON NOW TALLER THAN DAD!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/17/funeral-for-robert-trump-to-take-place-on-friday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said he intends to hold his younger brother Robert Trump’s funeral at the White House on Friday, telling reporters it would be “a great honor” to the late executiv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA FACING LARGEST POWER OUTAGE IN ITS HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/california-the-largest-power-outages-in-its-history-this-week-1203015664/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As California struggles to rebound from the coronavirus pandemic, wilting heat and wildfires, it’s facing another dangerous crisis: blackouts. As temperatures broke records across the state, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING BLACKOUTS CONTINUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/PG-E-power-outage-California-Bay-Area-blackout-new-15490417.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacific Gas and Electric is warning it is "likely" many customers will lose power for one-to-two hours Monday afternoon and evening due to rolling blackouts caused by increased strain on California's electrical grid amid a statewide heat wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anonymous' urges vote for Joe...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/17/anonymous-official-supports-biden-397090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unknown administration official who wrote a book trashing Trump says a second term will mean "a nation undone" in a new book preface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Organization for Women out after 'toxic work environment' allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/now-president-steps-down-after-allegations-she-oversaw-a-toxic-work-environment-and-racism-claims-health-reasons-cited-for-her-departure/ar-BB184uva</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential race neck-in-neck in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/politics-blog/wsb-poll-trump-and-biden-are-neck-and-neck-in-georgia-as-dnc-meet-begins/2ZXKNCBA5BDS5GBS3G5QMDYBNM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump and former Vice President Joe Biden are running roughly even in Georgia ahead of two weeks of political conventions that aim to reframe the publicâ€™s attention on the race for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan College Will Digitally Track Students At All Times...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/campus/michigan-college-will-digitally-track-students-movements-at-all-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan college is requiring students to download a phone application that tracks their location and private health data at all times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb-Sniffing 'Cyborg' Locusts Distinguish Between Different Explosives...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/bomb-sniffing-cyborg-locusts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locusts are part of the grasshopper family and can travel great distances through the air. Dating all the way back to biblical times, these infamous insects are known for two things: swarms and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>130 more students infected. UNC moves all classes online...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/education/article245014185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ongoing Party' in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-alabama-students-crowds-safety-football-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;University of Alabama's athletic director tweeted a photo that showed dozens of people, many not wearing face masks or staying away from others, waiting to get in a popular bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Antifa' rioters trash NYC stores...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/17/antifa-protesters-trash-apple-store-whole-foods-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of protesters, including suspected members of the anti-fascist group Antifa, rampaged through Williamsburg over the weekend, trashing several national chain stores and spraying anti-police g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Push MN Gov for Reparations...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/08/16/protesters-rally-outside-governors-mansion-to-demand-reparations-for-american-decedents-of-slaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered outside the governor's residence Sunday afternoon in St. Paul to demand payment to those impacted by slavery and racial injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Set To Pass Nation's First Wealth Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/california-set-pass-nations-first-wealth-tax-targeting-ultra-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat sinks in Portland as 'Boat Parade' passes by...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/2020/08/boat-sinks-on-willamette-river-as-trump-boat-parade-passes-by.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A boat on the Willamette River took on water and sank Sunday afternoon after being swamped by waves as a “Trump Boat Parade” passed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CIA officer charged with spying for China...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/former-cia-officer-charged-spying-china-n1236976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The method prosecutors said they used to get Alexander Yuk Ching Ma to reveal the nature of his espionage was worthy of a spy novel itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China partygoers cram into Wuhan water park...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/newsworld/china-partygoers-cram-into-wuhan-water-park/ar-BB183kn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former senior Trump administration official endorses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/17/politics/miles-taylor-trump-joe-biden-endorse/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miles Taylor, a former senior Trump administration official, endorsed Joe Biden's presidential campaign on Monday, becoming one of the highest-ranking former Trump administration officials to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Horrifying' data glitch skews key Iowa metrics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c15b742f95a73ba2a45f7e7bf7d7255d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — A state agency says it is working to fix a data error on Iowa’s coronavirus website that lowers the number of new confirmed cases and therefore downplays the severity of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe clamps down on nightlife to regain grip on pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Europe-clamps-down-on-nightlife-to-regain-grip-on-15489772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe is tightening some restrictions on public life again as summer partying risks reigniting the spread of the coronavirus.  Wary of returning vacationers spreading covid-19 at workplaces and schools, European officials are caught between fostering an economic recovery and the threat of a widespread outbreak.  The concerns prompted Spain and Italy to shut discos and Greece to restrict hours for bars and restaurants in hopes of avoiding more stringent measures after the holiday season winds down.  "We cannot waste the sacrifices made in the past months," Italian Health Minister Roberto Speranza said in a Facebook post. The government also made wearing face masks compulsory from 6 p.m. to 6 a.m. in public venues and in outdoor spaces, including squares and streets, where crowds can gather.  German Chancellor Angela Merkel echoed the sentiment, telling a meeting of her CDU party in Berlin that rising infections are of concern and there is no scope currently for loosening restrictions.  Spain has again emerged as a hot spot, with a 1,833 new infections in the last 24 hours, according to Health Ministry data published Monday.  By comparison, Italy -- the original epicenter of the outbreak on the continent -- reported 320 new coronavirus cases on Monday, the lowest increase in a week. Even so, the number of active Italian patients continued to climb to 14,867.  Irish authorities are considering new measures to curb the pandemic.  In addition to outbreaks at food-processing plants, concern is mounting around potential contagion in bars following a weekend video of a Dublin barman standing on a counter to pour shots into customers' mouths. Ireland's Chief Medical Officer Ronan Glynn described such scenes as "reckless."  "The next three weeks are incredibly important," Irish Health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE wants to connect your shirts, rugs to internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/apple-connected-rug-shirts-internet-patent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus blockchain-based supply chains, robot shelves, Amazon puzzles and other patents from Big Tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FITBITs for Chickens -- Might Mean More Eggs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2020-07-17/supply-chains-latest-fitbit-like-device-for-chickens-boosts-eggs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Klepto Kitty': Neighborhood Terrorized By Cat Burglar...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/08/14/klepto-kitty-citrus-heights-cat-burglar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His name is Jax, but in one Citrus Heights neighborhood this furry feline goes by the name of “Klepto Kitty.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
