<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Judgment Day for Merkel as Migration Divide   Hardens...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-01/merkel-faces-crunch-time-in-coalition-showdown-on-migrant-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fate of Chancellor Angela Merkel’s ruling bloc is due to be decided on Monday as a coalition dispute over migration policy reaches its endgame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boom at Texas hospital: 48 born in 41 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/baylor-scott-white-all-saints-medical-center-fort-worth-baby-boom-48-babies-41-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra staff was called in; pizza ordered and even after 48 babies in a short span of time, the hospital says they are ready for more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea drops max workweek to 52 hours to promote work-life balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/south-korea-officially-drops-its-maximum-workweek-to-52-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL (THE KOREA HERALD/ASIA NEWS NETWORK) - South Korea officially dropped its maximum workweek to 52 hours on Sunday (July 1), in an effort to improve the quality of life among its citizens by tackling the country's notoriously long work hours.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Istanbul Pride to march despite ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/istanbul-pride-organizers-march-despite-ban-090512838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey's lesbian, gay, bisexual, trans and intersex activists planned to go ahead with a pride march Sunday despite a ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NSA 'deleting' 685 million call records due to 'technical irregularities'...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/1/nsa-deletes-685-million-call-records-obtained-2015/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency is deleting more than 685 million call records the government obtained since 2015 from telecommunication companies in connection with investigations, raising questions about the viability of the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  11 bodies, 10 hanging, found in India home...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/police-11-bodies-home-indian-capital-042437208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Police in India's capital said they found 11 bodies in a home under mysterious circumstances on Sunday, including 10 that were blindfolded and hanging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Fall of New York; Death of Once Great City...</title>
      <link>https://harpers.org/archive/2018/07/the-death-of-new-york-city-gentrification/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;harpers.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fall of New York and the urban crisis of affluence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal arrested for starting dozens of CO wildfires...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5905453/Illegal-immigrant-arrested-starting-dozens-wildfires-Colorado-destroying-38-000-acres.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesper Joergensen, 52, was taken into custody last Saturday for the suspected arson that started the Springs Fire. The fire has scorched over 38,000 acres around Fort Garland and La Veta, Colorado</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ambassador to Estonia resigns in protest...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/world/ny-news-estonia-nato-07012018-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James D. Melville Jr. has served under six different presidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangster escapes prison by HELICOPTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-top-gangster-escapes-french-12829634</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Redoine Faïd, 46, reportedly escaped from Réau prison via a helicopter, which was later found partially burned in Gonesse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermont legal marijuana era dawns...</title>
      <link>https://www.burlingtonfreepress.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/01/recreational-marijuana-use-now-legal-vermont/748793002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.burlingtonfreepress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational use of marijuana is legal now in Vermont -- within boundaries of some clear and not-so-clear rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 injured in mass stabbing at Idaho apartment complex...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7c1eb7337664e58ba5fa224ed5cd9a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho police say nine people were hospitalized early Sunday and one man is in custody after a mass stabbing at a Boise apartment complex that is home to many r</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bag rage' hits Australian supermarkets as plastics ban takes effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/australian-supermarkets-prevent-bag-rage-plastics-ban-takes-103953702--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's biggest supermarket chains are scrambling to combat "bag rage" as frustrated shoppers vent their anger over the removal of single-use plastic bags. One man put his hands around a supermarket worker's throat, the West Australian newspaper reported, while grocery stores are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTLAND RIOT: Antifa Attacks Prayer Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/index.ssf/2018/06/portland_police_revoke_permit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Swedish law recognizes sex without 'explicit consent' as rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/swedish-law-recognises-sex-without-consent-rape-093136060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tough new law that will recognise sex without explicit consent as rape comes into effect in Sweden on Sunday, after the country was rocked by the #MeToo movement denouncing sexual harassment and assault. More than 10,000 women in Sweden -- including actresses, journalists, lawyers, musicians, doctors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD to diversify -- by recruiting from Trump country...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/06/30/bacow-promises-more-outward-looking-harvard/775WSyrNerKqGh8B06TM2O/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Bacow, who takes the helm of Harvard University Sunday, promised to be an outspoken advocate for higher education willing to engage a presidential administration increasingly hostile to academia and an American public skeptical about its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submarine sent to find source of MYSTERY sonar noise off US coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/713315/noaa-submarine-shipwrecks-mysterious-sonar-noise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot brothel opens 24 hours-a-day as demand during World Cup SKYROCKETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/712680/sex-doll-brothel-russia-world-cup-moscow-lumidolls-fans-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abolish ICE' becomes rallying call... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/abolish-ice-call-democrats-left-flank-195227858--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Several prominent Democrats who are mulling a bid for the White House in 2020 sought to bolster their progressive credentials this week by calling for major changes to immigration enforcement, with some pressing for the outright abolition of the federal government's chief immigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic elections marred by vote-buying and violence...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-mexico-election-20180701-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mexico's presidential election approaches, the ruling party is accused of using government institutions to try sway the results. Opposition parties warn of possible fraud on election day. And vote-buying has been rampant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President defends 'brave' ICE agents...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/30/trump-defends-brave-ice-agents-as-dems-call-to-abolish-agency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more Democrats join the parade of liberal pols calling for the end of the federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) agency, President Trump is pushing back. “To the great and brave men a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Does Deep Dive on High Court Finalists Before July 9 Pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-29/trump-has-narrowed-supreme-court-list-will-reveal-pick-july-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump spent Saturday engaged in a deep dive into the backgrounds of the top prospects to fill an opening on the U.S. Supreme Court but hasn’t begun interviews with the finalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters responds to death threats: 'You better shoot straight'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/395016-maxine-waters-responds-to-serious-death-threats-you-better-shoot-straight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN: Left needs to face reality: Trump is winning...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/30/the-left-needs-to-face-reality-trump-is-winning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To understand the madness gripping American leftists, try to see the world through their eyes. Presto, you’re now part of the raging resistance. Like the Palestinians who mark Israel’s birth as the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua's crisis deals crushing blow to businesses large and small...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nicaraguas-crisis-deals-crushing-blow-businesses-large-small-012929256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With hotels, restaurants, bars, stores, workshops and even tortilla sellers driven out of business or struggling to survive, and with thousands of people left jobless, the turbulent political crisis sundering Nicaragua has taken a broader toll, plunging its economy into a tailspin. Business closings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO ON THE BRINK: Leftist favorite as Mexico heads to polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/leftist-amlo-favorite-mexico-heads-polls-013217052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed up with corruption and violence, Mexicans will elect their next president Sunday, deciding whether to believe in the change promised by the anti-establishment leftist Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador, the heavy favorite. Leading by more than 20 points in the polls, the sharp-tongued, silver-haired politician</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
