<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Radio host Michael Savage hit with death threats, heads to secret location...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/2/michael-savage-target-death-threats-i-own-3-guns-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City, state and federal agencies are taking a look at a vicious, hateful email sent a restaurant frequented by talk radio icon Michael Savage that threatens to shoot up the establishment if he’s not denied future service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CANCER BREATHALYZER...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jan/03/uk-scientists-test-breathalyser-for-detecting-early-cancers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major study at Addenbrooke’s hospital could lead to cancer detectors in GPs’ surgeries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hackers Threaten To Reveal 'Secret' Data Linked To 9/11 Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/9-11-attacks-september-11-attack-hackers-threaten-to-reveal-secret-data-linked-to-9-11-attacks-1971754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hacker group has threatened to reveal "secret" data related to September 11 attacks in the US after claiming to have got access to a large cache of confidential files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Bernie Sanders, Claims of Sexism Hang Over 2020 Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-bernie-sanders-claims-of-sexism-in-2016-campaign-hang-over-2020-bid/ar-BBRIM7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles unveils earthquake warning app...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6550265/Los-Angeles-unveils-earthquake-warning-app.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) - Los Angeles has released an earthquake warning app that could give LA County residents precious seconds to drop, cover and hold on in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Male model who is suing Bruce Weber for 'soliciting sex' sent the fashion photographer nude images...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6548467/Male-model-suing-Bruce-Weber-soliciting-sex-exchange-work-sent-photographer-nude-pics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In documents filed on Wednesday, Bruce Weber hits back at the allegations being made by Jason Boyce and dismisses the lawsuit as nothing more than a money grab by a failed model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22,000 Minors 'Illegally Crossed' Border in December......</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/01/02/22k-minors-illegally-crossed-border-in-december-says-dhs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOfficials with the Department of Homeland Security say that 22,000 minors "illegally crossed the border" in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APOLOGIZES, VOWS TO 'DO BETTER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/sanders-on-reports-of-harassment-in-2016-campaign-well-do-better-next-time-c6881299-e710-4b7e-80dd-7e6b840b8b89.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He said he wasn't aware of the allegations at the time: "I was a little bit busy running around the country..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren headed to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/423578-warren-headed-to-iowa-after-announcing-white-house-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) will visit Iowa this weekend for a series of events, days after announcing she is forming an exploratory committee for a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump invokes Vatican's 'biggest wall of all'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/423609-trump-suggests-vatican-proves-border-wall-is-moral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday suggested that a border wall can't be immoral because there are walls around the Vatican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Suicide Prevention Program Raises Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://smartinvestor.business-standard.com/market/Compnews-563632-Compnewsdet-Facebooks_new_role_as_global_arbiter_of_mental_distress_is_a_tricky_one.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;smartinvestor.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Market News from one of the most comprehensive financial news networks in India, it provides daily insight of the stock market, industry news, business news, economy news, loans &amp; credit card news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Claims 'Southern Poverty Law Center' Abetted Theft, Spread Lies to Destroy Lawyer for Thought Crime...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/lawsuit-claims-splc-abetted-theft-spread-lies-to-destroy-lawyer-for-thought-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Says Left-wing smear group should lose non-profit status, face RICO prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone finds time for best-and worst-dressed list amid scandal...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/02/roger-stone-finds-time-for-best-and-worst-dressed-list-amid-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He expects to be indicted any minute by Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Ratings Rebound;  'SUNDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL Eyes No. 1 Finish...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/football-ratings-rebound-2018-snf-eyes-8th-no-1-finish-2018-19-season-1202528319/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the national anthem controversy took a toll on NFL ratings last fall, pushing down TV ratings, the games’ performance recovered in 2018, with the main football franchises posting year-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshman class not asking permission...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/politics/nation/democratic-congress-freshmen-tensions-nancy-pelosi-20190101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before the start of the new Congress, the Democratic freshman class is unified, but tensions have emerged that could test Nancy Pelosi's leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl 'cries blood' after contracting mystery illness on cruise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8107438/jordyn-walker-girl-bleeding-eyes-mystery-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEENAGE girl was left blind with blood pouring from her eyes after contracting a mystery illness on family cruise. Jordyn Walker’s face was left swollen – with medics having to remove…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: He 'Will Fold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/ann-coulter-trump-will-fold-on-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest orders purification ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/india-kerala-hindu-temple-women-religion-11079646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women secretly entered one of Hinduism's holiest shrines on Wednesday, breaching a blockade around the Sabarimala temple where devotees have ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW PERMANENTLY BLIND, MEDICAL NIGHTMARE BAFFLES DOCTORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/state-and-regional/my-whole-face-just-turned-purple-missouri-teen-goes-blind/article_33b4107a-b8b0-5642-8fcc-ffc675d8a87b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twice in the past 18 months, Jordyn Walker has dealt with painful facial swelling and an illness that has taken away her senses and left doctors baffled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico finds Flayed god temple; Priests wore skins of dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e4e92bc35ead46309f632ec12df8ddf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican experts have found the first temple of the Flayed Lord, a pre-Hispanic fertility god depicted as a skinned human corpse, authorities said Wednesday. Mexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History said the find was made during recent excavations of Popoloca Indian ruins in the central state of Puebla. The institute said experts found two skull-like stone carvings and a stone trunk depicting the god, Xipe Totec. It had an extra hand dangling off one arm, suggesting the god was wearing the skin of a sacrificial victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: GIRL LOSES SENSES AFTER RETURNING FROM CRUISE...</title>
      <link>https://fox4kc.com/2018/12/31/smithville-15-year-old-faces-medical-mystery-with-positivity-and-determination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox4kc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SMITHVILLE, Mo. -- Imagine feeling perfectly healthy one day, then winding up in the hospital with crippling pain and swelling the next. It's the dilemma facing a Northland 15-year-old right now. And doctors are baffled as to why it's happening. Jordyn Walker enjoyed a family cruise last summer. But when she came back to the states, her medical nightmare began. It started with stomach pain and bloody stools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Pacific garbage patch device breaks, entire system towed back to port...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/01/02/ocean-cleanup-device-great-pacific-garbage-patch-breaks/2465082002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 60-foot chunk of the Ocean Cleanup device in the Great Pacific Garbage Patch has broken off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stoneman Douglas commission calls for arming teachers in tough final report...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/parkland/florida-school-shooting/fl-ne-stoneman-douglas-commission-report-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state commission investigating the shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School unanimously approved its report Wednesday. Now the focus shifts to Gov.-elect Ron DeSantis and the state Legislature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road rage starts with teens egging cars -- ends with mom dead, 14-year-old facing murder charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article223816880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deputies in Harris County, outside of Houston, say three teen boys in an SUV were egging cars when a driver started chasing them, causing a wreck in Aldine that killed a mother on New Year’s Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President invokes Vatican's 'biggest wall of all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12185091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump falsely claims Mexico is paying for wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS PANIC: STILL NO HOST!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/why-oscars-still-doesnt-have-a-host-1172331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Reporter's awards columnist breaks down the challenges — and possibilities — facing the Academy as it nears a record-late date for announcing a host or hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUCH!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6547487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a scathing op-ed Tuesday, Romney referred to President Donald Trump as 'the incumbent.' His niece, Ronna Romney McDaniel, is the Republican Party's chairwoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drop costs Buffett big bucks, adding to struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/buffetts-berkshire-set-to-lose-about-2point8-billion-on-apples-after-market-drop-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Apple's more than 10 percent drop in share prices Wednesday, Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway could be down about $2.8 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daughter warns: She'll 'cut head off' and you won't even know you're bleeding...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/pelosis-daughter-warns-shell-cut-your-head-off-and-you-wont-even-know-youre-bleeding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive incoming House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s daughter issued a warning to President Trump on Wednesday as her mother and other top Democrats met with president to discuss the government shutdown. “She’ll cut your head off and you won’t even know you’re bleeding,” Alexandria Pelosi, a documentary filmmaker, told CNN. ﻿ “That’s all you need to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Rare Cut to Sales Guidance, Blames Performance in China ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-revises-guidance-sees-lower-revenue-in-fiscal-1st-quarter-11546465050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple lowered its sales outlook for its fiscal first quarter, a rare revision to its guidance, blaming slowing sales of smartphones and other devices in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 18 month search for missing body, cops blame GOOGLE MAPS mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/queensland/news/coroner-hits-out-at-police-use-of-google-maps-printouts-in-search-for-missing-man/news-story/0d005d8018e694433313ab2b941c7df4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Darrell Simon set off on his usual morning bike ride from his partner’s bushland home in November 2014, there was an excruciating wait for answers which lasted more than 18 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  STOCK MARKET 'GLITCH' IN DECEMBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/trump-says-stocks-will-rise-once-trade-battle-settled-calls-last-months-market-decline-a-glitch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said there was a "glitch" in the stock market last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeks After 'Blockbuster' Assange-Manafort Scoop, No Evidence Emerges...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/02/five-weeks-after-the-guardians-viral-blockbuster-assangemanafort-scoop-no-evidence-has-emerged-just-stonewalling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. media is very adept at being outraged when they’re denounced as “fake news.” They should think more about why that attack resonates for so many.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Quizzes Brother On Detained American's 'Fake News' Social Post...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/02/cnn-grills-brother-of-detained-american/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whelan could face up to 20 years in prison in Russia if convicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warship spotted carrying 'next gen' hypersonic superweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8105762/china-warship-railgun-superweapon-picture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHINESE warship carrying a terrifying next generation hypersonic railgun suggests Beijing has beaten the world in developing the superweapon. Rumours first circulated last year when images shared…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez bashes 'bad economics' of Dem budget rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/budget-rules-sow-discord-among-democrats-as-new-congress-set-to-open-2019-01-02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are clashing over rules for the new Congress before it even opens, with three members slamming a budget provision they say will hamper their plans for health care and other priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious red sphere spotted flying off SC coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.greensboro.com/news/north_carolina/is-it-a-ufo-multiple-people-report-seeing-flying-red/article_9283f0dc-5c64-5e71-b4d7-e618776e0755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greensboro.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Carolina woman says she filmed a possible UFO off South Carolina’s Kiawah Island on Christmas Eve, and other witnesses are stepping forward on social media to report they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contentious meeting on border security in WH Situation Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-meets-with-congressional-leaders-in-situation-room-amid-partial-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has called for congressional leaders to return to the White House on Friday, top Republicans said shortly after a hotly anticipated, contentious closed-door meeting on border security in the Situation Room concluded Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300-foot tall dust wall devours rural town...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1066318/australia-news-latest-dust-storm-new-south-wales-dubbo-boona-mount-new-year-eve-nye-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPECTACULAR footage has been released of a red dust storm covering Dubbo in New South Wales, Australia, on New Year’s Eve, causing the cancellation of fireworks due to the poor weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK DROPS 7%... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/apple-warns-on-q1-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple lowered its guidance for its Q1 following disappointing iPhone sales and trade tensions between the U.S. and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women describe alleged abuse by nuns: 'Secret not yet told'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/women-describe-alleged-abuse-by-nuns-the-secret-not-yet-told/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trish Cahill says a nun plied her with drugs and alcohol while teaching her how to have sex with a woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE lowers revenue guidance citing weak iPhone sales in China...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2019/01/02/apple-revenue-iphone-tim-cook-letter-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Apple have been in a slump the past few months and a new letter from Tim Cook will likely make things worse. In a letter to investors released this afternoon, Cook relayed that Apple was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start-Up Pushes Women to Give Birth In Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/01/space-childbirth-babies/579064/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A start-up wants a woman to deliver a child 250 miles above Earth. The first question: Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Bernie Sanders, Claims of Sexism Hang Over 2020 Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/02/us/politics/bernie-sanders-campaign-sexism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complaints of sexual harassment and pay disparity by former campaign staffers, which have gone unaddressed by the Vermont senator, could hinder a second presidential run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Brain tumors different in males, females...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/why-are-men-more-likely-die-glioblastoma-study-helps-explain-n953861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain tumors are different in males and females at a basic cellular level, the researchers found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermont top destination for people moving to new state...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6547907/Study-funds-Vermont-state-inbound-moves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont's population is among the smallest in the U.S., but a new study finds the New England state has the highest proportion of people moving there from out of state compared to elsewhere in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey tops list of people leaving...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/02/more-people-moved-out-of-this-state-than-any-other-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey residents are on the outs with their state. More people moved out of the Garden State in 2018 than any other state, according to a new study by United Van Lines – though New York wasn’t …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Beaten By Pack Of Teens At Chicago Train Station...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/video-shows-beating-at-cta-red-line-chicago-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police are looking for a group of male teenagers wanted in connection with several attacks that happened Dec. 29 at the Chicago Avenue Red Line station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binge Watching Binge Eating Blamed for Obesity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/think-you-ate-too-much-one-nation-says-blame-the-internet-11546444899</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online videos of people consuming huge amounts of food are popular in South Korea, but government officials say they can lead to obesity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves use diggers to peel open armored van on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/europe/article/2180452/thieves-use-mechanical-diggers-peel-open-armoured-van-italian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thieves stole US$2.3 million after blocking the security van on the highway between Bari and Matera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD Arrests Suspect In Series Of Celebrity Home Burglaries...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/lapd-arrests-suspect-in-series-of-celebrity-home-burglaries-1202527916/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD has arrested a home-burglary suspect who targeted more than a dozen celebrities – including Usher, Adam Lambert, singer Jason Derulo and The Real Housewives Dorit Lemel – recovering more t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA: Icy object past Pluto looks like reddish snowman....</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52d17627726846dd8f234b6fa2715b48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAUREL, Md. (AP) — A NASA spacecraft traveling 4 billion miles from Earth has sent back its first close-up pictures of the most distant celestial object ever explored, and it looks like a reddish snowman. Ultima Thule, as the small, icy object has been dubbed, is an elongated body about 20 miles long, consisting of two fused-together spheres. NASA's New Horizons, the spacecraft that sent back pictures of Pluto 3½ years ago, swept past the ancient, mysterious object early on New Year's Day. It is a billion miles past Pluto. The pictures from Ultima Thule were revealed Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW kicks off 2019 volatile...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/17422737cb9f4b8aa72260b70e1e4b85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The roller coaster ride on Wall Street resumed on Wednesday, the first trading day of the new year, as stocks plunged in the morning and then climbed their way back by midday. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped as much as 398 points in the first few minutes of trading after more shaky economic news from China. But it soon recouped those losses and turned slightly higher. About two-thirds of the stocks on the New York Stock Exchange were trading higher. That kind of whiplash was typical during the last three months of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital worker known as 'Groin Crusher' has crushed 10,000 'without even a sweat'...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/news/philadelphia/pete-the-groin-crusher-pennsylvania-hospital-20190102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m holding someone’s groin for 20 minutes, they tend to remember me and nobody else."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen was bleeding from eyes, then went blind; Doctors baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article223820240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jordyn Walker, a 15-year-old girl from Smithville, Missouri, fell ill with a mystery disease after she went on a cruise in summer 2017. It came back in December, leaving her without vision, smell or taste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY PLOTS 2020 REVOLT?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Romney-asserts-his-independence-and-Trump-s-GOP-13503426.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For weeks, incoming Utah Sen. Mitt Romney has been tight-lipped as he prepares to be sworn in on Thursday, disappointing his longtime friends who hoped he would emerge as a new power center for mainstream Republicans in President Donald Trump's Washington, particularly with the Senate now without the late John McCain. Romney's tweets last month included a musing on church hymns and pictures of his grandchildren - and nothing about Trump. "Sorry, guys," he'd say as he rushed by and ignored reporters' questions in the Capitol's halls. But on Tuesday night, Romney jolted his allies - and the White House - by publishing a scathing critique of Trump in The Washington Post that said the president "has not risen to the mantle of the office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy Dies From Allergic Reaction To Smell Of Cooked Fish Cooked...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/fish-allergy-eyed-in-boys-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say his father was cooking cod at his home on 82nd Street near Flatlands Avenue Tuesday evening when the boy began to have an apparent allergic reaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Samaritan Holds Drunk Driver At Gunpoint After Destructive Ride...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/01/01/portsmouth-new-hampshire-drunk-driver-held-at-gunpoint-aaron-marconi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged drunk driver hit several parked cars and a sandwich shop before a Good Samaritan held him at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY PLOTS 2020 REVOLT?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/romney-asserts-his-independence--and-trumps-gop-critics-see-an-opening/2019/01/02/6f0aa9d6-0ea8-11e9-84fc-d58c33d6c8c7_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Romney’s assertion of independence is a thunder clap in the GOP, thrusting him forward as Trump’s highest-profile Republican foil in the new Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI SET FOR CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f93f2eb5c4e24cf88ab0d465b49188cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats are sweeping into power this week on a campaign promise of improving government for ordinary Americans. But first, they'll have to get government reopened from the partial shutdown. As the Congress gavels in for the 116th session the early votes will be the usual ones — establishing the House rules and electing the House speaker, presumably California Democrat Nancy Pelosi. But the new majority will quickly pivot Thursday to a pair of bills to fund the parts of the government that have been shuttered in the dispute over money for President Donald Trump's border wall with Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico to Recruit 50,000 for National Guard...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-looks-recruit-50-000-national-guard-162553359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador used his first news conference of 2019 to start recruitment for his new National Guard, which will become the country's primary security force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Protests in India after women defy ancient ban on visiting Hindu temple...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190102110445-phlly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Hindu groups say they believe women of menstruating age will defile the temple's inner shrine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Gov. Inslee running...</title>
      <link>https://www.wect.com/2019/01/02/washington-gov-inslee-running-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wect.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor’s intention to vie for the Democratic nomination was announced in an article published Wednesday in The Atlantic. He intends to focus on climate change as a threat to economic and natural systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul hits 'Big Government' Mitt...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/its-war-rand-paul-hits-big-government-romney-trump-an-actual-conservative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is already taking sides in the battle between President Trump and incoming Utah Sen. Mitt Romney, with Trump ally Sen. Rand Paul slamming the 2012 GOP presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese spacecraft to become first to land on far side of moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jan/02/chinese-spacecraft-to-become-first-to-land-on-far-side-of-moon-chang-e-4 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chang’e 4 to explore giant crater and could give clues as to how moon was formed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC chair slams her uncle...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/02/ronna-mcdaniel-sides-with-trump-1077411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDaniel was critical of Romney, referring to him in a post to Twitter only as “an incoming Republican freshman senator.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots get smarter, cuter, cooler...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/at-ces-2019-robots-will-be-smarter-cuter-and-cooler-than-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the lovable to the practical, robots will be hard to escape at the Las Vegas tech show this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA misses vehicle delivery estimates, cuts prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/31/tesla-4q-2018-production-and-delivery-numbers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla delivered fewer vehicles than expected during the fourth quarter despite efforts to ramp up production. Shares fell in morning trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE MULE' surprises with impressive boxoffice haul...</title>
      <link>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2464311/clint-eastwoods-latest-the-mule-has-made-a-surprising-amount-of-money-at-the-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cinemablend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While everyone is paying attention to the nanny, the Transformer and the fishman, Clint Eastwood's latest is quietly smuggling away a nice box office haul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL sets penalties record for season...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/01/02/nfl-referees-sets-record-most-penalties-called-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the constant conversation topics among fans and media this season, has been how NFL officials have impacted the game more than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 400 Migrants Died Crossing U.S. Border in 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/01/01/nearly-400-migrants-died-crossing-unsecured-u-s-border-in-2018/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 400 migrants lost their lives while or shortly after crossing the U.S. border with Mexico. More than half died in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Fears of Recession Growing Amid Consolidation, Cord-Cutting, Rising Debt...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/recession-hollywood-movie-business-trump-1203096883/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market is tanking, debt levels are rising, China is locked in a trade war with the United States and economics sage Alan Greenspan recently warned investors to run for cover. No wonder pe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Meditation, exercise helps ward off illness...</title>
      <link>https://madison.com/wsj/news/local/health-med-fit/uw-study-meditation-exercise-could-help-ward-off-colds-flu/article_de1ac60e-3032-5f56-8315-76f725145e24.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;madison.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you resolve to meditate or exercise this year — and follow through — you might reduce your chance of getting a cold or the flu, according to a UW-Madison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hill leaders to meet on border in White House Situation Room...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae92bd6af49d43fdb6e59fa70d665572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic and Republican congressional leaders are expected to attend a briefing on border security at the White House as the government remains partially shut down and President Donald Trump asks in a tweet, "Let's make a deal?" The partial government shutdown began on Dec. 22. Funding for Trump's pet project, a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border, has been the sticking point in passing budgets for several government departments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Seattle-ization'? Cities fear what's happened...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/data/seattle-ization-american-cities-fear-whats-happened-here/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You're paying a premium to live here: The cost of living has risen faster in Seattle than in any other American city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrologer reveals where should travel in 2019 according to star sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6545599/Astrologer-reveals-travel-2019-according-star-sign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a new year comes a fresh sense of opportunity and various places to travel in 2019. Now, Australian astrologers Katie Huang and Paula Pavlova have revealed where to go for each sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Most overrated and underrated...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/814715/most-overrated-underrated-2020-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The horse race comes for us all, in the end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC chair slams her uncle for criticism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/423477-rnc-chair-slams-her-uncle-mitt-romney-for-trump-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican National Committee (RNC) Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel, the niece of Mitt Romney, blasted the incoming GOP Senator on Wednesday, saying that the op-ed he wrote criticizing President Trump was "disappointing and unproductive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Vietnam 'totalitarian' law bans online criticism of govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/02/vietnam-criticised-for-totalitarian-law-banning-online-criticism-of-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law forces internet providers to censor content deemed ‘toxic’ by the ruling communist government and hand over user data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers threaten to expose secret 9/11 documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/hackers-threaten-expose-911-documents-13802700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hackers say that the documents will be released unless a hefty, yet undisclosed, ransom is paid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP-FREE SHOW?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/golden-globes-hosts-sandra-andy-samberg-preview-crazy-pants-show-1172092 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first-time Golden Globes MCs interview each other (with The Hollywood Reporter's help) about their "five days" of prep, taking advantage of the "looser atmosphere," why they will avoid Trump and whether they might get, uh, naked during NBC's live telecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron govt on tenterhooks as new tax regime takes effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190102-macron-govt-tenterhooks-new-tax-regime-takes-effect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron govt on tenterhooks as new tax regime takes effect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at CDC for failing to act on mystery polio-like virus; 'Disease is monster'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6545673/Furious-parents-blast-CDC-failing-act-virus-left-hundreds-kids-paralyzed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious mothers of children, who have been left partially disabled and fully paralyzed by the polio-like illness of Acute Flaccid Myelitis (AFM) have blasted the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT RESPONDS:  BE TEAM PLAYER AND WIN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/423455-trump-to-romney-after-op-ed-be-a-team-player-win </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday responded to an op-ed written by Sen.-elect Mitt Romney (R-Utah), suggesting the incoming senator should be more supportive of his policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying Harry Reid on Trump: He's Amoral, Has No Conscience...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dying-harry-reid-on-trump-hes-amoral-has-no-conscience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Senate Majority Leader says Trump lacks the discipline of a mob boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NYT editor rips paper's anti-Trump bias; Eroding credibility...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-n-y-times-editor-rips-trump-coverage-as-biased</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former executive editor of the New York Times says the paper’s news pages, the home of its straight-news coverage, have become “unmistakably anti-Trump.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clever AI hid data from its creators to cheat at appointed task...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/31/this-clever-ai-hid-data-from-its-creators-to-cheat-at-its-appointed-task/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depending on how paranoid you are, this research from Stanford and Google will be either terrifying or fascinating. A machine learning agent intended to transform aerial images into street maps and back was found to be cheating by hiding information it would need later in "a nearly imperceptible, h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California inmate takes unlikely path to freedom: Podcasting...</title>
      <link>http://www.therepublic.com/2019/01/02/us-podcasting-inmate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.therepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California inmate will continue working on a popular podcast after his recent release from San Quentin State Prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Year, Oscar More Likely to Go to Film You've Actually Seen...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2019/01/02/oscars-2019-best-picture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is already heated with big studio blockbusters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Weather App Collects Too Much User Data, Security Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/popular-weather-app-collects-too-much-user-data-security-experts-say-11546428914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weather-forecasting app from TCL Communication Technology Holdings—maker of Alcatel smartphones—asks for data beyond what’s normal for a weather program, a security firm says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$73 MILLION: 20-year-old most expensive American soccer player ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/christian-pulisic-becomes-most-expensive-u-s-soccer-star-after-record-transfer-11546427455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Pulisic agreed a $73 million move to English side Chelsea from Borussia Dortmund of Germany that should see him playing in the English Premier League from the start of next season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Warns Taiwan Unification Is Goal and Military Force Is Option...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/world/article-a-more-confident-china-threatens-military-force-in-taiwan-holds-up/?cmpid=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing intensifies efforts for unification with self-governing democratic region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests in India after women defy ancient ban on visiting Hindu temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-temple/protests-in-india-after-women-defy-ancient-ban-on-visiting-hindu-temple-idUSKCN1OW07Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women defied a centuries-old ban on entering a Hindu temple in the Indian st...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army, in Need of Recruits, Turns Focus to Liberal-Leaning Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/02/us/army-recruiting-tech-industry-seattle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too few recruits are signing up from cities like Chicago and Seattle, so the Army is trying to frame enlistment as a patriotic detour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Open 2019 With Tumble... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/stock-markets-dow-futures-fall-after-weak-economic-data-in-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street is set for a weak start to 2019, as more disappointing data from China weighed on global markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Worst Start Since 1995...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hong-kong-stocks-kick-off-075113201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hang Seng Index closed down 2.8 percent, its biggest loss since Oct. 23. Cnooc Ltd. was the worst performer, suffering its largest drop in nearly three years. The Hang Seng China Enterprises Index retreated below the 10,000 level, closing at its lowest since February 2017, while the Shanghai Composite</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
