<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New Religion Could Rise From Ashes of Q...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-a-new-religion-could-rise-from-the-ashes-of-qanon </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variants may cut shot effectiveness...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/962339/new-coronavirus-variants-may-cut-vaccine-effectiveness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The good news is that the new mutations of the COVID-19 coronavirus found in Britain, South Africa, Brazil, and other countries don't appear so far to be inherently more deadly than other variants. The bad news is that because they spread more easily, more people are getting infected and dying — and the rise in infections is giving the virus more chances to mutate. Worse, the new mutations appear to modestly curb the effectiveness of the vaccines from Moderna and Pfizer/BioNTech, researchers reported Wednesday. Researchers at New York's Rockefeller University and National Institutes of Health took blood from 10 people inoculated with either the Moderna or Pfizer vaccine and tested those samples with coronavirus variants from Britain, South Africa, and Brazil. With some of the samples, the antibodies spurred by the vaccine were up to three times less effective at blocking the virus from infecting cells, Rockefeller's Dr. Michel Nussenzweig said. 'It's a small difference but it is definitely a difference.' Neither these findings nor separate, more hopeful research from Pfizer have been peer-reviewed. Pfizer said Wednesday that a second study has shown its vaccine to be just as effective against several mutations found in the U.K. Moderna and AstraZeneca are also testing their vaccines against various mutations. The vaccines still protect people against developing COVID-19, immunologists say. 'We don't want people thinking that the current vaccine is already outdated. That's absolutely not true,' said E. John Wherry at the University of Pennsylvania. 'There's still immunity here ... a good level of protection,' but the mutations 'do in fact reduce how well our immune response is recognizing the virus.' The vaccines may have to be tweaked — a fairly easy process for Pfizer and Moderna's vaccines — and countries shouldn't count on vaccinations alone, experts caution. 'We've got an arms race between the vaccines and the virus,' Dr. Buddy Creech, a vaccine specialist at Vanderbilt University, tells The Associated Press. 'The slower we roll out vaccine around the world, the more opportunities we give this virus to escape' and mutate. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Worrying case of MMA's 'Proud Girl'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jan/21/tara-larosa-mma-far-right-proud-boys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former professional fighter has been a prominent figure at far-right events but has faced abuse from the same people she runs with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cesar Chavez bust in Oval Office signals new era for Latinos...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Biden-s-Cesar-Chavez-bust-in-the-Oval-Office-15887104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Paul Chavez was watching TV coverage of President Joe Biden's first address from the Oval Office on Wednesday when he suddenly recognized the sculpture right behind him.  It was his father.  The 22-inch-tall bronze bust of civil rights and farm labor leader Cesar Chavez stood just behind the Resolute Desk, surrounded by portraits of the president and his family.  "We were just as surprised and thrilled as everybody else to see its placement, it was so prominent," Paul Chavez, 63, told The Washington Post late Wednesday. "We were excited not just because it was a bust of my father, but what it represented. To us, it was an affirmation of the importance and the contributions of our community, immigrants and Latinos."  For many Latino leaders like Chavez's son, it spoke volumes that Biden decided to make the community organizer's bust a central piece of Oval Office decor. They say it symbolizes his commitment to the Latino community and marks the beginning of a new relationship with a president they hope is far less adversarial than his predecessor.  "It sent a strong message that he understands the pain and the angst that we've been feeling," Darryl Morin, president of the advocacy group Forward Latino, told The Post. "It shows that he's authentic and his concern is for real."  On Wednesday, Biden signed an executive order repealing the travel ban from several majority-Muslim countries, while reversing the Trump administration's directive that attempted to exclude noncitizens from being counted in the census. He also asked the Department of Homeland Security to continue the Deferred Action for Childhood Arrivals program protecting "Dreamers" from deportation and issuing work permits to those who still met the program's criteria.  Other major immigration reform...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 1: Sweeping Executive Orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/21/biden-to-sign-10-executive-orders-to-combat-covid-pandemic-invoke-defense-production-act.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the new administration implements the federal initiatives, it will also emphasize the safe reopening of schools and businesses, the plan says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of LAX Jet Pack Guy: Person-Shaped Drone?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/38802/airliner-pilot-says-jet-pack-guy-over-los-angeles-looked-just-like-this-crazy-drone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months after the first sighting of the jet pack guy over Southern California, we get new insights into the official investigation into the incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs order invoking 2-year lobbying ban...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/535176-biden-signs-executive-order-invoking-2-year-lobbying-ban-for-appointees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden signed an executive order on Wednesday that required all political appointees to sign an ethics pledge including a ban on certain lobbying for two years after they leave the administration, which was designed to restore and maintai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Capable Of 'De-Aging' Brain, Reversing Cognitive Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/scientists-discover-potential-drug-to-reverse-age-related-cognitive-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that a set of immune cells cause chronic inflammation as people age, leading to side-effects like mental decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportations halted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/20/politics/homeland-security-pause-some-deportations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is pausing deportations for 100 days, the department announced late Wednesday, with some exceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Saudi troll campaign targeting Khashoggi movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/An-alleged-Saudi-troll-campaign-is-targeting-a-15886875.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Fogel made the investigative documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More Money Really Does Make Happier...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/making-more-money-really-does-make-people-happier-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The old saying goes that "money can't buy happiness," but a new study finds that's not exactly true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race for Mars Takes China-USA Tensions Into Outer Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-race-for-mars-takes-china-us-tensions-into-outer-space/ar-BB1cW1lO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both countries plan to visit the red planet, the moon, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of crown princes: Oman heir joins youthful Gulf royals...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210121-rise-of-the-crown-princes-oman-heir-joins-youthful-gulf-royals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rise of the crown princes: Oman heir joins youthful Gulf royals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden unveils ambitious pandemic strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210121-as-pandemic-worsens-biden-unveils-ambitious-covid-19-strategy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As pandemic worsens, Biden unveils ambitious Covid-19 strategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Wildlife Fund Sounds Alarm on Turkey Water Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/world-wildlife-fund-sounds-alarm-on-turkey-water-shortages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Wildlife Fund Sounds Alarm on Turkey Water Shortages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psaki Debut: No Attacks, No Lectures, No Crowd Size Fixation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/20/jen-psakis-debut-no-attacks-no-lectures-no-crowd-size-fixation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — There was no discussion of the inauguration’s crowd size. The White House press secretary, Jen Psaki, arrived in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions wade into debate over requiring vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/535143-unions-wade-into-debate-over-requiring-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor unions may soon find themselves in an unexpected role during the coronavirus pandemic: defending members who refuse to take a vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida 'Monkey Whisperer' Charged With Illegal Animal Sales...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/21/florida-monkey-whisperer-is-charged-with-illegal-animal-sales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On its website, the Monkey Whisperer in Central Florida describes itself as a family-owned, “fastidiously clean and well organized exotic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire hits building at world's largest vaccine maker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pune-india-coronavirus-pandemic-fires-6537cec12b3d902958bdebdd257fad6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUNE, India (AP) — A fire broke out Thursday at a building under construction at Serum Institute of India, the world’s largest vaccine manufacturer, possibly affecting its future expansion of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITH RECORD DEATH DAY...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EsNsGmZVEAY00XM?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Mask-Slipping the New Manspreading?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/20/is-mask-slipping-the-new-manspreading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I saw Bill Clinton’s mask slip below his nose during the inaugural festivities, I figured, well, it could happen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush called Clyburn 'savior' over Biden boost...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-2020-joe-biden-donald-trump-elections-south-carolina-5aa4825cdd42d638b52cfb633b66352b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — As they witnessed President Joe Biden take the oath of office on Wednesday, House Majority Whip Jim Clyburn said former Republican President George W. Bush lauded him...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Winter of peril'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/20/biden-speech-inauguration-address-sketch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New president’s inauguration marks a return to the old order, as a longtime moderate prepares to think big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK suffers deadliest day of pandemic, with some hospitals 'like a war zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/uk-suffers-deadliest-day-some-hospitals-e2-80-98like-a-war-zone-e2-80-99/ar-BB1cVOaD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.K. suffered its worst day in the pandemic on Wednesday, with more than 1,800 deaths recorded in 24 hours, as Boris Johnson’s chief scientific adviser warned some hospitals now look “like a war zone.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANGEROUS:  Trump extended Secret Service protection to his adult children, three top officials as he left office...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-extended-Secret-Service-protection-for-13-15885319.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In the days before he left office, President Donald Trump instructed that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems take control of 50-50 Senate, with Kamala presiding for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Democrats-take-control-of-50-50-Senate-with-15885749.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democrats claimed control of the Senate by the thinnest possible margin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's unity plea met with reminders that divisions run deep...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-s-unity-plea-is-met-with-reminders-that-15886036.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas - They had lost a sister to covid-19 and watched in horror as the Capitol...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISGRACED DONALD FLEES TO FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-president-joe-biden-empathizer-010347146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was derided as too entrenched in Washington, too hesitant to campaign during Covid-19, and too old, but Joe Biden outmaneuvered doubters to become the 46th US president Wednesday, inheriting a multi-tiered nightmare that will take shrewd political skill to overcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian village cheers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trailblazer-kamala-harris-americas-first-000659852.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris smashed through one of America's highest glass ceilings Wednesday, becoming the first woman, first Black American and first person of Asian heritage to be appointed vice president, blazing a trail in the most diverse White House ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tells appointees 'I will fire you on the spot' for showing disrespect to colleagues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-tells-appointees-i-will-fire-you-on-the-spot-for-showing-disrespect-to-colleagues-235922489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden issued a warning Wednesday to his appointees that a hostile workplace will not be allowed in his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 1: Sweeping Executive Orders Day One...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-plans-sweeping-executive-orders-to-unwind-trump-legacy-on-day-one/ar-BB1cV2jc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden plans to begin immediately unwinding his predecessor’s policies on immigration, climate and other issues on Wednesday with at least 15 executive actions, including moves to reverse U.S. withdrawals from the Paris Agreement and the World Health Organization, and stop construction of a border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA to enforce rules forbidding hugs with midcourt security...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/30749252/nba-enforce-rules-forbidding-hugs-handshakes-midcourt-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because there were still instances of traditional postgame contact between players, the NBA issued a memo reaffirming rules requiring teams to remain on their half of the court in pregame and halftime warm-ups, and limiting contact after games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moves for Mass Amnesty...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/policy/biden-moves-for-mass-amnesty-in-first-day-as-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Wednesday sent legislation to Congress which would offer amnesty and a path to citizenship to the bulk of the 11 million illegal immigrants currently in the United States, teeing up a potentially momentous struggle with Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pork exec gives $25K to Iowa gov; Company got virus aid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-iowa-iowa-city-coronavirus-pandemic-campaigns-e97f37fa3274b2afd5ff71c05a4a2a24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — An owner of a large pork production company that disproportionately benefited from an Iowa coronavirus aid program recently donated $25,000 to Gov. Kim Reynolds' campaign, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Alarm Bells Over New Strain, Vaccine Stumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden-team-sees-virus-vow-at-risk-on-new-strain-vaccine-stumble/ar-BB1cW3IS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s team is increasingly worried the coronavirus pandemic is spiraling out of control -- imperiling his promise to contain the outbreak -- as cases and deaths mount, vaccinations lag and a more-transmissible strain emerges in the U.S., according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS OFFICIALLY HAVE SENATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/20/democrats-to-take-senate-majority-when-warnock-ossoff-and-padilla-are-sworn-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raphael Warnock, Jon Ossoff and Alex Padilla were sworn in, giving Democrats a Senate majority after Vice President Kamala Harris' inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAN quietly deleted articles about DOMINION...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/oan-deletes-articles-about-dominion-voting-election-conspiracy-2021-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One America News hasn't issued a retraction notice after taking down articles about Dominion, Sidney Powell, Rudy Giuliani, and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioter Compares Himself To Civil Rights Heroes: 'Rosa Parks, MLK Moment For Me'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/01/20/felipe-marquez-storm-capitol-rosa-parks-martin-luther-king-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I went on the 6th to D.C. to protest against communism and prostitution,” Felipe Marquez said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Marks 1 Year Since 1st COVID Case...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/01/20/coronavirus-pandemic-1-year-anniversary-nyc-vaccine-bill-de-blasio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio is calling for dramatic changes in his ability to use his dwindling supply of COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boon for well-connected fraudsters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-defense-contracts-f4dea24fa4adf5a03e08a5271402ca08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former congressman who pocketed millions of dollars in bribes from defense contractors. A Republican fundraiser who paid handsome sums to illicitly lobby a presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official's brush with internet cult gone horribly wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/19/qanon-trump-ezra-cohen-watnick-460520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some believed he was “Q,” the mythical figure behind an intricate and sprawling conspiracy theory. Here Ezra Cohen-Watnick, a senior Trump intelligence official, shares the story of his ordeal for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian village cheers...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/asia/2021/01/indian-village-cheers-for-harris-before-swearing-in-as-us-vp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THULASENDRAPURAM, India (AP) — Residents of a tiny Indian village surrounded by rice paddies flocked to a Hindu temple, setting off firecrackers and praying and as they watched Kamala Harris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the ugly Pentagon transition: 'Shocking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/20/biden-pentagon-transition-460768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to obstruct the Biden team is unprecedented in modern presidential transitions and will hobble the new administration on key national security matters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON now offers to help...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/live-blog/2021-01-20-covid-live-updates-vaccine-news-n1254842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To heal, we must remember," Biden said, as 400 lights illuminated the Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool, each representing a thousand Americans who died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poet Becomes Breakout Star...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/inaugural-poet-amanda-gorman-becomes-the-breakout-star-of-biden-inauguration-such-powerful-and-inspiring-words/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inauguration's breakout star, unquestionably, was youth poet laureate Amanda Gorman. The 22-year-old became the youngest poet to perform at a presidential inauguration, and judging by social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy tries hunting subs with aerial drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2021/01/18/off-the-california-coast-the-us-navy-tests-hunting-subs-with-an-aerial-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy is testing new concepts of operations using aerial drones to hunt submarines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-race-and-ethnicity-coronavirus-pandemic-democracy-257977393cd241c5bde6ee7043f65124</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's inaugural address Wednesday, as provided by CQ Transcripts: Chief Justice Roberts, Vice President Harris. Speaker Pelosi, Leader Schumer, Leader McConnell, Vice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did SHUTTING outdoor dining contribute to California's surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/coronavirus/article/California-outdoor-dining-ban-COVID-19-surge-worse-15882565.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state has had one of the worst winter COVID-19 surges in the country, which begs the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genocide in research labs: Controversial study to count number of dead lab mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/01/19/a-study-that-attempts-to-count-the-number-of-rodents-used-in-lab-research-sparks-a-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 110 million laboratory research animals may be mice or rats, if the numbers are correct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana abuse by youth linked to suicide attempts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/20/health/marijuana-abuse-teens-suicide-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy use of marijuana by teens and young adults with mood disorders -- such as depression and bipolar disorder -- is linked to an increased risk of self-harm, suicide attempts and death, a new study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Person Granted UK Refugee Status For Being Non-Binary...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7axga/i-feel-blessed-first-person-granted-uk-refugee-status-for-being-non-binary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing consistent physical and verbal abuse, Arthur Britney Joestar left El Salvador in 2017. Now they live in Liverpool, where girls stop them in the street to say they love their hair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army testing 'Iron Man' suit for next-generation squad weapon...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/military-tech/army-next-generation-squad-weapon-iron-man-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system is designed to enhance soldier's aim by stabilizing their weapon's barrel against unnecessary movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica strain poses 're-infection risk'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210120-s-africa-virus-strain-poses-re-infection-risk-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;S.Africa virus strain poses 're-infection risk': study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton appears to fall asleep...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/20/bill-clinton-appears-to-fall-asleep-during-bidens-inaugural/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton appeared to be nodding off during Wednesday’s inauguration ceremony for President Joe Biden. Brief video clips posted online show Clinton, 74, with his eyes shut…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALLACE:  'Best Inaugural Address I Have Ever Heard'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chris-wallace-praises-biden-speech-the-best-inaugural-address-i-have-ever-heard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Chris Wallace had effusive praise for President Joe Biden's inaugural address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAnon believers grapple with doubt, spin new theories: 'We all got played'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/QAnon-believers-grapple-with-doubt-spin-new-15884779.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Followers of the extremist ideology QAnon saw their hopes once again dashed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Rebukes Trump In Promise To 'Lead Without Selfishness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/joe-biden-inauguration-2021-01-20/#post-update-852e896b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his hand on the Bible, Mr. Biden vowed to "preserve, protect and defend the Constitution of the United States."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extends clemency to sports gamblers and rappers...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-extends-clemency-to-sports-gamblers-and-a-15884718.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In one of his final White House acts, President Donald Trump granted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEMOCRACY HAS PREVAILED'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/democracy-has-prevailed-president-joe-biden-says-unity-is-the-path-forward-in-inaugural-address/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden called for unity in his inaugural address on Wednesday, saying, "This is America's day. This is democracy's day... At this hour, my friends, democracy has prevailed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TAKES THE OATH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-inauguration-news-0a49b6d8b3c9904d88d5bccfd854ab25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Joe Biden's presidential inauguration (all times local): 12:30 p.m. Garth Brooks has sung a gospel-tinged and beautiful rendition of “Amazing Grace” at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga Anthem...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/01/20/watch-lady-gaga-inauguration-day-national-anthem-performance-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga continued to show her support for President Joe Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris on Wednesday, performing “The Star-Spangled Banner” during the duo’s inauguration …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEMOCRACY HAS PREVAILED'</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210120154932-dszn0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/INAUGURATION (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Biden sworn in as U.S. president, takes helm of deeply divided nation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police officer lauded for defending Capitol escorts new VP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article248630540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The officer was captured in a viral video leading the mob at the Capitol away from the Senate chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge explosion destroys Catholic building in Madrid... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9168209/Building-destroyed-explosion-Madrid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several floors of the building in Madrid's Toledo Street have been affected by the blast, that ripped through the building at around 2:30 p.m. local time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN GOD HE TRUSTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9167931/Joe-Biden-shows-real-power-lies-attends-mass-leaders-parties.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President-elect Joe Biden orchestrated a demonstration of faith and political power before he took the oath of office - attending mass with congressional leaders from both parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK competitions watchdog launches investigation into algorithms used by AMAZONFACEBOOKGOOGLE amid fears they are 'manipulating' lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9167661/CMA-launches-investigation-algorithms-used-Google-Amazon-Facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) will probe fears whether the software used by tech giants is corrupting lives and livelihoods by limiting choice and bumping up prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HITS RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/19/stock-futures-flat-in-overnight-trading-ahead-of-bidens-inauguration-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden will succeed President Donald Trump as the 46th president of the United States shortly after noon ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parade of purple at inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/534999-a-parade-of-purple-at-biden-inauguration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President-elect Joe Biden's inauguration is proving to be a parade of purple, as several high-profile figures are sporting various shades of the "bipartisan" color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE OOOOH...</title>
      <link>https://footwearnews.com/2021/fashion/celebrity-style/michelle-obama-coat-pants-inauguration-joe-biden-barack-dc-1203096343/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;footwearnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former first lady joined her husband for the momentous occasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SET TO TAKE OATH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-inauguration-a01d1ffa7862661914cb92b22e359854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden swears the oath of office at noon Wednesday to become the 46th president of the United States, taking the helm of a deeply divided nation and inheriting a confluence of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxygen thefts mount in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/oxygen-thefts-mount-as-mexico-reports-record-coronavirus-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thefts of oxygen mounted as Mexico reported its highest daily death toll since the coronavirus pandemic began, with 1,584 deaths confirmed Tuesday. There was also a near-record one-day rise in new virus cases of 18,894.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas, Florida turn business hubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/employers-look-to-flee-san-francisco-and-new-york-city-2021-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote work has undermined the importance of living in expensive hubs like San Francisco and New York City, as employers look for cheaper locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unwell' Appearance...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/inauguration-day-2021-donald-trump-unwell-appearance-sparks-chatter-among-americans/#7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As President Donald Trump left the White House for the final time Wednesday morning, plenty of [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claudia Conway Accuses Mom Kellyanne of Physical and Verbal Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/claudia-conway-accuses-mom-kellyanne-of-physical-and-verbal-abuse-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of Tiktok videos posted to Twitter, Kellyanne Conway's daughter Claudia is accusing [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala poised to make several historic firsts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/kamala-harris-historical-firsts-inaugurated-vice-president/35259696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday, history will be made when Kamala Harris becomes the first female vice president and the first vice president of color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHINING' Scene, Stuff of Nightmares, Turns Criminal Case Upside Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/after-prosecutor-uses-the-shining-photo-in-court-accused-bank-robber-gets-new-trial/2672986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey Supreme Court ruled Tuesday that a prosecutor erred by including a photo of Jack Nicholson from the 1980 classic “The Shining,” in the closing argument of a bank robbery trial.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
