<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PRESUMED DEAD:  Search for 124 people stopped as officials prepare to blow up Surfside condo...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/22-dead-surfside-tower-collapse-demolition-ea87a854-7c96-489d-9016-3e79cfcc56a2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The search and rescue mission is expected to resume "minutes" after the demolition, said Kevin Guthrie, head of emergency management for Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Measures in England Become 'Matters of Personal Choice'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/face-masks-to-become-personal-choice-as-uk-lifts-covid-19-lockdown/ar-AALL8zU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A further 24,885 cases of coronavirus and 18 Covid-19 deaths were recorded in the UK on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore to become first in world to STOP counting cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3217277/singapore-stop-counting-covid-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE could become one of the first countries to stop recording daily Covid case numbers in a bid to get life back to normal by treating the virus “like the flu”. The south-east Asi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sha'Carri Richardson breaks silence after weed suspension...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3217079/shacarri-richardson-slams-critics-olympic-games-ban-tokyo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHA’CARRI Richardson has hit back at the “perfect people” who have been commenting on her Olympic ban for smoking weed. Richardson, 21, is currently the fastest woman in the US but was handed a one…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS HOST MARK LEVIN WON'T STOP CRITICIZING OTHER FOXNEWS HOSTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mark-levin-the-fox-news-host-who-won-e2-80-99t-stop-criticizing-other-fox-news-personalities/ar-AALL0dH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m an American first,” says Levin, who also has a popular radio show, "and I’m going to tell it like it is.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black abolitionist Frederick Douglass had nothing but scorn for July 4th because of slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/frederick-douglass-had-nothing-but-scorn-for-july-fourth-the-black-abolitionist-spoke-for-the-enslaved/ar-AALL3t7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What to the Slave is the Fourth of July?” Douglass demanded in 1852 in what is considered one of the most brilliant speeches ever delivered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one rural town without a pharmacy is crowdsourcing to get meds...</title>
      <link>https://www.modernhealthcare.com/supply-chain/how-one-rural-town-without-pharmacy-crowdsourcing-get-meds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modernhealthcare.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY cuts 'boys and girls' from fireworks greeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article252565098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But some praised the change, calling it “more heartwarming” and more inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA test to protect planet from asteroid; Smash spaceship into rock...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/07/03/opinion/following-asteroid-collision-is-only-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plot of countless sci-fi thrillers — a massive space rock hurtling toward Earth — isn’t fantasy. Can a NASA-led team head off catastrophe?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor-Greene, Pompeo targeted in hack of pro-Trump app GETTR...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3217127/trump-app-gettr-hacked-launch-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW social media app set up by allies of Donald Trump was hacked on its official July 4 launch day. The hack targeted GETTR’s most popular verified users which included the app’s foun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli doctors develop 'pig-human' hybrid organ for transplant...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-doctors-develop-pig-human-hybrid-organ-for-transplant-672861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been many attempts to implant animal organs in humans, however there have been very acute rejections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elsa Heads to Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-elsa-forecast-landfall-in-florida-us/974557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm will charge through Cuba before making landfall near the Tampa, Florida, area, and despite its tropical-storm status, it will pose dangers this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden sees virus 'independence'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-holidays-health-783d9b71e62a257964291f6d40384aa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After nearly six months in office, grappling with a pandemic every step of that way, President Joe Biden was determined to party. “This is a holiday weekend,” Biden declared on Friday as he parried journalists’ “negative” questions about the ongoing U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kucinich mayoral campaign creates mailer with bloody Cleveland script sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkyc.com/article/news/local/cleveland/dennis-kucinich-mayor-campaign-bloody-cleveland-script-sign/95-33618026-16d3-4ce9-85ae-6510ae932844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkyc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His team is calling the mailer 'an honest illustration of Cleveland today.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Gov. Abbott has razor-thin edge over McConaughey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/07/04/gov-abbott-rebounds-against-possible-challenger-matthew-mcconaughey-has-razor-thin-edge-over-actor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Greg Abbott, after trailing potential challenger Matthew McConaughey in the spring, has rebounded and now has a slight – but not statistically...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest: Exorcisms on rise as demons now haunt victims by text...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/03/dark-stories-of-catholic-priest-who-performs-20-exorcisms-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US priest Stephen Rossetti, who performs some 20 exorcisms a week, says demons are everywhere — even haunting their victims by text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama lawmaker's home shot at two dozen times...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/04/sen-vivian-figures-alabama-home-subjected-to-several-rounds-of-gunshots-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Vivian Figures’ Alabama home was the target of several rounds of gunfire this past week. The Democratic senator was not home at the time of the incident, but police are saying it was not…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BIGGEST NIGHTMARE:  New DA poised to take over investigation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/manhattan-election-2020-campaign-2016-business-race-and-ethnicity-12d18d5d7be2ecdfe44e5526080a7f5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Alvin Bragg, a former top deputy to New York’s attorney general, was poised to become Manhattan’s first Black district attorney and to take over the investigation of former President Donald Trump after his closest opponent conceded in the Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des Moines faces extreme measures to find clean water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/des-moines-business-environment-and-nature-b7f1e431a601dfb6536452d743012948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — In the dim light just after dawn, Bill Blubaugh parks his Des Moines Water Works pickup truck, grabs a dipper and a couple plastic bottles and walks down a boat ramp to the Raccoon River, where he scoops up samples from a waterway that cuts through some of the nation’s most intensely farmed land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disparaging Video Prompts Explosive Fallout Within ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/04/a-disparaging-video-prompts-explosive-fallout-within-espn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the N.B.A. playoffs started in May, the stars of ESPN’s marquee basketball show, “NBA Countdown,” discussed whether they would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try and try again: Republicans test out myriad attacks on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/561442-try-and-try-again-gop-tests-out-myriad-attacks-on-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are testing out a myriad of attacks against President Biden, trying to turn public opinion against a popular president among key sectors of the electorate in hopes of boosting their chances in the 2022 midterm elections and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Wave of Automation May Be Bad News for Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/pandemic-wave-of-automation-may-be-bad-news-for-workers/ar-AALJQdJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Kroger customers in Cincinnati shop online these days, their groceries may be picked out not by a worker in their local supermarket but by a robot in a nearby warehouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mask could diagnose wearer...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/new-mask-could-diagnose-the-wearer-with-covid-19-within-90-minutes-672732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The face mask has small sensors that, when activated, analyze the accumulated breath droplets and test for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper swarms overwhelm West...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/04/grasshopper-swarms-us-west-drought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drought has created ideal conditions for grasshopper eggs to hatch and for the insatiable eaters to survive into adulthood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic Socialists of America Meet with Venezuelan President Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/democratic-socialists-of-america-meet-with-venezuelan-president-maduro/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DSA, the largest socialist political organization in the United States, has previously called for an end to U.S. sanctions on the dictatorial regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burst pipeline causes 'eye of fire' in Gulf of Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fire-ocean-gulf-of-mexico-burst-pipeline-eye-of-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viral video shows a harrowing image of ships attempting to put out a massive fire that formed underneath the ocean's surface when a gas pipeline ruptured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo vaccinating animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/oakland-zoo-vaccinating-animals-covid-fc088b7b-84b8-4890-8590-ccbe4c77ad3c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Californian zoo says it wants to "reduce the risk of COVID-19" among the animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol, symbol of democracy, off-limits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-michael-pence-dc-wire-health-coronavirus-pandemic-ca928021462570b840a491a9d80f524d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As it has been for nearly 16 months, longer than any time in the nation’s history, the U.S. Capitol is closed to most public visitors. The one-two punch of the coronavirus pandemic  that shuttered the Capitol’s doors in the spring of 2020 and the deadly insurrection by then-President Donald Trump's supporters on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese shun grueling careers for 'low-desire life'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-d2b9f71d73219b32d78709b0afb443ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Fed up with work stress, Guo Jianlong quit a newspaper job in Beijing and moved to China’s mountain southwest to “lie flat.” Guo joined a small but visible handful of Chinese urban professionals who are rattling the ruling Communist Party by rejecting grueling careers for a “low-desire life." That is clashing with the party's message of success and consumerism as its celebrates the 100th anniversary of its founding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appears to acknowledge tax schemes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-appears-to-acknowledge-tax-schemes-while-questioning-whether-alleged-violations-are-crimes/ar-AALKqI5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan District Attorney’s Office charged the Trump Organization and CFO Allen Weisselberg with orchestrating a 15-year scheme to avoid taxes by providing benefits hidden from the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for 124 people suspended as officials prepare to blow up Surfside condo...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3211444/miami-condo-collapse-remainder-of-building-demolished/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE search for victims of the Miami condo collapse was suspended on Saturday afternoon with officials planning to demolish the remainder of the building with explosives. A top Miami-Dade fire offic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wreckage Hints at First Signs of Possible Construction Flaw...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/surfside-condo-wreckage-hints-at-first-signs-of-possible-construction-flaw/ar-AALJKsd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers who have visited or examined photos of the wreckage of the Champlain Towers South condominium complex have been struck by a possible flaw in its construction: Critical places near the base of the building appeared to use less steel reinforcement than called for in the project’s original design drawings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta's Rapid Spread Clouds Summer With Fear of Covid Revival...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/delta-s-rapid-spread-clouds-summer-with-fear-of-covid-revival/ar-AALJH2H?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-spreading delta variant is clouding Americans’ hopes for a carefree summer -- and casting a shadow of doubt over plans to get back to business as usual in the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm embarrassed to be American': Shocking campus video from Georgetown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9753539/Shocking-campus-video-Georgetown-sees-students-struggle-say-proud-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students from Georgetown and American Universities were asked if they felt proud to be American. The Majority of students said they were not proud but none could name a better country than the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald lashes Out:  'It's reminiscent of a communist dictatorship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9753277/Trump-tells-Florida-rally-New-York-prosecutors-behaving-like-world-dictators.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump accused New York prosecutors of behaving like a 'communist dictatorship' as he railed against charges leveled against his company during Florida rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CABLE NEWS RATINGS CONTINUE PLUNGE ACROSS THE BOARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fox-news-really-wants-think-032215334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyIf you’ve been on Fox News’ digital news site or bouncing around the right-wing media ecosphere in recent weeks, you’ve no doubt come across an article or three about the recent collapse in viewership at CNN and MSNBC. And the tanking ratings have largely been tied to the “credibility” issues the two networks supposedly have in covering President Joe Biden’s administration following Donald Trump’s exit from the White House.Lost in all this cove</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'rules are rules' about runner banned from Olympic race for smoking weed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3213426/joe-biden-rules-shacarri-richardson-olympic-ban-weed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden has seemingly backed the Olympics decision to ban Sha’Carri Richardson from competing in the 100m race by saying “rules are rules”. Richardson, 21, was suspended from competing for one mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIOLENT VENICE:    Homeless man beaten by two women on  Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3211225/homeless-man-beaten-venice-beach-tents-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO women in Venice Beach beat a homeless man after a tent city was removed due to residents’ anger about drugs and violence. The vicious beating was captured on video was posted online on Fr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She called 911 to report herself as victim of abuse hours before court hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3211172/britney-spears-called-911-report-herself-victim-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears “called 911 to report herself as a victim of conservatorship abuse” the night before her explosive court hearing. The pop star slammed her conservatorship during a court …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Israeli breakthrough migraine treatment 'zaps' away pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-device-could-zap-migraine-pain-away-new-study-672708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At two hours post-treatment, pain freedom was achieved by 37% of participants with REN compared to 9% of the participants who took oral triptans and over the counter analgesic medications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Dominican Republic turns into vacation from hell: 'We've lost everything'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/trip-to-the-dominican-republic-turns-into-a-vacation-from-hell-we-ve-lost-everything/ar-AALJeYS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was supposed to be an eight-day getaway, a chance for three South Florida brothers to reconnect with family living in the Dominican Republic amid coronavirus lockdowns and quarantine. But four days in, the trip in late July 2020 turned into the yearlong vacation from hell. Now the three brothers hope that a hearing on Monday may finally lead to their ticket back home. The Nalus brothers — ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashad offers 'most sincere apology' to Howard students for celebrating release...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/phylicia-rashad-apologizes-to-students-after-voicing-support-for-bill-cosbys-prison-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I intend to earn your trust and your forgiveness," the former actress wrote in an email addressed to Howard University students and parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vigilantes claimed voter fraud. A thousand false leads later, investigators found one case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vigilantes-claimed-voter-fraud-thousand-120019315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Riverside County investigation illustrates the challenge authorities face when dealing with allegations of massive voter fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala isn't getting any honeymoon, and some Dems are fretting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kamala-harris-isnt-getting-honeymoon-220854640.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris' poll numbers have consistently lagged behind Biden's, and she's getting bad press. Some allies worry the White House doesn't have her back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI muscles up against hackers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fbi-turns-offense-thwart-growing-100000672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For the last several years, FBI agents debated turning the tables on hackers by remotely accessing breached computer networks and booting out the attackers caught in mid-hack.They got their chance earlier this year after state-backed Chinese hackers compromised thousands of private Microsoft Exchange email servers. In response, an FBI special agent petitioned a Houston federal judge on April 9 for authorization to remotely access hundreds of hacking victims’ computer networks and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PzZmvlL3lCs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin 'lockdown lite' as Moscow stops millions from dining out...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/covid/2021-07-03/putin-lockdown-moscow-millions-stop-dining-out-2041443.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the COVID-19 pandemic rears up again in Russia, President Vladimir Putin is following Israel’s example as Moscow stops millions of residents from entering bars and restaurants without proof of vaccination or recovery from the illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Are we next?' Worried high-rise dwellers take photos, seek answers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/are-we-next-worried-high-rise-dwellers-take-photos-seek-answers-after-surfside/ar-AALK9lg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. — After the Champlain Towers South Condo collapsed a couple of miles away from his home, Miami Beach resident Dan Ribeiro began feverishly snapping photos of what he said were concerning conditions in the garage of his high-rise — a condo taller and older than the one that partially collapsed in Surfside. He is so worried about the cracked concrete, rusted steel and water ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
