<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>As home runs fly at record pace, MLB doping question back...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/columnist/bob-nightengale/2019/07/08/mlb-as-home-runs-fly-at-record-pace-doping-steroid-question-returns/1662455001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juiced baseballs are cited as the reason for home runs being hit at a record pace, but what if PED use is also to blame? "You can't help but wonder."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEMUNDO on rise with political coverage, soccer, edgy programming...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/telemundo-presidential-debate-under-its-belt-moves-into-2020-spotlight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long in the shadow of its bigger, older rival, Univision signaled its intent to aggressively cover the 2020 campaign by cohosting the first Democratic debate and airing a one-on-one interview with President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nervous times for friends, enablers...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article232385422.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay voters take pride in Mayor Pete -- but many question whether can win...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-2020-election-buttigieg-gay-voters-lgbt-20190708-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg has made a mark for the LGBTQ community, but many gay supporters question whether the U.S. is ready for a gay president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot films circular objects flying over Grand Canyon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/790555/Grand-Canyon-UFOs-spotted-pilot-peaks-conspiracist-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans rarely seek guidance from clergy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8c8727e06c1a4e81a4b74ff556f49781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal grand jury probing GOP fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5e69440f45024366891330a02c221279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa, Nevada to launch caucus voting by phone for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/iowa-nevada-launch-caucus-voting-phone-2020-64184805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats in the early presidential voting states of Iowa and Nevada will be able next year to skip their states' traditional neighborhood caucus meetings and instead cast their votes over the phone, according to plans unveiled by the state parties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holding grudge can make you ill...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/mind/holding-grudge-can-make-let-go/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of us have harboured feelings of resentment after being hurt or deceived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens to restart centrifuges, ramp up enrichment in next nuclear steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-iran-nuclear/iran-threatens-to-restart-centrifuges-ramp-up-enrichment-in-next-nuclear-steps-idUSKCN1U30Y1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran threatened on Monday to restart deactivated centrifuges and sharply step up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorean follows parents in rare defection to NORTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190708-south-korean-follows-parents-rare-defection-north-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korean follows parents in rare defection to North: media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of bees drop dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/790520/California-earthquake-thousands-bees-drop-dead-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies from protein shake containing 'caffeine from 50 coffees'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/790570/Protein-shake-caffeine-powder-death-dangerous-Blackheath-New-South-Wales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC fighter KO's rival in 5 secs with flying knee; Fastest win ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/790403/ufc-fastest-ko-ever-flying-knee-five-seconds-jorge-masvidal-ben-askren</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports of scabies, shingles, chickenpox at Texas border facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/clint-texas-border-facility-reports-of-scabies-shingles-chickenpox-prompts-calls-for-answers/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are calling for testimony from top Trump administration immigration officials in response to a New York Times report about conditions at the southern border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Satellites Dot the Heavens, Leaving Stargazers Upset...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-satellites-dot-heavens-080000400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Two days after Elon Musk’s SpaceX launched 60 satellites in May as part of a mission to bring quick internet service to people worldwide, astronomers noticed something different.As some of the satellites zipped past the Lowell Observatory in Flagstaff, Arizona, telescopes trained on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In age of deepfakes, could virtual actors put humans out of business?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/jul/03/in-the-age-of-deepfakes-could-virtual-actors-put-humans-out-of-business </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In film and video games, we’ve already seen what’s possible with ‘digital humans’. Are we on the brink of the world’s first totally virtual acting star?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Chance for tropical development in Gulf increases to 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/fl-ne-tropical-system-gulf-20190707-ooquc25hqbb43mru7maofeq4dq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A low pressure system over the southeastern U.S. has 60% chance of strengthening into a tropical depression or storm in the next five days, according to the National Hurricane Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran raises uranium enrichment beyond nuclear deal limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6759b954fcf3492abcfb90a982a85b95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released on Bail?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-released-bail-080000462.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Jeffrey Epstein’s fate may rest partly on whether his lawyers convince a judge he should be freed while he faces federal sex-trafficking charges.Epstein was taken into custody on Saturday in a surprise arrest after years of accusations of child molestation. Prosecutors are expected to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems can save their presidential-nomination process by giving voters real debates...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/save-the-democrats-nomination-process-by-giving-voters-real-debates-2019-07-08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scrap the no-talent show, writes Brett Arends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body found in Florida with more than 100 dog bites!</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/highlands-county/body-found-with-more-than-100-dog-bites-in-highlands-county-investigations-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE PLACID, Fla. (WFLA) – A Highlands County man was likely killed by a pack of dogs, according to autopsy results and investigations conducted by the Highlands County Sheriff’s Office, the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nice Guys Finish First! Research Shows Finding Kind Partner More Important Than Compatibility...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/finding-kind-partner-more-important-than-compatibility-relationships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While sharing interests certainly doesn't hurt, a long-term study on relationships claims that at the end of the day, simply finding a nice and pleasant partner is more important .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS apologizes to police after six officers were asked to leave store...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-starbucks-arizona-police/starbucks-apologizes-to-police-after-six-officers-were-asked-to-leave-arizona-store-idUSKCN1U20I9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks Corp on Sunday apologized after an employee at one of its stores in Te...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES 45 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7222503/Jeffrey-Epstein-prison-El-Chapo-facing-45-years-bars-assaulting-underage-girls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted pedophile, who is now facing federal sex trafficking charges, is being housed at the Metropolitan Correction Center in downtown Manhattan, the same facility as 'El Chapo'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI, ICE using state driver's license photos without consent for facial recognition searches...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2019/07/07/fbi-ice-use-driver-license-photos-without-owners-knowledge-consent/WmDbiCrNNWaWQrVrp7q3CL/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators have turned state Department of Motor Vehicles databases into the bedrock of an unprecedented surveillance infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC To Throw Ticker-Tape Parade...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/07/07/womens-world-cup-victory-parade-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio tweeted after the team's victory Sunday, saying, "You have inspired the entire country -- and New York City knows how to celebrate champions."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's president jeered at match in Rio...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-president-jeered-soccer-match-001951850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro was booed Sunday while attending the championship match of the Copa América soccer tournament at Maracana Stadium in Rio de Janeiro. Bolsonaro was accompanied by several Cabinet ministers and received mostly jeers from 70,000 fans at the stadium for Brazil's 3-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOTING AFTER 7.1 MAG...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/06/its-shocking-ridgecrest-store-looted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local store owner says shortly after he closed Friday night someone cut the power and broke in, stealing the cash register and hundreds of lottery scratchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is 'Big One' coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article232380412.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Accused of Luring Girls to His Manhattan Mansion and Abusing Them...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jeffrey-epstein-is-accused-of-luring-girls-to-his-manhattan-mansion-and-abusing-them/ar-AADZnPh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Attacks FOXNEWS Anchors: Worse Than CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-attacks-fox-news-anchors-in-wild-tweetstorm-worse-than-watching-cnn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump again complained about the weekend news anchor line-up on Fox News, saying it is "worse than watching low ratings Fake News CNN."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Detroit priest removed from pulpit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4158492b0f4e4befa7e97d81d6178119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions flare...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/tensions-flare-over-pelosis-comments-about-four-house-democratic-women-and-border-bill/2019/07/07/a1bf7b04-a0de-11e9-bd56-eac6bb02d01d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speaker faced criticism from some of the four first-term lawmakers as animosity over the emergency aid package lingered in the Democratic caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: THE INTERVIEW THAT STARTED IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/06/opinion/sunday/nancy-pelosi-pride-parade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If the left doesn’t think I’m left enough, so be it,” she told me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cortez hits back at Pelosi for knocking far-left lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/07/politics/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-nancy-pelosi-border-funding-bill/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez responded on Twitter on Saturday to an interview with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, in which Pelosi criticized far-left Democrats in Congress for their vote against a negotiated border funding bill last week, saying "we have to have a solution, not just a Twitter fight."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday talk shows falter in ratings and relevance...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/4/inside-the-beltway-sunday-talk-shows-falter-in-the/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday morning political talk shows have some surprising heritage. It is interesting to note, for example, that NBC’s “Meet the Press” is the nation’s longest running television show, debuting as a half-hour program on Nov. 6, 1947, with serious topics and notable guests — back in the days when anchors spoke in the voice of doom, with an intense demeanor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATIONS SWIRL</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Trump-is-a-huge-headache-for-Deutsche-but-the-14077336.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigations surrounding Deutsche Bank's more than decade-long relationship with President Donald Trump and his business have created a crisis for the German financial giant.  It's caught in a legal tug of war between Trump and House Democrats for the president's financial records and calls for broad investigations of its anti-money laundering practices.  But for the 150-year old bank, Trump is just the beginning of its problems.  Once a global powerhouse, catering to the U.S. elite from a tower on Wall Street, Deutsche Bank's fortunes have waned. Sunday, it announced a major restructuring, including ending its global equities business and reducing its investment bank operations.  The restructuring reportedly will mean a reduction of 18,000 jobs by 2022. The news followed an announcement Friday that Deutsche Bank's investment banking chief, Garth Ritchie, was stepping down by mutual agreement.  Shareholders are growing increasingly frustrated by the bank's lackluster profits and growing legal bills. The bank's stock dipped to record lows in recent months, though it has rebounded some recently.  At its annual meeting in Frankfurt, shareholders quizzed company executives for more than nine hours over a series of missteps that have kept the bank under pressure.  "I'm leading a bank that is undoubtedly going through a challenging period," said Deutsche Bank CEO Christian Sewing, who has been at the bank for more than 20 years and became chief executive in 2018. "I want to bring back the pride people feel in working for Deutsche Bank. This is crucial for motivation." Deutsche was prepared to make "tough cutbacks," he told shareholders.  The bank reported a profit for the first time since 2014 last year, but shareholders are still not satisfied.  Deutsche "used to be the biggest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey's Daughter to prosecute?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/guess-whose-daughter-is-reportedly-a-prosecutor-in-jeffrey-epstein-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long accused of molesting young girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jeffrey-epstein-billionaire-long-accused-of-molesting-minors-is-charged/ar-AADX7RQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs Could Expose Powerful Politicians, Businessmen... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lisettevoytko/2019/07/03/jeffrey-epstein-documents-could-expose-powerful-politicians-businessmen/#37a6096b5ac9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“American politicians, powerful business executives, foreign presidents, [and] a well‐known Prime Minister” could be named.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns will turn Gulf into 'sea of blood'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/790365/iran-us-war-fears-sea-of-blood-nuclear-deal-tankers-cleric-gulf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA defeats Netherlands 2-0 in Women's World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7221813/U-S-womens-soccer-team-plays-fourth-World-Cup-title-against-Netherlands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is vying for its fourth Women's World Cup title when it meets the Netherlands on Sunday. The U.S. is the defending champion, while the Dutch are in their first final.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked secret cables...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7220875/UK-Ambassador-USs-memo-says-doesnt-believe-Trump-stopped-Iran-strike-kill-150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a damning indictment of Trump's administration, Britain's Ambassador to Washington described '36 hours of contradictory messaging' after Iran shot down a US drone (stock RQ-4 Global Hawk).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump quote surfaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/jeffrey-epstein-trump-link-liking-women-on-the-younger-side-2019-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeffrey Epstein was arrested on sex trafficking charges, a quote from Trump about the billionaire liking women 'on the younger side' resurfaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran raises uranium enrichment beyond nuclear deal limits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b969f30f6b1143a9914caadc44297ad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA wants to dump 1.5 tons of rat poison on Farallon Islands. Biologists say it's best...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-farallon-islands-rat-poison-20190707-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's Farallon Islands are overrun with swarms of invading mice. The federal government says it must poison them to stop an ecological disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple sues fertility clinic after 'giving birth to two babies who belonged to other people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7221117/Asian-couple-sues-fertility-clinic-giving-birth-two-babies-belonged-else.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York couple is suing CHA Fertility Center in Los Angeles after giving birth to someone else's babies. Clinic co-owners Simon Hong (right) and Dr. Joshua Berger (left) are seen above.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans have no plans to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/7/1-4-americans-have-no-plans-retire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one-quarter of Americans say they never plan to retire, according to a poll that suggests a disconnection between individuals’ retirement plans and the realities of aging in the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare on the ropes in federal appeals court?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/07/07/affordable-care-act-obamacare-faces-doom-federal-appeals-court/1633128001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The health care law has helped insure 20 million people since 2010 and survived two Supreme Court battles in 2012 and 2015, but it's threatened again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab grown STEAKS could soon be on the menu...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7218283/Lab-grown-STEAKS-soon-menu-thanks-breakthroughs-cultured-meats-experts-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animal cells can replicate most of the meat experience, says Natalie Rubio, from Tufts University. But without blood vessels and connective tissue, you get neat 3D tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival charging double for tickets for 'non-people of color'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/festival-charges-double-ticket-price-for-non-people-of-colour-11758249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial pricing plan has led to one artist pulling out of the event, saying she was "enraged" by the policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems embrace religion in campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9de001e6bb7843618ab42fc3ee674584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Trump reaches career-high approval...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-reaches-career-high-approval-faces-range-reelection/story?id=64117018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolstered by the economy, Donald Trump reached his highest approval in this poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O WON'T DEFEND JOE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michelle-obama-comment-biden-apology-holds-off-endorsement/story?id=64174424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Democratic presidential candidates took the stage at the Essence Festival on Saturday, but it was a former inhabitant of the White House who got a rock star's welcome -- regardless of her tendency to deflect questions on the 2020 election. Former first lady Michelle Obama refused to comment...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
