<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Weighs pardons for servicemembers accused of war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/vets-contractors-families-await-trump-pardon-decision-after-war-crime-convictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is considering potential pardons for military members and contractors accused of war crimes as Memorial Day approaches -- deliberations that have prompted warnings from critics that the move could undermine the rule of law but also raised the hopes of their families who say the servicemembers were wrongly prosecuted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW longest weekly losing streak since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/stock-market-slight-rebound-after-trade-fears-roil-markets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Friday, but notched weekly losses as investors worried the U.S.-China trade war is hurting economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum sorry for racist 'no watermelons' remark...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-48402601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teacher accuses staff at the Museum of Fine Arts in Boston of racism towards her pupils.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo 'elaborate ruse' to escape prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/24/el-chapo-is-lying-about-prison-life-to-plot-an-escape-prosecutors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman is only whining about his lack of earplugs and outdoor activity as an elaborate ruse to escape prison ahead of sentencing, according to a new court filing. Guz…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 600 birds and pit bulls rescued tied to animal fighting...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2019/05/23/nearly-600-birds-dogs-rescued-from-indiana-properties-allegedly-tied-to-animal-fighting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGAN COUNTY, Ind. – A Crime Stoppers tip led to a pair of search warrants being served in Morgan and Owen counties, where hundreds of birds and dogs were recovered as part of an animal fighting investigation. As a result of the raids, Martin Anderson of Camby was arrested at his home on Hadley Road at about 9 a.m. Thursday. At that location, investigators say they seized one pit bull and searched for documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botswana hires Hollywood firm to fight elephant hunting PR...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtrf.com/entertainment/botswana-hires-hollywood-firm-to-fight-elephant-hunting-pr/2024969841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtrf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - The Botswanan government has enlisted a public relations firm with deep ties to Hollywood to push back against the bad publicity generated by the southern African nation's decision to lift its ban on elephant hunting.42 West, a firm mostly known for its work with celebrities and the film industry, notified the U.S. Justice Department last week that it will be working with Botswana's tourism ministry, according to a filing made under the Foreign Agents Registration Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Bolton's dangerous 'obsession'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190524-john-bolton-nuclear-iran-military-trump-usa-ayatollah-khamenei</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the US announced plans on Friday to send 1,500 more troops to the Middle East amid hostilities with Iran, analysts say the ultra-hawkish National Security Adviser John Bolton has driven much of the escalation in tensions between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils 372MPH train...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/china-highspeed-maglev-prototype/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new high-speed maglev train capable of hitting speeds of 600 kilometers per hour (about 372 miles per hour) is one step closer to reality in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian heroes to power new MARVEL series...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/asian-asian-american-heroes-power-new-marvel-comics-series-n1010126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marvel Comics is giving ink to an unprecedented team-up of its mightiest Asian and Asian American heroes, also known as the new Agents of Atlas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY WORLD employee busted trying to lure child for sex...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/disney-world-employee-charged-with-trying-to-lure-child-for-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, FLA. (WSVN) - A Disney World employee has been arrested and accused of trying to lure an 8-year-old child for sex. According to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to get respite from Washington woes in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/445444-trump-to-get-respite-from-washington-woes-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump arrives in Japan this weekend for a visit heavy on ceremony and light on pressure to get things done, offering him a respite from a series of difficult developments in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 more deaths on traffic-jammed Everest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-more-deaths-overcrowded-everest-075220256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A traffic jam of climbers in the Everest "death zone" was blamed for two of four new deaths reported Friday, heightening concerns that the drive for profits is trumping safety on the world's highest peak. Nepal has issued a record 381 permits costing $11,000 each for the current spring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Companies Building Exoskeleton Around Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/05/spacex-satellites-starlink/590269/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX and its competitors plan to envelop the planet with thousands of small objects in the next few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL HUMILIATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2019/05/theresa-may-resigns/590218/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British prime minister, who said she will resign on June 7, had one job: to deliver Brexit. She failed to do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking temps expected as 'death ridge' hits Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2019/05/24/heat-wave-more-like-death-ridge-weather-tennessee-georgia-memorial-day/1220545001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high temperatures are expected to hit portions of the South as a dangerous heat wave, also dubbed death ridge, spreads across the region over Memorial Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA okays $2M medicine, most expensive ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/05/24/hold-novartis-zolgensma-approval/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as Zolgensma, the gene therapy treats children under two years of age with spinal muscular atrophy, an inherited neuromuscular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle explores congestion pricing...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/seattle-explores-congestion-pricing/952094235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle said Thursday it’s exploring possibly charging drivers to use some city streets to ease congestion and reduce pollution – using tolls to clear roads during peak driving times and shift people to public transportation and carpools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP MORGAN slashes GDP forecast to just 1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/jp-morgan-slashes-second-quarter-gdp-forecast-to-just-1percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.P. Morgan economists say they now see a much slower economy in the second quarter, with growth of just 1%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will use loophole to sell arms to Saudis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4a1fef7a381045a783b27479f191809d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration notified Congress on Friday that it is invoking a rarely used provision in federal law to bypass congressional review of arms sales to Saudi Arabia, two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon eyes expanding DARPA future warfare research...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190524104353-xy3gm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DEFENSE/RESEARCH:Pentagon eyes expanding DARPA future warfare research office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband on team Nancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7067171/Kellyannes-husband-blasts-Trump-saying-Pelosi-playing-like-drum-impeachment-battle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Counselor to the President Kellyanne Conway’s husband George Conway believes House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is winning the impeachment battle against President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: 'Medical Episode'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/24/rep-jerry-nadler-medical-episode/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nadler is the chairman of the House Judiciary Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK plans cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/may/24/facebook-plans-to-launch-globalcoin-cryptocurrency-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg met governor of Bank of England last month to discuss decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Newspaper Editors Alarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/top-newspaper-editors-dean-baquet-marty-baron-matt-murray-alarmed-by-assange-indictment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newsroom chiefs at NYT, WaPo, and WSJ raised concerns about the Trump administration’s latest threat to the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glittery film festival literally costs the earth... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannes-glittery-film-festival-literally-costs-earth-110019310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fleet of energy-guzzling luxury yachts and private planes, kilos of gourmet food dumped, limousines driving stars just a few hundred metres: for environmentalists, the Cannes film festival is just "one big mess". "There is, without a doubt, a huge amount that needs to be done by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenya's High Court Upholds Ban on Gay Sex...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/kenyas-high-court-unanimously-upholds-ban-gay-sex-150352631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Same-sex relationships are a crime in more than 70 countries around the world, almost half of them in Africa. Neighboring Uganda once enacted a law imposing a life sentence for certain acts of gay sex although it was later nullified by court. South Africa is the only African nation to have legalized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sending 1,500 more troops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/10044ee6ce494283ba4c2e7f86f7b650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration notified Congress on Friday that it plans to send about 1,500 additional troops to the Middle East amid heightened tensions with Iran, officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: The conspiracy to bring down Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/05/gridlock-first-then-down-impeachment-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a stroke felled Woodrow Wilson during his national tour to save his League of Nations, an old rival, Sen. Albert Fall, went to the White House to tell the president, “I have been praying for you, Sir.” To which Wilson is said to have replied, “Which way, Senator?” Historians are in dispute as to […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Director Trolls Cannes With 3-1/2 Hour Pornographic 'Provocation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mektoub-my-love-intermezzo-film-review-abdellatif-kechiche-trolls-cannes-nsfw-excess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannes 2019: This sexually explicit three-and-half-hour-long provocation feels like a director self-immolating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog survives after shot rescuing family during home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/crime/dog-rescues-family-before-being-shot-during-home-invasion-police-say/285-ee5ba32d-b5b6-4b06-8e16-4341204e58fb </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog attacked the gunmen, allowing the father to grab his gun and chase the intruders away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Ratings Freefall: 90% of Broadcast Shows Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ratings-broadcast-network-series-2018-19-1213344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Same-day numbers may not tell the whole story, but nearly every show's starting point retreated from the previous season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Wants To Scan Bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90355120/would-you-let-amazon-3d-scan-your-body-for-a-25-gift-card</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because the company is looking for volunteers to do just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to Testify IN PRIVATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/robert-mueller-wants-to-testify-in-private-before-congress-jerrold-nadler.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler says Mueller told the committee he would make his opening statement before the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter of Americans say in credit card debt to pay for necessities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/23/nearly-25-percent-of-americans-are-going-into-debt-trying-to-pay-for-necessities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey found that 23% of Americans say that paying for basic necessities such as rent, utilities and food contributes the most to their credit card debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says talks won't resume unless Trump changes position...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c20ba627fe4c4c38a45246e4df5ffb8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Friday that nuclear negotiations with the United States will never resume unless the Trump administration moves away from what Pyongyang described as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ramps up war of rhetoric in trade standoff with US...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67e83f62aa7340249637c83c77a7597b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Stepping up Beijing's propaganda offensive in the tariffs standoff with Washington, Chinese state media on Friday accused the U.S. of seeking to "colonize global business" with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS, VOICE CRACK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ac10eef56b941b6b2f405a3319a7720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Bowing to the inevitable, Theresa May announced Friday that she will step down as U.K. Conservative Party leader in two weeks, admitting defeat in her attempt to take Britain out of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal swims across Niagara River...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-accused-of-swimming-across-niagara-river-to-enter-us-illegally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday evening U.S. Border Patrol agents assigned to Niagara Falls Station responded to a report of a man swimming across the Niagara River, just south of the Whirlpool Bridge in Niagara Falls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-U.S. marine held by Russia on spying charge complains of threats...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190524143843-58dwl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/ESPIONAGE-WHELAN (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Ex-U.S. marine held by Russia on spying charge complains of threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley loves sanctuary label, but housing crisis testing liberal values...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Berkeley-loves-its-sanctuary-label-but-a-housing-13890080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY, Calif. - This eccentric Northern California enclave was a sanctuary long before the designation became a must-have merit badge for any left-leaning city.  Berkeley politicians proclaimed the place a refuge for Navy sailors resisting deployment to the Vietnam War nearly a half-century ago. It was the birth of a movement to protect the outcast - and, in some cases, the outlaw - from rules that this beat-of-its-own-drum city and its followers found immoral, most recently the deportation of undocumented immigrants.  But California's housing crisis is testing whether Berkeley can remain that kind of place.  Faced with sharp criticism from a changing population, city leaders have banned people from living in recreational vehicles here, proving that even the most accepting of cities is not immune to the demands that often accompany wealth and gentrification. Businesses and residents have complained about the RVs' blighting of city streets and the burden they place on public safety and sanitation services.  "We had to do something," said Mayor Jesse Arreguín, referring to the March city council vote. "The ordinance we passed, I will admit we rushed into it. But we were facing a lot of pressure from businesses and residents."  The outcry over the ban was instant. The anger came from progressive neighbors such as Oakland, which feared that a scores-long caravan of RVs would soon head across the invisible city limits to its streets. The council suspended the law's enforcement until a more collective approach to the borderless problem might be found.  But Berkeley's move serves as a parable for how one seemingly small government decision and a lack of basic coordination can rumble through a region short on housing and high on frustration. The ban was itself a reaction to steps larger cities and the state have taken that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air rage passenger collapses, dies after 'trying to strangle woman' on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/air-rage-passenger-collapses-dies-16192810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed 32-year-old from Russia was pronounced dead by paramedics waiting for the Red Wings plane on the runway</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenya's High Court Upholds Ban on Gay Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/24/health/kenya-lgbtqi-ruling-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a blow to the LGBTQI movement in Africa, Kenya's High Court ruled Friday that a colonial-era law banning same-sex relations should remain in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After shark attacks, Cape Cod ready for tourist season?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9081f9d149714b68921f705a68b38203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLFLEET, Mass. (AP) — As Cape Cod's tourist season gets underway, there's uncertainty after two shark attacks — including Massachusetts' first fatal attack since 1936 — rattled beachgoers last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJO'S TO LOSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9145100/theresa-may-resigns-boris-johnson-favourite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson looks set to take over from Theresa May as Prime Minister now she’s finally announced she will step down. The 54-year-old ex-Foreign Secretary revealed last week he WOULD run to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX successfully deploys 60 internet satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/05/23/spacex-starlink-launch/?utm_campaign=homepage&amp;utm_medium=internal&amp;utm_source=dl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 SpaceX Starlink satellites are on their way into orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shows Employee Bathing In WENDY'S Kitchen Sink...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/23/viral-video-appears-show-man-bathing-wendys-kitchen-sink/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee who appeared to be taking a bath in an industrial sink at a Florida Wendy's "no longer works" at the restaurant, according to the franchise owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Shirtless Man Goes On Rock-Throwing Rampage In Middle Of LA Boulevard...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/23/shirtless-man-goes-on-rock-throwing-rampage-targeting-buses-motorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the passengers were brave enough to go back onto the bus and, together, they threw the man off the bus and slammed him to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley loves sanctuary label, but housing crisis testing liberal values...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/berkeley-loves-its-sanctuary-label-but-a-housing-crisis-is-testing-its-liberal-values/2019/05/23/805b2b48-7721-11e9-b3f5-5673edf2d127_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As homelessness surges, the Northern California city’s move to push out campers and their occupants triggers anger from its neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil at 'TONIGHT SHOW' after Fallon stunning ratings loss...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/05/23/turmoil-at-tonight-show-after-jimmy-fallons-stunning-ratings-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve learned that Fallon’s longtime producer Katie Hockmeyer has now left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_t25xAp270o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May has named 7 June as the day she will step aside as Conservative leader, drawing her turbulent three-year premiership to a close. May says it has ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANCE ARMSTRONG: It wasn't legal but I wouldn't change a thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/may/24/lance-armstrong-it-wasnt-legal-but-i-wouldnt-change-a-thing </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeach Bolsonaro? Just Five Months In, Talk Has Already Begun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeach-bolsonaro-just-five-months-090001196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Propelled to the presidency by a vociferous army of online ideologues, including his sons, Bolsonaro’s government comprises an uneasy mix of radicals, pragmatists and economic liberals. In his five months in office, Bolsonaro has done little to rein in the extremist fringe, even when they target Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY CALLS IT A DAY... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9144415/theresa-may-resigns-brexit-tory-leadership-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEARFUL Theresa May today finally admitted her time was up and quit as Prime Minister insisting: “I’ve done my best”. The PM was forced to resign after she failed to deliver Brexi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPERM COUNTS DECLINE; PLASTICS TO BLAME?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/24/toxic-america-sperm-counts-plastics-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study that tested both men and dogs added to concerns that chemicals in the environment are damaging the quality and quantity of sperm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS, VOICE CRACKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/theresa-resignation-live-pm-holds-16192866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After almost three years of gridlock, Theresa May has named her resignation date and plunged the nation into a chaotic Tory leadership race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1131491/theresa-may-resigns-next-prime-minister-Tory-leader-boris-johnson-dominic-raab-andrea-lead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA MAY has tearfully announced she will stand down as Prime Minister and Conservative leader in two week’s time on June 7 following significant pressure for her to quit - but who will replace her in the top job? Here are all the runners and riders for the top position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'VE DONE MY BEST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7066101/PM-summons-inner-circle-Downing-Street-gets-ready-quit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM announced her departure in an emotional statement on the steps of Downing Street after meeting Tory backbench chief Sir Graham Brady and giving the news to her staff behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/uk-politics-48394091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest reaction as Mrs May announces she will step down as party leader on 7 June</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinating genius: Did da Vinci have attention disorder?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190523224436-nov8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-DAVINCI/ (PIX):Procrastinating genius: did da Vinci have attention disorder?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to Testify IN PRIVATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/05/23/nadler-mueller-wants-to-testify-in-private/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday's broadcast of MSNBC's "Rachel Maddow Show," House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler (D-NY) stated that Special Counsel Robert Mueller | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES DEATH PENALTY?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-23/assange-faces-death-penalty-doj-files-espionage-act-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM DEBATES START IN MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/23/bill-de-blasio-and-michael-bennet-2020-democrats-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20 podiums allotted for the first Democratic presidential debates are quickly filling up, and the decision about who gets on stage could soon become much more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN: NO SURRENDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-commander/iran-says-it-will-not-surrender-even-if-it-is-bombed-idUSKCN1ST13X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will not surrender to U.S. pressure and will not abandon its goals even if ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused 'sex cult' leader had trouble having sex, trial witness says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-cult-leader-erectile-dysfunction-20190523-oepapt2slncxnlb2aag7qzgfx4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The charismatic leader of a controversial “sex cult” had trouble having sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: 'Villainous' Trump wants us to impeach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/pelosi-trump-wants-be-impeached-n1009236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House speaker's message to Democrats came as vocal support for impeachment rose among lawmakers in the caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-security Ebola burials spark dismay, anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190524-high-security-ebola-burials-spark-dismay-anger-dr-congo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-security Ebola burials spark dismay, anger in DR Congo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORK 9-HOUR WEEK TO SAVE PLANET?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/780956/britain-nine-hour-week-work-greenhouse-gas-emissions-united-nations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago slips in population but still third-largest in USA... </title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-census-chicago-metro-population-towns-05172019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago remains the third-largest U.S. city, though fourth-place Houston continued to close the gap, new census data show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do swarms of tiny temblors rattling West Coast warn of catastrophic quake?</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article230765154.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>185K Released in 5 Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/22/dhs-releases-7-9k-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-8-days-185k-released-in-5-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's DHS has released about 7,900 border crossers and illegal aliens into the U.S. in the past eight days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Movie Boxoffice Lagging Well Behind Previous Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/05/23/endgame-did-not-save-a-box-office-still-10-behind-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With "Avengers: Endgame" running out of steam, this year's box office still lags ten percent behind 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOONEY ISIS FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/05/23/george-clooney-worried-for-kids-safety-as-amal-works-on-isis-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have real security issues on a daily basis,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE MONDE director summoned by French intelligence service...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/le-monde-director-summoned-french-intelligence-211346945.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The managing director of the newspaper Le Monde, Louis Dreyfus, said Thursday he has been summoned for questioning by France's domestic intelligence agency, following a similar order against one of the daily's senior reporters. Dreyfus told AFP he and Ariane Chemin -- who broke the story of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Taliban' Lindh released as Afghan war still boils...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/american-taliban-lindh-released-afghan-war-still-boils-191325947.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Walker Lindh, the US Muslim convert who came to be known as the "American Taliban" after being captured while fighting in Afghanistan in 2001, was released Thursday after serving 17 years in a federal prison. The US Bureau of Prisons confirmed his early morning release from the federal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Booms...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-largest-cities-shrinking-040101410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fort Worth, Texas, is now the 13th most populous U.S. city, surpassing both San Francisco and Columbus, Ohio, according to newly released population estimates from the Census Bureau. Fort Worth grew by 19,552 residents during the twelve-month period ending in July 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ce08485cee37470db8983b8bd06c40a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — She's calling for an "intervention" to save the nation from him. He says she's "crazy." The enmity between President Donald Trump and House Speaker Nancy Pelosi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILLEGALS FLOOD CITIES FAR FROM BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c7aec8b18ae4cb3a8ed0a624c641eb9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A surge of asylum-seeking families has been straining cities along the southern U.S. border for months, but now the issue is flowing into cities far from Mexico, where immigrants are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-help guru filmed using N-word repeatedly...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/janebradley/tony-robbins-filmed-using-racial-slurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows the self-help guru using the n-word repeatedly and describing how he responded to a skeptical participant by getting “in her face” and kissing her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel agencies ordered to cooperate with 2016 campaign 'spying' probe...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/445347-trump-orders-intel-agencies-to-cooperate-with-barr-probe-into-spying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has ordered U.S. intelligence officials to cooperate with Attorney General William Barr's investigation into surveillance of members of his 2016 campaign, the White House said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Investigate the investigators' escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9e926bfccb5947d5a5f8eb260cb0a7e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump directed the U.S. intelligence community on Thursday to "quickly and fully cooperate" with Attorney General William Barr's investigation of the origins of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper plate Kurt Cobain ate pizza off of sells for $22,000...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox46charlotte.com/news/unusual/a-paper-plate-that-kurt-cobain-ate-pizza-off-of-just-sold-for-22000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox46charlotte.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California-based auction house Julien&amp;rsquo;s Auctions, which specializes in celebrity memorabilia, just sold an old paper plate that Kurt Cobain ate pizza off of and wrote a set list on for a staggering $22,000.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarium mystified by birth of baby anacondas in all-female exhibit...</title>
      <link>https://whdh.com/news/new-england-aquarium-mystified-by-birth-of-baby-anacondas-in-all-female-exhibit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whdh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (WHDH) - Two green baby anacondas were recently born in an all-female exhibit at the New England Aquarium in Boston, making them “biological celebrities”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots conduct daily health inspections of schoolchildren...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2204279-robots-conduct-daily-health-inspections-of-schoolchildren-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of preschools in China are using robots to give students heath checks. Each morning they examine pupils looking for signs of contagious diseases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Letters Underscore Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/American-Taliban-John-Walker-Lindh-Prison-Letters-ISIS-Terrorism-510286491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prison letters from the Northern California man who became known as the 'American Taliban' after his capture by U.S. forces in the 2001 invasion of Afghanistan underscore concerns among authorities that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials fighting measles outbreaks threaten rare air travel ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Officials-fighting-US-measles-outbreaks-threaten-13884328.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in five states have warned people believed to be infected with measles and planning to travel that a federal regulation could prevent them from boarding planes.  All eight individuals agreed to cancel their flights after learning the government could place them on the "do not board list" managed by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, said Martin Cetron, director of the agency's Division of Global Migration and Quarantine, which tracks disease outbreaks.  "The deterrent effect is huge," even in cases like these where the government's authority was not invoked, Cetron said. The agency had been contacted about the individuals by health officials from New York, California, Illinois, Texas and Washington state, CDC officials said.  Officials are often reluctant to talk about the government's travel ban authority "because it is a politically charged and politically visible request," said Lawrence Gostin, a professor of global health policy at Georgetown University.  The step is less restrictive than other public health measures like isolation or quarantine, but it "is seen as a government using its power over the people and the states, which is kind of toxic in America right now," said Gostin. "There is nothing unethical or wrong about it. It's just plain common sense that if you have an actively infectious individual, they should not get on an airplane."  Health officials emphasize that vaccination is the best and most effective way to protect against measles and that the majority of people with infectious, communicable diseases, like measles, listen to doctors' advice to not travel.  But for those who insist on traveling, federal authorities can use the list, which is managed by the CDC.  Officials in Rockland County, New York, and New York City, at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-13 gangster guilty of killing man for wearing Peyton Manning jersey...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/23/ms-13-gangster-convicted-of-killing-man-for-wearing-peyton-manning-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MS-13 gangster was found guilty on Thursday of conspiring to kill a man for wearing a No. 18 Peyton Manning jersey. Jose Suarez, also known as “Chompira,” was convicted on murder, racketeering a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: GOVT DECLARES WAR ON JOURNALISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/edward-snowden-doj-declared-war-on-journalism-by-charging-julian-assange-with-espionage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edward Snowden said the Justice Department declared "war" on journalism after accusing WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange of violating the Espionage Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record store bans Morrissey over political views...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/worlds-oldest-record-store-bans-morrissey-sales-because-he-has-a-different-opinion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diversity of thought? Not here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Trump faked being disabled to get out of Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445220-buttigieg-trump-faked-being-disabled-to-get-out-of-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Pete Buttigieg on Thursday hammered President Trump for in the past saying he had bone spurs to avoid being drafted into the Vietnam War, saying he faked the disability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jimmy Pitaro silenced screams of 'left-wing' ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/23/how-jimmy-pitaro-silenced-the-screams-of-left-wing-espn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nadir of ESPN’s failure with politics came in September 2017, when Jemele Hill, lucratively paid and newly minted co-host of a network family jewel, the 6 p.m. “SportsCenter,” respo…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
