<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Antifa urges members to take up up arms after Rittenhouse verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/23/antifa-urges-members-take-arms-after-kyle-rittenho/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of Antifa are responding to the acquittal of Kyle Rittenhouse last week by getting guns themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooks rapped 'we TERRORISTS' --  but cops rule out terror motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4127569/darrell-brooks-lyrics-waukesha-rapped-terrorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect in the Waukesha Christmas parade crash that killed five people had rapped about being a “terrorist” and a “killer in the city”, according to songs he posted onli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at judge for setting $5M bond for Xmas parade suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235965/Waukesha-SUV-killer-Darrell-Brooks-appears-court-face-six-murder-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darrell Brooks Jr, 39, appeared in court in Wisconsin on Tuesday for his bail hearing. Bail was set at $5 million in cash, which the judge described as 'extraordinary' but appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidens Thanksgiving at billionaire's private island compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10236561/Hunter-baby-Beau-gaggle-grandkids-join-Joe-Jill-Biden-Thanksgiving-Nantucket.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe and Jill Biden arrived on Nantucket for Thanksgiving after the White House defended their stay at billionaire David Rubenstein's private compound with Hunter and gaggle of grandkids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as Australians ordered to wear masks even as 95% of population is fully vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10236353/Coronavirus-Australia-Backlash-mask-rule-NSW-reaches-95-cent-vaccination.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal by NSW health bureaucrats to extend the mask wearing rule for millions of shoppers beyond the pre-Christmas rush has sparked furious backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge extends ban on keeping NYT from publishing material about PROJECT VERITAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235207/Judge-extends-New-York-Times-ban-Project-Veritas-coverage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York judge extended a ban keeping the New York Times from publishing or seeking certain materials concerning Project Veritas, a conservative activist group, on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Bond movie could  lose up to $100 million...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/no-time-to-die-highest-grossing-movie-losing-money-blockbusters-1235111919/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the weekend, “No Time to Die” eclipsed $730 million in global ticket sales, making the James Bond sequel both the year’s highest-grossing Hollywood film and the top performin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even in Highly Vaccinated New England, Hospitals Are Suffering...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/even-in-highly-vaccinated-new-england-hospitals-are-suffering/ar-AAR3y5h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AstraZeneca gives longer protection?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/health/medical/astrazeneca-vaccine-may-give-longer-protection-that-is-shielding-uk-from-new-covid-wave/ar-AAR1YSM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AstraZeneca vaccine may give longer protection that is shielding UK from new Covid wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETAILERS SOUND ALARM ON ORGANIZED THEFT</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/retail/retailers-sound-alarm-organized-theft-states-warn-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illinois and California have stepped up anti-shoplifting efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Renews Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2021/11/23/denver-mask-mandate-covid-19-cases-surge-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mandate, which takes effect Wednesday, will require businesses and other indoor public spaces to wear masks until Jan. 3 to curb the spread of coronavirus infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's Recovery Trails Other Cities as Tourism Loss Weighs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyc-recovery-trails-other-u-190403960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- New York City’s recovery from the Covid-19 pandemic is lagging behind that of other major U.S. metropolitan areas as the iconic destination continues to suffer from the loss of tourism jobs, Fitch Ratings said Tuesday.Most Read from BloombergAsia’s Richest Man Looks to Walton Family Playbook on SuccessionThe 24-Year-Old Aiming to Dethrone Victoria’s SecretNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsThe Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rwandan mountain gorillas a rare conservation success...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rwanda-gorillas-60-minutes-2021-11-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 Minutes cameras visited the gorillas and their babies in the Rwandan mountains for a new Lesley Stahl report airing Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll rises to 6...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/wisconsin-waukesha-christmas-parade-car-plow-11-23-21/h_266f4489fda50b7993eee51b67a85ad8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial charges are expected to be filed Tuesday against the suspect in Sunday's fatal incident at the Waukesha Christmas parade. At least five people were killed and more than 40 were injured when an SUV plowed into the crowd. Follow here for the latest news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Files emergency order to immediately reinstate mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235075/Biden-files-emergency-order-reinstate-sweeping-vaccine-mandate-private-companies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOJ filed with the Sixth Circuit Court of Appeals, which a federal judicial panel designated as the court that will decide legal challenges related to Biden's vaccine-or-test rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some deer ingested chemicals, shouldn't be eaten, Maine says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-environment-maine-wildlife-pollution-8c08f6ce0e0f020ba6b16107c0024004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAIRFIELD, Maine (AP) — Deer harvested by hunters in part of central Maine should not be consumed as food because of elevated levels of an environmental pollutant, authorities in the state said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE JABS FOR ALL BORDER CROSSERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-business-health-07c377d92f85bc061bf7e2c690f4bbca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will require essential, nonresident travelers crossing U.S. land borders, such as truck drivers, government and emergency response officials, to be fully vaccinated beginning on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising theft 'traumatizing' BEST BUY employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/business/best-buy-retail-theft/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Buy CEO Corie Barry said theft is a growing problem at the company's stores — and it is implementing added security measure to safeguard employees and shoppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Covid Made Democracies More Authoritarian...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/23/covid-19-made-democracies-more-authoritarian-and-authoritarianism-even-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 pandemic is contributing to a significant decline in democratic values across the globe as many countries have taken aggressive and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K., Chappelle Nominated for GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/23/dave-chappelle-louis-ck-cancel-culture-grammy-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis C.K. and Dave Chappelle both grabbed Grammy nominations, despite their individual battles with "cancel culture", a signal maybe "canceling" people is on the wane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GENERAL HOSPITAL' actor fired for refusing shot...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/general-hospital-steve-burton-vaccine-mandate-soap-actor-fired/11265347/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Steve Burton, a fixture on "General Hospital" for more than three decades, has been fired from the soap for his refusal to get vaccinated, he told fans on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys, Oath Keepers probed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/23/january-6-subpoena-proud-boys-oath-keepers-523255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House select committee’s latest round of summonses target leaders of the groups, as well as a third far-right entity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media use linked to depression in adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/social-media-use-linked-depression-adults-rcna6445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While social media has been widely linked to anxiety and depression in teenagers, new evidence suggests that platforms such as TikTok and Instagram can leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Responds to Jan. 6 Subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/alex-jones-issues-emergency-message-concerning-jan-6th-congressional-subpoena/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a declaration of war against free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury awards millions in damages for Unite the Right violence...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/unite-jurors-begin-day-deliberations-81344570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jury has ordered white nationalist leaders and organizations to pay more than $25 million in damages over violence that erupted during the deadly 2017 Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Says U.S. Rehearsed Nuclear Strike Against Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-11-23/russia-notes-significant-increase-in-u-s-bomber-activity-in-east-minister</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild hogs running rampant outside LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/feral-hogs-corona-california-yards-destroyed-wild-pigs/11265222/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wild hogs are running rampant in Corona and residents say it's becoming a growing problem that's posing a threat to the safety of families and pets all across the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Declared Him Dead. He Came Out Alive From Freezer 6 Hours Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awvmw/declared-dead-man-alive-in-morgue-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I touched his cheeks. To my happiness and horror, it was warm. He was breathing,” says a relative who came to identify the body at the morgue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT faces extended ban on 'VERITAS' coverage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123192426-1aml0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PROJECT VERITAS/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-New York Times faces extended ban on Project Veritas coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY chef wants to change diets -- 1 bug at a time...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/chef-joseph-yoon-brooklyn-bugs-insect-diet-spc-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chef Joseph Yoon wants to introduce the US to the delights of insect-based cuisine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury holds pharmacies responsible for role in opioid crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-ohio-medication-opioids-d778b97c0eb409aa0d53dcfd9e4f2ad0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — Three retail pharmacy chains recklessly distributed massive amounts of pain pills in two Ohio counties, a federal jury said Tuesday in a verdict that could set the tone for U.S. city and county governments that want to hold pharmacies accountable for their roles in the opioid crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leto's 'Super Mario' Italian accent mocked...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/23/jared-letos-house-of-gucci-accent-mocked-as-super-mario/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruthless Twitter critics have lasered in on Jared Leto’s accent, taking potshots at the actors’ performance, which many analogized to the titular character in “Super Mario.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House members describe roiling animosity among lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/politics/congress-anger-house-fights/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many members within the House of Representatives told CNN in recent days that they find themselves in a toxic work environment, wrought with bitter exchanges, threats and fears about what the erosion of decorum in the chamber will mean for a body that has still not recovered 10 months after the Capitol Hill riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE sues company known for hacking iPhones on behalf of govts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/apple-sues-nso-group-company-known-for-hacking-iphones-on-behalf-of-governments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bail draws questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/suspect-e2-80-99s-bail-draws-questions-as-investigations-begin-into-wisconsin-parade-tragedy/ar-AAR1Ww2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  WAIT ANOTHER YEAR FOR INFLATION TO COOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.macaubusiness.com/monthly-us-inflation-to-return-to-0-2-0-3-pct-in-second-half-of-2022-yellen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macaubusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Island ER forced to close over lack of vaccinated nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/shortage-of-vaccinated-nurses-prompts-closure-of-er-on-long-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mount Sinai South Nassau said the decision to close the Long Beach Emergency Room came after all options were exhausted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZEN ROBBERS HIT CALI LUXE</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/23/update-shaken-holiday-shoppers-changing-plans-in-wake-of-retail-smash-and-grab-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent smash-and-grab robbery spree targeting retail shops across the Bay Area has shoppers, store employees and business owners on edge at the start the holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMAS SMASH AND GRAB</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/breed-brazen-takeover-robbers-hitting-130021558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-end retailers such as Nordstrom and Louis Vuitton have been targeted by brazen robbers in Northern and Southern California, raising alarm among authorities, politicians and retailers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Arrested On Nov. 5 For Punching Woman, Then Running Over Her In Same SUV!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/waukesha-christmas-parade-darrell-brooks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darrell Brooks, 39, was charged with five counts of murder after he allegedly plowed through a Christmas parade in Waukesha, Wisconsin, on Sunday, killing at least five and injuring dozens more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes of terror recounted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/waukesha-wisconsin-christmas-parade-crash-what-happened-daee4565c7a36e88029c5fe6393d1be3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours before it started, they were already there — people sitting on lawn chairs or wrapped in blankets, awaiting an event the city's mayor described as straight out of Norman Rockwell. The Waukesha Christmas Parade, a tradition in its Milwaukee suburb for six decades, was to be particularly special this time around after its pandemic-related cancellation last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Expect To Gain 8 Pounds During Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/holiday-weight-gain-8-pounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holiday weight gain is inevitable for many of us who can't help but to take a second slice of grandma's pecan pie or another slice of turkey (or three).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Warms to Saudi Money Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywood-saudi-arabia-money-again-1235051906/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t too long ago that power brokers rushed to distance themselves from the country after the killing of columnist Jamal Khashoggi. Now it’s hosting a star-studded film festival and backing big-budget features with U.S. talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News Hedging on Streaming Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/cnn-fox-msnbc-streaming-plan-1235051688/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While touting new platforms (think: CNN+ or Fox Nation), top broadcast and cable executives are incentivized to protect the linear status quo, given that’s where the money is — even if it’s a rapidly declining business model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Deploying Highway Patrol...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/police-smash-and-grab-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stopping the swarm of smash and grabs as holiday shoppers begin their buying spree, local police have a plan to keep criminals out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense after new covid curbs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123142632-1ol47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-GUADELOUPE (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving challenges airlines as travel nears pre-pandemic levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/23/thanksgiving-travel-airports-staffing-cancelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers fear airport chaos as airlines contend with staffing shortages, which could lead to flight cancelations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR TREE Gives Up on Buck With $1.25 Price Standard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/dollar-tree-says-dollar125-price-point-to-become-new-standard/ar-AAR2CvB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last surviving woman born in 19th century dies at 124...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4125578/oldest-ever-human-francisca-susano-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN believed to be the oldest person in world has died at the reported age of 124. Francisca Susano, affectionately known as Lola Iska, died on Monday night at her home in the Philippines. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Low-Key Media Strategy Draws Allies' Concern...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/bidens-low-key-media-strategy-draws-allies-concern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As president, Donald J. Trump was a media maximalist whose unavoidable-for-comment style helped generate saturation news coverage, for better or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: China Hypersonic Weapon Released Payload And Nobody Knows Why...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43242/chinas-hypersonic-mystery-weapon-released-its-own-payload-and-nobody-knows-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mystery surrounding China's hypersonic vehicle test last summer has deepened after the craft reportedly launched its own projectile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video: Fan Attacks WWE Wrestler At Monday Night Raw...</title>
      <link>https://thespun.com/more/wrestling/video-fan-attacks-wwe-wrestler-seth-rollins-monday-night-raw-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thespun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tonight's WWE “Monday Night Raw” event at Barclays Center in Brooklyn went off the rails when a fan attacked wrestler Seth Rollins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage over 'long, dirty toenails'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/22/us/ahmaud-arbery-trial-toenails-comment-outrage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sentence uttered by a defense attorney in the trial of those accused in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery brought an audible gasp from people in the courtroom Monday -- and elicited outrage from his family and legal experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NASA probe set for historic asteroid deflection test...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-dart-launch-asteroid-defense-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $330 million DART probe will crash head-on into a small asteroid to test the possibility of averting future threats to Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN to launch Michael Strahan, 5 others into space...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/23/bezos-blue-origin-to-launch-michael-strahan-5-others-into-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos’ Blue Origin on Tuesday announced the crew of its Dec. 9 launch, which will carry “Good Morning America” co-anchor and former New York Giant Michael Strahan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Cadets Steal Wrong Goat in Botched Pre-Game Navy Mascot Raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/army-cadets-steal-wrong-goat-in-botched-pre-game-navy-mascot-raid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cadets have stolen the goat mascots, all named Bill, at least 10 times since the first raid in 1953.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors set sights on new Trump target: Widely different valuations on same properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/n-y-prosecutors-set-sights-on-new-trump-target-widely-different-valuations-on-the-same-properties/ar-AAQZtcr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC records 200th homicide of  year; Not seen since '04...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-records-200th-homicide-of-the-year-a-mark-not-seen-since-2004/ar-AAR2sb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Lined Up at ER...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/minnesota-covid-bed-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Because we have so many patients in our hospital emergency department waiting to get in the hospital, we have lost the ability and the bed capacity to safely accept many transfers from throughout the region,” Dr. Dan Hoody said. “This is commonly us having to decline five to 50 transfers a day.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Deployed To MN...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/covid-in-minnesota-natl-guard-arrives-as-hospitals-are-overrun-with-covid-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals like Hennepin Healthcare are desperate for people to get vaccinated as Minnesota grapples with one of the worst infection rates in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY to Allow 800,000 Noncitizens to Vote in Local Elections...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/new-york-moves-to-allow-800000-noncitizens-to-vote-in-local-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City lawmakers are poised to allow more than 800,000 New Yorkers who are green card holders or have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup host Qatar used ex-CIA officer to spy on FIFA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/soccer-sports-business-migration-middle-east-d9716b62fc69ab88beb3553d402da7d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The tiny Arab nation of Qatar has for years employed a former CIA officer to help spy on soccer officials as part of a no-expense-spared effort to win and hold on to the 2022 World Cup tournament, an investigation by The Associated Press has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan sparks sell-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/turkish-lira-plummets-to-historic-low-after-erdogan-sparks-selloff-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation in Turkey is now near 20%, meaning basic goods for Turks have soared in price and their local currency salaries are severely devalued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA will tap strategic petroleum reserve as gas prices hover at 7-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/biden-says-us-will-tap-strategic-petroleum-reserve-as-gas-prices-hover-around-7-hear-high.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. will release 50 millions barrels of oil from the Strategic Petroleum Reserve in an effort to combat climbing gas prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NASA to Launch Mission to Crush Asteroid Heading for Earth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123115820-dn7bi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-EXPLORATION/ASTEROID (TV):NASA to launch test mission of asteroid-deflecting spacecraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghans 'marry off' baby girls for dowries as starvation looms...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123035757-ylrch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghanistan's economic meltdown following the Taliban's takeover 100 days ago is pushing destitute families to marry off young daughters - and even baby girls, campaigners say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lira Losses Snowball in Turkey's Worst Streak in 20 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lira-weakens-past-12-per-104006032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Turkish lira’s freefall is shattering all kinds of records as President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s renewed campaign for lower interest rates pushes the country deeper into crisis. Most Read from BloombergAsia’s Richest Man Looks to Walton Family Playbook on SuccessionNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsThe Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheries, Hidden Inflation Is Creeping Across JapanMaverick 70-Year-Old CEO Is Determined to Sha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Brands, Blue Brands: Hyper-Partisanship Coming for Corporate America...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/red-brands-and-blue-brands-is-hyper-partisanship-coming-for-corporate-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year is 2041, and Starbucks has real competition. Black Rifle Coffee Company, the java brand favored by conservatives, has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns of surge in deaths ahead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-united-nations-denmark-579fe691ceefadd8a205188be52436d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization's Europe office says projections show its 53-country region could face another 700,000 deaths in the coronavirus pandemic by next spring, topping 2 million in total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housework boosts memories?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4123581/housework-keeps-people-better-in-shape/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOING more housework can boost Brits’ memories and attention span for older people, scientists say. Researchers have found that elderly people who participate in a combination of light housew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORDSTROM smash-and-grab in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/us/los-angeles-the-grove-nordstrom-burglary/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 20 people were involved in a burglary Monday night at the Nordstrom department store at The Grove retail complex in Los Angeles, CNN affiliate KCAL/KCBS reported, citing the Los Angeles Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four-Day Workweek Finally Within Grasp?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/is-the-four-day-workweek-finally-within-our-grasp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May 2020, as the pandemic sent stress levels through the roof, an online children’s clothes retailer called Primary started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Was This Ancient Tusk 150 Miles From Land, 10,000 Feet Deep?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/22/why-was-this-ancient-tusk-150-miles-from-land-10000-feet-deep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young female mammoth was wandering long ago near what would become the Central Coast of California, when her life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm X daughter found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4123852/malcolm-xs-daughter-malikah-shabazz-dead-days-men-exonerated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MALCOLM X’s daughter has been found dead inside her Brooklyn apartment late Monday night. Officers found the late assassinated Black civil rights leader’s daughter Malikah Shabazz dead …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial in Arbery killing nears going to jury...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-georgia-brunswick-a6c84fde31dc86a9b2230f1002ed25af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — Final steps in the trial of three white men charged in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery were scheduled Tuesday before the case of the 25-year-old Black man's death goes to the jury.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
