<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump lashes out at 'photoshopped' image of face... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-reacts-angrily-image-highlighting-120851207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has described photographs revealing a pale ring around the edge of his distinctly orange face as “more fake news”, after a particularly unflattering image went viral over the weekend.Mr Trump’s eccentric range of facial colourations has been the subject of repeated enquiry by journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after gunman ambushes NYC police twice in 12 hours...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bc2296db89a22c7c313f717ce76ff6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A gunman is in custody after he ambushed police officers in the Bronx twice in 12 hours, wounding two in attacks that ignited outrage from officials who blamed the violence on an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BA flight breaks NY to London speed record as it reaches 825mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/378853/ba-flight-breaks-storm-record-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH Airways jet has today smashed the record for the fastest subsonic New York to London flight – thanks to incredible storm force winds. The Boeing 747-436 reached speeds of 825mph at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county 'ground zero' for 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article239947073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN:  Most devastating plague of locusts in recent history could come within weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/most-devastating-plague-locusts-recent-history-could-come-within-weeks-n1133171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change and al-Shabab extremists contributed to circumstances that could produce crippling swarms of locusts in Somalia and East Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab media accuse Israel of  conspiracy against China...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Arab-media-accuse-US-Israel-of-coronavirus-conspiracy-against-China-617021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One report claimed that it was no coincidence that the coronavirus was largely absent from the US and Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead flesh smells, demon voices and scratches; Possessed teen's exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/dead-flesh-smells-demon-voices-21428694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This woman claims she was exorcised by a Christian pastor as a teenager after an experiment with Wicca magic went wrong and she ended up possessed by a demon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS 7-DAY HELL: DYSFUNCTIONAL DISARRAY, DEFEATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democrats-worst-week-iowa-caucus-1897dc63-341b-4f5d-a274-566c6704cbdb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg Walks Back Gayle King Comments: 'I'm a Non-Violent Person'...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2020/02/09/snoop-dogg-walks-back-gayle-king-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snoop Dogg previously warned Gayle King "back off b--ch before we come get you.” He was upset about her interview on Kobe Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASHES OUT AT 'DOG-FACED' VOTER</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-calls-skeptical-new-hampshire-voter-lying-dog-faced-po</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dust-up came after the voter asked whether he can rebound from Iowa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PREY' Misfires With DC COMICS' Worst Opening in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/birds-of-prey-weekend-box-office-margot-robbie-1202853768/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4th UPDATE, Sunday AM w/final chart: In the wake of hitting highs with Wonder Woman, Aquaman and the highest-grossing R-rated movie of all-time in the 11-time Oscar-nominated and billion-dollar-plu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/09/video-shows-moment-gunman-opens-fire-inside-bronx-nypd-precinct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman who stormed a Bronx precinct station Sunday morning shooting at cops dove behind a desk when officers pulled their guns and threw down his firearm, new shocking videos show. The surveillan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/09/surveillance-video-shows-thug-firing-on-bronx-nypd-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video obtained by The Post shows the moment a cop-hating thug brazenly opened fire at two on-duty officers in the Bronx Saturday night. The shooting left one of the officers with graze wounds to hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second attack reported as man opens fire inside precinct...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/09/bronx-nypd-shootings-second-attack-reported-as-man-opens-fire-inside-precinct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man walked into a Bronx police precinct and opened fire Sunday morning — just hours after a pair of officers were ambushed in the same NYPD precinct, police sources told The Post. Law enforcement…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors tracked killer via CCTV...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thai-mall-shooting-survivors-tracked-killer-via-cctv-102758326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a fourth-floor toilet of the Terminal 21 mall, shoppers jammed cubicle doors against the entrance to keep out a Thai soldier on a shooting spree, tracing his movements through fragments of CCTV passed on by friends on the outside. Barricaded in the women's toilet with a few dozen others, Chanathip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll jumps again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-02-09-20-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He spoke out. Now his family fears he's been silenced...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/09/asia/wuhan-citizen-journalist-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people across China mourned the death of a whistleblower doctor in an almost unprecedented outpouring of grief and anger on Thursday, little did they know that another truth-teller of the coronavirus outbreak was being silenced, according to friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Barbara Walters 'Not Doing Great'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/2020/02/09/barbara-walters-not-doing-great-the-view-jenny-mccarthy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid reports that legendary news anchor, Barbara Walters has been struggling with her health, the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Peterson's year of 'absolute hell': Professor retreats because of addiction...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/jordan-petersons-year-of-absolute-hell-professor-forced-to-retreat-from-public-life-because-of-tranquilizer-addiction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial author and professor is recovering from addiction to tranquilizers and near-death in Russia, his family says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Over Sex Work Raging Inside Biggest Feminist Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-national-organization-for-women-is-tearing-itself-apart-over-sex-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a growing divide within the feminist movement on whether the sale and purchase of consensual, adult sex should be decriminalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver runs van through Republican voter registration tent...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/local/2020/02/08/police-van-drives-through-republican-partys-voter-registration-tent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers with the Jacksonville Sheriff’s Office are looking for a brown Chevrolet van they said drove through a tent Sunday where volunteers were registering people to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA agent tricks traveler into showing her breasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/tsa-agent-tricked-traveler-baring-herself-officials-say-n1132971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 22-year-old agent was arrested for deceiving a traveler into twice showing him her breasts as she went through security at Los Angeles International Airport, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many married couples sleep in separate beds...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/09/separate-beds-married-couples-can-help-relationship-experts-say/4657215002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey says almost a quarter of married couple sleep in separate bed. Here's why some are opting to part ways at nighttime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Out of Gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joe-biden-is-running-out-of-gas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former VP has lost the plot, voters say. And they’re wondering if he will ever get it back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online preschool gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.concordmonitor.com/Online-preschool-32456408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.concordmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We read with concern David Brooks’s Jan. 28 article about the New Hampshire Department of Education’s goal of enrolling 200 families in a pilot program for online preschool called Upstart. Although Brooks’s article did not mention the concerns about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg booms...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/08/nh-primary-poll-sanders-buttigieg-klobuchar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All week long, the story has been the rise of Pete Buttigieg to co-frontrunner status with Bernie Sanders. The latest exclusive WBZ/Boston Globe/Suffolk University tracking poll shows they're still co-leaders within the poll's 4.4% margin of error, with Sanders holding steady at 24% and Buttigieg slipping a bit to 22%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where did they go? Millions left Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/9/millions-left-wuhan-china-coronavirus-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials finally began to seal the borders on Jan. 23. But it was too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed573fec92465305a5e3256cda62160c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Two U.S. soldiers were killed and six wounded in a so-called insider attack in eastern Afghanistan's Nangarhar province late Saturday when an Afghan dressed in an Afghan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Officer shot, wounded in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/nypd-officer-shot-wounded-assassination-attempt-68856407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's police commissioner says an officer was wounded by gunfire in the Bronx in “an assassination attempt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid gang peril, a Mexican village arms its children... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Amid-gang-peril-a-Mexican-village-arms-its-15041386.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AYAHUALTEMPA, Mexico - Before he picked up a rifle and joined a squad of armed children, Alex wanted to become a schoolteacher. He'd teach anything - "whatever the principal asks" - because spending his days in a classroom sounded pretty good.  He was 13, a B student with a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles bicycle who got nervous around the girls in his middle school.  Then, in November, as violence surged in the mountains of Guerrero state, the men of Ayahualtempa decided it was time for their sons to take up arms.  Alex was handed a hunting rifle and told to show up for daily training on the village basketball court. He and his young comrades, some as young as 6, marched and crawled with loaded guns almost as tall as they were. Their uniforms said "Community Police" in yellow letters.  When the photographers started coming, the boys were told to cover their faces with handkerchiefs. Arming children to defend the town against a violent gang wasn't a media stunt, Alex's commanders insisted. Yet if the images drew the government's attention to a place Mexico's security forces had forgotten, it would be a triumph of its own.  But were the boys training to defend their village, or were they being paraded in front of visiting photographers to send a message to the government, a plea for more resources? Sometimes even Alex wasn't sure. What he knew was that the gun was heavy and loaded, and the training felt real enough to him.  Alex's father, Santos Martínez, looked at his son's face, trying to gauge whether Alex was mature enough to join the force.  "There was no fear in his eyes," Martínez said. "That's how I knew he was ready."  Alex repeated the words of his commander: "I'm preparing to defend my village."  Mexico suffered 35,588 homicides in 2019, a record. It was another data...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  LOW KEY OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75ca3451d6974bfa1228025fa4790be2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Oscars are here, already. After the shortest awards season in decades, the 92nd annual Academy Awards will get underway Sunday evening at the Dolby Theatre in Los...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSH TO ENSURE FOOD SUPPLY IN HOT ZONES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48256188e39d4e2db49e8e8d68a6bd90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The rate of increase in new cases of the virus in China rose again after a brief respite, as the death toll rose to 722 on the mainland and countries around the world enforced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zirinsky defends anchor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b8a3ad60aa2728fa721fb69e4af4b63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The CBS News chief called threats against journalist Gayle King “reprehensible” Saturday as backlash grew against rapper Snoop Dogg and others critical of King for an interview...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor-comedian Orson Bean, 91, hit and killed by car in LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/5912587/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran actor Orson Bean was struck and killed by a car in the Friday night in Venice, California, authorities said. He was 91.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 DEAD...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200208231736-g2njf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AFGHANISTAN/ (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-American, Afghan soldiers killed in shootout in Afghanistan-NY Times</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
