<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'I made $3.75 an hour': LYFT, UBER drivers push to unionize for better pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/22/uber-lyft-ipo-drivers-unionize-low-pay-expenses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers for the rideshare companies are seeing much of their pay go to expenses while Lyft and Uber prepare for their IPOs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCETON seminary students asking for reparations for school's role in slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Princeton-seminary-students-are-asking-for-13708289.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princeton Theological Seminary last year released a report describing its founders' and early faculty's ties to slavery. Now, some of its students want the school to take it a step further and provide reparations as financial restitution for its role in the slave trade.  A group of black seminarians have collected more than 400 signatures in an online petition calling on the New Jersey school to "make amends" by setting aside $5.3 million annually - or 15 percent of what the seminary uses from the school's endowment for its operating expenses - to fund tuition grants for black students and establish a Black Church Studies program.  A progressive seminary like Princeton could be a pioneer by distributing reparations, said Justin Henderson, president of the Association of Black Seminarians, the group behind the petition. The school has confessed and repented for the "sin" of its role in slavery, but "repentance doesn't end with confession," said Henderson, who will finish his master of divinity studies in May.  "Restitution is evidence of the repentance.," he said. "This is how we know the person has repented."  The idea of reparations was popularized by Ta-Nehisi Coates' 2014 cover story in The Atlantic, "The Case for Reparations." It has resurfaced in recent months as an issue in the 2020 presidential race, finding support among Sens. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and former Housing and Urban Development Secretary Julián Castro. They have not revealed specific plans, but those Democratic candidates signaled a shift from other leaders, such as former president Barack Obama, Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., who is running again for the Democratic Party nominee, and 2016 presidential candidate Hillary Clinton, who declined to support reparations in the past.  Princeton's report resulted after a two-year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan urges fight on Islamophobia 'like anti-Semitism after Holocaust'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190322-erdogan-urges-fight-islamophobia-like-anti-semitism-after-holocaust</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erdogan urges fight on Islamophobia 'like anti-Semitism after Holocaust'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside story of how John Roberts negotiated to save Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/21/politics/john-roberts-obamacare-the-chief/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roberts' moves behind the scenes were as extraordinary as his ruling. He changed course multiple times. And it's a vote that means the conservative chief justice will always be viewed with skepticism by Republicans, including Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's Tallest of Them All? No Longer Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/whos-the-tallest-of-them-all-its-no-longer-the-americans-11553254201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 200 years, Americans towered over everyone else. Now, the tallest people are the Dutch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Vacations: New Age of Sleeper Trains...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dream-vacations-the-new-age-of-sleeper-trains-11553255489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good news for train romantics: The once-endangered sleeper is back on track. Here’s where—and why—you might to ride the midnight express.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother Russia: Florida sees boom in 'birth tourism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/161a0db2666044dc8d42932edd9b9ce6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Every year, hundreds of pregnant Russian women travel to the United States to give birth so that their child can acquire all the privileges of American citizenship. They pay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim former detainee tells of China camp trauma...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-muslim-detainee-tells-china-camp-trauma-033412860.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Muslims in China's re-education camps, indoctrination starts with early morning patriotic songs and sessions of self-criticism, and often ends with a meal of only pork, according to one exiled former detainee. UN experts say China holds one million Muslims in camps in the heavily policed Xinjiang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pole Vaulter, 84, Sets Sights On More Records...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/clevelandbanner/article/d30e7bb0b8ad42a09e9782a8cbe98ef1/pole-vaulter-84-sets-her-sights-more-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. (AP) — An 84-year-old pole vaulter isn't putting her pole down anytime soon.Flo Filion Meiler left Thursday for the World Masters Athletics Championship Indoor in Poland, where she'll compete in events including the long jump, 60-meter hurdles, 800-meter run, pentathlon and pole vault, for which she's the shoo-in.The petite, energetic woman from Shelburne, Vermont, said she feels more like 70 than nearly 85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn in smartphones! How Mueller kept lid on Trump-Russia probe...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190322104821-p3bfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-SECRECY (PIX):Turn in your smartphones! How Mueller kept a lid on Trump-Russia probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half young people don't have romantic partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/It-s-not-just-you-New-data-shows-more-than-half-13706291.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austin Spivey, a 24-year-old woman in Washington, has been looking for a relationship for years. She's been on several dating apps - OkCupid, Coffee Meets Bagel, Hinge, Tinder, Bumble. She's on a volleyball team, where she has a chance to meet people with similar interests in a casual setting. She's even let The Washington Post set her up.  "I'm a very optimistic dater," Spivey says, adding that she's "always energetic to keep trying." But it can get a little frustrating, she adds, when she's talking to someone on a dating app and they disappear mid-conversation. (She's vanished too, she admits.)  Spivey has a lot of company in her frustration, and in her singledom. Just over half of Americans between the ages of 18 and 34 - 51 percent of them - said they do not have a steady romantic partner, according to data from the General Social Survey released this week. That 2018 figure is up significantly from 33 percent in 2004 - the lowest figure since the question was first asked in 1986 - and up slightly from 45 percent in 2016. The shift has helped drive singledom to a record high among the overall public, among whom 35 percent say they have no steady partner, but only up slightly from 33 percent in 2016 and 2014.  There are several other trends that go along with the increase in young single Americans. Women are having fewer children, and they're having them later in life. The median age of first marriage is increasing. And according to a 2017 report from the Pew Research Center, among those who have never married but are open to it, most say a major reason is because they haven't found the right person.  Of course, not everyone who's under 35 and single is looking to change that. Caitlin Phillips, a 22-year-old student at the University of Georgia, is open to love if it walked into her life, but she's not actively...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Medieval' diseases flare as unsanitary living conditions proliferate...</title>
      <link>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/medieval-diseases-flare-as-unsanitary-living-conditions-proliferate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scientificamerican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typhus and other infectious illnesses hit homeless communities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two U.S. service members killed in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-afghanistan/two-u-s-service-members-killed-in-afghanistan-idUSKCN1R30F0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two U.S. service members were killed in Afghanistan on Friday while conducting a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarms sound after 6 suicides by Chicago cops over 8 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-chicago-police-suicides-20190315-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cluster of suicides by Chicago police officers has caught the attention of national experts, some of whom will be in the city in the coming weeks to study the problem as the department takes a harder look at mental health services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does NETFLIX have killer problem? Shows spolight gruesome violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/tv/ct-ent-netflix-violence-20190321-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than other entertainment outlets, a number of Netflix's hit shows spotlight gruesome violence, often committed against women, according to viewership statistics and industry experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living on pennies with million-dollar view: Car campers survive in beach parking lots...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/living-on-pennies-with-a-million-dollar-view-how-car/article_edf4971c-045a-5265-b772-b857df180d4b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — A year ago, he was homeless. Today, he owns a residence that boasts a million-dollar view of the rolling Pacific.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Megamansion Bigger Than White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.northjersey.com/story/news/essex/montclair/2019/03/20/montclair-mansion-will-be-bigger-than-white-house-billionaire-owner-melih-abdulhayoglu-comodo/3152616002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.northjersey.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mansion with NYC skyline views that will be bigger than the White House could replace two historic Montclair homes razed to public outcry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressured to name RESIGNATION date...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8692880/theresa-may-resignation-pressure-brexit-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA MAY was under intense pressure to name a date for her resignation as Tories panned her blistering attack on Parliament. Amid uproar in Westminster, backbenchers Anne Marie Trevelyan and Tra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAMOUNT demands naked sex scene cut from Elton John 'ROCKET MAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6837177/BAZ-BAMIGBOYE-Rocket-Man-bit-cheeky-Hollywood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Paramount Pictures have demanded that Rocketman director Dexter Fletcher and producer Matthew Vaughn cut a 40-second scene between Taron Egerton and Richard Madden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I was too worried about approval' says feminist icon Steinem...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/too-worried-approval-says-feminist-icon-steinem-160400293.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris (AFP) - Feminist icon Gloria Steinem would not be so meek "or worried about approval" if she had her life again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NO MORE INDICTMENTS'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/letter-deputy-attorney-general-rod-rosenstein-offers-potential/story?id=61847216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The road map comes in the form a little-noticed 12-page letter written by Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein last June to Senate Judiciary Chairman Chuck Grassley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Millions of User Passwords Exposed to Employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-says-millions-of-users-passwords-were-improperly-stored-in-internal-systems-11553186974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook for years stored hundreds of millions of user passwords in a format that was accessible to its employees, in yet another privacy snafu for the social-media giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOONAN:  Congress's Mean Girls Are Trump's Offspring...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/congresss-mean-girls-are-trumps-offspring-11553209914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omar and Ocasio-Cortez equate roughness with authenticity. So does the man they despise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge overwhelms govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/21/ice-releasing-1000-illegal-immigrant-family-member/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deportation officers are cutting loose more than 1,000 illegal immigrant family members a day, setting them free into border states as the surge of migrations overwhelms the government’s ability to handle them, officials revealed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshman Dems to meet with Obama next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/21/barack-obama-meet-freshmen-dems-1231285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After keeping a low profile for much of Trump’s first year and a half in office, Obama was heavily involved in the midterms, endorsing dozens of candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTICIPOINTMENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/you-may-be-disappointed-mueller-report-n971601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel operates under rules that severely constrain how much information can be made public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toilet seat detects heart conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6835549/The-toilet-seat-save-millions-lives-detecting-heart-failure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from the Rochester Institute of Technology in New York have created a gadget which has sensors in to detect someone's blood pressure and heart rate while they're on the loo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Border Crossers to Be Released Over Weekend.....</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/21/report-dhs-to-release-1-8k-border-crossers-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-over-weekend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 1,800 border crossers and illegal aliens are expected to be released into the interior of the United States this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM to block anti-vaccine hashtags amid 'misinformation' crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/435207-instagram-to-block-anti-vaccine-hashtags-amid-misinformation-crackdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram said Thursday it plans to block a slew of anti-vaccine hashtags amid an ongoing crackdown on medical misinformation on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President keeps up attacks on 'horrible' McCain...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435189-trump-keeps-up-attacks-on-horrible-mccain-despite-calls-from-gop-vets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday took more shots at the late Sen. John McCain, despite growing calls from Republicans and veterans groups to stop attacking the Arizona GOP lawmaker who died last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King stays queen of CBSNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/21/gayle-king-to-sign-multimillion-dollar-deal-to-stay-at-cbs-news/?_ga=2.99336861.2067518488.1553219232-1659663997.1548819272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insiders believe King — who already has a $5.5 million-a-year deal — is much needed on struggling “CBS This Morning,” as news chiefs attempt to boost the show’s plunging ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blames Fed for holding back economic growth...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96e9b2129a9b4d48adabd0457f4fba8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump says the economy would have grown much faster last year if the Federal Reserve had not been tightening credit last year. In a broadcast interview,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT CEO warns publishers ahead of APPLE news launch...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190321223545-g99e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDIA-NEW YORK TIMES/ (PIX):New York Times CEO warns publishers ahead of Apple news launch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration arrests fall under Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190321222414-gt7xr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/ (PIX):U.S. immigration arrests fall under Trump as resources shift to the border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan gov't accuses detained Guaido aide of planning attacks...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190321211638-h8trs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ARREST (URGENT):Venezuelan gov't accuses detained Guaido aide of planning attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers shot 'execution style' during school shooting drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.theindychannel.com/news/politics/indiana-teachers-hit-with-pellets-during-active-shooter-training-ista-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theindychannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indiana teachers were hit with pellets during an active shooter training at a school, the Indiana State Teachers Association said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust lawsuit against mega hotel chains moves forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-leisure-antitrust/lawsuit-on-hotels-internet-advertising-tactics-moves-forward-idUSKCN1R22JT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Thursday rebuffed a request by hotel chains including Hyatt H...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical flaw lets hackers control lifesaving devices implanted inside patients...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2019/03/critical-flaw-lets-hackers-control-lifesaving-devices-implanted-inside-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Implanted devices from Medtronic can have their firmware rewritten, DHS warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Amendment 'Sanctuary' Cities, Counties, States Spring Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-20/second-amendment-sanctuary-cities-counties-states-spring-across-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans in special election use as foe to run against...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/article228235684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERAL TO GRILL GOOGLE ON CHINA TIES</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/cultural-clash/2019/03/21/dunford-to-meet-with-google-for-debate-on-chinese-ties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon's top uniformed officer thinks tech companies need to be smarter with how they approach China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possessing, distributing footage cause for prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/21/new-zealand-vows-pragmatic-approach-to-policing-ba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Police warned Thursday that social media companies will face consequences for failing to keep their platforms free of footage recorded during last week’s mass shootings at two mosques in Christchurch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears -- communicate like humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2019/03/sun-bears-play-mimic-faces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's smallest bears have a social skill set previously thought limited to apes and dogs, and there may be more species like them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz pleads with visitors: Stop disrespectful photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/auschwitz-museum-asks-visitors-not-to-balance-on-train-tracks/a-48006024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The museum called on visitors to behave more respectfully after finding photos of people balancing on the tracks at the former Nazi death camp. "There are better places to learn how to walk on a balance beam," it said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial expressions throw doubt on mankind superiority...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-03-world-smallest-facial-human-superiority.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's smallest bears can exactly mimic another bear's facial expressions, casting doubt on humans and other primates' supremacy at this subtle form of communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Bans Ads That Help Chinese Circumvent Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-21/be-evil-google-bans-vpn-ads-helping-chinese-circumvent-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard investigates student 'trauma' after prof agrees to represent Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/21/harvard-investigates-trauma-among-students-law-professor-agrees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard University has launched an investigation into law professor Ronald Sullivan after he agreed to represent Harvey Weinstein in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biker gangs guard  NZ mosques during Friday prayer...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/biker-gangs-stand-guard-outside-nz-mosques-during-first-friday-prayer-since-massacre-a4096341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bikers have vowed to stand guard outside New Zealand mosques as Muslims take part in their first Friday prayer following the Christchurch shootings. Gangs like The Mongrel Mob, King Cobra and The Black Power have promised to support and protect their local Muslim communities across the country, after 50 people were killed and 50 injured in the attack on March 15. Waikato Mongrel Mob president Sonny Fatu offered to shield the Jamia Masjid Mosque in Hamilton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA bans ROUNDUP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/LA-County-Halts-Use-of-Popular-Weed-Killer-on-County-Property-507399471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors Tuesday directed all departments to stop using a popular weed killer until more is known about its potential health and environmental effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapper made woman pose for selfies, read Bible...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/suspected-kidnapper-made-boston-woman-pose-selfies-read-bible-officials-n985791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman was found alive on Jan. 21 in Victor Peña's apartment, three days after she went missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters weigh personality vs. policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/to-nerd-out-or-rock-out-democratic-voters-weigh-personality-vs-policy-in-primary-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the campaign heats up, voters in early primary states are trying to figure out the best way to beat Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines practice seizing islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/us-marines-seize-small-island-to-train-for-a-possible-china-fight-2019-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Marines are dusting off the island-hopping strategy they used in the Pacific during World War II as they prepare for a high-end fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOKER:  President 'Literally' Could 'Cause People's Death'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/booker-trump-policies-literally-could-cause-peoples-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Cory Booker said Donald Trump's policies could "literally" cause people to die, called for "radical love" in politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating billboards turn Miami waterfront into Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article228192969.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Marine: Troops at Border 'Unacceptable Risk'...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/03/21/commandant-of-the-marines-says-deploying-troops-to-the-border-poses-unacceptable-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commandant of the Marines has warned the Pentagon that deployments to the southwest border and funding transfers under the president's emergency declaration, among other unexpected demands, have posed “unacceptable risk to Marine Corps combat readiness and solvency.” In two internal memos, Marine Corps Gen. Robert Neller said the “unplanned/unbudgeted” deployment along the border that President Trump ordered last fall, and shifts of other funds to support border security, had forced him to cancel or reduce planned military training in at least five countries, and delay urgent repairs at bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey birth a step to saving fertility of boys with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34fc33ade9aa4406a214e0fe2605ff9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Scientists are closing in on a way to help young boys undergoing cancer treatment preserve their future fertility — and the proof is the first monkey born from the experimental...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More whales under Golden Gate Bridge spark starvation worries...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/whales-sharks/article/gray-whale-in-sf-bay-golden-gate-whale-watching-13703705.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On their way from Mexico to Alaska, gray whales are making a pit-stop in San Francisco - and staying a while.  "Historically, one or two gray whales would temporarily pass underneath the Golden Gate Bridge during this time period. Last week alone, experts counted five entering the Bay," said the Marine Mammal Center in a recent press release.  Not only are more coming to town, they're also hanging out much longer than expected. One gray whale has been in and around the San Francisco Bay for more than a month now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last stronghold liberated...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/isis-has-officially-crumbled-and-last-stronghold-liberated-fox-news-has-learned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The caliphate has crumbled, and the final offensive is over. While the official announcement hasn’t yet been made – Fox News has been told that this village, the last ISIS stronghold, is liberated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADHD drugs lead to psychosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/adhd-drugs-can-lead-psychosis-some-according-new-study/dUyKiThflPYe0ySlMn9I1K/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADHD drugs can lead to psychosis in some according to new study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT: Military steps up preparations in case of no deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/brexit-military-steps-up-preparations-in-case-of-no-deal-11671941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation Redfold will direct some 3,500 military personnel who have been put on standby for a no-deal scenario.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to recognize Golan Heights as part of Israel...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6835799/Trump-says-U-S-recognize-Golan-Heights-Israel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors of the potential move swirled in diplomatic circles this week as the American Israel Public Affairs Committee prepares for its annual meeting next week, where Netanyahu will speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model with Down syndrome breaks stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/lifestyles/parenting/aisha-sultan/wildwood-model-with-down-syndrome-breaks-down-stereotypes/article_2cbb30a1-342e-5476-948a-d12599490a74.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lunchroom can get a little rowdy when the kindergarten through second-grade classes fill up the tables. Grace Strobel scans the room for little hands waving in the air. She</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More revelations to come in Trudeau scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-politics/ex-canadian-minister-says-more-revelations-to-come-in-scandal-surrounding-trudeau-idUSKCN1R21NG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Canadian cabinet minister, who had quit in protest over the government's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Letterman: I stayed on TV too long...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/40180066e2cd44c5848c22ba4e2eae61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — David Letterman says he stuck around on network television about 10 years too long. He made that admission during an appearance Thursday on Ellen DeGeneres' talk show....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Left Up Video of New Zealand Shootings for an Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-our-ai-tools-failed-to-catch-new-zealand-attack-video-11553156141?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook left a gruesome video of shootings at a New Zealand mosque up on its site for half an hour after a user brought it to the company’s attention, a previously unreported delay that highlights the social media company’s difficulty in controlling violent content on its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Ratings Sink to All-Time Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/empire-ratings-series-lows-jussie-smollett/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Empire" sunk to series lows on Wednesday, a week after an already-rough midseason return. It was the Fox drama's 2nd episode since Jussie Smollett's arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATION:  Our phones ARE listening to us...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/8678640/proof-phones-listening-to-us/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVE you ever been talking about a pair of trainers or holiday destination, and then suddenly seen an advert for that precise thing pop up on social media? Us too. As incredible as it sounds, it mi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 STRIKES:  Macron says no-deal Brexit if UK MPs reject accord AGAIN... </title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/454403-macron-no-deal-brexit-deal-reject/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK will have to leave the EU with “no deal” if the British MPs reject the EU-backed accord once again, the French President Emmanuel Macron has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TODAY'S EPISODE:  THE CONWAY SHOW!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kellyanne-conway-calls-husbands-attacks-on-trump-unusual-thanks-president-for-defending-her-from-perceived-unfairness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kellyanne Conway weighed in Thursday on the bitter Twitter feud between her husband George and President Trump, calling her spouse's criticism of her boss "unusual" while thanking Trump for defending her from what “he thinks is unfairness.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Passwords Visible Internally...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-21/facebook-says-millions-of-passwords-were-visible-internally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE: TRUMP WORST KIND OF DUMB...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435059-george-conway-goes-on-early-morning-tweetstorm-against-trump-worst</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, lashed out at President Trump in a new series of tweets early Thursday, saying that he is a liar and "the worst kind of dumb."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro 'turned me into a pariah', says gay lawmaker who fled Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-turned-pariah-says-gay-lawmaker-fled-brazil-175945188.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's first openly gay lawmaker, Jean Wyllys, who fled his country over mounting death threats after the election of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro, fears he won't be returning home anytime soon. In recent months, he said: "I received death threats by telephone, on social media and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labrador Retriever Top Dog Breed For 28th Straight Year!</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/labrador-retriever-most-popular-dog-breed-28th-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labrador retrievers aren't letting go of their hold on U.S. dog lovers, but German shorthaired pointers are tugging on the top ranks of doggy popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May stares into the abyss...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190321141839-tntz7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-No deal beckons: EU presses May on Brexit deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration court backlog up 300%...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/immigration-court-backlog-up-300-system-on-brink-of-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Bar Association is warning of an “existential crisis” over the unprecedented surge in the number of immigration cases clogging up courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Moves More Data to AMAZON Cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2019/03/another-defense-agency-migrates-data-amazon-cloud/155699/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Health Agency joins a growing list of defense agencies moving their data to the commercial cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Drops 3 Busloads of Illegals At Bus Station; Churches Scrambled to Provide Shelter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mrctv.org/blog/ice-reportedly-dropped-3-busloads-illegal-aliens-greyhound-station-churches-scrambled-provide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mrctv.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA wants to track data on scooter users...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/la-wants-to-track-data-on-scooter-users-is-it/article_ca99e38b-52f3-535b-8444-73411cf32a97.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The abrupt arrival of thousands of electric scooters in Los Angeles last year has already forced public, sometimes ugly, disagreements about how the city’s street and sidewalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan forces detain key aide to opposition leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dc2c5f751aa04454b79769d17748ee94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Masked security forces detained a key aide to Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido in a raid on his home early Thursday, arriving in a convoy of vehicles and breaking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigative division of ICE feels ostracized...</title>
      <link>https://pressfrom.info/us/news/us/-257742-investigative-division-of-ice-feels-ostracized.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pressfrom.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mammoth moves: frozen cells come to life, but only just  	 A team of scientists in Japan has successfully coaxed activity from 28,000-year-old cells from a frozen mammoth implanted into mouse c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER GETS READY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/093727be24b649f7adad971e0b48878d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said he believes special counsel Robert Mueller's report should be released to the public, even as he disparaged its very existence as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne Bashes Husband: 'Air Grievances in Private'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/kellyanne-conway-bashes-her-husband-on-fox-you-air-your-grievances-in-private/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to blast people across Atlantic in 30 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6830075/SpaceX-blast-people-Atlantic-rocket-30-minutes-2030.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-haul flights in a rocket will soon wipe out plane travel on Earth, said UBS analysts. It may only take 29 minutes from London to New York and less than one hour to Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/435073-ocasio-cortez-staff-received-risk-assessment-training-from-police-due-to-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's (D-N.Y.) staff has reportedly been trained on performing risk assessments due to the amount of death threats the congresswoman has received.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The naked populist: Baudet stuns Netherlands...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/naked-populist-thierry-baudet-stuns-netherlands-131930952.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former academic with a love of classical allusions and naked poolside Instagram photos, Thierry Baudet has stunned the Dutch political world with his victory in provincial elections. The latest in a line of flamboyant Dutch populists, 36-year-old Baudet and his Forum for Democracy party have been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wingsuit Stunt Lights Up LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/red-bull-wingsuit-stunt-downtown-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People in downtown Los Angeles saw what appeared to be a flaming fireball burning through the sky Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police put out PSA to calm residents...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/03/20/fireball-above-l-a-not-an-alien-invasion-just-a-film-shoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Police Department would like residents to know that aliens are not invading. The LAPD says a fireball that dashed through the sky over downtown Wednesday evening was part of a movie production. The department tweeted a video of the fiery streak with the reassuring message that it wasn't a meteor or an alien invasion — "just a film shoot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers Call for Help With Debt at 1980s Levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/americas-farmers-call-help-debts-climb-1980s-levels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US figure skater accused of deliberately slashing rival at world championships...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/21/us-figure-skater-accused-deliberately-slashing-rival-world-championships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American figure skater has been accused of colliding into a 16-year-old Korean rival in the final warm-up session ahead of the opening of the World Figure Skating Championships in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden advisers debate Stacey Abrams as out-of-the-gate VP choice...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2020-presidential-election-joe-biden-stacey-abrams-vp-54472f8f-5bb2-4d1f-bc7c-0544a09ebba5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They want to show the former V.P. "isn't just another old white guy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New populist star emerges from Dutch local elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/602a05ea46894b2a859fa9c6595a9da7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Netherlands has woken up to a new star of right-wing populism, as the party of a Latin-quoting, philosophy-reading lawmaker surged past anti-Islam firebrand Geert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Military to be deployed for next round of Yellow Vest protests...</title>
      <link>http://en.rfi.fr/france/20190320-military-be-deployed-saturdays-french-yellow-vests-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.rfi.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is to deploy its military anti-terror force as reinforcement during Act 19 of Saturday Yellow Vest protests.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
