<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Secret planet size of Jupiter found by citizen scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4496015/secret-planet-jupiter-nasa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEAM of citizen scientists and astronomers has found a planet the size of Jupiter that NASA missed. The team announced the discovery of the exoplanet, which floats outside of our solar system, la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREDICTS INCURSION</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/biden-predicts-putin-will-launch-incursion-into-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX synagogue terrorist ranted about 'f***ing Jews' in call during siege to family...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/exclusive-texas-synagogue-terrorist-ranted-about-fing-jews-in-last-call-to-family-made-during-siege-2Y5rmNYVAwKPfoV3fMv8i6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How landlocked state of Nebraska got own navy...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2022/01/19/how-the-landlocked-state-of-nebraska-got-its-own-navy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska admirals are in charge of the tadpoles and the goldfish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI tool to detect when patients will recover...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10419907/Machine-learning-process-predict-Covid-patients-recover-disease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German research team has developed an AI tool that can predict whether a person will survive their Covid bout with just a blood sample - at near 100 percent accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declassified drone footage shows botched strike that killed 10 Afghans...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/declassified-drone-footage-shows-botched-strike-that-killed-10-afghans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon released footage showing the final moments before 10 innocent Afghans, including seven children, were killed in an errant drone strike during the final days of the US pullout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-vermont-211fb12ef7ffc5ae3dd5ca4f0476009d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark ruling: Smoking ban on balcony...</title>
      <link>https://www.realestate.com.au/news/unit-owner-barred-from-smoking-on-their-balcony-and-the-decision-that-will-reverberate-through-qld-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realestate.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark ruling against a unit owner, barring them from smoking on their own balcony is a game-changer for strata title complexes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coal town grapples with future as plant shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-coal-environment-colorado-82d2d2af2c8e0f8c56cae205c5b5b9bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAIG, Colorado (AP) — In a quiet valley tucked away from Colorado’s bustling ski resorts, far from his hometown in northern Mexico, Trinidad Loya found a way to support his family’s American dream: Coal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who recovered from prior infection MORE protected than jabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2022/01/19/those-who-recovered-from-covid-19-were-less-likely-than-vaccinated-to-get-infected-during-delta-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data show those who recovered from Covid-19 were less likely than vaccinated people to get infected during the Delta wave. But the data contain caveats that stress the value of vaccination, even with prior infection, experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel turns down UN job offer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/germanys-merkel-turns-down-top-un-job-offer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former German chancellor says no to António Guterres’ proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Supremes deny mask drama report...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/sotomayor-gorsuch-deny-npr-report-of-supreme-court-mask-drama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justices Sonia Sotomayor and Neil Gorsuch issued a joint statement Wednesday denying a National Public Radio report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing laundry getting more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/19/business/tide-gain-downy-laundry-detergent-prices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's going to cost you more to wash your clothes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer dies after catching Covid intentionally...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60050996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hana Horka's son tells the BBC his mother was unvaccinated but wanted to acquire immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex says Clinton, Epstein were 'like brothers'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/prince-andrews-ex-clinton-epstein-were-like-brothers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Clinton was definitely very close to Jeffrey,” Lady Victoria Hervey said in the new ITV documentary, “Ghislaine, Prince Andrew and the Pedophile.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominates first Muslim woman to federal bench...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2022/01/19/biden-nominate-first-muslim-woman-federal-judge/6571815001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's 13th round of federal judge nominations continues the efforts to put more women and judges of color on the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic, who risks being frozen out of tennis, bets on cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/djokovic-buys-80-danish-biotech-developing-covid-19-treatment-ceo-2022-01-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has blocked Novak Djokovic's march to tennis history, so the 34-year-old may be pinning his hopes on a cure for COVID to get his hands on another glorious grand slam before time runs out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-jab parents send children to clandestine schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220119-italian-anti-vax-parents-send-children-to-clandestine-schools-over-covid-19-protocol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy may have reported more than 80,000 Covid-19 cases on Monday, but the anti-vax movement there is still strong. Particularly in northern Italy where distrust of the vaccine has had a real impact…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NFL Prescott 'Deeply Regrets' Comments About Fans Throwing Trash at NFL Referees...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/dak-prescott-says-deeply-regrets-163051927.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dallas Cowboys quarterback apologized for not condemning fans after they threw trash at the referees following Sunday's game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's core cooling faster than previously thought, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/earths-core-cooling-faster-previously-thought-researchers-say-rcna12732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earth's core is cooling at rates faster than previously thought, which could speed the planet's inevitable march toward inhabitability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump and Weisselberg invoked the Fifth more than 500 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/4-big-points-from-the-ny-attorney-general-e2-80-99s-trump-allegations/ar-AASW9Pr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss researchers launch trial for covid 'patch' vax...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220119164630-7ji73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs scrap compulsory vaccination, want to avoid split in society...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220119151524-ly020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skier charged with manslaughter after killing 5-year-old in crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/skier-charged-with-manslaughter-after-killing-5-year-old-in-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man faces manslaughter charges in connection with a high-speed crash on a ski slope that left a 5-year-old girl dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaspard Ulliel, French Actor and 'MOON KNIGHT' Star, Dies at 37 After Ski Accident...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/gaspard-ulliel-dead-dies-moon-knight-french-actor-1235157242/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French actor Gaspard Ulliel (“It’s Only the End of the World”), who stars in Marvel’s upcoming “Moon Knight” series, has died following a ski accident in the Alps on W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew quits social media as sex assault case looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220119-prince-andrew-quits-social-media-as-us-sex-assault-case-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II's second son Prince Andrew has deactivated his social media accounts, users said Wednesday, as he faces a US civil case for sexual assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio police occupy favelas in new push to combat gangs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220119131710-dp6cy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-RIO/FAVELAS (PIX):Rio police occupy favelas in new push to combat gangs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Eye Test Can Reveal How Long You Have Left To Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eye-test-how-long-youll-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery could lead to a routine screening tool for a host of life-threatening illnesses - including Alzheimer's disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than Third of  Country Gives Him 'F'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/new-poll-more-than-a-third-of-the-country-gives-biden-an-f-for-his-first-year-in-office-just-11-percent-give-him-an-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year into his term, more than a third of the country believes President Joe Biden is flunking out, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE, Wintour Called Out for Not Paying Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10416999/Andre-Leon-Talley-dead-73-Former-Vogue-editor-fashion-icon-passes-away-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion icon Andre Leon Talley has passed away of COVID complications at the age of 73. Talley is remembered as 'incredible' and recognized as one of the driving forces in Vogue's success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE, Wintour Called Out for Not Paying Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vogue-called-out-for-not-paying-tribute-to-andre-leon-talley-after-his-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critic Roxane Gay said it’s a case study in “how your job will never love you no matter how much you give them.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham on Her First Film in Decade, Youthful Blind Spots and Rebooting 'GIRLS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/lena-dunham-interview-sharp-stick-girls-reboot-1235076390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarizing auteur, back at Sundance with "sexual fable" 'Sharp Stick,’ reveals how surviving hate, sickness and addiction led to artistic rebirth: "I'd love the next decade to be less about apologizing and just about openly making art."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars including Jay-Z call for end to use of rap lyrics as criminal evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2022/jan/19/stars-including-jay-z-call-for-end-to-use-of-rap-lyrics-as-criminal-evidence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meek Mill, Kelly Rowland and more sign letter supporting proposed change in New York state law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal may bring hundreds of Qatar Air Force members to Idaho base...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/branches/air_force/2022-01-18/deal-qatar-air-rorce-members-idaho-base-4330963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Qatar's air force would live on Mountain Home Air Force Base to learn to fly the newest model of the F-15 fighter jet specially modified for the Persian Gulf state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power struggle among appointees gets personal over race...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/power-struggle-among-biden-appointees-gets-personal-over-race/ar-AASVzVf </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson, Facing Mutiny, Says England Will Ease Virus Rules...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/19/boris-johnson-facing-a-mutiny-says-england-will-ease-virus-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Prime Minister Boris Johnson, fighting for his political life, said on Wednesday that he would ease coronavirus restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traders Bet Oil at $100 a Question of When, Not If...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/only-china-virus-outbreak-shale-084115815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Surging demand, fading omicron fears, and OPEC+’s inability to ramp up output have underpinned an eye-watering rally in oil prices. Most Read from BloombergMicrosoft Buys Scandal-Tainted Activision in Bet on MetaverseFourth Pfizer Dose Is Insufficient to Ward Off Omicron, Israeli Trial SuggestsCovid-19 Infected Lions Prompt Variant Warning in South AfricaStock Selloff Deepens as Treasury Yields Climb: Markets WrapNew Satellite Images Show How Tonga Volcano Blew Island to PiecesGlo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sixth Mass Extinction -- Already Underway...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mass-extinction-already-underway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study reveals that 7.5 to 13 percent of the two million different living organisms which inhabit the planet are now extinct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthritis Cured -- By Zapping Bone With Electricity?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/arthritis-pain-regrowing-cartilage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technique, which researchers have successfully tested on rabbits, uses small electric shocks to stimulate cartilage growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's All Just Wild': Tech Start-Ups Reach New Peak of Froth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/19/its-all-just-wild-tech-start-ups-reach-a-new-peak-of-froth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — How crazy is the money sloshing around in start-up land right now? It’s so crazy that more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative MP defects to Labour in protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-tory-mp-christian-wakeford-25989176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bury South MP Christian Wakeford, who was only elected to the 'Red Wall' seat in 2019, has abandoned the Tories for Labour in a seismic move as the Prime Minister faces a possible vote of no confidence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions facing president at his second solo presser...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/590295-questions-facing-biden-at-his-second-solo-presser</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden on Wednesday will host just his second solo press conference from the White House since taking office, offering reporters a rare opportunity to press him on news of the day in such a format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK mysterious robot eyeball tracks where person looking...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-working-mysterious-authentic-robot-165815802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eye would ‘resemble a human eye’ that would appear ‘authentic to an observer’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wealthy LA enclave, harsher penalties for wasting water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-environment-and-nature-droughts-7eb1fdf1a19e15b1db41a000168b2cf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wealthy enclave along the Santa Monica Mountains that is a haven for celebrities, residents are now facing more aggressive consequences for wasting water. The Las Virgenes Municipal Water District northwest of Los Angeles hopes to spur water savings by making it easier to fine households that go over their allotted “water budgets" and threatening to vastly limit water flow to customers who repeatedly fail to conserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple trapped on lockdown date get engaged...</title>
      <link>https://www.news24.com/news24/world/news/chinese-couple-trapped-on-lockdown-date-get-engaged-20220119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese couple who were trapped on a neverending date thanks to a virus lockdown have been relieved to find that love, not the coronavirus, is in the air and have agreed to tie the knot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns foreign Olympic athletes against speaking out on politics at Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/China-warns-foreign-Olympic-athletes-against-16786929.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of China's Olympics organizing committee warned that foreign athletes may face...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biden's declining popularity as he struggles with multiple crises...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Inside-Biden-s-declining-popularity-as-he-16786935.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The second week of August began as a time for vacation for President Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY RECORD INFECTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/covid-19-germany-passes-100000-new-infections-in-past-24-hours/ar-AASV9nI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country has further tightened curbs to cut contamination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO  ALERT</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10415817/White-House-says-Russian-invasion-Ukraine-come-point.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Tuesday said it believed a Russian invasion of Ukraine could come at any time, as Press Secretary Jen Psaki warned of an 'extremely dangerous situation' at the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front row fixture...</title>
      <link>https://wwd.com/business-news/media/fashion-journalist-andre-leon-tally-dead-at-1235039207/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wwd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fashion journalist, New York Times bestselling author and former Vogue creative director has died, TAA PR has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires group calls for wealth tax at Davos...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220118235659-5pnw5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEALTH-BILLIONAIRES/ (PIX):Millionaires group calls for wealth tax at virtual Davos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTY'S OVER?  BORIS ON THE BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2022/jan/18/boris-johnson-challenge-leadership-tory-mps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MPs from across party confident of enough letters to trigger leadership contest after Sue Gray’s report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant 28 lb cat may break world weight record!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4491293/giant-cat-weighs-27-5-pounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NO kitten around — Yulia Minina’s pet looks furmidable. She says the Maine Coon weighs 12.5kg (27.5lb), making it just a whisker away from a world record. And as Kefir is only 22 months, she still …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun used to kill Tijuana photojournalist linked to five other violent crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2022-01-18/gun-tijuana-photojournalist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief prosecutor for central Baja California released details of the fatal shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plot to unseat Prime Minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10415969/Dozens-new-intake-Red-Wall-Tory-MPs-launch-pork-pie-plot-bring-Boris-Johnson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson was last night battling to put down a coup attempt by Red Wall MPs. Ministers rounded on the group of newly-elected Tories after details emerged of their 'Pork Pie Plot' to unseat the PM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil reports record daily infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220119013233-pnd4h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL-TALLY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Brazil reports record daily COVID-19 infections as Omicron spreads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mild cases still lead to memory issues...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220118235759-kpcer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-ATTENTION (PIX):Mild COVID cases still lead to attention and memory issues - study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN WAR GAMES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/moscow-russia-europe-belarus-ukraine-555703583c8f9d54bd42e60aca895590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDRE LEON TALLEY DEAD AT 73...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/18/andre-leon-talley-dead-dies-vogue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andre Leon Talley, a giant in the fashion world, has died at 73.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis says backing Trump for 2024 now 'is too much to ask'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10413077/DeSantis-NOT-bend-knee-Trump-says-backing-ex-president-2024-ask.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeSantis, a once-loyal member of  Trump's court, told his inner circle that backing Trump is 'too much to ask'. He also said his biggest regret was not standing up to Trump's pandemic restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELS:  50,000-300,000 MORE DEAD IN USA BY SPRING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-08f8db29985b992d5ef98ccfa1459eb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-moving omicron variant may cause less severe disease on average, but COVID-19 deaths in the U.S. are climbing and modelers forecast 50,000 to 300,000 more Americans could die by the time the wave subsides in mid-March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee subpoenas Giuliani, other lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/jan-6-committee-subpoenas-giuliani-3-other-trump-lawyers-accuses-n1287670</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee said Rudy Giuliani, Jenna Ellis, Sidney Powell and Boris Epshteyn "publicly promoted unsupported claims about the 2020 election and participated in attempts to disrupt or delay the certification of election results."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida could shield whites from 'discomfort' of racist past...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-florida-lawsuits-ron-desantis-racial-injustice-3ec10492b7421543315acf4491813c1b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — A bill pushed by Republican Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis that would prohibit public schools and private businesses from making white people feel “discomfort” when they teach students or train employees about discrimination in the nation's past received its first approval Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
