<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>World's tiniest twin boys defy odds after being born at 23 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10318673/worlds-tiniest-twin-boys-23-weeks-one-pound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUM Talia Keates cradles her “little miracles” — the world’s tiniest twin boys. Ashley and Joe each weighed less than 1lb when born at 23 weeks. The Brit mum says the boys are her “one in a million…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Can Marriage Counseling Save America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/12/better-angels-can-this-union-be-saved/600775/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Borrowing techniques from couples therapy to bring liberals and conservatives back together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy launching -- podcast?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/politics/rudy-giuliani-impeachment-podcast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani is considering re-entering the impeachment fray by launching a podcast to provide impeachment analysis of the public hearings in the House of Representatives scheduled for later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor arrested for performing procedures on patients without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/health/virginia-doctor-hysterectomies-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia doctor has been arrested after he was accused of performing hysterectomies and other unnecessary medical procedures on patients without their consent, according to a federal affidavit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can't sue NY to stop release of tax returns, judge says...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/judge-dismisses-trump-lawsuit-ny-officials-house-committee/story?id=66918561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Monday issued another blow to President Donald Trump and his ongoing effort to avoid having his tax records turned over to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub crawl in NKorea? Tour offers St Patrick's Day party like no other...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/pub-crawl-north-korea-tour-172859249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cities dye their rivers green (looking at you, Chicago), others light up the sky with emerald fireworks, but across the globe, St Patrick’s Day is universally celebrated with a drink or two. And it seems in North Korea it is no different. Although the Foreign Office advises against visiting North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7672837/Simon-Cowell-looks-slimmer-steps-London.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The X Factor head judge revealed a noticeably slender physique while greeting onlookers ahead of his appearance at Heart Radio studios in Leicester Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense firms on track to make killer bots reality...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1746154/lacking-regulation-firms-on-track-to-make-killer-robots-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such weapons “violate fundamental legal and ethical principles and would destabilize international peace and security,” says a Dutch NGO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students turn against free speech amid 'culture of conformity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7672091/Fewer-HALF-UK-students-support-freedom-speech-polls-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey by think tank The Policy Exchange shows youngsters whose views don't conform with the majority of students, such as those who support Brexit, feel silenced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO REPLACE IPHONES WITH GLASSES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/11/smart-glasses-that-replace-phones-may-be-the-next-hottest-tech-trend.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft, Snap, Facebook, Google, Apple and Amazon are all racing to replace our phones with glasses we wear everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. abandons book event after being drowned out  by hecklers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/11/donald-trump-jr-walks-out-of-triggered-book-launch-after-heckling-from-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Event at University of California is cut short amid anger at his refusal to take questions from the audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Happiness Most Dominant Human Expression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/reason-to-smile-happiness-most-dominant-human-expression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the thousands of possibilities, there are but 35 universally accepted facial expressions. Yet perhaps most remarkable is roughly half of these are expressions of happiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the President's Yes Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-road-to-impeachment-paved-by-all-the-presidents-yes-men/ar-BBWAnPf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Threatens to Sue Hillary Over 'Defamatory' Russia Comment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/tulsi-gabbard-demands-hillary-clinton-retract-russia-comments-your-statement-is-defamatory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard has sent a letter to Hillary Clinton demanding the 2016 presidential candidate retract her statements on Gabbard and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPEYE'S worker brutally attacks woman seeking refund...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/popeyes-worker-accused-of-attacking-customer-seeking-refund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Popeyes worker recorded throwing a woman onto the pavement outside a restaurant in Tennessee has been charged with felony aggravated assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB rental turns out to be NYC public housing apartment...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/airbnb-rental-turns-out-to-be-public-housing-apartment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tourist discovered her Airbnb rental was actually in a public housing complex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/politics/elections/ct-iowa-joe-biden-pete-buttigieg-2020-presidential-race-moderates-20191107-qdqrz2fb3fd55o4xlkaq2ogzye-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Iowa, Pete Buttigieg has emerged as the major alternative to Joe Biden among moderate voters the former vice president has counted on as the bedrock of his campaign in the first-in-the-nation caucus state. The Midwestern mayor not only has caught Biden in the polls, but his campaign is better funded, has drawn larger and louder crowds at events, and has shown signs of a more effective ground operation in a state where the former vice president is making his third bid for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Booed Offstage, Stormy Daniels Raps at Bizarre L.A. Concert...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/drake-booed-off-stage-stormy-daniels-donald-trump-camp-flog-gnaw-watch-1203400388/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler, The Creator’s Camp Flog Gnaw Carnival is always entertaining — last year featured Kanye West and Kid Cudi performing inside a giant glass box. But it inadvertently outdid itself this year wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDBERG:  Worst thing about Trump's 'fake news' warning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/469408-the-worst-thing-about-trumps-fake-news-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if there were proof that Trump tries to discredit journalists so he won't look bad, his fans wouldn't care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napoleon expert confesses to chopping up lover...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russias-napoleon-expert-confesses-chopping-lover-114345339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Saint Petersburg-based Napoleon expert has confessed to murdering his young lover and former student and dismembering her body in a grisly crime that sent shock waves across Russia. Oleg Sokolov, a 63-year-old history lecturer who received France's Legion d'Honneur from Jacques Chirac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsule living: 'Cheap' option for young people flocking to LA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/capsule-living-cheap-option-young-people-flocking-la-161917564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kay Wilson packed up her life in a hurry and moved to Los Angeles... only to find that what she paid in Pennsylvania for a nice studio apartment would only get her a 2.9-square-meter box in California. Wilson arrived a month ago at UP(st)ART, a community for young people with artistic aspirations in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still teaching at 95, Jimmy Carter draws devotees to church...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0fb39dc916d48c1a8fa5bf72f5deb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLAINS, Ga. (AP) — The pilgrims arrive early and from all over, gathering hours before daybreak in an old pecan grove that surrounds a country church. They come, they say, for a dose of simple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napolitano emerges as Trump critic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52b6a16fa159457b907cc90c4846d6a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More than two decades into his career as a commentator at Fox News Channel, Andrew Napolitano reached a milestone of sorts when he was called a "fool" on his own network. Not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain sees widening political divide as nationalism rises...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ef48230926d485faeb551ef17e91127</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain looked set Monday to endure many more months of political uncertainty after the country's fourth election in as many years reflected a widening political chasm between parties...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WARMING ON HOLD:  WINTER COMES EARLY TO WINDY CITY...</title>
      <link>https://accuweather.com/en/weather-news/snow-arctic-cold-to-blast-the-northeast-us-in-the-coming-days/622226 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hundreds of records could fall in cold snap...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/11/veterans-day-weather-snow-record-breaking-cold-sweep-nation/2560318001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wintry weather pattern was rolling across a wide swath of the nation, threatening to break hundreds of records and a freeze as far south as Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACH SIGNS HANG OVER TRUMP VETERAN'S DAY SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ABC/status/1193919259510001664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Signs spelling out "Impeach" adorn windows of a building overlooking Pres. Trump's speech at New York City's Veterans Day Parade. https://t.co/qUl8R8XHCY”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. abandons book event after being drowned out -- by angry supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/lions-den-don-trump-jr-abandons-book-event-after-being-drowned-out-by-angry-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump, Jr. ended a book event after his own supporters heckled him for not taking questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly Internet Comeback Fizzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/11/megyn-kelly-internet-comeback-fizzles-with-only-six-thousand-instagram-subscribers-22k-on-youtube</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly’s big comeback on You Tube and Instagram has fizzled. She’s scratched up just 22,000 followers on the latter, and a mere 6 subscribers on the former. For her big interview w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo cartel puts on show of strength with armored convoy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/el-chapos-cartel-puts-show-20860240</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vehicles were seen barreling into the village filled with armed cartel members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Starts Sending Captured Foreign Fighters Home From Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-50372155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey says one US jihadist has been expelled, and several Europeans will follow shortly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews Egged in Brooklyn...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/hate-crime-anti-semitism-boro-park-jews-egged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another hate crime investigation is underway in Brooklyn. Once again, community leaders say Jewish people are being targeted in Borough Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Of Needles Wash Ashore Along Venice Beach...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/large-amount-of-needles-other-medical-supplies-appear-along-venice-beach-shoreline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities cordoned off an area of Venice Beach Sunday after a large amount of medical supplies appeared on the sand, including needles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER CEO comment about murdered journalist sparks backlash...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-murdered-journalist-jamal-khashoggi-serious-mistake-boycott-uber-142945393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtag #BoycottUber began trending on Twitter (TWTR) Monday morning after CEO Dara Khosrowshahi called the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi “a serious mistake” during an interview with Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland Criticizes NETFLIX After 'Terrible Mistake' on Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-netflix-poland/poland-asks-netflix-to-make-changes-to-documentary-about-nazi-death-camp-guard-idUSKBN1XL1PI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish Prime Minister Mateusz Morawiecki has pressed Netflix, the U.S. streaming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable news networks to preempt regular programming...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/469846-broadcast-cable-news-networks-to-preempt-regular-programming-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC, CBS, NBC and PBS on Wednesday will preempt their regularly scheduled programming for live coverage of the House Intelligence Committee's open impeachment hearings of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment week: Probe hits crucial point...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/469822-impeachment-week-trump-probe-hits-crucial-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It all comes down to this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American robots lose jobs to Asian robots as ADIDAS shifts manufacturing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/11/american-robots-lose-jobs-to-asian-robots-as-adidas-shifts-manufacturing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adidas plans to close high-tech “robot” factories in Germany and the United States it launched to bring production closer to customers, saying on Monday deploying some of the technology in Asia wou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARAGE STANDS DOWN; LIFTS BORIS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uks-farage-withdraws-brexit-threat-pm-johnson-135343952.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Populist Brexit Party leader Nigel Farage on Monday withdrew his threat to challenge the governing Conservatives at every seat in next month's election, in a boost for Prime Minister Boris Johnson. Farage, a leading force behind the 2016 referendum vote to leave the European Union, had faced criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Millions, It Feels Like Economic Depression...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/for-millions-of-americans-in-the-middle-of-the-country-it-feels-like-an-economic-depression-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you do when you have lost all hope that things will ever turn around?  It may still feel like "the economy is booming" for those at the top end of the economic food</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tiger next door: America's backyard big cats...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2019/nov/10/the-tiger-next-door-americas-backyard-big-cats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more tigers in American gardens than there are left in the wild. Alex Hannaford meets the owners who live cheek by jowl with their pets, and also those ensuring the big cats are treated without cruelty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The West's left-right battle lines run through Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-West-s-left-right-battle-lines-run-through-14825130.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They did not jail a man," declared the released prisoner. "They tried to kill an idea, and ideas don't disappear."  The freed man was Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the former left-wing Brazilian president who was jailed last year on corruption charges that his supporters believe were politically motivated. Lula left office in 2010 with a staggering 80 percent approval rating and was favored to be on course to return to power in 2018; his imprisonment paved the path to the presidency for far-right firebrand Jair Bolsonaro, who, both on the campaign trail and now in office, has loudly banged the drum against perceived perfidy and tyranny of leftist dogma.  But last week, Brazil's Supreme Court ruled that Lula, as well dozens of others ensnared in a rolling corruption probe that reshaped Brazilian politics, had been unjustly jailed without receiving due process - that is, they had been denied the ability to exhaust their right to appeal their sentences before imprisonment. On Friday, Lula walked out of jail and was greeted by a throng of supporters from his left-leaning Workers' Party.  "You have no idea of the meaning of me being here with you," he said soon after his release in the southern city of Curitiba. "I, who have been speaking to the Brazilian people through all my life, did not think that I would be able to speak today . . . Every day you were the democracy's fuel I needed to exist."  From thousands of miles to the north came a striking message of support. Democratic presidential candidate Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., tweeted his admiration for Lula's socially minded policies and decried his imprisonment. "I am delighted that he has been released from jail, something that never should have happened in the first place," Sanders said. Lula thanked the U.S. candidate for his "solidarity," and expressed his "hope"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigar-shaped UFO now over Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/cigar-shaped-ufo-appears-plane-20847849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some believed the UFO was following the plane and the shape of the "craft" mirrored others that have been spotted above the US this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING: Bezos buying NFL team?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/amazon-founder-jeff-bezos-interested-in-owning-nfl-team-has-strong-support-among-current-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of Amazon and the Washington Post could be the next person to join the NFL's ownership ranks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a sin': Cambodia's brutal and shadowy dog meat trade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sin-cambodias-brutal-shadowy-dog-meat-trade-065939849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cambodian dog meat traders drown, strangle and stab thousands of canines a day in a shadowy but sprawling business that traumatises workers and exposes them to deadly health risks like rabies. Khieu Chan bursts into tears when describing a job that haunts him as he goes to sleep: he kills up to six</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After push from Perry, backers got huge gas deal in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d8ae551fb884371a2a592ed85a74426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Two political supporters of U.S. Energy Secretary Rick Perry secured a potentially lucrative oil and gas exploration deal from the Ukrainian government soon after Perry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Go back to California': Wave of newcomers fuels backlash in Boise...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-10/go-back-to-california-wave-of-newcomers-fuels-backlash-in-boise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bashing newcomers from California is a cyclical sport with a long history in the heart of Idaho’s Treasure Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER: Longtime Republican Rep. Peter King won't seek reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/rep-peter-king-r-ny-will-not-seek-re-election-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Peter King, R-N.Y., the powerful 14-term congressman who once chaired the House Committee on Homeland Security, announced Monday he will not seek re-election in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Socialist Hell: Living in Post-Electricity Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/11/10/venezuela-socialist-hell-electricity-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela has always had trouble maintaining a functional power grid. I lived in the city of Punto Fijo from 1992 to 1996, blackouts were occasional back then.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic test to predict embryo intelligence, health...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/09/genetic-test-aims-to-predict-an-embryos-intelligence-and-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new genetic test straight out of a dystopian sci-fi film aims to let hopeful parents pick smarter, taller, and healthier babies. Laurent Tellier, the founder of New Jersey startup Genomic Predict…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMY new recruiting ads focus less on combat roles...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/armys-recruiting-ads-focus-combat-roles/story?id=66893818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army is targeting Generation Z with roles less centered around combat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD HEALTH:  KAISER PERMANENTE CEO dies unexpectedly at 60...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bernard-tyson/kaiser-permanente-ceo-bernard-tyson-dies-unexpectedly-at-60-idUSKBN1XL05U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernard J. Tyson, chairman and chief executive officer of not-for-profit health ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg outlasts the pundits by emerging as alternative to Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-10/pete-buttigieg-rising-alternative-biden-warren</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg is fast threatening former Vice President Joe Biden’s dominance of the Democratic primary’s pragmatic lane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway Dares 'Weak and Scared' Trump to Testify...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/politics/kellyanne-conways-husband-dares-weak-and-scared-trump-to-testify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students turn against free speech amid 'culture of conformity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/students-turn-against-free-speech-amid-culture-of-conformity-tfrnzx8kt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer than half of students consistently support freedom of speech and two fifths favour censorship and no-platforming of controversial speakers, research has shown. A “culture of conformity” may...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV on rise among older women... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10319591/hiv-rise-older-women-sexually-active-without-using-protection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIV is on the rise among older women as they remain sexually active without using protection. There has been a five-fold increase in women aged between 45 and 56 receiving care for HIV in the past …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON ALEXA MAY SOON HAVE EYES AS WELL AS EARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/614676/amazon-alexa-will-run-your-life-data-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The creator of the famous voice assistant dreams of a world where Alexa is everywhere, anticipating your every need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican moderate breaks with party over identifying whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/10/will-hurd-ukraine-whistleblower-identity-068657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC and Bernie Star in Their Own Iowa Buddy Movie... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/10/alexandria-ocasio-corteziowa-sanders-068786</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINGERPRINT TEST CAN TELL IF SOMEONE HAS USED DRUGS, EVEN AFTER WASHING HANDS... </title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2019-11-11/fingerprint-test-can-tell-if-someone-has-used-heroin-even-after-washing-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN:  Don't rule out Hillary run...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/2020-hillary-clinton-michael-bloomberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is still time for Hillary Clinton and Michael Bloomberg to enter the 2020 presidential race, as a field of weak candidates continues to fuel speculation of a dark horse savior, said former Clinton strategist Mark Penn on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong police shoot two pro-democracy protesters... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7671231/Two-protesters-shot-police-Hong-Kong-officers-open-fire-live-rounds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shots rang out at a blockaded junction in the district of Sai Wan Ho as a police officer attempted to arrest a masked man during a wild scuffle on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOTHING WAS DONE WRONG!'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-faces-perilous-test-impeachment-hearings-open-014316777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump faces the prospect of becoming only the third US president to be impeached when open hearings begin this week into his alleged effort to bolster his re-election hopes by pushing Ukraine to find dirt on a Democratic rival. Having survived special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney's move to join impeachment lawsuit rankles Bolton allies... </title>
      <link>https://hamodia.com/2019/11/10/mulvaneys-move-join-impeachment-testimony-lawsuit-rankles-bolton-allies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hamodia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House acting chief of staff Mick Mulvaney's last-minute effort to join a lawsuit that could determine whether senior administration officials testify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  AIDES TRIED TO 'SAVE COUNTRY' FROM TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Nikki-Haley-claims-top-aides-tried-to-recruit-her-14824057.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of President Donald Trump's senior advisers undermined and ignored him in what they claimed was an effort to "save the country," former United Nations ambassador Nikki Haley claims in a new memoir.  Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson and former White House Chief of Staff John Kelly sought to recruit her to work around and subvert Trump, but she refused, Haley writes in a new book, "With All Due Respect," which also describes Tillerson as "exhausting" and imperious and Kelly as suspicious of her access to Trump.  "Kelly and Tillerson confided in me that when they resisted the president, they weren't being insubordinate, they were trying to save the country," Haley wrote.  "It was their decisions, not the president's, that were in the best interests of America, they said. The president didn't know what he was doing," Haley wrote of the views the two men held.  Tillerson also told her that people would die if Trump was unchecked, Haley wrote.  Tillerson did not respond to a request for comment. Kelly declined to comment in detail, but said that if providing the president "with the best and most open, legal and ethical staffing advice from across the (government) so he could make an informed decision is 'working against Trump,' then guilty as charged."  In the book, which was obtained by The Washington Post ahead of its release Tuesday, Haley offers only glancing critiques of her former boss, saying she and others who worked for Trump had an obligation to carry out his wishes since he was the one elected by voters.  The former South Carolina governor, widely viewed by Republicans as a top potential presidential candidate, has repeatedly sought to minimize differences with Trump while distancing herself from his excesses. Haley, 47, writes that she backed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President tweets 82 times  -- in one day...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-twitter-tweets-impeachment-inquiry-70f705e6-17ba-4adb-9975-ff1c11ea2d5f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He mentioned "impeachment," "impeach" or "impeachable" nine times, "Democrats" five times, and "whistleblower" 11 times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As impeachment goes public, forget 'conventional wisdom'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/469753-as-impeachment-goes-public-forget-conventional-wisdom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public and political attitudes will be shaped by how the deliberations come across.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
