<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How vitamin C craze led to FBI raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2020/07/21/coronavirus-vitamin-c-demand-surged-during-pandemic/5403847002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitamin C has become the subject of faith, controversy and even frequent government crackdowns amid the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci responds to Trump: I'm realist, not alarmist...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/fauci-responds-trump-i-consider-myself-realist-opposed-alarmist-n1234441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president said in a Fox News interview that Fauci is “a little bit of an alarmist" and had made some mistakes but that they had 'a very good relationship.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 51 photographs show rarely seen angles of secret base...</title>
      <link>https://www.kget.com/national-news/exclusive-area-51-photographs-show-rarely-seen-angles-of-secret-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As revealed on The Joe Rogan Experience podcast, a private pilot has released images and video showing new angles of the mysterious Area 51.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD reveals seven-motor electric Mustang with 1,400 horsepower!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/21/success/ford-electric-mustang-mach-e-1400/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking to explore how far it can push the limits of electric vehicle performance, Ford has created a version of its Mustang Mach-E SUV with seven electric motors that can produce a total of up to 1,400 horsepower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to re-up virus briefings amid lagging polls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfb8402551605ff40d8a16efbd827b92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is set to once again take center stage in the government's coronavirus response after a White House debate over how best to deploy its greatest and most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Red flag'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/597b63c1ddf52ef57a5eccfaa67b8a94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Federal officers’ actions at protests in Oregon’s largest city, hailed by President Donald Trump but done without local consent, are raising the prospect of a constitutional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Asks Police to Step Up Arrest of Those Not Wearing Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/duterte-asks-police-to-step-up-arrest-of-those-not-wearing-masks/ar-BB16Z6OC?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Trump Moved Millions From Campaign Donors To His Private Business...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michelatindera/2020/07/21/how-donald-trump-moved-millions-from-his-campaign-donors-to-his-private-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions from his campaign, millions from the RNC, millions from committees. While other billionaires spend big on the election, the Donald is raking it in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT releases deepfake video of 'Nixon' announcing NASA Apollo 11 disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mit-releases-deepfake-video-of-nixon-announcing-nasa-apollo-11-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT and Modzilla want people to better understand the disturbing power of deepfake videos in a new project called In Event of Moon Disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Votes in 2020 Election Will Be Cast in Six Weeks!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/first-votes-in-the-2020-election-will-be-cast-in-six-weeks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First Votes in the 2020 Election Will Be Cast in Six Weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caged like 'canary', Vivienne Westwood protests for Assange in London...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200721072057-zn5we</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ASSANGE/WESTWOOD (PIX, TV):Caged like a 'canary', Vivienne Westwood protests for Assange in London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Glimpse Into Fiscal Gloom Bearing Down on America...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/glimpse-fiscal-gloom-bearing-down-100011417.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In Cincinnati, a city of 300,000 on the banks of the Ohio River, Mayor John Cranley faces cuts to police, fire and sanitation without more help from Washington.The city has already had to tiptoe back from the fiscal abyss earlier this year by temporarily laying off one-quarter of its workforce</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Jobless Rate 21%?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/real-unemployment-rate-21-and-heading-higher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis Police Experience Surge of Departures...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/21/minneapolis-police-experience-surge-of-departures-in-aftermath-of-george-floyd-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS — Nearly two months after four of its officers were charged with killing George Floyd, the Minneapolis Police Department</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bret Easton Ellis, Irvine Welsh To Co-Create Press Satire 'AMERICAN TABLOID'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/irvine-welsh-bret-easton-ellis-us-press-satire-series-american-tabloid-1202990599/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irvine Welsh and Bret Easton Ellis are set to team up on a satirical drama series about America’s tabloid press culture, according to UK producer Burning Wheel Productions. Working title American T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goes on BiPolar TWITTER Spree, Attacks Kris Jenner...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/20/kanye-goes-on-bipolar-twitter-spree-says-wife-kim-kardashian-tried-to-bring-a-doctor-to-lock-me-up-with-a-doctor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has gone on a Twitter spree. It’s a bipolar breakdown and it’s not funny. He needs help. It looks like Kim Kardashian tried to get help, but he rejected it. And now he’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson accuses NYT of endangering his family with forthcoming story... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/tucker-carlson-accuses-new-york-times-of-endangering-his-family-with-forthcoming-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Tucker Carlson said the New York Times will put his family in danger by publishing his address in a forthcoming story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Hikes in a Pandemic: Some States, Cities Say Yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2020/07/17/tax-hikes-in-a-pandemic-some-states-cities-say-yes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State budget shortfalls could total $555 billion over the next two fiscal years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS to collect data on monument protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.lawfareblog.com/dhs-authorizes-domestic-surveillance-protect-statues-and-monuments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lawfareblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A document provided to Lawfare indicates that the intelligence community is being tasked with monitoring and collecting information on some protest activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85 crew members infected on Alaska fishing boat...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2020/07/19/85-crewmembers-aboard-seafood-ship-in-unalaska-test-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crew members did not leave the ship once it reached Unalaska, according to an American Seafoods spokeswoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napolitano declares 'unconstitutional'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/508205-foxs-napolitano-rips-unconstitutional-trump-crackdown-on-portland-just-plain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Napolitano slammed the Trump administration for sending federal law enforcement to Portland in response to violent protests in Oregon's largest city, with the Fox News senior judicial analyst calling the move "unconstitutional" and "ju</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW IT'S SPREADING IN IDAHO!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-taking-off-rural-us-state-idaho-190458553.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since last week, the small, rural northwestern US state of Idaho has been racking up 500 new coronavirus cases a day -- a sign of the exponential spread of the disease across the country. With just 1.8 million inhabitants, Idaho -- famous for its potatoes and meat processing plants -- is seeing a virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil set to test Chinese coronavirus vaccine... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-set-test-chinese-coronavirus-vaccine-011830936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil will begin advanced clinical testing of a Chinese-made vaccine against the new coronavirus Tuesday, issuing the first doses to around 900 volunteers, officials said. The coronavirus vaccine, developed by private Chinese pharmaceutical firm Sinovac, is the third in the world to enter Phase 3 trials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein judge in 24-hour protection after son shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1171191/judge-esther-salas-in-24-hour-protection-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FEDERAL judge whose son was killed and her husband critically injured in a shooting at their home is receiving 24-hour protection from US Marshals, according to reports. The incident took place o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moms form human wall in face-off with officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1171114/portland-protest-mom-human-wall-trump-federal-officers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND protesters were protected by their moms who formed a human wall during a face-off with Trump’s federal officers. At least 30 parents linked arms with one another on Saturday chanting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Will Be Most Litigated in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/2020-election-will-be-the-most-litigated-in-u-s-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden is shaping up to be the most litigated in U.S. history, as changes to balloting prompted by the coronavirus pandemic spur lawsuits that could leave the outcome in suspense for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies fear airborne risk amid pressure to reopen...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-airborne/u-s-companies-fear-workplace-coronavirus-precautions-do-not-address-airborne-risk-idUSKCN24L17L?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. companies are raising new questions about how they can make workplaces safe after the world’s top public health agency acknowledged the risk that tiny airborne droplets of the novel coronavirus may contribute to its spread, industry healthcare consultants said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Will reveals he is voting for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2020/07/george-will-reveals-he-is-voting-for-joe-biden-the-first-time-hes-ever-cast-a-vote-for-a-democrat-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pulitzer Prize-winning Washington Post columnist George Will says he will be casting a vote for a Democrat in November — for the first time in his life. Will was interviewed at the Aspen Institute on Monday by USA TODAY Washington bureau chief Susan Page. Page reports that Will said that will be voting for Biden […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis couple who aimed guns at protesters charged with felony weapons count...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/st-louis-couple-who-aimed-guns-at-protesters-charged-with-felony-weapons-count/ar-BB16Yx5A?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sex cult' led by 77-year-old man known only as The Doctor uncovered in Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-cult-led-77-year-22386623?_ga=2.101743941.579266895.1595291746-1911521288.1594507464#source=push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 77-year-old man who is accused of running the unnamed group in Novara near the Italian city of Milan allegedly subjected young women and minors to sexual acts over the course of 30 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuralink chip will stream music directly to brain!</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-computer-chip-music-stream-a9627686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient who gave birth on ventilator dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/brooklyn-center-woman-dies-after-giving-birth-on-ventilator-battling-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juan Duran’s wife, Aurora, was on a ventilator at North Memorial Hospital since June 19. Since then, her baby was delivered via emergency C-section.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heavy Social Media Use Linked To Callous And Cruel Personalities...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90530068/people-who-like-embarrassing-or-angering-others-find-social-media-more-addictive-study-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruel and callous? You’ll love social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Orders Christians to Take Down Images of Jesus from Homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/07/20/china-orders-christians-to-take-down-images-of-jesus-from-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have ordered believers to replace Christian images in their homes with portraits of Communist heroes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week of Vandalism and Arson Against Churches Across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/07/20/catholics-decry-week-of-vandalism-and-arson-against-churches-across-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic churches from Florida to Los Angeles to Boston suffered a devastating week of vandalism and arson from July 10-16. | Faith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 450-foot 'blue hole' off Florida has researchers looking for signs of life...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2020-07-mysterious-foot-blue-hole-florida.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tales of the ocean swallowing places are as ancient as the myth of Atlantis, but there is an element of truth in the science, according to a NOAA-backed expedition set for Florida's Gulf Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  St. Louis couple hit with felony charges for pulling guns at protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/20/mark-and-patricia-mccloskey-st-louis-couple-face-f/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Louis’ top prosecutor told The Associated Press on Monday that she is charging a white husband and wife with felony unlawful use of a weapon for displaying guns during a racial injustice protest outside their mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall of CBS Showrunner: 'This Was Abuse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2020/07/the-fall-of-a-cbs-showrunner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this month, CBS fired Peter Lenkov, who’d overseen a powerful fiefdom. V.F. spoke to 30 sources about what happens when a network gives somebody a difficult job, then seems to let problems pile up for years because he’s making it money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 450-foot 'blue hole' off Florida has researchers looking for signs of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article244345437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county warns positive residents must stay home or face prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/local/article/Texas-county-warns-COVID-19-positive-residents-to-15420079.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 surge in rural Texas has escalated into a deepening public health crisis for Hidalgo County, where officials issued an order Sunday requiring those who test positive for the virus to not leave home for 14 days under threat of criminal prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The people with hidden immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200716-the-people-with-hidden-protection-from-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the latest research suggests that antibodies against Covid-19 could be lost in just three months, a new hope has appeared on the horizon: the enigmatic T cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Musk Now 5th Richest Man in the World!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/elon-musk-keeps-climbing-list-of-worlds-wealthiest-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s some pay raise. Tesla CEO Elon Musk added a whopping $5 billion to his net worth on Monday thanks to Tesla’s never-ending stock rally, allowing him to finish the day as the fifth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to send federal forces to more 'Democrat' cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200720182331-pw695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-RACE/PROTESTS-PORTLAND (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Trump to send federal forces to more 'Democrat' cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hecklers Interrupt DeSantis News Conference Claiming Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/hecklers-interrupt-gov-ron-desantis-news-conference-claiming-covid-19-data-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis put out a call Monday for people who have had COVID-19 to donate blood, but shortly after his news conference started, he was heckled by protesters who accused him of mishandling the pandemic and covering up COVID-19 data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Time with Mrs. Stephanopoulos: Watching PORN with the Kids!</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/gabriel-hays/2020/07/19/family-time-mrs-stephanopoulos-watching-porn-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know which side ABC anchor George Stephanopoulos comes down on whether our kids should go to school this fall during the Chinese virus outbreak. He wouldn’t want us to endanger our kids’ lives, of course. But his wife’s latest admission should have you wondering whether the Stephanopoulos family knows what’s in your kids' best interests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA Passengers Must Undergo Medical Screening To Fly Without Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/delta-face-mask-customers-maskless-medical-screening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major airlines have for months required masks on board their flights, but struggled to enforce this rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to send federal agents to major cities...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/508138-trump-signals-he-will-send-federal-agents-to-major-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday signaled he may order federal agents to be deployed to Chicago, New York City, Philadelphia and other major cities as he threatens to crack down further on unrest across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect in shooting identified as lawyer, men's rights activist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/roy-den-hollander-idd-as-suspect-in-shooting-at-judge-esther-salas-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman suspected of killing the son and wounding the husband of a federal judge in New Jersey before taking his own life has been identified as lawyer and men's rights activist Roy Den Hol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci: 'Worst Nightmare Comes True'...</title>
      <link>https://health.usnews.com/hospital-heroes/articles/dr-anthony-fauci-fighting-the-coronavirus-pandemic-is-my-entire-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;health.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate giants shut down Trump texting program...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/20/trump-massive-texting-program-suspended-372302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took days to resolve anti-spam concerns that halted a July 4 test run, costing Trump donations and raising GOP fears about November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida sheriff says he can't muster security for GOP convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/20/florida-sheriff-gop-convention-security-373089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a lack of clear plans, adequate funding and enough law enforcement officers, he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Poor diets threaten US national security...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/20/health/us-poor-nutrition-illness-death-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poor nutrition is the leading cause of US illnesses, creating a growing burden on the nation's economy, exacerbating health disparities and impacting national security, according to a white paper in the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Develops Electrostatic Drone to Disinfect Stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/electrostatic-disinfecting-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pittsburgh area company says they have developed a drone that could sanitize entire stadiums in three hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to remain closed to foreign visitors until at least September...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-to-remain-closed-to-foreign-visitors-until-at-least-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airports Authority says current restrictions, under which entry granted only to nationals or those obtaining special permit from Immigration Authority, to stay in force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz sounds alarm on Republicans losing Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8541229/Ted-Cruz-warns-Democrats-win-Texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz warned the Texas GOP State Convention if the Democrats win the Lone Star State both the White House and the Senate are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man found dead of self-inflicted gunshot wound possibly linked...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/man-found-dead-possibly-linked-to-shooting-of-nj-judge-esther-salas-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man found dead in New York’s Catskills may have been behind the shooting of federal Judge Esther Salas’ son and husband in New Jersey, police sources said Monday. The man was found on Monday in R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC apologizes for playing song with racial slur...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bbc-apologises-playing-song-containing-174300336.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will work to ensure this does not happen again."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  FEAR OF COVID TURNING INTO ANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/global-frustration-covid-19-fear-turning-to-anger-twitter-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study in JMIR Public Health &amp; Surveillance adds angry coronavirus posts made up nearly 30 percent of Twitter reaction on March 12. That is the same day the World Health Organization officially declared COVID-19 a global pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE VAX HYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/20/oxford-universitys-coronavirus-vaccine-shows-positive-immune-response-in-an-early-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers said in the medical journal The Lancet that the vaccine produced antibodies and killer T-cells to combat the infection that lasted at least two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATAKI:  For the first time ever I fear for the future of New York City...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/18/george-pataki-warns-big-apple-on-brink-nyc-is-going-to-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in his life, George Pataki is worried about New York City’s future. In an exclusive interview with The Post at his Peekskill, New York, office, the former three-term Republ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Sees Push to Tax Trades With Revenue in Free Fall...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/york-sees-push-tax-stock-133340361.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democrats in New York, the world’s financial capital, may finally have the right moment to resurrect the state tax on stock trades.One-fifth of the state’s revenue is disappearing, leaving a projected four-year deficit of $61 billion. Progressive Democrats are on the ascent in the state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP says it will capitalize Black but not white...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e36c00c5af0436abc09e051261fff1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After changing its usage rules last month to capitalize the word “Black” when used in the context of race and culture, The Associated Press on Monday said it would not do the same...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:   JOE WOULD KNOCKOUT DONALD IN BOXING MATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/pow-most-see-biden-beating-trump-in-boxing-match</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political polls haven’t been very good for President Trump, even those that have shown him treading water against Democratic challenger Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:   Trump may have to be 'fumigated' out of White House!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/second-in-line-nancy-pelosi-trump-may-have-to-be-fumigated-out-of-the-white-house  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE CRACKING</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/20/kanyes-campaign-appearance-seriously-upset-kardashian-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West's off-the-rails campaign stop Sunday in North Charleston, South Carolina may not only hurt Ye politically, he has concerned, upset and alarmed many of his friends and the Kardashians ... sources connected to Kanye tell TMZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple forced to wear ankle monitors for refusing to sign quarantine documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1166277/coronavirus-couple-house-arrest-ankle-monitors/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY bans eating while walking after guests break mask rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/travel/1168535/disney-world-food-drink-ban-face-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISNEY World has banned guests from eating and drinking while walking around the park after people were using the loophole to avoid wearing face masks. Less than 10 days after reopening, the theme …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rapped for health secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/19/ruth-bader-ginsburg-scotus-transparency-370570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the court sharply divided on many pivotal issues, a health crisis on the part of one justice has the potential to upend Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity sexologist found naked and dead in luxury hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/celebrity-sexologist-26-found-dead-22383280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Married TV doctor and psychologist Anna Ambartsumyan, who often gave her opinions on celebrities in Russia, was found dead aged just 26 - police are now investigating her death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists provide conclusive data that mosquitoes can't spread it...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/scientists-provide-conclusive-data-that-mosquitoes-cant-spread-covid-19-635648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To date there has been no information nor evidence to suggest that the new coronavirus could be transmitted by mosquitoes," WHO said on their COVID-19 "mythbusters" page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kasich set to speak at DEM convention!</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/open/2020/07/ex-gov-john-kasich-slated-to-speak-at-the-democratic-national-convention-for-joe-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a move that would be unthinkable just a few years ago, when Kasich clashed with Democrats on a range of issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Will Be Most Litigated in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2020-election-will-be-the-most-litigated-in-u-s-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 Election Will Be the Most Litigated in U.S. History</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian President calls for multilateral covid solutions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/508015-the-hill-interview-colombian-president-duque-calls-for-multilateral-covid-19-solutions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombian President Iván Duque believes the missing ingredient in the Western Hemisphere's response to the pandemic was multilateralism, and an accelerant in the virus's spread was populism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a breaking point. We're at a critical stage'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/hialeah-mayor-carlos-hernandez-one-plan-in-place-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hialeah Mayor Carlos Hernandez wants one plan in place for South Florida to fight the rising surge of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Struggles To Explain Handcuffed, Blindfolded Uighurs Loaded Onto Train...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/chinese-ambassador-struggles-explain-shocking-footage-handcuffed-blindfolded-uighurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep South supermarket takes stand: No masks required...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2020/07/19/winn-dixie-doesnt-require-masks-while-other-supermarkets-do/5467748002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart, Target, CVS, Walgreens and Kroger are the biggest retailers to announce they will soon mandate masks at stores nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: Rural real estate prices rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/rural-real-estate-prices-rise-people-consider-leaving-cities-n1234309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus is impacting how we spend money, how we shop and, perhaps, even where we want to live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's elite given experimental 'vaccine' for months...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/russias-elite-experimental-vaccine-months-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Russia’s business and ruling elite have been given access to an experimental vaccine against the novel coronavirus since April, according to a report on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Cuban warns of stock similarities to dot-com bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/20/mark-cuban-coronavirus-stock-comeback-similar-to-1990s-dot-com-bubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire businessman Monday on CNBC compared the stock market's big run-up from its late March coronavirus low to the 1990s tech frenzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Camps Bring Ominous Warning in Test Run for Schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/coronavirus-outbreak/summer-camps-bring-ominous-virus-warning-in-test-run-for-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer camps in parts of the U.S. are closing as children and counselors test positive for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida reports over 10,000 new cases for sixth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200720140811-wyc7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida reports over 10,000 new cases of COVID-19 for sixth day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pandemic surges, so do waistlines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cde7e5cca347c7303e7b35211fd21d99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When Allison Weiss Brady and Michael Ladin emerged from weeks of locking down during the pandemic, they needed new clothes in new sizes — for different reasons. Brady, 49, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First COVID-19, now mosquitoes: Bracing for bug-borne ills...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d588bb4f42d92dca86c43443204fe1ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sophia Garabedian had been dealing with a persistent fever and painful headache when her parents found her unresponsive in her bed one morning last fall. Doctors ultimately diagnosed the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona turns blue?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jul/20/arizona-trump-republicans-white-house-democrats-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changing demographics and a backlash to Trump has reshaped the state’s politics – so could Arizona really turn Democratic?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging 'Master Circuit' Discovered: Extended Human Lifespan To Follow?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cellular-aging-master-circuit-discovered-extended-human-lifespan-to-follow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by UCSD molecular biologists and bioengineers reveal a groundbreaking discovery regarding the intricacies of cellular aging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuralink chip will stream music directly to brain?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-computer-chip-music-stream-a9627686.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Portland tear gas, an apparition emerges, capturing imagination of protesters...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/portland-tear-gas-apparition-emerges-020522608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iconic image has emerged on Twitter since early Saturday morning in Portland, when a woman wearing nothing but a mask and cap strode toward federal agents as they fired tear gas at protesters — a surreal image of human vulnerability in the face of an overpowering force.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
