<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Suppressed Posts by 'Ugly', Poor to Attract New Users...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/03/16/tiktok-app-moderators-users-discrimination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The China-based social media company also has policies censoring various forms of political speech, leaked documents reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD Researchers:  Will need many times of social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/harvard-researchers-social-distancing-during-covid-19-may-have-to-be-turned-on-and-off-like-a-spigot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unlikely one single, long stretch of "social distancing" is going to solve COVID-19 for the US before a vaccine arrives, say Harvard researchers. Instead, it may be necessary to keep having periodic intervals of quarantine until the US healthcare system is fortified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients 'charged with attempted murder' for failing to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-patients-charged-attempted-murder-21756317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in South Africa said two men, who tested positive for coronavirus, were being investigated over allegations they refused to self-isolate after the country was placed on lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  TREASURY NEGATIVE INTEREST RATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/negative-rates-come-to-the-us-1-month-and-3-month-treasury-bill-yields-are-now-negative.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yields on both the 1-month and 3-month Treasury bills dipped below zero Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 BILLION NOW ON LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/one-third-humanity-under-virus-lockdown-040324730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the number of confirmed cases worldwide soared past 450,000, UN Secretary General Antonio Guterres warned that only a concerted global effort could stop the spread of the virus. In Spain, the number of fatalities surpassed those of China, where the novel coronavirus first emerged three months ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economies Already Look Totally Different From Pre-Virus Age...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/economies-already-look-totally-different-235439273.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the heat of a global crisis more sudden and severe than anything in living memory, economic orthodoxies are getting tossed aside at a furious pace. Some of them may be gone for good.Public debt, for example, has often been seen as a drag on economies -- but right now it’s more like</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  Virus could become seasonal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-could-become-seasonal-top-us-scientist-001146451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a strong chance the new coronavirus could return in seasonal cycles, a senior US scientist said Wednesday, underscoring the urgent need to find a vaccine and effective treatments. Anthony Fauci, who leads research into infectious diseases at the National Institutes of Health, told a briefing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home-bound users fume as video apps do not sync with TVs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325232411-4h06h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GOOGLE (PIX):Home-bound users fume as video apps do not sync with TVs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls lockdown in major cities a 'crime'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325213423-7wbyf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Bolsonaro calls coronavirus lockdown in Brazil's major cities a 'crime'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon orders halt of overseas movement for military... </title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325203242-zgoc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-PENTAGON (UPDATE 2, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Pentagon orders halt overseas movement for U.S. military over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans emerges as next virus epicenter, threatening rest of South...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325200808-oc1ie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-NEWORLEANS (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-New Orleans emerges as next coronavirus epicenter, threatening rest of South</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro:  It's just 'a little cold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Brazil-s-Bolsonaro-channeling-Trump-dismisses-15157384.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - He said self-isolation was "mass confinement." He called the novel coronavirus a "little cold." He asked, if only people older than 60 are at risk, "why close the schools?"  This was Jair Bolsonaro, leader of Latin America's largest country, calling on Brazilians to return to jobs, public spaces and commerce amid the coronavirus pandemic, contradicting not only his own health officials, but also the global consensus on how to see countries through the pandemic without a crippling loss of life.  It was a portrait of Bolsonaro isolated and unbound: Alone before the camera, attacking the media, undermining political opponents, indulging talking points he's used since the crisis began even as the disturbing reality overtook his sanguine predictions.  "Most of the media has been countervailing," he declared in a national address Tuesday. "They spread the sensation of dread, with their flagship the high number of victims in Italy. The perfect scenario to be used by the media to spread hysteria."  "In my particular case," the 65-year-old former army officer added, "with my history as an athlete, if I were infected by the virus, I wouldn't need to worry. I wouldn't feel anything or, if very affected, it would be like a little flu or little cold."  Rather than calming panic and confusion, Bolsonaro's pronouncements appear to be only fueling them. As confirmed cases and deaths mount - Brazil leads Latin America in both - fear is growing over whether the country's institutions and leaders will rise to the challenge of a historic moment, with far less room for error than wealthier countries already in the full grip of coronavirus.  The minister of health has warned the health system will collapse by the end of April. Millions of already impoverished people face weeks without income. Hunger could sweep the country....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians jockeying for covid-19 tests find proximity to Trump is fastest route...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Politicians-jockeying-for-covid-19-tests-find-15157424.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last month, Mick Mulvaney, who was still the acting White House chief of staff at the time, told a crowd of conservative activists that the media was exaggerating the threat posed by covid-19 because "they think this will bring down the president, that's what this is all about. . . . It's not a death sentence, it's not the same as the Ebola crisis."  But unbeknown to attendees at the Conservative Political Action Conference, Mulvaney had already received a coronavirus test, at the recommendation of the White House physician. The test, which has not been reported until now, was followed by a second this month after a niece with whom Mulvaney shares an apartment was around members of a Brazilian delegation who later tested positive for the virus.  Mulvaney is one of three President Donald Trump confidants to get a coronavirustest while exhibiting no symptoms of the disease. And on Sunday, Sen. Rand Paul, R-Ky., announced he tested positive despite being asymptomatic, refusing to disclose how he was able to get tested in Washington on March 16.  The easy access Paul and other high-ranking politicians have gotten to coronavirus tests highlights the extent to which members of America's elite continue to have greater access to medical care during the pandemic, even as federal officials emphasize that testing should be reserved for health care providers and people who are seriously ill. Even in the nation's capital, hospitals are reporting a shortage of tests and the protective gear needed to administer them.  "It's a horrible flouting of our public health recommendations," Robyn Gershon, a clinical professor of epidemiology at the New York University School of Global Public Health, said in a phone interview.  In the cases of Mulvaney, Trump's incoming chief of staff Mark Meadows and Rep. Matt Gaetz, R-Fla., White House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley became California's epicenter of virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-silicon-valley-became-californias-epicenter-of-the-coronavirus/ar-BB11Hksi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors Say Massive Federal Bailout Falls Short...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/governors-say-massive-federal-stimulus-deal-falls-short/ar-BB11Ia3V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals consider universal do-not-resuscitate orders for patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2020/03/25/hospitals-across-us-consider-universal-do-not-resuscitate-orders-for-coronavirus-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a sign of the grim choices ahead, officials worry that “all hands” responses may expose doctors and nurses to infection and some prioritize the survival of the many over the one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYOR: HALF OF NEW YORKERS WILL GET INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/25/de-blasio-warns-half-of-all-new-yorkers-will-get-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 4 million New Yorkers — or 50 percent of the city’s population — will get the coronavirus, Mayor de Blasio warned Wednesday. “It’s a fair bet to say that half of all New Yorkers an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distressed Debt Balloons to Almost $1 Trillion, Nears 2008 Peak...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/distressed-debt-balloons-almost-1-171644746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The amount of distressed debt in the U.S. has quadrupled in less than a week to nearly $1 trillion, reaching levels not seen since 2008 as the collapse of oil prices and fallout from the coronavirus shutters entire industries across the globe.In total, the tally has ballooned to $934 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Kathy Griffin hospitalized with 'unbearably painful' symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/celebrity/kathy-griffin-coronavirus-slams-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After checking into a hospital with "unbearably painful" symptoms, comedian Kathy Griffin has spoken out against Donald Trump's response to the coronavirus outbreak. In a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural America watches pandemic erupt in cities as fear grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/316123a978e61bc6df7863f05fa419fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUFUR, Ore. (AP) — The social distancing rules repeated like a mantra in America's urban centers, where the coronavirus is spreading exponentially, might seem silly in wide-open places where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Levinson, ex-FBI agent, presumed dead over decade after disappearance in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/robert-levinson-retired-fbi-agent-presumed-dead-in-iranian-custody-over-a-decade-after-disappearance-family-reveals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Levinson, a retired FBI agent and private investigator who disappeared from an Iranian island in 2007, is believed to have died in Iranian custody, his family revealed in a statement Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ackman makes $2 billion on market short...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/bill-ackman-exits-market-hedges-uses-2-billion-he-made-to-buy-more-stocks-including-hilton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ackman said he used the cash to add to stakes in Agilent, Berkshire Hathaway, Hilton, Lowe's and Restaurant Brands. He reentered Starbucks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie threatens to hold up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/bernie-sanders-4-gop-senators-threaten-to-hold-up-coronavirus-stimulus-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chances for a Senate vote on a $2 trillion coronavirus relief bill looked murky as senators threatened to delay it over unemployment insurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House briefings draw 'BACHELOR', 'MNF' ratings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/25/trumps-white-house-coronavirus-briefings-draw-bachelor-mnf-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s daily White House coronavirus briefings are a ratings hit. The president, who has taken the lead in the task force’s daily updates to the nation, has attracted an aver…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Whole city laid off': Jobless claims climb sky high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5f960f1907bd1ef4ef22d040ac7c99a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Barely a week ago, David McGraw was cooking daily for hundreds of fine diners at one of New Orleans’ illustrious restaurants. Today, he’s cooking for himself, at home —...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reusable shopping bags banned in Mass...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/gov-baker-grocery-store-pharmacy-public-health-order-bans-reusable-bags-march-25-2020/31931763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part of new public health order regarding grocery stores and pharmacies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM: 4 of largest banks to suspend mortgage payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/25/gavin-newsom-4-banks-suspend-mortgage-payments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four of the nation’s largest banks agreed to temporarily suspend residential mortgage payments for Californians affected by the coronavirus, Gov. Gavin Newsom said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Prison Workers Say They're Not Actually Making Hand Sanitizer...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/5dma4k/cuomos-prison-workers-say-theyre-not-actually-making-hand-sanitizer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates told VICE that they're really just putting a mysterious vendor's existing product in 'NYS Clean' bottles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All 94 residents of NJ nursing home presumed positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/03/25/whippany-nursing-home-takes-covid-19-seniors-woodbridge-facility/5081292002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 94 residents of St. Joseph's Senior Nursing Home in Woodbridge, New Jersey, are deemed presumptive positive for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Suppressed Posts by 'Ugly', Poor to Attract New Users...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/03/16/tiktok-app-moderators-users-discrimination/0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Reporters Stuck in Limbo as 2020 Race Gets Drowned Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/03/campaign-reporters-are-stuck-in-limbo-as-the-2020-race-gets-drowned-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With America under quarantine, the boys—and girls—are off the bus. They’re now watching Joe Biden beam into CNN from his Wilmington rec room and fundraise via Zoom. Will the press corps be staring at screens through November?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus spreads to TEN AMAZON warehouses...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/590381/amazon-cleaning-exposed-employees-coronavirus-warehouses/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has reportedly ramped up cleaning measures and sent exposed workers home after the killer coronavirus spread to ten of its warehouses. COVID-19 cases were confirmed in the company’s te…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarkets instal protective barriers between staff, customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/protective-barriers-being-installed-at-supermarket-registers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transparent barriers, a.k.a. sneeze guards, are going up in checkout lanes of several major supermarket chains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one woman helped inform Amish...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/nation/2020/03/25/coronavirus-amish-iowa-woman-mary-swander/5076223002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Swander put the wheels in motion and with the help of others, the Amish community of Kalona has seemed to heed warnings about the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300 inmates to be released from Rikers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8148777/Mayor-Bill-Blasio-says-release-300-criminals-Rikers-Island.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio says he will release 300 criminals from Rikers Island to stop them from contracting coronavirus.  In the city, 131 people have died and there are nearly 15,000 cases of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacies Running Low On Prescriptions For Other Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-pharmacy-prescription-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One local pharmacist is low on some prescription drugs and doesn’t know when she will get a new shipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT'S IN THERE?  Full text of stimulus hasn't been released --  but vote expected today...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/wheres-bill-full-text-stimulus-hasnt-been-released-vote-expected-today</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell says chamber will vote Wednesday on a $2 trillion coronavirus release package but text of final bill isn't public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon tests 'scarce' despite assurances; Sick troops told to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/25/pentagon-coronavirus-tests-are-scarce-despite-assu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top defense leaders are assuring troops that coronavirus testing is available, but for Pentagon warriors the coveted test is “scarce,” according to an internal memo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED Slashes Employee Pay Amid Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/buzzfeed-slashing-employee-pay-amid-the-coronavirus-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some staffers, including executives, will see a nearly 25-percent pay cut. CEO Jonah Peretti confirmed he will not take a salary as the crisis continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest shortage in NY: City running out of dogs to adopt...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/coronavirus/newest-shortage-new-york-city-running-out-dogs-adopt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: 'We've had enough debates'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/489482-biden-i-think-weve-had-enough-debates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Wednesday said it’s time for the Democratic primary to draw to a close and signaled a disinterest in participating in a final debate against Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRITO-LAY Factory Shut Down After Multiple Employees Show Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/03/24/modesto-frito-lay-factory-covid-19-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Frito-Lay factory in Modesto is temporarily closed after multiple employees showed symptoms of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADER JOE'S closes stores after workers test positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-in-ny-trader-joes-closes-2-stores-after-workers-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Trader Joe’s locations in New York City shut their doors this week because staffers tested positive for coronavirus, the company said in a statement. The Union Square store location — and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Population of Holocaust Survivors Endangered...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/coronavirus-holocaust-survivors-crown-heights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic inflicts miseries that are particular to each place it visits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops called on X-rated video store offering curbside service...</title>
      <link>https://www.pjstar.com/news/20200325/cops-called-on-x-rated-video-store-in-west-peoria-offering-curbside-service-during-stay-at-home-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pjstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PEORIA — After a citizen complaint to police, an X-rated video has stopped offering curbside service during the state's coronavirus shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World's Richest Country Ran Out of 75-Cent Face Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-the-worlds-richest-country-ran-out-of-a-75-cent-face-mask/ar-BB11GgLi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Imprisoning Corona Whistleblowers...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-lying-about-coronavirus-statistics-state-department-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iranian government is lying to the international community about the number of Iranian citizens infected and killed by the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Mask, No Gloves, No Service: Brooklyn Businesses Crack Down on Customers...</title>
      <link>https://bklyner.com/no-mask-no-gloves-no-service-brooklyn-businesses-start-to-turn-away-customers-without-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bklyner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fong and Zhou Supermarket in Bensonhurst and AAA Pharmacy in Midwood are turning away customers who aren’t wearing face masks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Punishment for gay people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/589777/donald-trump-ralph-dollinger-coronavirus-bible-study-minister/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE minister who hosts a weekly bible study for President Donald Trump’s cabinet members has appeared to place blame for the coronavirus on gays and environmentalism. Ralph Drollinger, a former bas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires want people back to work, but employees not so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/coronavirus-billionaires-want-people-back-to-work-but-their-employees-arent-so</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (BLOOMBERG) - The billionaire Tom Golisano was smoking a Padron cigar on his patio in Florida on Tuesday afternoon (March 24). He was worried.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CABINET BIBLE TEACHER BLAMES PANDEMIC ON GOD'S WRATH...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/03/24/trump-cabinet-bible-studies-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ralph Drollinger argues the coronavirus is an act of God’s judgment. His Bible studies are attended by Mike Pompeo, Ben Carson, Betsy DeVos, and Alex Azar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Daily presidential tracking polls...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE CHARLES TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11216131/prince-charles-positive-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCES Charles, 71, has tested positive for coronavirus, Clarence House announced today. The future king had been displaying mild symptoms but remains in “good health” after being diag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prince-charles-tests-positive-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Charles has caught the coronavirus. Now courtiers are desperately hoping he wasn’t contagious when he last met the Queen on March 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First US child to die from virus diagnosed after death, 'didn't meet test criteria'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/585672/first-us-minor-not-meet-criteria-coronavirus-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE FIRST US child to succumb to coronavirus was only diagnosed with the deadly infection after he died as he did not “meet the criteria” for the test, the Sun has learned.  Lancaster, Los Angeles,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORGUES NEAR CAPACITY</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/25/dhs-briefing-nyc-morgues-near-capacity-148259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials were told that morgues in the city are expected to reach capacity next week, per the briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Londoners spooked after mystery air raid siren goes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/coronavirus-mystery-air-raid-siren-217519 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Licked Products at WALMART Charged with Terror Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/man-who-licked-products-at-walmart-charged-with-making-terrorist-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri man asked, 'Who's afraid of the coronavirus?' before licking various items on Walmart shelf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF DIGITAL DOLLAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/cashless-society-democrats-propose-digital-dollar-run-by-the-fed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New World Order using coronavirus to wage war on cash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gingrich trapped in Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/newt-gingrich-trapped-in-quarantine-in-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker Newt Gingrich and his wife have been in quarantine in Italy due to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man faces terror charges after coughing on grocery store worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-faces-terror-charges-after-coughing-on-grocery-store-worker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey man the governor described as a "knucklehead" faces multiple charges after he allegedly coughed on a grocery store worker and then claimed to have coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How govt can track social media posts to enforce quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/governments-could-track-covid-19-lockdowns-through-social-media-posts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A research group scrapes more than 500,000 Instagram profiles in Italy to see if people are abiding by the quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC COULD CLOSE STREETS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-new-york-city-weighs-closing-parks-playgrounds-and-streets-to-enforce-social-distancing-gov-cuomo-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor: Virus Of Demonic Origin...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/03/23/westmoreland-co-pastor-holds-services-amid-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Westmoreland County pastor held church services over the weekend as the coronavirus continues to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers to vote on 4th, 5th spending bill to fix 'mistakes'...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/lawmakers-ready-vote-4th-and-5th-coronavirus-stimulus-package-fix-mistakes-2t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We know this bill is going to be very good. It’s going to be over $2 trillion but it’s not going to be enough. We will have missed some people in certain places," Rep. Beyer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas, devastated by '08 economic crash, struggles with shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-gazette.com/news/nation-world/las-vegas-devastated-by-the-economic-crash-struggles-with-coronavirus/article_135623cc-b684-58dc-9167-e5c944b20ef2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS — It was just two weeks ago that Las Vegas native Carlos Rosales Jr. told his cousin that business at his new barbershop was doing so well that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 1940, Republicans Picked Candidate Who Hadn't Won Single Primary!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/03/could-a-draft-cuomo-movement-be-in-the-democrats-future/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not out of the question if Biden keeps looking out of touch and irrelevant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide hotline calls soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article241493126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore says app can slow spread of coronavirus; Critics say it's govt surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/singapore-says-its-app-can-slow-spread-of-coronavirus-critics/article_6958f2b4-6a06-5813-b245-49629f642c3d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE — One of the most effective ways authorities can limit the spread of a pandemic is to immediately locate, test and isolate anyone who has had contact with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Thousands of inmates released as jails face coronavirus threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Thousands-of-inmates-released-as-jails-face-15155940.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid fears that the coronavirus will carve a deadly path through prisons and jails, counties and states are releasing thousands of inmates - New Jersey alone began freeing hundreds of people this week - and the federal prison system is coming under intense pressure to take similar measures.  Public health and corrections officials have issued dire warnings that cramped and unsanitary conditions could turn prisons into a haven for the virus, endangering not just inmates but also corrections officers and prison health-care workers as well as their families and communities.  Criminal-justice reform advocates from across the political spectrum urged President Donald Trump on Tuesday to use his clemency power to commute the sentences of inmates eligible for "compassionate release" and others who could be at risk, particularly the elderly and those with underlying medical conditions.  "This is a real disaster waiting to happen," David Patton, the executive director of he nonprofit Federal Defenders of New York, said Sunday, the day after the first federal inmate tested positive at the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn. "These are places that are particularly susceptible to contagion."  Inside a county jail in Alabama on Friday, two inmates threatened to commit suicide if newly arrived Immigration and Customs Enforcement detainees they feared had been exposed to the virus were not removed. According to video live-streamed on an inmate's Facebook page, the two detainees stood on a ledge over a common area, nooses fashioned from sheets wrapped around their necks, and threatened to jump.  "We're not having no more people come in here with that symptom," another inmate says in the video, which was obtained by The Washington Post. "We're not trying to put no more lives at risk."  The three new detainees had described being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus bill prevents Trump and  family from benefiting from loan programs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Stimulus-bill-prevents-Trump-and-his-family-from-15155772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Businesses controlled by President Donald Trump and his children would be prohibited from receiving loans or investments from Treasury Department programs included in a $2 trillion stimulus plan agreed to early Wednesday by White House and Senate leaders in response to the coronavirus crisis.  The provision, which was touted by Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., in an early-morning letter to colleagues, would also apply to Vice President Mike Pence, members of Congress and heads of federal departments, as well as their children, spouses and in-laws.  During a television interview Wednesday morning, Schumer stressed that the provision applies not only to Trump but to "any major figure in government."  "That makes sense. Those of us who write the law shouldn't benefit from the law," Schumer said on CNN.  The Senate plans to vote later Wednesday on the massive package, which aims to flood the economy with capital by sending $1,200 checks to many Americans, creating a $367 billion loan program for small businesses and setting up a $500 billion fund for industries, cities and states. The House is expected to act in coming days.  Trump's dual roles as both chief executive of the nation and owner of a sprawling business empire has been frequently criticized by Democrats, who accuse him of trying to profit from the presidency.  Representatives of the Trump Organization did not immediately respond to a request for comment Wednesday morning.  The Washington Post reported this week that Trump's private business has shut down six of its top seven revenue-producing clubs and hotels because of restrictions meant to slow the spread of the novel coronavirus, potentially depriving his company of millions of dollars in revenue.  So far, the Trump Organization - which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body count leaps...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/spain-reports-deadliest-day-of-outbreak-as-virus-crisis-deepens/article_03dc9cb8-17cc-594d-9c31-78dd56be2bf5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain reported another 738 deaths from the coronavirus on Wednesday, the deadliest day in the country to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will California look like Italy soon?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-crisis-look-italys-140024299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 2,600 cases of coronavirus infection have been confirmed in California and 55 people have died of COVID-19. Will the state be the next Italy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus hospital bills: A look at the costs...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/coronavirus-hospital-bills-cost-142902046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the Kaiser Family Foundation estimated that the total cost of coronavirus treatment in a hospital could top $20,000 when factoring in out-of-pocket costs and insurance coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are collapsing': Virus pummels medics in Spain and Italy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ec91dc45d8d7c2ea86b0a97446a303a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — By the time Patricia Núñez’s cough started, she was already familiar with the dreaded dry hacking sound tormenting patients who had for weeks been filling the Madrid emergency ward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile phone industry explores worldwide tracking of users...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/25/mobile-phone-industry-explores-worldwide-tracking-of-users-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talks about global data-sharing to counter coronavirus will raise privacy concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice from Mexico's president: 'Live life as usual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/25/coronavirus-advice-from-mexicos-president-live-life-as-usual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;López Obrador’s nonchalance and resistance to tough action in face of pandemic draws barrage of criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans rush to make online wills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/coronavirus-pandemic-triggers-rush-by-americans-to-make-online-wills.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With COVID-19 impacting more and more Americans, individuals across the country are scrambling to set up wills and end-of-life directives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNANKE: Disruptions 'closer to major snowstorm' than Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/25/bernanke-says-this-is-much-closer-to-a-natural-disaster-than-the-great-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If we don't get the public health right," no Fed monetary policy or Washington fiscal package is going to work, Bernanke added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complaining, inertia are seeds of the devil, pope says...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholic-sf.org/news/complaining-inertia-are-seeds-of-the-devil-pope-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholic-sf.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY -- Many Christians are caught in a trap of complaining about everything and doing nothing about it, Pope Francis said in his morning Mass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARCETTI: Water, power will be shut off for businesses that don't close...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/coronavirus/mayor-garcetti-expected-to-hold-daily-briefing-on-l-a-s-covid-19-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti opened his daily briefing Tuesday recognizing what may have been the first teenage COVID-19 death in L.A. County and went on to announce actions against nonessential…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Cuomo Walk Away From Brokered Convention With Dem Nomination?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/24/andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-brokered-convention-democratic-nominee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unexpected global pandemic could give New York Governor Andrew Cuomo what he wants most: a Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Hundreds Of CEOs Resign Just Before World Started Going Crazy?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/why-did-hundreds-of-ceos-resign-just-before-the-world-started-going-absolutely-crazy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months prior to the most ferocious stock market crash in history and the eruption of the biggest public health crisis of our generation, we witnessed the biggest exodus of corporate CEOs that we have ever seen.  And as you will see below, corporate insiders also sold off billions of dollars w</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of locusts cover streets in Oman with footage showing 'ground moving'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/millions-locusts-cover-streets-oman-21751908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating locust swarms continue to wreak havoc across east Africa and the Middle East in scenes described as "apocalyptic"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment claims could spike to 3.4 million...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/489300-unemployment-claims-could-spike-to-34-million-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekly initial unemployment claims are on track to spike to a historic 3.4 million for the third week of March, according to an analysis by the left-leaning Economic Policy Institute (EPI).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick nurse kills self over fear of infecting others...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/25/italian-nurse-with-coronavirus-kills-herself-amid-fears-of-infecting-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniela Trezzi had been suffering “heavy stress” amid fears she was spreading coronavirus while working at the San Gerardo Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makeshift morgue outside hospital...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/24/makeshift-morgue-for-coronavirus-victims-set-up-outside-nyc-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two refrigerated trailers were trucked to the site at 30th Street and the FDR Drive, along with a customized RV labeled “MOBILE COMMAND CENTER — MEDICAL EXAMINER.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ally resigns as speaker of Israel parliament...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-ally-resigns-speaker-israel-parliament-112154165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's parliamentary speaker, an ally of Benjamin Netanyahu, resigned Wednesday, clearing the way for a vote that could see him replaced by an opponent of the embattled premier. Yuli Edelstein, a member of Netanyahu's right-wing Likud party, had refused to schedule a speakership vote until</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life under lockdown ups precarity for France's prostitutes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/life-under-lockdown-ups-precarity-frances-prostitutes-105514794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their health in jeopardy and customers evaporating, sex workers in France are struggling as the novel coronavirus threatens their livelihoods -- and there is no safety net in sight. France has been in lockdown for a week, with only essential trips outside allowed, in a bid to halt the acceleration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout revives talk of 'universal basic income'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-fallout-revives-talk-universal-basic-income-082539735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scoffed-at idea of paying everyone a basic income as machines take people's jobs is getting a fresh look as a possible remedy for economies cratered by the coronavirus pandemic. Aspiring Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang argued for it on the campaign trail, even as his opponents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner hands, bluer skies: What has coronavirus done for us?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cleaner-hands-bluer-skies-coronavirus-done-us-100533027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths, economic meltdown and a planet on lockdown: the coronavirus pandemic has brought us waves of bad news, but squint and you might just see a few bright spots. From better hygiene that has reduced other infectious diseases to people reaching out as they self-isolate, here are some slivers of silver</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bali's 'Day of Silence' even quieter than usual...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/balis-day-silence-hit-virus-fears-050654815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bali (Indonésie) (AFP) - Bali's "Day of Silence" was even quieter than usual this year as coronavirus fears prompted authorities to scale back an annual celebration that sees the Hindu-majority island in Indonesia come to a near standstill. Known as Nyepi, the festival calls on locals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST BAILOUT IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edd230801c0e181169915e67b1fd64c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House and Senate leaders of both parties announced agreement early Wednesday on an unprecedented $2 trillion emergency bill to rush sweeping aid to businesses, workers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of America and sacrifice: Is country ready to step up?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db49c4310a37161661b3d3f86a861e4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For most Americans alive today, the idea of shared national sacrifice is a collective abstraction, a memory handed down from a grandparent or passed on through a book or movie....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in WWII references, but is it merited?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/495f72d25c62c1fa455a622b643bd7a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — In the first week of June 2019, World War II was on many people's minds. It was the 75th anniversary of D-Day, a week filled with events honoring the sacrifice and blood of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's body count leaps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00cfd8fb188c237ee4e75031fcd85638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — The coronavirus outbreak hit home Wednesday among the well-born and the desperately poor alike as Britain's Prince Charles tested positive and India's 1.3 billion people, or nearly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>160-year-old Vatican newspaper succumbs to coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavius-vatican-newspaper/160-year-old-vatican-newspaper-succumbs-to-coronavirus-idUSKBN21C199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican daily L'Osservatore Romano, which Pope Francis has jokingly cal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who intentionally spread could be charged as terrorists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/24/coronavirus-terrorism-justice-department-147821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department offers guidance on how to deal with “purposeful exposure and infection of others.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress? Fear of COVID-19? Therapists treating vulnerable go online to help...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325104355-g6rxp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/COUNSELLING:Stress? Fear of COVID-19? Therapists treating the vulnerable go online to help</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn off microwave to boost wifi, says media regulator...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325100548-6dya8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-BROADBAND:Turn off the microwave to boost wifi, says UK's media regulator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On road through pandemic, truckers fear for lives...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325092335-y5hof</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRUCKERS (PIX):On the road through a pandemic, some truckers fear for their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese students fleeing virus-hit U.S. pay $20,000 for seats on private jets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200325063102-go9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHINA-STUDENTS (PIX):Chinese students fleeing virus-hit U.S. pay $20,000 for seats on private jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Icelanders skip the hot springs for ice baths...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/icelanders-skip-hot-springs-ice-baths-042840206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using slow, deliberate movements and deep breathing, bathers immerse themselves in the waters of an ice-covered lake in southwestern Iceland. While others might opt for the soothing hot springs for which the country is famous, this hardy group prefers an ice bath, all in the name of wellness. The temperature</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired Americans Send Unemployment Websites Crashing Down...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fired-americans-send-unemployment-websites-105208498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been three weeks since Aaron Garza lost his job as a parts specialist at a Toyota dealership in Grand Rapids, Michigan. When he was dismissed, he joined a tidal wave of unemployed people swamping systems to help them and straining state finances to the breaking point.On Monday, Garza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST BAILOUT IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db4a954801ab08b492aedddfcf7132c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House and Senate leaders of both parties announced agreement early Wednesday on unprecedented emergency legislation to rush sweeping aid to businesses, workers and a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
