<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>California police, cities fight statewide pot deliveries...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/california-police-cities-fight-statewide-195321423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing dispute over where legal marijuana can be delivered in California is unsettling the nation's largest pot market. Police chiefs on Friday lined up against a proposed state rule that critics say would allow unchecked home marijuana deliveries anywhere in California — even in communities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil-worshipping church in heart of US bible belt burns holy book, uses menstrual blood for rituals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7148589/inside-church-of-ahriman-america-devil-worshipping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HIGH PRIEST at one of America’s most prominent devil-worshipping churches has lifted the lid on the secretive religion.  Adam Daniels, 35, is the “dastur” – or high priest – of the Ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND Will Sell Alcohol for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.eonline.com/news/964576/disneyland-will-sell-alcohol-for-the-first-time-ever-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oga's Cantina, part of the new Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge attraction, will offer themed drinks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star charged with smashing photo-seeking fan's phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/metro/index.ssf/2018/08/cavs_guard_jr_smith_arrested_i.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cavs guard J.R. Smith was arrested Friday in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain suddenly falls as McCain casket carried into Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/31/politics/john-mccain-us-capitol-lie-in-state/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was a war hero who survived more than five years of torture as a prisoner in Vietnam and the 2008 Republican presidential nominee, but it's John McCain's role as a legislator that may have most defined his public life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT DEADLINE?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6118945/Mueller-snubs-Trumps-attorneys-letter-setting-interview-conditions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller has not responded to a weeks-old letter from Trump's legal team, suggesting the president's testimony isn't needed or investigators are tracking down new leads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARETHA'S FINAL SHOW...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6118217/Aretha-Franklin-funeral-spiritual-awakening-Bill-Clinton-Stevie-Wonder-attend.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bishop Charles Ellis said: 'This is a real life that has been lived, that a person regardless of how famous she became. It's not a show'. Franklin's funeral will be at Detroit's Greater Grace Temple later today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA gives Mars rover 45 days to call home...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/08/31/nasa-mars-opportunity-rover-storm-deadline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA set a deadline for the lost Mars rover Opportunity to contact home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHN KERRY REFUSES TO RULE OUT 2020 BID...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/john-kerry-wont-rule-out-2020-white-house-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview to air Sept. 2 on "Sunday Morning" and "Face the Nation," the former secretary of state says, "We are in a moment of crisis for our country"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade talks with Canada to restart next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/31/trade-talks-with-canada-will-restart-next-week-as-trump-seeks-a-deal-in-90-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-Canada Talks Break Up With No Agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-canada-rush-to-hash-out-nafta-compromise-1535724907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. and Canadian talks on a trade deal ended without an agreement Friday. President Trump is expected to notify Congress of plans to proceed with a Mexico-only deal to replace Nafta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screening Plagued By Technical Malfunction...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/lady-gagas-star-is-born-premiere-plagued-by-technical-malfunction-1139031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie was said to have gone black in the middle of the screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS misconduct bombshell 'only the beginning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/only-the-beginning-daily-beast-has-a-lot-more-reporting-to-come-on-nbc-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER TO MAKE MAJOR MOVE?</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/mueller-obstruction-report-russia-investigation-labor-day-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes are on the special counsel Robert Mueller amid mounting speculation that he could come out with something substantial in the Russia investigation before Labor Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of THE VILLAGE VOICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/business_of_news/village-voice-news-layoff.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada considers 'right to disconnect' outside work...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/liberals-eye-closer-look-at-right-to-disconnect-in-labour-rule-revamp-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some employees choose to stay connected because they don’t work a traditional workday. At least one employer group called any government action a ‘legislative over-step’ the repor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women cheer as Swedish man-free music fest opens...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/women-cheer-swedish-man-free-music-festival-opens-182515249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matilda Hagerman laughs with her friends as she queues at a man-free music festival, which kicked off in Sweden on Friday in protest against a wave of sexual assaults at festivals in recent years. Held in Sweden's second-largest city of Gothenburg, the two-day Statement Festival, forbids men but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steered 'Straw Donation' To Inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/washington-consultant-for-ukraine-party-set-to-plead-guilty-to-violating-lobbyist-disclosure-law/2018/08/31/172cf2c8-ad23-11e8-a8d7-0f63ab8b1370_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;W. Sam Patten, who pleaded guilty Friday to failing to register as a foreign lobbyist, told prosecutors that he arranged for a straw donor to give $50,000 to Trump’s inauguration in place of a Ukrainian businessman who was legally barred from contributing to the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton Caught Staring at Funeral Performer's Derriere?</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/aretha-franklin-funeral-internet-frenzy-at-bill-clinton-s-gaze-during-ariana-grande-s-performance-at-a3925066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media has erupted at a video of Bill Clinton watching Ariana Grande perform at Aretha Franklin’s funeral. Video footage of Miss Grande performing the hit (You Make Me Feel Like) A Natural Woman had social media paying more attention to Mr Clinton’s gaze, rather than Miss Grande’s vocals. Social media users criticised the former president as “gross” after his eyes appeared to wander onto Miss Grande's derriere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ER' Actress Shot, Killed by Police; Claimed Clooney Blacklisted...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/vanessa-marquez-er-shot-killed-police-1202923337/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vanessa Marquez, an actress best known for her role as a nurse on “ER,” was shot and killed by South Pasadena police on Thursday, authorities confirmed on Friday. Officers were called t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Flawed -- But Gutsy...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/a-star-is-born-review-venice-2018-1137601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bradley Cooper makes his directing debut and headlines opposite Lady Gaga in this third remake of the enduring romantic drama about the meteoric rise of one talent while another crashes and burns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC Atty General Blocks Records to Secret DMV Office...</title>
      <link>http://www.wbtv.com/story/38998532/who-used-special-dmv-office-attorney-general-blocking-access-to-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DMV Commissioner Torre Jessup told employees Wednesday the secret driver’s license facility would no longer be used after WBTV exposed the office on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yard sign anxieties...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2018/08/29/beto-orourke-ted-cruz-yard-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As O'Rourke's yard signs are popping up in neighborhoods around the state, frustrated Cruz supporters are having trouble finding ones promoting the current U.S. senator's re-election bid. Until recently, that was by design, according to Cruz's camp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh last-minute hearing prep; Ready for theatrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/30/kavanaugh-senate-hearing-prep-supreme-court-white-house-805490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is setting up a pair of war rooms in which aides will provide rapid responses as the Supreme Court nominee testifies next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo installs HUMAN CAGES in famous tiger enclosure...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/dehli-zoo-human-cages-white-tiger-attacks-enclosure-india-a8516706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Measure inspired by 2014 death when a young man became trapped after falling into tigers’ pit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PLANS MASSIVE RALLY FOR CRUZ IN TX...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1035575198169411584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I will be doing a major rally for Senator Ted Cruz in October. I’m picking the biggest stadium in Texas we can find. As you know, Ted has my complete and total Endorsement. His opponent is a disaster for Texas - weak on Second Amendment, Crime, Borders, Military, and Vets!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Couple had drive-thru window on mobile home to sell drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wftv.com/news/local/overdoses-lead-police-to-alleged-drug-house-that-had-drive-thru-window/824035901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wftv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four drug overdoses led police last week to raid a drug house that had a drive-thru and walk-up window, the Ocala Police Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese turn to fortune tellers to divine trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-fortunetellers/predicting-trump-chinese-turn-to-fortune-tellers-to-divine-trade-war-idUSKCN1LG0KQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As analysts crunch trade data and political commentators dissect official statements for signs of how the Sino-American trade war will develop, some ordinary Chinese are using different sources to predict U.S. President Donald Trump's next moves: fortune tellers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCARDGOOGLE Secret  Deal to Track Retail Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/30/google-and-mastercard-cut-a-secret-ad-deal-to-track-retail-sales#gs.ebgJc0Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet Inc.’s Google and Mastercard Inc. brokered a business partnership during about four years of negotiations, according to four people with knowledge of the deal, three of whom worked on it directly. The alliance gave Google an unprecedented asset for measuring retail spending, part of the search giant’s strategy to fortify its primary business against onslaughts from Amazon.com Inc. and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TORONTO STAR Publishes Trump 'Off Record' NAFTA Comments to BLOOMBERG...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/world/2018/08/31/bombshell-leak-to-toronto-star-upends-nafta-talks-in-secret-so-insulting-remarks-trump-says-he-isnt-compromising-at-all-with-canada.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel staffed by robot dinosaurs...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-08-robotel-japan-hotel-staffed-robot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reception at the Henn na Hotel east of Tokyo is eerily quiet until customers approach the robot dinosaurs manning the front desk. Their sensors detect the motion and they bellow "Welcome."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telecom Plan of Attack on Tech Giants Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20180829/18030740541/that-time-telco-lobbyists-sent-me-all-their-talking-points-about-trying-to-shift-blame-to-internet-companies.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techdirt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not every day that big telco lobbyists email me their internal documents about how they're going to try to shift all the negative press about themselves and try to flip it onto internet companies. But it did happen yesterday. In what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankrupt TITANIC Exhibitor Sets Biggest Sale of Relics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/2018/08/31/bankrupt-titanic-exhibitor-sets-biggest-sale-ever-of-ship-relics#gs.sB7qHNU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story of the doomed luxury liner R.M.S. Titanic proved so alluring that divers were searching for the wreck seven decades after it sank to the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean. Once it was found in 1985, fanfare over retrieved relics led to exhibits around the world and a blockbuster movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort associate charged with violating foreign agents act...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/sam-patten-manafort-associate-charged-violating-foreign-agents/story?id=57528245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran lobbyist with reported ties to a Russian national whom special counsel Robert Mueller indicted in June has been charged with foreign lobbying violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>83% execs say business better, 76% see more growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/boom-times-83-execs-say-business-is-better-76-see-more-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over eight-in-10 executives believe that business is better than it was two years ago, and almost as many expect further growth in the third year of the Trump administration, according to a new survey of decision makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepper spray, arrests, obscenities: Heated UNC 'Silent Sam' protest engulfs campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/pepper-spray-arrests-obscenities-heated-unc-silent-sam-protest-engulfs-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police used pepper spray toward the end of the protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: GOOGLE Pushes Liberal News in Top 5 Search Suggestions...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/corinne-weaver/2018/08/31/study-google-pushes-liberal-news-top-5-search-suggestions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study about Google News shows that while everyone gets the same results,t five liberal news organizations “alone” made up 49 percent of the total recommendations from the respective experiments. The five were The New York Times, CNN, Politico, The Washington Post and HuffPost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran moves missiles to Iraq in warning to enemies...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-iraq-missiles-exclusive/exclusive-iran-moves-missiles-to-iraq-in-warning-to-enemies-idUSKCN1LG0WB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has given ballistic missiles to Shi'ite proxies in Iraq and is developing the capacity to build more there to deter attacks on its interests in the Middle East and to give it the means to hit regional foes, Iranian, Iraqi and Western sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Lawyers Quit Special Counsel Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/31/politics/dickey-richardson-leave-mueller/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors Ryan Dickey and Brian Richardson are no longer working for the office of special counsel Robert Mueller, the Justice Department confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENICE GOES GAGA...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6118435/Lady-Gaga-holds-hands-Bradley-Cooper-photocall-Venice-Film-Festival.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper showed just how close they have become after working on their movie, A Star Is Born, when they were pictured out at the 75th annual Venice Film Festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHATNER: Use of tech to affect minds so powerful; Need to be on guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2018/aug/31/a-screaming-nightmare-william-shatner-boldly-goes-into-vr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Trek’s Captain Kirk voices concerns about virtual reality after simulating a walk on Mars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $1 billion price cut: Luxury real estate gets slashed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/31/the-1-billion-price-cut-luxury-real-estate-gets-slashed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new federal tax law, which limits deductions of state and local taxes, is also putting pressure on real-estate in high-tax states. And foreign buyers, who were driving some of the highest-priced sales in 2014 and 2015, have pulled back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Baltimore Drivers Worst In Nation...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/08/30/new-study-baltimore-drivers-are-the-worst/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city has consistently ranked among Allstate's bottom 10 cities for safe drivers over the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>District Distributing Condoms To High Schoolers As STD Rates Soar...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/08/30/montgomery-co-provides-condoms-for-4-high-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public school system has decided to provide condoms at four high schools, Gaithersburg, Northwood, Watkins Mills and Wheaton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: ARGENTINA CURRENCY COLLAPSES...</title>
      <link>hhttps://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/31/argentinas-peso-has-fallen-108percent-against-the-dollar-so-far-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking roller coaster to reach 78 mph in 2 seconds!</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2018/08/30/record-breaking-maxx-force-launch-coaster-coming-to-great-america-in-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GURNEE, Ill. -- Six Flags Great America in Gurnee has announced a triple-record breaking roller coaster coming to the park in summer 2019 -- and our very own Marcus Leshock predicted it!  Maxx Force will be the fastest launch coaster in North America. It will feature the fastest inversion and highest double inversion of any roller coaster in the world, according to a news release from Six Flags.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror pics reveal brutality of bare knuckle boxing as it makes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7140811/bare-knuckle-fighting-fc2-bkfc-drew-lipton-chris-lytle/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE horrifying pictures reveal the sickening reality of bare knuckle boxing – with pulverised fighters getting punched square in the jaw without ANY gloves. The barbaric sport made a comeba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas unveils 24-foot-long, fully functional bong...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-largest-bong-vegas-20180831-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed the world's first marijuana museum and set to open in Las Vegas, Cannibation will feature what it calls the world's longest bong, coming in at 24 feet. How was it made, transported and brought to Vegas? Very carefully, man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURNING MAN: Dirty burners line up for group foam bath...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/life/arts/burning-man/2018/08/30/dirty-burners-line-up-group-foam-bath-dr-bronners-soap-funded-camp/1151270002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not-quite-decommodified camp sponsored by soap company cycles through more than 22,000 gallons of water during three days at Burning Man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Fitting End To Rap's Underwhelming Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryanrolli/2018/08/31/eminem-kamikaze-review/#7435196caa20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year’s critical lashing has inspired some of Eminem’s most intricate wordplay and spirited flows in years, but he still flaunts his vile behavior and outdated stylistic choices on 'Kamikaze.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas town scrutinized for blocking Muslim cemetery plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article217576505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials may sue a Texas town over its decision to halt a religious association's plans to build a Muslim cemetery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concern in White House over shortage of lawyers, press aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-allies-raise-alarm-team-040849514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasingly convinced that the West Wing is wholly unprepared to handle the expected assault from Democrats if they win the House in November, President Donald Trump's aides and allies are privately raising alarm as his circle of legal and communications advisers continues to shrink. With vacancies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers feed seaweed to dairy cows to 'reduce emissions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/researchers-feed-seaweed-dairy-cows-045848837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. (AP) — University of California researchers are feeding seaweed to dairy cows in an attempt to make cattle more climate-friendly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorologist accused of fracturing anchor's skull in fight...</title>
      <link>https://wvva.com/news/west-virginia-news-from-the-associated-press/2018/08/31/meteorologist-accused-of-fracturing-anchors-skull-in-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wvva.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — A meteorologist at a West Virginia TV station is accused of shoving a news anchor and fracturing her skull. The Charleston</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Industry Booming...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tattoo-industry-wins-over-millennials-1535713200 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tattoos are leaving an indelible mark on society, and it’s shaped like a dollar sign. Over the next decade, the industry is expected to continue to grow at an annualized rate of 7.7%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon to FACEBOOK: Lots of Extreme Political Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/coming-soon-to-facebook-lots-of-extreme-political-ads-1535707802 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign strategists are gearing up to flood Facebook with inflammatory and polarizing ads heading into the midterm elections, saying its advertising platform rewards extreme messaging more than other venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishops Reject Reporting Abuse Revealed in Confession...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/australian-bishops-reject-reporting-sexual-abuse-revealed-in-confession-1535703402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic Church leaders in Australia said they oppose laws requiring priests break the “seal of confession” when told of possible sexual abuse, as recommended by a judicial inquiry into abuse in churches and schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy catcher says China using LINKEDIN to recruit Americans...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180831095955-jizcu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINKEDIN-CHINA/ESPIONAGE (EXCLUSIVE, PIX, TV):EXCLUSIVE-Chief U.S. spy catcher says China using LinkedIn to recruit Americans</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
