<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DNA sequencing clinics rolled out for healthy [and wealthy] clients...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/08/16/top-u-s-medical-centers-roll-out-dna-sequencing-clinics-for-healthy-and-often-wealthy-clients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top academic medical institutions are opening clinics that promise to probe much deeper into your DNA — if you’re willing to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WV SUSPECT SOUGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Suspicious-Package-Manhattan-Subway-2-Train-Evacuation-546622821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The father of a West Virginia man sought for questioning in connection to placing rice cookers in Manhattan that sparked a rush-hour scare Friday morning has identified him as Larry Griffin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF intercepts Gaza rocket after weeks of calm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190816-israel-intercepts-gaza-rocket-after-weeks-of-calm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel intercepts Gaza rocket after weeks of calm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top State Dept official labeled staff 'traitors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/16/politics/state-department-officials-watchdog-report-political-retaliation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top officials in the State Department's Bureau of International Organization Affairs subjected employees to "disrespectful and hostile treatment," accusations of disloyalty, and retaliation, a long-awaited report from the department's watchdog agency found. The report also said the bureau's leadership "did not take significant action" to address these concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Buttigieg found God...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/16/politics/pete-buttigieg-religious-journey/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path from analytic philosophy to the Episcopal Church is not especially well traveled. But then, Peter Paul Buttigieg's search for God contains a few crooked lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energized and anxious: Liberals worry...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-08-16/energized-liberals-fear-warren-sanders-cant-beat-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead zone': Dire warnings in Chesapeake Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/16/algae-threat-dead-zone-chesapeake-bay-growing/2028226001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maryland scientists have been warning of a growing "dead zone" in the Chesapeake Bay. Data confirms their dire warnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREYHOUND riders asked for immigration papers at FL bus terminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/greyhound-riders-are-being-asked-for-immigration-papers-at-south-florida-bus-terminals/ar-AAFU2yK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS building caliphate 2.0...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/isil-is-building-a-new-caliphate-from-inside-a-syrian-refugee-camp-and-the-west-has-no-plan-to-combat-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Josh Rogin: ISIL women run a morality police inside the camp, enforcing sharia law and even conducting brutal executions, officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN reporter details intimidation effort made on Russia story...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6fad81679ec642c5819de18f0717aaa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CNN's Clarissa Ward says her story this week about Russian involvement in the Central African Republic came with a price: she was trailed during her reporting and made the subject...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers flee Georgia poultry plant amid ICE rumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/state/georgia/article234078662.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly Mayor's Daughter Brawls With Councilwoman's Daughter...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/16/philadelphia-mayor-jim-kenney-daughter-nora-kenney-fight-north-wildwood-councilwomans-daughter-jersey-shore-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Kenney hasn't commented on the accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN DEAD FOR 20 MINUTES SHARES SURVIVAL STORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/man-who-was-dead-20-minutes-after-being-electrocuted-shares-t160758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors say it was "a miracle" that Michael Pruitt, 20, survived after he was without a pulse for 20 minutes after being electrocuted. "Everything just shut off," Pruitt tells TODAY.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: US reverses policy on wildlife-killing cyanide bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49364984?ocid=socialflow_twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency, which authorised their continued use in June, has reversed its decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tiananmen' crackdown?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ai-weiwei-fears-tiananmen-crackdown-hong-kong-084710427.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching the Hong Kong protests from afar, Chinese dissident-artist Ai Weiwei fears the worst, warning of a repeat of the 1989 Tiananmen Square crackdown in Beijing. China "is a society which sacrifices anything to maintain its control," he warned. Ai's bleak warning comes after two months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Locks Down Israeli Embassy After Threats...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/secret-service-clears-streets-near-israeli-embassy-following-reports-of-suspicious-person-vehicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Secret Service confirmed Friday morning that it has shuttered the streets surrounding the Israeli embassy in downtown Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google warns BILLIONS of passwords hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9734757/google-passwords-hacked-how-to-check/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE has warned users that billions of passwords – and hundreds of thousands of username and password combinations – have been hacked. Cyber-experts are now urging users to make sure they’r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires two missiles into sea in ANOTHER weapons test amid tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9733398/north-korea-missile-launch-us-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea has fired two missiles into the sea in yet another bullish weapons test – the SIXTH in just a month. It comes amid anger in Pyongyang at ongoing US-led military exercises with Sou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese prepare to use giant fork on Hong Kong protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/terrifying-giant-fork-chinese-forces-18947059?bustcache=1565964839768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amnesty International has criticised the use of the "electric shock capturing fork" against protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigar-shaped UFO spotted during meteor shower over Wyoming...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/wyoming-ufo-perseid-cigar-video-18946716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was spotted during the Perseid meteor shower – but the light stood out from anything else seen that night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fattest President since William Howard Taft'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7364129/Twitter-SUSPENDS-Scaramucci-calling-Trump-fattest-President-William-Howard-Taft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I think it is related to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Wildfire Victims Plead With AT&amp;T: My House Burned Down, Stop Billing Me!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/15/camp-fire-victims-plead-with-att-my-house-burned-down-stop-billing-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A couple who lost everything in the Camp Fire in Paradise kept getting billed by AT&amp;T for a landline they obviously no longer had, a Call Kurtis Investigation uncovered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katy Perry accused  -- again...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/16/katy-perry-accused-of-sexually-harassing-female-tv-presenter/?_ga=2.98150748.212389428.1565828529-2106091010.1565828529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the second accusation in less than a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD HUNTS FOR SUSPECT</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/16/nypd-hunts-for-suspect-behind-subway-scare-caused-by-rice-cookers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are hunting for a person of interest seen leaving at least two rice cookers in a subway station and sparking an evacuation in Lower Manhattan Friday morning. A white male in his 20s or 30s w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, EU Set for Showdown Over Record Tax Bill...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-set-september-showdown-eu-081105255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc.’s 13 billion-euro ($14.4 billion) battle with the European Union reaches the bloc’s courts next month in a hearing set to throw the spotlight on antitrust commissioner Margrethe Vestager’s crackdown on tax deals doled out to big companies.The EU’s General Court, its second-highest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Develop Vaccine For Cat Allergies...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/08/16/vaccine-cat-allergies-developed-swiss-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you love cats but are allergic to them, a team of scientists in Switzerland could have the purrfect solution for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious black voters weigh Mayor Pete's bid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d3f3e2dcee24746a6786060d015a94d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENVILLE, S.C. (AP) — Joe Darby, a South Carolina pastor in the African Methodist Episcopal Church, pondered a sensitive question that he knew was on the mind of his congregation. Would black...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA passengers stranded on JFK runway for 8 hours...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/delta-flight-gets-ugly-after-8-hour-delay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things got heated aboard a Delta Airlines plane after it was delayed eight hours at JFK Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>115-year-old woman credits faith in God for longevity...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox46charlotte.com/news/local-news/charlotte-woman-celebrates-115th-birthday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox46charlotte.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Charlotte woman turned 115 years old Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to meet with senior advisers to begin planning Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-plans-friday-meeting-to-make-arrangements-for-withdrawal-from-afghanistan/2019/08/16/cab8d6aa-c00e-11e9-a5c6-1e74f7ec4a93_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has summoned Cabinet officials and other senior national security advisers to his New Jersey golf resort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'IT: CHAPTER TWO' To Set Fall On Fire With $120M+ Opening...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/it-chapter-two-opening-weekend-box-office-projections-bill-hader-jessica-chastain-1202669396/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Line’s It: Chapter Two, the sequel to the biggest horror film of all time, is looking at a domestic opening similar to the 2017 pic’s $123.4 million first frame. We hear in regards …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadians sour on Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/canadians-sour-on-trudeau-less-popular-than-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada’s prime minister, Justin Trudeau, once celebrated as the start of a worldwide youth leadership movement, has lost his luster and is now suffering the same level of poor approval ratings that plagued President Trump in his first two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMB PRANK? TEST?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Suspicious-Package-Manhattan-Subway-2-Train-Evacuation-546622821.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are looking to question a tall, thin white man seen pushing a shopping cart near the Fulton Street subway station, where two rice cookers were found Friday morning. A third rice cooker was found next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2 MAG SHAKES KANSAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.kwch.com/content/news/42-magnitude-earthquake-shakes-Kansas-546834361.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kwch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 4.2 magnitude earthquake shook central Kansas early Friday morning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truman tried too...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-reportedly-wants-to-buy-Greenland-So-did-14319056.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should the United States buy Greenland from Denmark?  It's something that President Donald Trump has repeatedly asked his staff to explore in recent weeks, bewildering top aides. But he's not first to ponder the question, which was first floated in the 1860s, when a report commissioned by the State Department under President Andrew Johnson concluded that the icebound island's abundance of fish and mineral resources could make it a valuable investment.  And in 1946, President Harry Truman's administration went even further, offering to purchase Greenland from Denmark in exchange for $100 million in gold.  "People have forgotten about how important places like Greenland were in the Cold War," said Ronald Doel, an associate professor of history at Florida State University and a co-editor of "Exploring Greenland: Cold War Science and Technology on Ice."  These days, Doel told The Washington Post, Greenland is most commonly thought of as a canary in the coal mine when it comes to climate change, given the threats it faces at a time of melting glaciers and rising seas. But not too long ago, "it was a really different calculus."  In the late 1940s, the Soviet Union had just become the United States' main adversary. The shortest distance between the two rival powers was over the North Pole, and the Arctic region started to look like a potential battleground. Greenland sat practically dead center between the population centers of the United States and several major cities in the U.S.S.R. To Pentagon strategists, that made Greenland a valuable piece of real estate. If the Soviets launched an attack, American bombers stationed on the island would already be halfway to Moscow.  That wasn't the only reason the Defense Department was shopping around for land in the Arctic. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spits out insults, rejects talks with Seoul...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/North-Korea-spits-out-insults-launches-missiles-14318807.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - North Korea spat out insults at South Korean President Moon Jae-in on Friday, rejected the idea of dialogue with Seoul and launched two more missiles into the sea, in the latest display of rage at joint U.S.-South Korea military exercises.  The volley of saber-rattling was another slap in the face for Moon, who spoke optimistically in a Liberation Day speech a day earlier of his plans to "solidify denuclearization" of North Korea, initiate a "peace economy" and lay the foundations for the unification of the Korean Peninsula by 2045.  While North Korea has not closed the door to dialogue with the United States, its anger dampens expectations that Washington and Pyongyang can make meaningful progress in nuclear talks. Meanwhile, although Moon's relentlessly rosy view of relations with the North has helped smooth the path to dialogue, experts say his approach looks increasingly unrealistic.  "We will advance dialogue and cooperation so that seeds sown together with North Korea in the spring of peace will grow into trees of prosperity," Moon said on Thursday, gliding over the continued sanctions on North Korea and the absence of steps by the regime to dismantle its nuclear program.  Pyongyang's response: its sixth missile launch in a little over three weeks and a barrage of insults at Moon over the military exercises whose aim, it said, was to annihilate its army.  "His open talk about 'dialogue' between the north and the south under such situation raises a question as to whether he has proper thinking faculty," Pyongyang said in a statement from an unnamed spokesperson for its Committee for the Peaceful Reunification of the Country. "He is, indeed, an impudent guy rare to be found."  The statement, released by the Korean Central News Agency, also complained about drones and fighters purchased from the United States,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI missiles 'pick OWN targets' to blow up after scanning ground below...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7363823/US-Army-working-AI-guided-missiles-pick-targets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon will invest vast sums into the AI-guided munitions, which will avoid collateral damage could be ready by 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters plan run on banks as Chinese Army rehearses intervention...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7363105/Hong-Kong-protesters-target-bank-ATMs-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tycoon Li Ka-shing, has bought the front-page advertisements of the city's major newspapers to urged people to 'love China' while Beijing's troops were seen rehearsing again today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple to Hold First Public Black Mass in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/satanic-temple-ottowa-hold-first-public-black-mass-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images) The Satanic Temple in Ottawa plans to hold what apparently will be the first public Black Mass in Canada's history on Aug. 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Portland braces for Proud Boys, Antifa protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/14/us/portland-planned-protests-soh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right and extremist groups plan to protest in Portland, Oregon, this weekend where they may come face to face with anti-fascist counterdemonstrators. The mayor has asked people to stay away, while police are getting ready. Here's what we know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harper stuns with walk-off grand slam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/phillies-bryce-harper-stuns-cubs-with-walk-off-grand-slam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a huge win for the Phillies and a huge loss for the Cubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What you live for'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/16/bryce-harper-walk-off-grand-slam-is-what-you-live-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It still doesn’t get tired for the Nationals’ $330 million man. Bryce Harper’s walk-off grand slam, the sixth of his career, lifted the Phillies to a 7-5 win over the Cubs on Thur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches arm, train congregants in wake of mass shootings...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/churches-arm-train-congregants-wake-132925899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acrid gun smoke clouded the sunny entrance of a Texas church on a recent Sunday. The simulated gunfight at the church in Haslet was part of a niche industry that trains civilians to protect their churches using the techniques and equipment of law enforcement. The anxiety of one mass shooting after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Minster rips Tlaib: Hatred of Israel greater than love for grandmother...</title>
      <link>http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/News.aspx/267513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.israelnationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOOCH UNLEASHED: TRUMP 'CRAZY'; 'PAPER TIGER' WHO WILL DROP OUT BY MARCH 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/08/anthony-scaramucci-interview-trump </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colonialism comparisons and backlash in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Trump-s-reported-interest-in-acquiring-Greenland-14318975.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - President Donald Trump faced a fierce European backlash to his reported interest in acquiring Greenland from Denmark on Friday, as some lawmakers compared the idea to colonialism.  "The whole idea that another country could buy Greenland - like it should be a colony - is so strange to us," said Michael Aastrup Jensen, a member of parliament with the influential center-right Venstre party.  Another member of his party, former center-right Danish Prime Minister Lars Løkke Rasmussen, chimed in on Twitter, writing: "It must be an April Fool's Day joke."  "The Greenlandic people have their own rights," Martin Lidegaard, the chairman of the Danish parliament's foreign policy committee and former foreign minister told The Washington Post. "I hope it is a joke - to not just buy a country but also its people."  Speaking to Reuters, Greenland's Foreign Minister Ane Lone Bagger said: "We are open for business, but we're not for sale."  Greenland's fewer than 60,000 residents - spread out across roughly 840,000 square miles - mostly govern themselves, even though they are part of the kingdom of Denmark. Melting ice could uncover offshore oil resources. But Greenland has also long been of interest to U.S. governments because of its location between the Arctic and the Atlantic oceans, where both China and Russia are increasingly active militarily.  As Denmark is preparing for Trump's visit to their capital Copenhagen early next month, reports that he has pushed top aides to investigate whether the U.S. government can purchase the remote island triggered an immediate and fierce response in the country.  Even though Trump is not the first U.S. president to extend such an offer - the Truman administration reportedly offered Denmark $100 million for its purchase after World War II...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE COOKERS SHUT NYC SUBWAY</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/16/pair-of-pressure-cookers-shut-down-lower-manhattan-subway-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of suspicious pressure cookers shut down a subway station in Lower Manhattan on Friday morning — but the NYPD’s Bomb Squad later determined they were not explosives, authorities …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spent hours alone with mysterious woman in lockup...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/16/jeffrey-epstein-spent-hours-alone-with-mysterious-woman-in-lockup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein spent at least two hours locked up alone with a mystery woman — possibly part of his legal team — just a day after he was taken off suicide watch at the Metropolitan Correctional Ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMB PRANK? TEST?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1811919572243669349deb39162dcdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Two abandoned objects that looked like pressure cookers prompted an evacuation of a major lower Manhattan subway station during the morning commute Friday before police determined...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayton killer was on cocaine, alcohol and anti-depressants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c11e52c94be0473d9aed759275c3febe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — The Latest on the Aug. 4 mass shooting in Dayton, Ohio (all times local): 4:25 p.m. A friend of the Dayton gunman who investigators say bought body armor and an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF Americans don't change underwear daily, new survey says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-change-underwear-tommyjohn-survey-20190815-2jmi33jahvbi3eytrtpfydzxqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Americans apparently wear the same pair of skivvies two days in a row, and 13% of them can go a week or more without changing, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man committs 10 felonies, 2 misdemeanors in 21 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/16/us/rodney-edward-king-indictment-crime-spree-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio man committed 10 felonies and two misdemeanors against seven people within a span of 21 minutes, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'IT: CHAPTER TWO' Could Float to $110 Million Debut...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/box-office-it-chapter-two-opening-weekend-tracking-1203302473/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros.’ thriller “It” jolted the box office when it debuted two years ago, delivering the best debut for an R-rated horror movie with $123 million. Pennywise is floating bac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surrounded by Tragedy, Venezuelans Laughing Like Crazy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/surrounded-tragedy-venezuelans-laughing-crazy-100005285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Editors Note: There are few places as chaotic or dangerous as Venezuela. “Life in Caracas” is a series of short stories that seeks to capture the surreal quality of living in a land in total disarrayHe knew this one was going to get laughs. “Raise your hands if you’re only in here because</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of porn sites track user data -- without telling...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/nationworld/os-ne-porn-sites-track-user-data-20190815-4vadt77nyfdqzbiv2c6jn3zfp4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 9 in 10 pornography websites send user data to at least one third party, a new study has found. And going incognito may not always help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MULAN' Star Support for Crackdown Prompts Call for DISNEY Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hong-kong-protestors-call-disney-boycott-mulan-star-voices-support-police-crackdown-1232216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese-American actress Crystal Liu has pulled Disney into the heated political fray surrounding Hong Kong's pro-democracy and anti-police brutality protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet neglected 43-year-old stepchild of US military industrial complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/meet-the-neglected--year-old-stepchild-of-the-us/article_e05514c9-c9ac-5cd7-b2fc-f677b2426049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — The icebreaker Polar Star was 1,000 miles out of its home port of Seattle last December, three days into its yearly voyage to resupply scientific bases in Antarctica,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crying on the job? 8 in 10 workers shedding tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/crying-on-the-job-youre-not-alone-with-8-in-10-workers-shedding-tears/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workplace weeping is a common experience, with almost half of workers blaming their boss or colleagues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel grants Tlaib West Bank visit on humanitarian grounds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7d180b153a84170be53dfe2c365e439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel's interior minister said Friday he has received and granted a request by Democratic Rep. Rashida Tlaib to enter the Israeli-occupied West Bank on humanitarian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATHAY PACIFIC CEO resigns after Beijing pressure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6abb13ad13154d74aca766b368f668bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — The CEO of Cathay Pacific Airways, one of Hong Kong's most prominent companies, resigned Friday following pressure by Beijing on the carrier over participation by some of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROCKS RALLY</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/oM8_hTdP4WA?t=721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;youtu.be&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is rallying supporters Thursday night in Manchester, New Hampshire, a state he narrowly lost in 2016 and hopes to capture in 2020. Watch live...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD FRIDAY:  President frets over possible economic downturn... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-banking-on-strong-economy-to-win-14308399.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEWATER, N.J. - Mounting signs of global economic distress this week have alarmed President Donald Trump, who is worried that a downturn could imperil his reelection, even as administration officials acknowledge that they have not planned for a possible recession.  Trump is banking on a strong economy to win a second term in 2020, and in recent weeks has impulsively lashed out at the Federal Reserve, pressured Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin to label China a "currency manipulator," and unexpectedly delayed tariffs on Chinese imports out of fear they could depress holiday retail sales.  Yet despite gyrations in the U.S. stock market and economic slowdowns in other countries, officials in the White House, at the Treasury Department and throughout the administration are planning no new steps to attempt to stave off a recession. Rather, Trump's economic advisers have been delivering the president upbeat assessments in which they argue the domestic economy is stronger than many forecasters are making it out to be.  In turn, Trump has sought to use his Twitter pulpit to drown out negative indicators. On Thursday he promoted the U.S. economy as "the Biggest, Strongest and Most Powerful Economy in the World," and, citing growth in the retail sector, predicted that it would only get stronger. He also accused the news media of "doing everything they can to crash the economy because they think that will be bad for me and my re-election."  Privately, however, the president has sounded anxious and apprehensive. From his golf club in New Jersey where he is vacationing this week, Trump has called a number of business leaders and financial executives to sound them out - and they have provided him a decidedly mixed analysis, according to two people familiar with the discussions who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT PAGE ONE:  Trouble Signs Hang Over Trade War... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/15/business/economy/trump-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House advisers discount warnings of a possible recession. But the president may be gambling that the Federal Reserve can ward off that prospect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' Obi-Wan Kenobi Series Coming to DISNEY Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/star-wars-ewan-mcgregor-talks-an-obi-wan-kenobi-series-disney-1201364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor has played the role in three films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'KIMMEL' Fined $395K by FCC for Emergency Alert Misuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/abc-pay-395000-fcc-fine-jimmy-kimmel-live-emergency-alert-misuse-1232481 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMC and Discovery were also hit with fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  Trump losing to Biden, Warren, Sanders and Harris...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/457645-fox-news-poll-shows-trump-losing-to-biden-warren-sanders-and-harris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll released Thursday showed President Trump losing head-to-head matchups against four of the top Democratic presidential primary contenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI BLOCKS OMAR, TLAIB FROM ENTERING ISRAEL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/19a6c707c401467d91297e6e027308ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — With a push from President Donald Trump, Israel on Thursday barred two Muslim-American congresswomen from entering the country for a visit, an extraordinary step bringing the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunderstorm unleashes 18" of hail in Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/whopping-18-inches-of-hail-accumulates-in-parts-of-michigan/70009085 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had taxidermied tiger, poodle in NYC mansion...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/15/jeffrey-epstein-had-creepy-taxidermied-tiger-poodle-in-ues-mansion-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton in a blue dress was the least of it. Jeffrey Epstein kept a creepy home office in his Upper East Side townhouse that was decorated with a $5.9 million painting of a woman cupping her b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG IOWA LEAD</title>
      <link>https://iowastartingline.com/2019/08/15/poll-elizabeth-warren-jumps-out-to-big-lead-in-the-iowa-caucus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;iowastartingline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Iowa Starting Line-Change Research poll shows a major shake-up in the Iowa Caucus standings as Warren takes a commanding lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Doctors Purposely Misdiagnose Patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/08/when-doctors-purposely-misdiagnose-patients/596068/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people say a Michigan doctor falsely diagnosed them with epilepsy. He wouldn’t be the first to lie to patients about how sick they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dale Earnhardt Jr.'s plane crashes... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/sports/2019/08/15/dale-earnhardt-jr-wife-ok-plane-crash-elizabethton-tennessee/2023565001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR legend Dale Earnhardt Jr. and his wife are OK after a plane crash Thursday afternoonÂ at an Elizabethton, Tennessee airport, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water crisis grips US city after lead contamination...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/water-crisis-grips-us-city-after-lead-contamination/ar-AAFQUso</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rushed to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://wcyb.com/news/local/plane-crashes-at-elizabethton-municipal-airport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcyb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: The Carter County Sheriff's Office has confirmed that Dale Earnhardt Jr. 's plane crashed at the Elizabethton Municipal Airport. Earnhardt Jr. has been transported to the hospital. The department also says Earnhardt Jr. 's wife Amy Reimann was also on board. The Elizabethton Fire Chief Barry Carrier says everyone survived the crash and none of the injuries were serious. We have exclusive footage sent to us of Dale Earnhardt, Jr. being treated at the scene. Earnhardt, Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gal pal finally found; At IN-N-OUT reading book on 'Deaths of CIA Operatives'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/15/jeffrey-epsteins-gal-pal-ghislaine-maxwell-spotted-at-in-n-out-burger-in-first-photos-since-his-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once spotted, Maxwell — who was sitting alone with a pet pooch — told an onlooker: “Well, I guess this is the last time I’ll be eating here!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese military personnel parade near Hong Kong border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinese-military-personnel-parade-near-hong-kong-border-055151905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Chinese military personnel waving red flags paraded at a sports stadium in a city across the border from Hong Kong on Thursday, an AFP reporter witnessed. Armoured vehicles were also seen inside the stadium in Shenzhen, with the event taking place as concerns build that China may intervene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff: Escaped without serious injuries...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/dale-earnhardt-jr-family-escape-plane-crash-tennessee/story?id=65000224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NASCAR driver Dale Earnhardt Jr. and his wife and child escaped a plane crash in Tennessee without serious injuries on Thursday, said Carter County Sheriff Dexter Lunceford. The Cessna Citation rolled off the end of a runway after landing at Elizabethton Municipal Airport in Elizabethton,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
