<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>May have tried to live stream shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2019/04/27/California-synagogue-shooting-injuries-Chabad-of-Poway/stories/201904270048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in anti-Jewish hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/la-me-poway-jewish-hate-synagogue-20190427-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack at a Poway synagogue in San Diego County that killed one and injured three others comes amid a rise in hate crimes and anti-Semitic incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead after construction crane crushes cars in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/crane-falls-on-multiple-cars-on-boren-and-mercer-blocking-eastbound-lanes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people are dead after a construction crane collapsed on several cars on the west side of Fairview Ave North and the Mercer Street intersection Saturday, according to the Seattle Department of Transportation. According to the Seattle Fire Department, two crane operators were killed and two people in cars on the ground died. Three others were taken to Harborview Medical Center in Seattle. Their condition is unknown at this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan Markle due to give birth as Britain awaits royal baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8954862/meghan-markle-due-give-birth-today-baby-sussex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUM-to-be Meghan’s due date is today, The Sun on Sunday can reveal. She and Prince Harry are on standby but relaxed about the arrival of baby Sussex. Harry, 34, still plans to attend today’s London…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left a manifesto?</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/04/poway-synagogue-shooter-left-a-manifesto-admits-to-arson-at-mosque-calls-trump-a-zionist-anti-white-traitorous-ccksucker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 19 YEAR OLD SUSPECT... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6967437/Several-injured-gun-man-opens-fire-San-Diego-Synagogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident is said to have taken place at the Chabad of Poway house of worship sometime after 11:30 local time, the San Diego County Sheriff's Office reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of congregation attempted to overpower gunman....</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/27/us/san-diego-synagogue/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 19-year-old man was in custody after a shooting at a synagogue in the California city of Poway left at least one person dead and several others wounded, Mayor Steve Vaus said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson's name to remain on L.A. school auditorium despite sex abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/entertainment/entertainmenttoday/s-2202300?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- The on-again, off-again relationship between Michael Jackson and Gardner Street Elementary School in Hollywood is still on, although perhaps more tenuously so than at the height of the pop star's popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido makes new appeal to Venezuela army ahead of Mayday protests... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guaido-makes-appeal-venezuela-army-ahead-mayday-protests-230013926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's opposition leader Juan Guaido used his latest mass rally on Saturday to reiterate an appeal to the army to end its support for Nicolas Maduro's regime, and announced massive Mayday protests to oust the embattled president. Despite support from more than 50 states who recognize him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 DEAD:  Four people shot at San Diego synagogue... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/poway-synagogue-shooting-chabad-way-san-diego-sherrifs-department-509162631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has died after shots were fired inside a Poway, California synagogue filled with people celebrating the last day of Passover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS powerhouse Lou Dobbs shaping Trump immigration policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/04/27/hard-line-views-made-lou-dobbs-a-fox-powerhouse-now-hes-shaping-trumps-border-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The relationship between President Donald Trump and Fox star Lou Dobbs has become an object of curiosity and amusement, but also something more profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter taken into custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbs8.com/article/news/local/man-detained-multiple-injuries-reported-after-shooting-incident-at-synagogue-in-poway/509-70fe3d8c-050d-4bba-a3bf-21d2bf0137e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shots were fired at Congregation Chabad in Poway. Police have confirmed multiple injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi conducting service suffered hand injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.10news.com/multiple-people-gunned-down-at-poway-synagogue-police-search-for-shooter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How eight 'bad grandpas' pulled off daring $20 million jewel heist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/27/how-eight-bad-grandpas-pulled-off-a-daring-20-million-jewel-heist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some senior citizens with too much time on their hands pick up bocce or dominoes as a hobby. And then there are the “Bad Grandpas”: Eight old men who pulled off one of Britain’s most audacious jewe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Last day of Passover... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36c8a77e02e4448ca1ef78e0b90ac2c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — A shooting at a synagogue outside San Diego where worshippers were celebrating the last day of Passover sent four people to the hospital Saturday, but the extent of their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden could escape the cosmetic surgery scrutiny Hillary Clinton endured</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/botox-hair-plugs-and-veneers-biden-could-escape-the-cosmetic-surgery-scrutiny-hillary-clinton-endured</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cosmetic doctors are certain that former Vice President Joe Biden’s full head of hair, smooth forehead, and Cheshire Cat grin are the result of plastic surgery and other procedures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding pigs among 50,000 animals killed at top-secret UK research base...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8954055/50000-animals-killed-mod-research/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALMOST 50,000 animals have been killed in experiments by military scientists at a top secret government research base, it can be revealed. Scientists blasted pigs with explosives, infected monkeys …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Saudi beheading victims were gay, court docs claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8951952/saudi-execution-gay-confessions-beheading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FIVE of the men brutally beheaded in Saudi Arabia were secret gay lovers tortured into terror confessions, it’s been claimed. One of the 37 “militants” ruthlessly executed during …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports of several people shot at San Diego synagogue... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2019-04-27/reports-of-several-people-shot-at-poway-synagogue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheriff's deputies warned of a man with a gun at Chabad of Poway about noon Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors urge women to stop putting garlic in vaginas...</title>
      <link>https://www.oprahmag.com/life/health/a27245254/garlic-vagina-yeast-infection-myth-dr-guntner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oprahmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Myth busted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House celebrates Melania Trump's birthday with bizarre photo... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/white-house-celebrates-melania-trump-s-birthday-bizarre-photo-n999141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mrs. Trump turned 49 on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' Headed for $1BILLION Weekend!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/avengers-endgame-box-office-rockets-record-156m-friday-1205348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The superhero pic earned an unprecedented $156.7 million on Friday in North America; overseas, it finished the day with a massive early foreign total of $487 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters set off stink bomb at Jeff Sessions speech at Amherst...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/04/25/protesters-set-off-stink-bomb-during-jeff-sessions-speech-at-amherst-college/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protester set off a stink bomb during a Jeff Sessions speech at Amherst College this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER PATROL DUMPING IN TUCSON</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/border-issues/2019/04/26/border-patrol-now-releasing-migrant-families-directly-tucson/3593532002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol's Tucson sector has followed in the footsteps of its counterparts in Yuma and is releasing families into the community in Tucson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The potential lie that could actually destroy Trump...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/837793/potential-lie-that-could-actually-destroy-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the circumstances of Otto Warmbier's release is a question neither side of the aisle will ignore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Spy Plane Flies Over DC, Nuke Bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-27/russian-spy-plane-flies-over-washington-us-military-nuclear-bases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIHADIS 'PLOTTING ATTACKS ON AMERICA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/774414/sri-lanka-news-bombings-blasts-explosions-bomb-attack-colombo-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX PISTOL Johnny Rotten rails against homeless anarchy in LA; 'Needles on beach, poo all over sand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6966735/Sex-Pistols-Johnny-Rotten-complains-homeless-crisis-LA-neighborhood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Rotten says homeless people have moved 'en masse' to his exclusive Los Angeles neighborhood of Venice Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo 10 lunar module finally found? Left orbiting Moon 50 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6965985/Astronomers-believe-spotted-module-moon-want-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1969, the Apollo 10 crew, inset left, ejected lunar module ‘Snoopy’ from the Apollo command module into orbit never to be seen again – or so they thought. It is possible that it has now been spotted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
With more than 500 kills, this vegetable farmer is world's deadliest hitman...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/27/meet-julio-santana-the-worlds-deadliest-hitman-with-500-kills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julio Santana dropped to his left knee and propped his right elbow on his hip, holding firm his hunting rifle until he had the man known as Yellow in his sights. It was Aug. 6, 1971, and Santana wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. general says will have what's needed to stop any dangerous act by Iran...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190427164730-gqg6x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ (URGENT):U.S. general says will have what's needed to stop any dangerous act by Iran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: POPE FUNDS CARAVANS</title>
      <link>https://www.vaticannews.va/en/pope/news/2019-04/pope-francis-central-american-migrants-aid-peters-pence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vaticannews.va&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Central American migrants in Mexico are in need of assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 5 Doctors Suffer From Emotional Distress; 4 In 5 Risk Burnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-40-percent-doctors-suffering-psychological-emotional-distress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing level of stress that doctors and health care practitioners face amid increasing workloads is taking a major toll on their mental health. A new study finds that four in 10 are suffering from psychological or emotional distress and eight in 10 are at serious risk of burnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Kim warns of return to tension, blames USA 'bad faith'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-russia-kcna/north-korean-leader-warns-of-a-return-to-tension-blames-u-s-bad-faith-idUSKCN1S12QH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un told Russian President Vladimir Putin that peace...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Guard monitors US aircraft carrier with drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/irans-guard-monitors-us-aircraft-carrier-with-drone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's semi-official Tasnim news agency is reporting that the country's powerful Revolutionary Guard has successfully managed a surveillance flight over a U.S. aircraft carrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force plans combat exercise, weapons evaluation in Utah...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/30133950e2b44f9ba6017225de5d0707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILL AIR FORCE BASE, Utah (AP) — The U.S. Air Force will conduct a large training exercise and a weapons evaluation in Utah in coming weeks. Hill Air Force Base officials said Saturday that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT apologizes for cartoon depicting anti-Semitic tropes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/440957-ny-times-opinion-apologizes-for-cartoon-depicting-anti-semitic-tropes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times Opinion section on Saturday apologized for a political cartoon that included anti-Semitic tropes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver North Out as NRA President...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d5d90ab1596f478c8f20d4dbe3f73979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — Retired Lt. Col. Oliver North has announced that he will not serve a second term as the president of the National Rifle Association amid inner turmoil in the gun-rights...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' Record $158M+ 1st Day...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/avengers-endgame-opening-weekend-box-office-record-1202602445/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;6TH UPDATE, Saturday 6:19 AM Writethru following Friday 10:14 PM post: And with a snap, Avengers: Endgame is swelling, just as expected.  Industry estimates as of last night for Friday stand at $15…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico: President Amlo's criticism of national newspaper sparks death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/27/mexico-president-campaign-vow-tested-press-battles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrés Manuel López Obrador promised to protect the press, but his barbs have resulted in journalists being harassed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pride vs. Pence: Gay Republicans grapple with Mayor Pete breakout...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/27/buttigieg-pence-gay-republicans-2020-1291201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 37-year-old mayor has climbed the ranks of the 2020 Democratic primary with help from a fundraising surge after launching barbs at the vice president, an icon among many Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame my brain: Killer's bold defense gets court hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/blame-my-brain-killer-s-bold-defense-gets-court-hearing-n998676</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More criminal defendants are turning to brain science to argue that they shouldn't face harsh punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson campaign TWITTER account suspended within hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/tommy-robinson-mep-campaign-twitter-account-suspended-election-8888976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Can't Monitor Autistic Son with GPS Tracker at School, Ruling Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/parents-cant-monitor-autistic-son-with-gps-tracker-at-school-nevada-ruling-says-11556357400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of an autistic child in Nevada who fought to have his school let him wear a GPS tracker with the ability to listen in on his surroundings lost their battle in a case that could resonate in school districts across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Spying Poses Rising Threat to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-spying-poses-rising-threat-to-u-s-11556359201 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese spies are increasingly recruiting U.S. intelligence officers as part of a widening, sustained campaign to shake loose government secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cracks Down on Apps That Fight iPhone Addiction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/27/technology/apple-screen-time-trackers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, with much fanfare, the tech giant unveiled a screen-time tracker of its own. Then it quietly began purging competitors from its store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers Tracking Where You Shop -- and Sleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-27/retailers-are-tracking-where-you-shop-and-where-you-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Playing Defense in Rust Belt as He Opens Re-Election Bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-playing-defense-rust-belt-080000511.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, he’ll hold a campaign rally in Green Bay, an event timed to compete for cable-news eyeballs with the White House press corps’ annual charity dinner. Trump’s interest in the region is already being matched by his top Democratic rivals -- former Vice President Joe Biden and Senator Bernie</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New theory suggests sisterhood ruled ancient Egypt before King Tut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/egyptologist-canada-presents-theory-two-queen-rule-tutankhamun-022746811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tutankhamun, the boy king of ancient Egypt, came to power only after two of his sisters jointly held the throne, according to an Egyptologist at Canada's Universite du Quebec a Montreal (UQAM). Researchers have known for more than half a century that a queen had reigned before Tutankhamun, whose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans at 'crossroads' as newly homeless numbers rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f85bb3d93ecf4022a591ca734ea4f8c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Daylight seeps through holes in the ceiling as 22-year-old Royon Rene Burbank walks across the sagging floor, the dirt below visible through gaps where rotten boards have given...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslims in hiding in Sri Lanka as tensions rise after bombings... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/25/muslims-flee-town-in-sri-lanka-as-tensions-rise-after-bombings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group of about 500 Muslims being sheltered in one city after fleeing Negomobo, as communal tensions rise</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
