<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/01/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose broadly after a better-than-expected June jobs report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker sparks fury wearing Star of David to protest COVID restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9749391/Washington-House-representative-apologizes-wearing-Star-David-protest-COVID-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, Republican Rep. Jim Walsh was giving a speech in Lacey, where he was wearing a pink shirt adorned with the Star of David.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am human'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9748245/American-sprint-sensation-set-MISS-Tokyo-Olympics-testing-positive-cannabis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sha'Carri Richardson failed a drugs test that will likely disqualify her from competing for Team USA in the Tokyo 2020 Games, sources told Reuters Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan real estate prices reach record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/02/manhattan-real-estate-prices-reach-new-record-with-buying-frenzy-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price jumps and shrinking inventory suggest the Manhattan real estate rebound is continuing to gain momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinema glitz returns with reborn Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210702-cinema-glitz-returns-with-a-reborn-cannes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cinema glitz returns with a reborn Cannes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUNE JOBS: +850K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/02/jobs-report-june-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase by 706,000 in June while the unemployment rate was forecast to fall to 5.6%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Pacquiao? King of the ring mulls Philippines' top job...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210702-president-pacquiao-king-of-the-ring-mulls-philippines-top-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Pacquiao? King of the ring mulls Philippines' top job</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For pot?</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/sports/shacarri-richardson-fails-drug-test-might-miss-summer-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old athlete reportedly tested positive for a prohibited substance about a week after securing a spot on Team USA for the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought upends life in West...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/droughts-climate-change-science-government-and-politics-environment-and-nature-dd8ef971f3083006b6f314e24d530f27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULELAKE, Calif. (AP) — Ben DuVal knelt in a barren field near the California-Oregon border and scooped up a handful of parched soil as dust devils whirled around him and birds flitted between empty irrigation pipes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Former Execs Wonder If It's 'Beginning of End'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-former-execs-wonder-if-it-s-the-beginning-of-the-end/ar-AALH1f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the former Trump Organization executive Barbara Res saw that the company’s longtime finance boss had turned himself in to face state tax charges, her mind turned to Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortress Australia Slashes Arrivals 50% to Stem Variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/fortress-australia-moves-to-further-isolate-as-delta-cases-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortress Australia Moves to Further Isolate as Delta Cases Rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Taxation Nears Historic Deal Amid Last-Minute Hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-international/global-tax-overhaul-wins-broad-consensus-but-obstacles-remain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration and global allies scored a major victory Thursday in their push for a more balanced international corporate tax system, but still face multiple significant obstacles to completing an ambitious plan that has been years in the making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC subpoenas FACEBOOK in escalating 'misinformation' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/01/dc-ag-subpoenas-facebook-497705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karl Racine is calling on Facebook to release by the end of next week an internal study it conducted looking into vaccine hesitancy among its users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Model S Plaid erupts in flames, traps owner after electronic doors fail, attorneys say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/tesla-model-s-plaid-erupts-in-flames-and-briefly-traps-owner-after-electronic-doors-fail-attorneys-say/ar-AALG30Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vehicle was among the first distributed to customers, after Elon Musk hosted a delivery event in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's fastest woman could miss Olympics after failed drug test...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/02/shacarri-richardson-could-miss-olympics-after-failed-drug-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s fastest woman may not get to compete in the Tokyo Olympics. Sha’Carri Richardson’s U.S. Olympic Trials performance in the 100 meters was disqualified Thursday after she failed a drug test…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi stabbed outside Boston synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/07/01/brighton-synagogue-rabbi-stabbed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rabbi is recovering at Boston Medical Center after he was stabbed eight times outside a Brighton synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As companies scramble to hire, workers enjoy upper hand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-98bd363ffa222cbfb38c50bff240223f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With the economy growing rapidly as it reopens from the pandemic, many employers are increasingly desperate to hire. Yet evidence suggests that as a group, the unemployed aren’t feeling the same urgency to take jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ORG CHARGED</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/01/trump-organization-cfo-expected-in-court-after-indictment-497485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan DA office leveled charges against the former president’s company and its chief financial officer, Allen Weisselberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEISSELBERG IN CUFFS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9746895/Trump-CFO-Allen-Weisselberg-paraded-court-CUFFS-face-charges-unpaid-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Organization's chief financial officer Allen Weisselberg was paraded in court wearing handcuffs to hear charges he failed to pay taxes on a company car, apartment and school fees for his grandchildren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVIDENCE UNVEILED</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-organization-indicted-allen-weisselberg-tax-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company and Allen Weisselberg, its longtime chief financial officer, pleaded not guilty in court on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body bag spotted MOVING by TV crew after motorcyclist pronounced dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/3197871/street-vendor-comes-back-from-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ELDERLY man had a “miracle” escape after paramedics pronounced him dead and placed him in a body bag – only for a reporter filming the scene to notice the bag moving. Street fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executions, sterilizations and cannibal banquets: Inside 100 year history...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3198028/china-executions-torture-communist-party-100/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILE executions, brutal torture, forced sterilisation, cannibalism and concentration camps — these are just some of the horrors the Chinese Communist Party has inflicted on its own people. And mean…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker Rescued, 4 Injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/reports-of-people-trapped-in-collapsed-building-in-northwest-dc/2717689/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters sawed through layers of rubble for more than an hour Thursday evening to rescue a construction worker from the wreckage of a building that collapsed in Northwest D.C. A special operations team with D.C. Fire and EMS talked to the man throughout the process, and he was alert, conscious and speaking as they got him out of the building…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC building collapses...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/07/1-trapped-others-injured-in-nw-dc-building-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rescue operation is underway in Northwest D.C. as a person has been trapped in the “full collapse” of a building under construction Thursday afternoon, the D.C. Fire and EMS Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom recall election set for September...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-entertainment-elections-government-and-politics-a2326a90364bf7ce502fa9f8e64532e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California on Thursday scheduled a Sept. 14 recall election that could drive Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom from office, the result of a political uprising largely driven by angst over state coronavirus orders that shuttered schools and businesses and upended life for millions of Californians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vaccine Sommeliers' Go to End of Line in Brazil Town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-sommeliers-go-to-the-end-of-the-line-in-one-brazilian-town/ar-AALFv61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian town is taking action against people who are pick and choosing which Covid-19 vaccine they want to take, a move that’s delaying a mass immunization campaign in one of the hardest-hit countries in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federally Protected Birds Terrorizing Passersby, Leaving Some Bloodied In TX...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/hit-head-pair-birds-harassing-people-southlake-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of seemingly angry birds have people ducking, dodging and generally avoiding a section of sidewalk in Southlake in order to stay away from the sudden aerial attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock injuries of woman 'raped &amp; punched in genitals' by DODGERS star...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3197915/trevor-bauer-accuser-injuries-claims-raped-punched/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TREVOR Bauer’s accuser says the baseball star raped and repeatedly punched her in the genitals, according to shocking legal documents. In disturbing images, the woman, identified by her lawye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chef dies after falling into boiling vat of soup...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/01/chef-dies-after-falling-into-boiling-vat-of-soup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iraqi chef tragically died last week after falling into a vat of soup, which left him severely scalded across large swathes of his body. The horrific accident had occurred June 15 while Issa Ism…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Rogan Too Big to Cancel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/01/joe-rogan-is-too-big-to-cancel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other comics called him “Little Ball of Anger” — semi-affectionately, never to his face — a man flammable by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein, Ghislaine gain confidence they'll be freed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3198376/bill-cosby-me-too-harvey-weinstein-ghislaine-maxwell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILL Cosby’s release is a “huge blow” to the #MeToo movement, experts claim, as Harvey Weinstein and Ghislaine Maxwell’s lawyers say their cases should also be overturned.  The disgraced TV st…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Companies Revolt Against AMAZON, Shut Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7ez5x/amazon-delivery-companies-revolt-against-amazon-shut-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent shutdown of two Amazon delivery companies in Portland appears to be the first public example in the United States of such companies using their leverage to protest against Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER revamps misinformation labels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-election-2020-misinformation-technology-37cee761758f1072f91e1a362f769f5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last May, as Twitter was testing warning labels for false and misleading tweets, it tried out the word “disputed" with a small focus group. It didn't go over well. “People were like, well, who’s disputing it?" said Anita Butler, a San Francisco-based design director at Twitter who has been working on the labels since December 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK untouchable? It's complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-untouchable-complicated-rcna1323</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook won a major battle against government regulators this week, but the war isn't over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The social media giant's &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA debt to hit $3 trillion THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-deficit-to-hit-243-trillion-in-2021-then-fade-as-stimulus-relief-expires-cbo-says/ar-AALFGpo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deficit is projected to remain historically high this year but then quickly shrink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Covid cases up 10% this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-covid-cases-10-percent-hypertransmissible-delta-variant-spreads-n1272895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lagging vaccination rates coupled with the rise of the delta variant could account for the uptick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>130 nations agree to global tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/01/nations-agree-to-support-us-proposal-for-global-minimum-tax-on-corporations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of 130 nations has agreed to a global minimum tax on corporations, part of a broader effort to overhaul international tax rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick as Dog? Pets Often Catch From Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-07-01/sick-as-a-dog-pets-often-catch-covid-from-humans-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin DiAngelo Very Disappointed in White People Making Her Rich...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/01/robin-diangelo-is-very-disappointed-in-the-white-people-making-her-rich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice Racism—and the "anti-racism" consulting business—rakes in the bucks while losing hearts and minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: French fries GOOD for blood pressure?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/potatoes-fries-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors explain that increasing dietary potassium from foods like baked and boiled potatoes helps to reduce sodium retention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fukushima: Radioactive boars create mutant hybrid species decade after disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/fukushima-radioactive-boars-create-mutant-24439268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade after the Fukushima disaster, wild boars have been mating with domestic pigs in the nuclear wasteland and creating a new mutant species, DNA researchers have determined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach residents debate leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/haunted-tragedy-safety-fears-surfside-212144655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chiara Mauriziano rolled a suitcase into Champlain Towers East in Surfside, Florida on Wednesday morning, returning home nearly a week after a condo tower a few hundred feet away collapsed, killing at least 16 and leaving scores missing. Mauriziano, like many of her neighbors in Champlain Towers East and other nearby buildings, awoke to a nightmare last Thursday. Around 1:30 am, Champlain Towers South, which sits on the same strip of beachfront as the building in which Mauriziano's family has owned a condo for two decades, partially collapsed into a smoldering mound of twisted metal and fragmented concrete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby release infuriates survivors; Lawyers hail win for Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/bill-cosbys-prison-release-provokes-202921475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;- "What happened to Cosby should never happen to any American in any social strata...the Constitution won today," former prosecutor Bruce Castor said in an interview. Castor made a deal with Cosby's attorneys in 2005 not to bring criminal charges and, as a result, he was unable to avoid testifying in a civil lawsuit brought against him by his accuser Andrea Constand. - “Today’s majority decision regarding Bill Cosby is not only disappointing but of concern in that it may discourage those who seek justice for sexual assault in the criminal justice system from reporting or participating in the prosecution of the assailant or may force a victim to choose between filing either a criminal or civil action,” Andrea Constand said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infection Changes Structure Of Blood Cells, May Explain 'Long-Hauler' Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-changes-blood-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests reveal the size and deformability of red blood cells differs greatly between those contracting COVID and those who have not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  MCCAIN QUITS 'VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/01/meghan-mccain-says-leaving-to-live-in-l-a-but-the-view-had-no-emmys-noms-this-year-for-the-first-time-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan McCain says she’s leaving “The View” because she likes living in Washington, DC. “When I said goodbye to all of you in the studio, I found out I was pregnant,” McCain said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorka claims NSA spied on him and Bannon!</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/01/trumpers-go-spy-crazy-now-seb-gorka-claims-nsa-spied-on-him-and-steve-bannon-in-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump aide, echoing Tucker Carlson, claims NSA surveilled him, Steve Bannon and other White House insiders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC hotel industry 'depression,' room revenue down 60%...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/nyc-hotel-industry-in-a-depression-room-revenue-down-60-report-says/3134878/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hotel industry is in a recession or worse in 21 of the top 25 U.S. markets, and New York City is one of the worst off of all, according to a new report released Thursday by a lodging trade group. The American Hotel &amp; Lodging Association said the city has lost about a third of its hotel rooms since…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: French fries GOOD for blood pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/eating-french-fries-could-be-good-for-blood-pressure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to lower your blood pressure? How does a plate of French fries sound?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shows Massive Explosion After LAPD Botches Detonation Of Illegal Fireworks; 10 Cops Injured...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/01/it-felt-like-a-really-hard-earthquake-9-people-injured-in-botched-illegal-firework-detonation-by-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 16 people, including 10 law enforcement officers, were injured and several cars and structures were damaged Wednesday evening when police attempted to safely detonate illegal fireworks that were seized in South Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County Orders Inspection Of 3-Building Condo Complex In Marina Del Rey!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/exclusive-county-orders-inspection-of-marina-city-club-towers-in-marina-del-rey-after-tragic-florida-condo-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County officials have ordered an inspection of the Marina City Club Towers, a condominium complex with three buildings in Marina Del Rey, after the tragic Champlain Tower collapse in Florida last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  MCCAIN QUITS 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3195499/meghan-mccain-quits-the-view-on-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN McCain quit The View live on-air after saying she’s “done” with her co-star clashes and joked they have “four weeks of fighting left.” The host will reportedly …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wally Funk was supposed to go to space 60 years ago. Now she's going with Bezos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wally-funk-was-supposed-to-go-space-60-years-ago-now-she-s-going-with-jeff-bezos/ar-AALF7FT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 82, the Mercury 13 pioneer is poised to become the oldest person to reach space when the first crewed Blue Origin rocket takes flight this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Announces Liz Cheney to Sit on 1/6 Committee, Despite Threats of Revenge From McCarthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/just-in-pelosi-announces-liz-cheney-to-sit-on-1-6-committee-despite-threats-of-revenge-from-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) announced Thursday that Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WI) will serve on the January 6 select committee, despite threats from House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-CA)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastated condo community looks to Biden visit for comfort...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-fl-state-wire-surfside-building-collapse-government-and-politics-cc101831be50a82fb9968bbe5c5df8c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — President Joe Biden is set to offer comfort and support Thursday to the families of the dead and missing after last week's collapse of a high-rise condo building along the Florida coastline.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
