<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Fed President to retire early, citing trading disclosures...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/27/dallas-fed-president-kaplan-to-retire-early-on-oct-8-citing-trading-disclosure-distraction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  FBI probing OZY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/27/fbi-investigating-ozy-co-founder-samir-rao-amid-youtube-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samir Rao, the co-founder and COO of the digital media company, allegedly pretended to be Alex Piper, the head of unscripted programming for YouTube Originals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden moves to protect 'Dreamers' from deportation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-administration-moves-to-protect-dreamers-from-deportation/ar-AAOSJoW?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden administration moves to protect 'Dreamers' from deportation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway's Big Night Flops...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/nfl-packers-beat-49ers-tony-wards-ratings-nbc-cbs-sunday-night-football-1234844793/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The much nominated and tremendous Slave Play came up empty handed and Jagged Little Pill’s Lauren Patten showed exactly what an acceptance speech should be last night as CBS took the Tony Awards to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's incredible shrinking Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/27/california-republicans-gop-514337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even party stalwarts acknowledge the GOP likely won’t be winning top-of-the-ticket statewide races for the foreseeable future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. successfully flight tests hypersonic weapon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-successfully-flight-tests-raytheon-180251221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has tested an air-breathing hypersonic weapon capable of speeds faster than five times the speed of sound, marking the first successful test of the class of weapon since 2013, the Pentagon said on Monday. The test took place as the United States and its global rivals quicken their pace to build hypersonic weapons - the next generation of arms that rob adversaries of reaction time and traditional defeat mechanisms. In July, Russia said it had successfully tested a Tsirkon(Zircon) hypersonic cruise missile, a weapon President Vladimir Putin has touted as part of a new generation of missile systems without equal in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Cuts 2 Years Off Life Expectancy of U.S. Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/covid-cuts-two-years-off-the-life-expectancy-of-u-s-men/ar-AAOR8PW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American men lost 2.2 years of life expectancy last year because of Covid-19, the biggest decline among 29 nations in a study of the pandemic’s impact on longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea President Raises Ban On Eating Dog Meat: 'Hasn't Time Come?'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/south-korea-dog-meat-ban-president-moon-jae-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meat has long been a part of South Korean cuisine with about one million dogs believed to be eaten annually​.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CIA's secret war plans against WIKILEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kidnapping-assassination-and-a-london-shoot-out-inside-the-ci-as-secret-war-plans-against-wiki-leaks-090057786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2017, as Julian Assange began his fifth year holed up in Ecuador’s embassy in London, the CIA plotted to kidnap the WikiLeaks founder, spurring heated debate among Trump administration officials over the legality and practicality of such an operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol regulations show cost of bipartisanship...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/573639-alcohol-regulations-show-that-bipartisanship-can-cost-the-public</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elected officials too often enrich select interest groups, and don’t feel much moral pressure to change things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Mask Protest Turns Violent At ROSCOE'S In Anaheim...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/09/27/caught-on-video-anti-mask-protest-turns-violent-roscoes-chicken-waffles-anaheim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security guards of the famed restaurant clashed with protesters outside its Anaheim location, 2110 S. Harbor Blvd. Video posted to social media showed at least one man being dragged out of the restaurant by several security guards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Gets 3rd Dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/27/biden-to-receive-covid-booster-shot-live-on-camera-monday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden received a Covid-19 booster shot Monday, in accordance with the latest guidance from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As daughter sought state license, Noem summoned agency head...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-discrimination-kristi-noem-south-dakota-age-discrimination-7942a78d5545205dff41a696ef9fc251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — Just days after a South Dakota agency moved to deny her daughter's application to become a certified real estate appraiser, Gov. Kristi Noem summoned to her office the state employee who ran the agency, the woman's direct supervisor and the state labor secretary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyday foods that could soon become luxuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210923-the-everyday-foods-that-could-become-luxuries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyday foods such as coffee, meat and spices could become luxury items due to global climate impacts and changing tastes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAA Acquiring ICM; Biggest Talent Agency Link-Up Since WMA-ENDEAVOR...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/caa-acquiring-icm-partners-1234844517/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: CAA has made it official, this blockbuster deal we have chased all weekend. Find release below the original Deadline scoop. EXCLUSIVE: Creative Artists Agency is acquiring ICM Partners, a m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social-ecological-liberal coalition...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/27/olaf-scholz-intends-three-way-coalition-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centre-left contender to replace Angela Merkel announces plan for ‘social-ecological-liberal’ alliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men too close to feeding bears in national park could face prison time...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article254557057.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As they waded into the Brooks River the three men came within 50 yards of the brown bears.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD Moves First-Year MBA Students Online Amid Virus Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/breaking-harvard-business-school-moves-130846644.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poets&amp;Quants has learned that Harvard Business School is going back to remote instruction for all first-year MBA students courses after a “steady rise in breakthrough infections” among students. “With the support of Harvard University leaders, advised by city and state public health officials, we have decided to move all first-year MBA students, and some in the second year, to remote learning for the week of 9/27 to 10/03.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens Of MA State Police Troopers Resigning Over Vaccine Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/27/massachusetts-state-police-covid-vaccine-mandate-resignations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Police Association of Massachusetts (SPAM) said dozens of troopers have submitted their resignation papers as a result of the state’s COVID vaccine mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN NEARS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-congress-government-funding-e7bfe8a6ffdb40a8d33e17ef11ded7a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It's a consequential week for President Joe Biden's agenda , as Democratic leaders trim back his $3.5 trillion tax and spending package to win over remaining lawmakers and work to quickly pass legislation to avoid a federal shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rowdy celebrations erupt in Norway as ALL covid restrictions end...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-europe-norway-4d3b34ca4362afa87772df309881216d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Police in Norway on Sunday reported dozens of disturbances and violent clashes including mass brawls in the Nordic country’s big cities after streets, bars, restaurants and nightclubs were filled with people celebrating the end of COVID-19 restrictions that lasted for more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Hinckley Jr to be 'unconditionally released'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3742710/john-hinckley-jr-released-ronald-reagan-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE man who tried to assassinate President Ronald Reagan is set to be “unconditionally released”, according to reports on Monday.  John Hinckley Jr. was 25 when he shot and wounded…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Outages Hit China, Threatening Economy and Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/27/power-outages-hit-china-threatening-the-economy-and-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONGGUAN, China — Power cuts and even blackouts have slowed or closed factories across China in recent days, adding a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Fireball Soars Through NC Skies At 32,000 MPH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/north-carolina-fireball-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five fireballs seen over the U.S. in the same night and 80 people reported the one over North Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin gets first female mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-capital-berlin-get-first-female-mayor-2021-09-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Social Democrats (SPD) won the regional election to lead the state government in Berlin, according to provisional results on Monday, meaning that their candidate Franziska Giffey will become the first female mayor of the German capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haunted house actor wanted to scare child. Then he cut boy with knife, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-haunted-house-actor-wanted-to-scare-a-child-then-he-cut-the-boy-with-a-knife-police-say/ar-AAORjIw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio haunted house actor wielded a real knife earlier this month to up the scare factor. The end result: He stabbed an 11-year-old boy in the foot, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Young People's Social Anxiety Worsened in Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/27/how-young-peoples-social-anxiety-has-worsened-in-the-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One student had several panic attacks a week, alone in his room. One felt her hands shake when walking on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Top General Back in Center of Political Battle...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/27/americas-top-general-back-in-the-center-of-a-political-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Nearly 16 months after he walked across a Lafayette Square aggressively cleared of protesters with then President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seize millions from private vaults without charging owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/federal-authorities-safety-box-seizures-owners-fight-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Married couple Jeni Pearsons and Michael Store aren't wealthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Afghanistan airlift: Split-second decisions, relentless chaos drove historic military mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/inside-the-afghanistan-airlift-split-second-decisions-relentless-chaos-drove-historic-military-mission/ar-AAORDRK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While nearly every aspect of the airlift has been politicized in the United States, the rescue of nearly 124,000 people in such a narrow time frame will go down as a historic accomplishment — albeit one overshadowed by tragedy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need new monitor for computer? You can wear one on face...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/need-a-new-monitor-for-your-computer-you-can-wear-one-on-your-face/ar-AAOS1bz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some new wearable displays are trying to make your office more portable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM Pausing Work on Kids Site After Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3741482/facebook-instagram-kids-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK is “pausing” its work on a controversial Instagram Kids app. The app was originally designed to target youngsters aged 13 or under – but has been met with significant backlash.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fight over 'The One' -- L.A.'s biggest and most extravagant mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2021-09-27/la-fi-the-one-niles-niami-don-hankey-mansion-trustee-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea was simple: Nile Niami would build and sell The One, the biggest and most extravagant new home in the country. Then things went sideways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Fed President to retire -- 9 months earlier than planned...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/27/boston-fed-president-rosengren-to-retire-september-30-9-months-earlier-than-planned.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro supporters have called for military takeover of Brazil. Why do they wave American flag?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/some-bolsonaro-supporters-have-called-for-a-military-takeover-of-brazil-why-do-they-wave-the-american-flag/ar-AAORCia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brazilian right has wielded the Stars and Stripes as a cudgel to convey a don’t-tread-on-me ethos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron egged by protester shouting 'vive la revolution'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/emmanuel-macron-projectile-lyon-protest-b1927645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French president was filmed being struck by a small projectile — believed to be an egg — while surrounded by press and members of the public in Lyon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Gaetz Lawyer Lineup Tells About His Troubles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/what-matt-gaetzs-legal-lineup-tells-us-about-his-troubles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have hardly been any developments in the alleged case against Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL). But the lawyers he’s hired indicate that he’s not out of the woods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two trans win seats in parliament...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210927103818-5yrog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-ELECTION/LGBT (PIX):Two transgender women win seats in German parliament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List Of Companies Paying NO TAXES Might INCREASE Under Biden Plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/list-companies-paying-no-taxes-might-increase-under-bidens-tax-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves drill holes in cars to steal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/16253282/thieves-drill-holes-to-steal-fuel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIEVES are drilling holes into parked cars to steal fuel after panic buying sparked a petrol shortage. Petrol stations up and down the country are running out of fuel as the pump chaos caused by h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staten Island crowd defies jab order by storming mall food court...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Staten-Island-crowd-defies-vaccine-mandate-by-16489484.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As customers enjoyed their Saturday afternoon at Staten Island Mall and prepared to enjoy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US general: Whisperer to presidents, target of intrigue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-afghanistan-lloyd-austin-joint-chiefs-of-staff-b93c6da6e9fdf61b2a185df9baa4e2a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Gen. Mark Milley has been the target of more political intrigue and debate in two years as chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff than any of his recent predecessors were in four. One after another, political firestorms have ignited around him — unusual for an officer who by law is a whisperer to presidents and by custom is careful to stay above the political fray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE DNA VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/could-dna-vaccines-be-the-next-tool-in-the-worlds-battle-against-covid-19-680371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India last month said that it had created the world’s first DNA vaccine, ZyCoV-D. While standard vaccines use actual 'hardware' protein, DNA vaccines use the 'software' blueprint of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE CEO Sees Free Speech as Core Value in Russia?</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/company-news/video/youtube-ceo-wojcicki-responds-to-russia-censorship-accusations~2289193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sep.26 -- Susan Wojcicki, chief executive officer at Google’s YouTube, responds to accusations the company is censoring its content in Russia, at the request of the Russian government. She also talks about balancing free speech values with local laws, and discusses regulatory scrutiny facing YouTube in the U.S. She speaks with Bloomberg's Emily Chang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholz, Social Democrats lead... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926202840-8j2vx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 7, TV, PIX):UPDATE 7-German Social Democrats beat conservatives in vote to decide Merkel successor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoarding!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/uk-gas-stations-run-dry-trucker-shortage-3f078d7eb6bbf2b5d130abfa44007278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of British gas stations ran dry Sunday, an industry group said, as motorists scrambled to fill up amid a supply disruption due to a shortage of truck drivers. The Petrol Retailers Association, which represents almost 5,500 independent outlets, said about two-thirds of its members were reporting that they had sold out their fuel, with the rest “partly dry and running out soon.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama lawmakers weigh using virus funds to build prisons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-prisons-alabama-4eb1ebe3327247a923284e0105992bdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — Alabama is weighing the use of $400 million in pandemic relief funds to build new prisons, a proposal that state Republican leaders say would save state taxpayer money but that critics argue is not the intended use of the federal aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland ALMOST elects Europe's first women-majority parliament...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-elections-environment-and-nature-iceland-f9e66907b6e25560a508de0f4b118ddd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REYKJAVIK, Iceland (AP) — Iceland briefly celebrated electing a female-majority parliament Sunday, before a recount produced a result just short of that landmark for gender parity in the North Atlantic island nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN:  Humanity on brink of nuclear annihilation with threat highest for 40 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3737906/human-annihilation-threat-highest-un-chief-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUMANITY is on the brink of “nuclear annihilation” with the threat reaching its highest boiling point in forty years, a top UN chief has warned. The nuclear arms race has the globe teet…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK PRAISES COMMUNIST CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/26/musk-praises-china-says-tesla-will-expand-investments-in-country.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the second time this month Musk was highly complimentary of the nation that's imperative to his electric vehicle company, saying it's a "global leader digitalization."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY DEFIANT: TRUTH BEFORE TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/liz-cheney-donald-trump-wyoming-60-minutes-2021-09-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Cheney tells Lesley Stahl about running for re-election as an anti-Trump Republican in Wyoming, as her own party there has called for her resignation, and joining the House Select committee investigating the January 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT BITES BACK:  Fuel Shortages Pile Pressure on Johnson as UK Crisis Escalates...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/fuel-shortages-pile-pressure-on-johnson-as-u-k-crisis-escalates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
