<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE Boat Tail May Be Most Expensive New Car in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/rolls-royce-boat-tail-may-120200931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-foot convertible features crockery from Christofle of Paris, a proper refrigerator and a giant parasol at the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Wing Scarcity Forcing Restaurants To Pull From Menus...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/chicken-wing-shortage-denver-colorado-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Denver-area restaurants are removing items from menus or even temporarily closing because they don't have enough chicken wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: First-Born More Likely To Suffer Heart Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-many-siblings-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First-born children generally had a lower risk of non-fatal cardiovascular and coronary events than their younger siblings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys adopt 'accent' of other species when in shared territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/may/27/monkeys-adopt-accent-of-other-species-when-in-shared-territory-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian Amazon primates found to adapt their calls to get along better with their neighbours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long bath almost as good as long run...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/may/26/hot-tub-health-kick-why-a-long-bath-is-almost-as-good-for-you-as-a-long-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that prolonged immersion in a piping hot bath has many of the same medical benefits as aerobic exercise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Public transit worker fatally shoots 9, then kills self at San Jose rail yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-near-northern-california-rail-yard-authorities-say-n1268623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A public transit employee, Samuel Cassidy, opened fire on co-workers at the Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority before taking his own life, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: WIZARDS Star Restrained After Fan Dumps Popcorn On Him...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/russell-westbrook-sixers-fan-popcorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westbrook had to be restrained by multiple people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Propose $6 Trillion Budget...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/27/biden-to-propose-6-trillion-budget-to-boost-middle-class-and-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden will propose a $6 trillion budget on Friday that would take the United States to its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime boss shakes govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210527-crime-boss-s-wild-claims-shake-turkish-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime boss's wild claims shake Turkish government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physician warns Tokyo Olympics could spread variants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-olympic-games-coronavirus-pandemic-health-sports-793b0a9b231b2a148e38beb924f0000a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A physician representing a Japanese medical body warned Thursday that holding the postponed Tokyo Olympics in two months could lead to the spread of variants of the coronavirus. Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-rooted racism, discrimination permeate military...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-racial-injustice-race-and-ethnicity-discrimination-business-4e840e0acc7ef07fd635a312d9375413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Stephanie Davis, who grew up with little, the military was a path to the American dream, a realm where everyone would receive equal treatment. She joined the service in 1988 after finishing high school in Thomasville, Georgia, a small town said to be named for a soldier who fought in the War of 1812.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia Claims Expose Erdogan Vulnerability...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/erdogan-supports-interior-minister-against-corruption-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mafia Claims Expose Erdogan’s Political Vulnerability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Oz, Births of Tasmanian Devils Are Milestone After 3,000 Years...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/27/in-australia-births-of-tasmanian-devils-are-a-milestone-after-3000-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia — Pink, hairless, deaf and blind, the roughly month-old joeys were but the size of a shelled peanut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seychelles Mysteries Pit Anti-Vaxxers Against Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/seychelles-e2-80-99s-covid-mysteries-pit-anti-vaxxers-against-scientists/ar-AAKqFfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases in the world’s most vaccinated nation are ticking up, forcing researchers to wage war against misinformation on whether jabs are effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT president: Orwell's 1984 could happen in 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57122120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech executives warned that democracy has to win the AI arms race, in a new BBC Panorama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  7 MILLION AUSTRALIANS ORDERED INTO NEW COVID LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527003449-ixaur</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Australia's Victoria state to enter COVID-19 lockdown after fresh outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-official who revealed UFO project accuses Pentagon of 'disinformation' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/26/ufo-whistleblower-ig-complaint-pentagon-491098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lue Elizondo's IG complaint asserts that officials have tried to discredit him after he went public in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents flee Melbourne...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9623007/Melbourne-Covid-residents-flee-Victoria-head-Sydney-ahead-imminent-five-day-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An announcement by Acting Victorian Premier James Merlino about the probable lockdown is expected to come at about 9am on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  7 MILLION AUSTRALIANS ORDERED INTO NEW COVID LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527001417-slw29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (URGENT):Australia's Victoria state to enter snap one-week COVID-19 lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  World Faces Longer Supply Shortage as Factories Squeezed...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-faces-longer-supply-shortage-002059342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Eric Li’s factory making glass lampshades for companies including Home Depot Inc. is being stretched to its limits with sales doubling their pre-pandemic level.But like many Chinese manufacturers, he doesn’t plan to expand operations -- a reticence that could slow the pace of China’s economic growth this year and prolong a shortage of goods being felt around the world as demand picks up.Surging prices of raw materials means “margins are compressed,” explains Li, owner of Huizhou Baizhan Glass Co. Ltd., in the southern Chinese province of Guangdong, which makes about $30 million in annual revenue. With the global economic recovery still uneven, “the future is very unclear, so there is not much push to expand capacity,” he adds.The combination of higher input prices, uncertainty about export prospects and a weak recovery in domestic consumer demand meant Chinese manufacturing investment from January to April was 0.4% below the same period in 2019, according to official statistics (comparing to 2019 strips out the distortion of last year’s pandemic data).Due to the vast size of China’s manufacturing sector, that poses a risk both to the nation’s growth -- which is currently predicted to reach 8.5% in 2021, according to a Bloomberg tally of economists’ estimates -- and to a global economy that’s grappling with supply shortages and rising prices.Falling ProfitsWeaker-than-expected investment could have a “sizable” impact on GDP growth this year, said Citigroup Inc.’s China economist, Li-gang Liu. Lower investment may dent imports of capital goods and equipment from developed economies like Japan and Germany, “which in turn could drag their economic recovery and rebound as well,” he added.AnHui HERO Electronic Sci &amp; Tec Co. Ltd. is one of those companies feeling the squeeze. Based in the eastern province of Anhui, the company manufactures capacitors used to make electronic circuits, with sales mainly in the domestic market. Jing Yuan, the founder, says orders are up as much as 30% year-on-year, but profits are down 50% due to increasing materials costs that are not easily passed onto clients.The company is under “huge cash pressure” as it needs to pay half a month in advance of delivery in order to secure copper and other metals, which they previously paid for months after receiving, he said. “The commodity issue has to be addressed by the government,” he added.What Bloomberg Economics Says...Chinese industry is absorbing significant cost pressures from rising commodity prices -- damping the inflationary impact for the rest of the world. Will it last? Our analysis of gross margins suggests it could for a while longer: downstream industries -- where the cost crunch is most severe -- still have a small cushion.David Qu, China economistFor the full report, click here.Input shortages mean some manufacturers aren’t able to make use of their existing facilities, so expansion would be of little use. Chinese electric vehicle maker Nio Inc. suspended production at one of its factories last month, due to a shortage of microchips.Modern Casting Ltd., which makes iron and steel products in Guangdong, issued a note to clients this month saying it would not be able to meet its current orders due to high raw material costs. A member of staff who answered the phone at the company’s office confirmed the note, but declined to give further details.Growth TransitionOn top of the higher input costs, Chinese companies face a bumpy transition toward domestic consumer spending to sustain its post-pandemic recovery.Exports, China’s strong-suit last year, may begin to slow as vaccine roll-outs cause consumers in wealthy countries to shift spending back to services. Meanwhile, the growth rate of Chinese consumer spending has yet to fully recover.Investment sentiment among Chinese small and medium-sized enterprises is below levels seen even in 2018-9 when uncertainties from the U.S.-China trade war were a brake on expansion plans, according to a regular survey of more than 500 Chinese companies by Standard Chartered Plc.“Demand is still mainly underpinned by exports, so domestic companies are aware that this is not sustainable,” said Standard Chartered’s China economist, Lan Shen.While some export-oriented sectors have been pushed to their limits, large amounts of slack remain for manufacturers targeting Chinese consumers due to subdued domestic demand.Retail sales growth was 4.3% in April on a two-year average basis, which strips out base effects from the pandemic, less than half pre-pandemic growth rates. Overall capacity use at China’s manufacturers fell to 77.6% in the first quarter from 78.4% in the previous three months, with the automotive sector hit hardest by overcapacity following three years of declining sales volumes.Even for electric vehicles whose sales are surging, most companies have already built their capacity and will now focus on incremental upgrades. “The majority of the investment has been done,” said Jochen Siebert of JSC Automotive Consulting.China ordered state-owned companies to expand last year, with their investment growth of 5.3% in 2020 from the prior year easily outstripping the 1% increase in private investment. But for a sustainable pick-up in investment, the market, not the state, needs to feel confident.Carsten Holz, an expert on Chinese investment statistics at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, estimates that privately-owned companies have accounted for 87% of manufacturing investment in 2015, the most recent year of available data. They are more sensitive to input costs.“There is a pandemic plus insecurity about future trade given a new U.S. administration, neither of which is conducive to investment that relies on long-term growth prospects,” Holz said.Mixed PoliciesTransport bottlenecks are also a challenge for export-oriented manufacturers. Gordon Gao, who exports gardening products from China, said that he has had to reject 80% of orders this year due to port delays. In one case, an order placed before mid-February could only be shipped three months later when a client finally secured a container.Beijing has tried to improve conditions for private companies by ordering a crackdown on speculation to curb commodity prices and easing access to bank loans.Yet the government continues to gradually withdraw fiscal and monetary stimulus measures introduced amid the pandemic last year. It set a relatively unambitious target of “above 6%” growth for this year, and the Communist Party’s Politburo signaled last month it would prioritize reforms to control house prices and debt growth.“The policy stance has definitely shifted away from supporting growth and back toward de-risking the financial sector,” said Adam Wolfe, an economist at London-based Absolute Strategy Research. “The risks for economic growth seem tilted to the downside, especially for capital-intensive, construction-linked sectors.”For manufacturers such as Li, a longer period of domestic growth and control over input prices will be needed before capacity expansion is on the cards. While his company of 200 workers took on new permanent staff before the pandemic, for now he’d rather pass the risks of investment on to others.“I wouldn’t do that now, I would rather hire some temporary workers and outsource the rest,” he said.More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile rolls out mobility pass for vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chile-loosen-restrictions-those-vaccinated-against-covid-19-2021-05-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chileans fully vaccinated against COVID-19 will be allowed to move more freely within the country, the government said on Monday, although the nation's borders will remain closed through mid-June to tamp down a fresh spike in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite controversy, Chris Cuomo secure at CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/with-his-star-status-secure-at-cnn-chris-cuomo-skirts-controversy-again/ar-AAKpInA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although some colleagues privately gripe about his involvement in his brother’s politics, the prime-time host remains a ratings star — and a favorite of CNN President Jeff Zucker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Public transit worker fatally shot 8, then killed himself at San Jose rail yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/public-transit-worker-fatally-shot-8-then-killed-himself-at-san-jose-rail-yard-authorities-say/ar-AAKposP?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooter was a Valley Transportation Association employee, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos assures shareholders they're in good hands at final meeting as CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/jeff-bezos-final-shareholder-meeting-as-amazon-ceo-highlights-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos on Wednesday capped off his last shareholder meeting as CEO of Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral candidate shot dead after sharing her location on FACEBOOK Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mayoral-candidate-shot-dead-mexico-24193982</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alma Barragán, 61, was shot dead in Mexico's most dangerous state after she revealed her location to the killers during a Facebook Live video while campaigning to become mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Throws Down With Jamie Dimon Over Bank Fees...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/bunch-of-baloney-elizabeth-warren-throws-down-with-jamie-dimon-over-chase-raking-in-massive-overdraft-fees-during-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) got into a heated showdown with the man who is, arguably, the banking industry's most well-known figure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin rules out making it compulsory...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210526-putin-rules-out-compulsory-coronavirus-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin rules out compulsory coronavirus vaccinations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALDEN puts stamp on TRIBUNE with new debt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-a1ddfd98054a1e77175cf62fec4d2718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hedge fund Alden Global Capital closed its deal for Tribune on Monday. It wasted little time installing new leadership and saddling the newspaper chain with $278 million in debt it took on for the acquisition, according to regulatory filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Execs sent to white male reeducation camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/lockheed-martin-put-executives-through-training-to-unlearn-white-male-privilege-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consulting firm claims that the ‘roots of white male culture’ include traits such as ‘a can-do-attitude’ and ‘hard work.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA cuts million$ from LAPD...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-cut-millions-lapd-george-120039767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year after George Floyd's murder, the L.A. City Council finalized a plan to spend $90 million on communities of color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcetti picked for ambassador to India...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/biden-picks-l-a-mayor-garcetti-as-ambassador-to-india-source-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is expected to announce he is nominating former senior State Department official Nicholas Burns to serve as his ambassador to China and Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti to be his…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federer on Retirement -- and Becoming Switzerland's New Tourism Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/roger-federer-retirement-wimbledon-switzerland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We kind of thought he already was Switzerland's tourism ambassador?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors investigating Trump tell witness to prepare for grand jury testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/26/politics/donald-trump-grand-jury/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan prosecutors pursuing a criminal case against former President Donald Trump, his company and its executives have told at least one witness to prepare for grand jury testimony, according to a person familiar with the matter -- a signal that the lengthy investigation is moving into an advanced stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKHEED's Woke-Industrial Complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/lockheed-martins-woke-industrial-complex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s largest defense contractor sends key executives on a mission to deconstruct their “white male privilege.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION CARNAGE: 88 Mexican politicians, political candidates murdered since September...</title>
      <link>https://www.telesurenglish.net/news/Mexico-Moroleon-Mayoral-Candidate-Shot-to-Death-20210526-0005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telesurenglish.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eighty-eight politicians have been murdered since the start of the electoral process in Sep. 2020.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz sues NETFLIX over documentary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-dershowitz-netflix-epstein-documentary-20210526-xz3vphyypjcs7jhjn4gog6rb6e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alan Dershowitz sued Netflix Wednesday over a Jeffrey Epstein documentary that he says bolstered “false allegations of sexual misconduct.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture of Fear at Firm Managing Bill Gates' Fortune...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/a-culture-of-fear-at-the-firm-that-manages-bill-gatess-fortune/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 27 years, Bill Gates has entrusted the management of his enormous wealth and the endowment of his giant foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee opened fire during union meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9621739/Police-respond-active-shooter-California-light-rail-yard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman - identified as Samuel Cassidy - opened fire a little before 7am local time at the yard. The victims include Valley Transportation Authority employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI emotion-detection software tested on Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57101248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A software engineer tells BBC's Panorama about installing the system in police stations in Xinjiang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM's newest vehicle: Off-road, self-driving rover for moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-moon-technology-business-science-e38637dc941374e20c352707e9005300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — General Motors is teaming up with Lockheed Martin to produce the ultimate off-road, self-driving, electric vehicles — for the moon. The project announced Wednesday is still in the early stages and has yet to score any NASA money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein 'recruiters, lovers' set to testify against Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2963403/jeffrey-epstein-recruiters-lovers-pals-testify-ghislaine-maxwell-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s recruiters, lovers and pals are reportedly set to testify against Ghislaine Maxwell in her sex trafficking trial. Prosecutors in Maxwell’s trial said that material wil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conwomen trick 19 men into fake marriages, steal $312,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/people-culture/gender-diversity/article/3134919/wedding-scam-china-sees-two-conwomen-allegedly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Against a backdrop of more single men than women, a group of men in rural China have allegedly been conned by two women with and fake relatives in a wedding scam that netted US$312,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver nearly runs over workers giving shots, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-vaccines-driver-nearly-runs-175234558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was yelling “no vaccines” as she sped through, witnesses said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baton to pass to new CEO July 5...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amazoncom-inc-jeff-bezos-business-0c901587710e5b3bea3447781137f1c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Amazon founder Jeff Bezos has picked a date to step down as CEO. Bezos, who grew Amazon from an internet bookstore to an online shopping behemoth, said Wednesday that Amazon executive Andy Jassy will take over the CEO role on July 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAMAS:  We have 10,000 terrorists within Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/hamass-sinwar-we-have-10000-terrorists-within-israel-669265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinwar claimed that Hamas has over 500 km of tunnels in Gaza and that not even 5% of the tunnels were damaged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: As Many As 7 Killed In Mass Shooting At CA Light Rail Facility...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/san-jose-vta-rail-yard-mass-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee opened fire in a mass shooting at a Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority light rail facility in San Jose that left eight victims dead and multiple others wounded. The incident was connected to a separate house fire in the city at around the same time of the shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media's lab leak fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://www.slowboring.com/p/the-medias-lab-leak-fiasco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.slowboring.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge fuckup, with perhaps not-so-huge policy stakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme stocks pop again as speculative trading ramps back up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/meme-stocks-gamestop-amc-are-popping-again-as-speculative-trading-ramps-back-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meme stocks have rallied double digits this week as enthusiastic investors piled back into speculative assets with the market near record highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate activists win EXXON board seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/engine-no-1-gets-at-least-2-candidates-elected-to-exxons-board-in-win-for-the-activist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New GB NEWS channel announces June launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-57252833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new network will feature shows hosted by Andrew Neil, Simon McCoy and Kirsty Gallacher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theatres promise to only cast trans actors in trans roles...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2021/may/26/uk-theatres-promise-to-only-cast-trans-actors-in-trans-roles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trans casting statement signatories pledge to cast trans, non-binary and gender non-conforming performers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of bizarre MLB injuries grows when pitcher breaks thumb while removing shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/esports/list-of-bizarre-mlb-injuries-grows-when-cleveland-pitcher-breaks-thumb-while-removing-shirt/ar-AAKoUx7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zach Plesac was “rather aggressively ripping off his shirt” when it got snagged on a locker room chair, said Indians Manager Terry Francona, placing the 26-year-old starter in quite the club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With most Trump appointees fired from fine arts commission, Biden to put progressive stamp on federal architecture...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-most-trump-appointees-off-the-fine-arts-commission-biden-can-put-a-progressive-stamp-on-federal-architecture/ar-AAKozSA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New appointments give the design group more diversity. This administration should also expand its purpose and scope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  The Don intervened to stop probe of Patriots' Spygate scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31484993/son-ghostwriter-late-senator-say-trump-intervened-stop-probe-patriots-spygate-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the enduring mysteries of Spygate is the identity of the person who reached out to Sen. Arlen Specter to coax him into dropping his Senate probe. Now the late Specter's son and ghostwriter have come forward with a name: Donald J. Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentines Expect Inflation to Hit 50% in Next Year...</title>
      <link>https://batimes.com.ar/news/economy/poll-shows-argentines-expect-inflation-to-hit-50-in-the-next-year.phtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;batimes.com.ar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Heartland Cities Are the Fast-Growing Immigration Hubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/american-heartland-cities-are-the-fast-growing-immigration-hubs/ar-AAKp0xD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities in the U.S. heartland have turned into hubs for immigration, a new study shows, helping in some cases to reverse generations of declining birthrates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Own Trump's 'APPRENTICE' Tapes?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/is-jeff-bezos-about-to-own-trumps-scandalous-apprentice-tapes-colbert-makes-the-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon officially signed an agreement to acquire film studio Metro Goldwyn Mayer (MGM), and Stephen Colbert has some guesses as to why Jeff Bezos agreed to pay the hefty $8.45 billion sum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner: Kardashians NOT producing gubernatorial bid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/555511-caitlyn-jenner-my-family-not-involved-whatsoever-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner says she doesn't want her famous family to be involved "whatsoever" in her California gubernatorial bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Bishop Robbed At Gunpoint During Afternoon Rosary Walk...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/25/oakland-catholic-bishop-michael-barber-robbed-gunpoint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic Bishop of Oakland was robbed over the weekend at gunpoint as he was on his afternoon walk, saying his rosary, near the Paramount Theater, church officials confirmed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEIR WE GO AGAIN:  Oprah and Harry team for more spillage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15074397/prince-harry-oprah-apple-tv-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry and Oprah are set for ANOTHER Apple+ show on Friday – days after the explosive release of their documentary. Viewers can expect more “truth bombs” as the pair discuss…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitt granted joint custody of kids with Angelina after NASTY trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2961808/brad-pitt-granted-joint-custody-kids-angelina-jolie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAD Pitt and Angelina Jolie have reportedly been awarded joint custody of their five kids. The decision comes after the Hollywood exes have been duking it out in a nasty custody battle over the la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP GRAND JURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutor-in-trump-criminal-probe-convenes-grand-jury-to-hear-evidence-weigh-potential-charges/ar-AAKnuWB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move by Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus R. Vance Jr. suggests his investigation of the former president’s business has entered an advanced stage after more than two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate MCDONALD'S giving away iPhones to find workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/a-mcdonalds-is-so-desperate-for-workers-it-is-giving-away-iphones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McDonald’s restaurant in Illinois is offering iPhones to try to attract new workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning photos show Super Moon dazzling skies around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9619899/Supermoon-obscured-clouds-graces-night-sky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This month's full moon is a Super Moon, as the moon is at its closest point to Earth in its orbit of the planet. Pictures from the UK, Turkey, US and more have been shared showing the stunning phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change may allow scientists to grow human embryos longer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-science-health-cfa61338240a926e8748c9a4d8b074ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — New guidelines released Wednesday remove a decades-old barrier to stem cell research, recommending that researchers be allowed to grow human embryos longer under limited conditions.  The “14-day rule,” an international ethical standard that limits laboratory studies of human embryos, has been in place for decades and has been written into law in countries including Britain and Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New American status symbol: Backyard that's basically fancy living room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/the-new-american-status-symbol-a-backyard-that-s-basically-a-fancy-living-room/ar-AAKoEd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outdoor rugs, TVs, day beds and $5,500 lamps: Welcome to the Great Fauxdoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resistance to vax mandates building. Powerful network helping...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/resistance-to-vaccine-mandates-is-building-a-powerful-network-is-helping/ar-AAKp8jm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York firm has filed suit or sent letters to employers in several states, part of an effort spearheaded by one of the largest anti-vaccination groups in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Warner, GOP Senate stalwart with air of glamour, dies at 94...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/john-warner-gop-senate-stalwart-with-air-of-glamour-dies-at-94/ar-AAKp3Ua</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Warner, a Republican who represented Virginia in the U.S. Senate for 30 years and brought to Washington a rare aura of glamour including a marriage to actress Elizabeth Taylor, has died. He was 94.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rx for pain relief: 30 mins with a story...</title>
      <link>https://californianewstimes.com/rx-for-pain-relief-30-minutes-with-a-story/360520/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californianewstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you know or have children suffering from a pandemic turmoil, there may be a way to avoid using medications to relieve their pain and stress: read the story to them. Brazilian scientists who studied the effects of storytelling and Riddle-based games on children admitted to the intensive care unit found that stories lower stress …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent Fasting May Improve Long-Term Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intermittent fasting (IF) is becoming a common practice among dieters trying to burn fat and lose weight, but a new study finds it may hold cognitive benefits as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope kisses Auschwitz tattoo of Holocaust survivor...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/pope-francis-kisses-auschwitz-tattoo-of-polish-survivor-of-holocaust-01622035723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lidia Maksymowicz showed the pope the number tattooed on her arm by the Nazis, and Francis leaned over and kissed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Raises Heat on TWITTERGOOGLEFACEBOOK in Online Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/russia-raises-heat-on-twitter-google-and-facebook-in-online-crackdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Russia is increasingly pressuring Google, Twitter and Facebook to fall in line with Kremlin internet crackdown orders or</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
