<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL GANGLAND: Platforms used to fan violence, protect turf...</title>
      <link>https://chicagotonight.wttw.com/2018/06/12/new-chicago-gang-book-highlights-rise-factions-social-media-use</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicagotonight.wttw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Crime Commission on Tuesday published its first new Gang Book in six years. In it, they examine the new and changing trends and issues within gang culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How gangs use socials to fan violence, protect turf...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/social-media-fanning-chicago-gang-violence-study-225350603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media interactions are playing a "significant" role in fanning violence in Chicago, the American city with the highest murder rate, a study found Tuesday. The Chicago Crime Commission found that many of the more than 100,000 gang members in the Midwestern city are engaged in regular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Dem Identity Politics View Appears Cynical...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/06/12/the-democratic-partys-2018-view-of-identity-politics-is-confusing-and-thus-appears-cynical-and-opportunistic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given its rhetoric, how does the party justify supporting white male machine politicians over credible female challengers, LGBT people, and people of color?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bees -- understand the concept of zero...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1302703/bees-understand-the-concept-of-zero-or-nothingness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans have flattered ourselves, thinking we're the only ones that understand the concept of zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Backs Obamacare Coverage of Pre-Existing Illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/mcconnell-backs-obamacare-s-coverage-of-pre-existing-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after the Trump administration chose not to defend Obamacare’s protections for people with pre-existing medical conditions in court, Republican leaders are hoping the lawsuit doesn’t undo one of the most popular parts of the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATIONS ORDERED...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/crews-battling-brush-fire-near-beverly-glen-homes-threatened</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are battling a brush fire in the Beverly Crest area, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Senator Used Private Plane During 'RV Tour'...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/claire-mccaskills-private-plane-used-on-campaigns-rv-tour-through-missouri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Claire McCaskill said her campaign was "hitting the road" in an RV, but public flight information indicates travel also occurred on her private plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVERLY HILLS FIRE THREATENS CELEB HOMES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/fire-homes-benedict-canyon-beverly-hills-celebrities-1202843597/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-burning brush fire is threatening the Beverly Crest area near Benedict Canyon, the location of numerous multi-million dollar mansions. KTTV reported that the fire was at 20 acres. LAFD spoke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATIONS EXPECTED... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://ktla.com/2018/06/12/brush-fire-burning-in-beverly-crest-area-in-west-l-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 10-acre brush fire was threatening homes in the Beverly Crest area in West Los Angeles on Tuesday afternoon, officials said.  An unknown number of homes were under "immediate threat" on both flanks of the blaze, south of Yoakum Drive and north of Portal Drive, according to the L.A. Fire Department. The fire was moving toward Benedict Canyon Drive, the agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Tigers Living in USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-44444016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US has more captive tigers than the rest of the world has wild ones. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues NASA for ownership of space dust, claims gift fom Neil Armstrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2018/06/12/nasa_space_dust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theregister.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She claims it was gift from Apollo veteran Neil Armstrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to boost US Marines in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/06/12/the-corps-plans-to-boost-the-number-of-marines-in-norway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three hundred additional Marines currently in Romania will beef up the Corps' rotation in Norway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Member Calls Bernie Supporter Who Attended DNC Meetings 'Russian Plant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/news/politics/dnc-member-calls-wv-sanders-supporter-a-russian-plant/article_52830d46-3ceb-53f0-8578-a155d74ce2b7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selina Vickers' weekend trip to Rhode Island was as cheap as she could make it. She shelled out $143.60 for a train ticket from her home in West Virginia to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERGER MANIA INTENSIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/at-t-time-warner-merger-approval-opens-floodgates-big-media-deals-1119374</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Time Warner instantly rose 5 percent after the closing bell the moment the news broke, while shares of AT&amp;T fell 1 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/att-time-warner-ruling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Time Warner jumped roughly 5 percent in extended trading. Shares of AT&amp;T dropped as much as 2 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CONDITIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/at-t-cleared-by-judge-to-buy-time-warner-create-media-giant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Inc. was cleared by a judge to take over Time Warner Inc. in an $85 billion deal that the mobile-phone giant says will fuel its evolution into a media powerhouse that can go head-to-head with Netflix Inc. and Amazon.com Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDDING WAR FOR FOX BEGINS; CBS NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-time-warner-m-a-at-t/att-wins-u-s-court-approval-to-buy-time-warner-for-85-billion-idUSKBN1J82QX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Inc won approval from a U.S. court on Tuesday to buy Time Warner Inc for $85 billion, without conditions, allowing AT&amp;T to compete with internet companies that dominate digital advertising and providing new sources of revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOW TO JUSTICE DEPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/judge-is-set-to-decide-whether-at-t-and-time-warner-can-merge-1528832942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge ruled AT&amp;T can proceed with its planned acquisition of Time Warner Inc., rejecting the Justice Department’s allegations that the deal would suppress competition in the pay-TV industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Kim claim big summit success, but details are scant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2d80cb7d512c49978e69853a7daa4d5c/Trump,-Kim-claim-big-summit-success,-but-details-are-scant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — Claiming success at their whirlwind summit, President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un left Singapore Tuesday, praising their face-to-face progres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Michael Cohen expects to be arrested soon...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-news-trump-michael-cohen-arrested-any-day-20180612-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's legal bulldog expects to land behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Americans arming themselves to stay alive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/12/gay-americans-are-arming-themselves-to-stay-alive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t want to get beaten to death, stabbed and burnt alive,” a slight woman with long blond hair and a checked shirt says. “I want a gun to feel equal.” She is a member of one of the Unite…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charm offensive overshadows rights abuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kim-charm-offensive-overshadows-n-korea-rights-abuses-092137476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un's charm offensive and his historic summit with US President Donald Trump have overshadowed a more sinister side of his regime -- widespread human rights abuses, activists say. The meeting in Singapore offered a dramatic image makeover for Kim, previously known for his apocalyptic threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/att-time-warner-decision-effects-on-telecoms-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire U.S. telecommunications industry is anxiously awaiting Judge Richard Leon's decision on whether AT&amp;T can buy Time Warner. Here is how the major companies in the industry could be affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller worries Russia could use case to spy on probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-worries-russia-could-court-case-spy-probe-193320299--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller's team is worried that Russian intelligence services will use a criminal case in Washington to gather information about its investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Budget Deficit Widens; Weak Revenue...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-federal-budget-deficit-widened-in-first-eight-months-of-fiscal-2018-1528826767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government’s budget deficit widened in the first eight months of its fiscal year as spending rose faster than revenues compared with the same period a year earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada looks to ride out Trump trade storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/canada-looks-ride-trump-trade-storm-181639548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada moved to tamp down spiking tensions with the United States Tuesday, brushing aside a warning by US President Donald Trump that it will pay for Justin Trudeau's G7 summit remarks. "If the US decides to apply new tariffs, Canada will be ready," the official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless accused of having sex beneath Virgin Mary statue... </title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/news/crime/jersey-mayhem/2018/06/12/seaside-heights-homeless-woman-denies-church-sex/694671002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noelle Smart, 48, pleaded not guilty to lewdness and three other charges on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alligator On Runway Stops Flights At Florida Airport...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/06/12/alligator-flight-stopped-alligator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers on a Spirit Airlines flight probably weren't expecting to hear that an alligator was keeping them from getting to their destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO school nurses can dispense marijuana...</title>
      <link>http://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article213001539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third-grade student Quintin Lovato uses medical marijuana to help with his seizures. He inspired Colorado lawmakers to sign a bill that allows school nurses to administer the medicine to students who qualify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May offers rebels HUGE concession paving way for SOFT Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/973124/eu-withdrawal-bill-vote-live-updates-brexit-news-debate-latest-theresa-may-philip-lee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May's Brexit plans have been plunged into uncertainty after she offered Tory rebels a huge concession as MPs voted on the EU Withdrawal Bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Mistakenly Wires $93K To Cyberscammer...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/11/state-agency-wires-public-funds-to-cyberscammer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts Clean Energy Center mistakenly wired $93,679 in public funds to a criminal’s bank account, according to the state auditor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE PRAISES...</title>
      <link>https://www.vermontbiz.com/news/2018/june/12/sanders-statement-trump-kim-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vermontbiz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Business Magazine Senator Bernie Sanders (I-Vermont) issued the following statement Tuesday following President Trump and Kim Jong Un's meeting in Singapore: "While very light on substance, the meeting between President Trump and Kim Jong Un in Singapore represents a positive step in de-escalating tensions between our countries..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS UNVEILS 'NORTHERN BORDER STRATEGY'...</title>
      <link>http://www.newsweek.com/dhs-announces-strengthened-northern-border-strategy-amid-growing-tensions-973115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The updated Northern Border Strategy’s release comes just days after President Donald Trump announced steel, aluminum and auto tariffs on its northern ally, citing a “national security” threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared to Israel, Egypt and Saudi for peace talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/kushner-travel-to-israel-egypt-saudi-arabia-for-peace-plan-talks-0c65acf3-aeb3-4aa7-9674-699de36168e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's peace plan is almost ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force boosts nuke sniffer aircraft fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2018/06/12/us-to-boost-nuke-sniffing-with-modified-c-130s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force doesn't have too many WC-135 Constant Phoenix. Enter the ever-versatile Hercules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass layoffs at TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/tesla-to-cut-about-9-percent-of-jobs-across-company-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt workers told to leave work, attend Stanley Cup parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.govexec.com/pay-benefits/2018/06/white-house-tells-agencies-give-dc-area-feds-time-during-capitals-stanley-cup-parade/148910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.govexec.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPM also authorizes agencies to allow employees to telework or take other flexibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half of Millennials expect to be millionaires...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5835419/More-half-Millennials-expect-millionaires-someday-according-new-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that 53 percent of Millennials (like multi-millionaire cosmetics mogul Kylie Jenner, pictured) believe they will one day be millionaires. Despite that, 25 percent say they'll never marry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation to change name to please neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/06/12/greece-reaches-deal-macedonia-name-dispute/694727002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Macedonia’s independence from Yugoslavia in 1991, Greece has argued that the young country’s name implied a claim to the territory and ancient heritage of Greece’s northern region of Macedonia – birthplace of ancient warrior king Alexander the Great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Confronted at Book Signing About Groping Women...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/biden-confronted-at-book-signing-about-groping-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charitable giving in USA tops $400 billion for first time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/84a9d91f4ff749398dd634dc10ff5938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fueled by a surging stock market and huge gifts from billionaires, charitable giving in the United States in 2017 topped the $400 billion mark for the first time,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flies home with lots to brag about...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0acd517d8f94b649c3d49bb17238235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — All North Korean leader Kim Jong Un really needed from his unprecedented summit with U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday was to keep his nuclear a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians fear for safety as threats skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/11/politicians-fear-for-safety-as-threats-against-congress-skyrocket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Rep. Barry Loudermilk of Georgia bought body armor. Rep. Gregg Harper hired armed security guards for events back home in Mississippi. And Rep. Dan Dovonan fortified his Brooklyn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia building 'laser cannon' death ray...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/11/russia-building-space-gun-laser-death-ray-terrifying-sounds-7621352/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Putin soon have the ability to wage space war using a massive new laser weapon?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's unlikely allies on  talks --  progressive Dems!</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article212960759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump found an unlikely source of support as he meets with North Korea leader Kim Jong-un: Democrats. Some of the same Democrats who complain that he stole the election and want to impeach him praise him for engaging in diplomacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Summit produced less than many analysts expected...</title>
      <link>http://www.courant.com/nation-world/ct-la-summit-assessment-20180612-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The much-hyped summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un produces little guidance for real de-nuclearization or other steps to pacify the Korean peninsula. Instead, it offers much of what failed in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/high-stakes-ruling-awaited-t-time-warner-merger-142911568.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-stakes decision in a US court Tuesday will be significant for the future of Big Media, Big Tech and big business in general. A US federal judge was set to announce his verdict in the $85 billion merger of wireless and broadband giant AT&amp;T with media-entertainment conglomerate Time Warner. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch anti-Islam party to hold Prophet Mohammad cartoon competition...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/dutch-anti-islam-party-hold-prophet-mohammad-cartoon-151742746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom Party of Dutch anti-Islam politician Geert Wilders will hold a competition of cartoons depicting the Prophet Mohammad, it said on Tuesday. The party said the plan to hold the competition in the party's secure offices in Dutch Parliament had been approved by the Dutch Counter-terrorism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGIN:  BIGGEST WINNER IS CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/josh-rogin/wp/2018/06/12/the-biggest-winner-of-the-trump-kim-summit-is-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has conceded to Beijing's plan for diplomacy, and he gave Xi Jinping lots of other gifts as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK denies building eye-tracking software...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/facebook-denies-building-eye-tracking-software.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook holds at least two patents for detecting eye movements and emotions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle reverses course on business tax after AMAZON pressure...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/391807-seattle-reverses-course-on-business-tax-after-amazon-pressure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just weeks after passing a new tax on big businesses, Seattle political l</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN WARNS KIM</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa-iran/iran-tells-north-korea-trump-could-cancel-deal-before-getting-home-idUSKBN1J813Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran warned North Korean leader Kim Jong Un on Tuesday against trusting U.S. President Donald Trump, saying he could cancel their denuclearization agreement within hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does God look like? Liberals and conservatives have very different ideas...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article213001044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group of psychologists at UNC Chapel Hill have created an image of what God might look like, based on a survey of 511 American Christians. Results showed politics plays a role in the image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning algorithm predicts GERMANY will win World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611397/machine-learning-predicts-world-cup-winner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have predicted the outcome after simulating the entire soccer tournament 100,000 times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Seeks to Store Data in Human DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/06/intelligence-community-wants-use-dna-store-exabytes-data/148908/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IC is exploring whether polymers could be the future of data storage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC CHAIR: CASE FOR 'FREE AND OPEN' INTERNET...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/fcc-chairman-our-job-is-to-protect-a-free-and-open-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commentary: Ajit Pai says the Restoring Internet Freedom Order, which takes effect Monday, protects consumers and will promote better access to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic summit ends with promise...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180612125139-rderz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (WRAPUP 19, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 19-Historic Trump-Kim summit ends with promise, light on substance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump surprises with pledge to end military exercises in South Korea...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180612122635-i9b02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/MILITARY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Trump surprises with pledge to end military exercises in South Korea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report describes Dubai real estate as money-laundering haven...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/report-describes-dubai-real-estate-050614824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — War profiteers, terror financiers and drug traffickers sanctioned by the U.S. in recent years have used Dubai's real-estate market as a haven for their assets, a new report released Tuesday alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pledge to Halt Military Exercises Surprises Pentagon, Seoul...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/12/world/asia/trump-military-exercises-north-south-korea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials, experts and allies warned that Mr. Trump’s promise to end military exercises on the Korean Peninsula could hurt combat readiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lottery winner stabbed to death inside home...</title>
      <link>http://abc7ny.com/$10k-lotto-winner-73-found-fatally-stabbed-in-neck/3592750/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owen Dillard, 73, lived in his apartment for years, according to neighbors, and he was well-known and loved in this community in Mott Haven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI: 10,000 jobs could be lost to robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.finextra.com/newsarticle/32240/10000-jobs-could-be-lost-to-robots-says-citi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.finextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US bank Citi has warned that it could shed half of its 20,000 tech and ops staff in the next five years due to the rise of robotics and automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror, hooligan threats cast shadow over Russia's World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/terror--hooligan-threats-cast-shadow-over-russia-s-world-cup-10423988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathalyzer Aims to Predict Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/06/12/this-breathalyzer-aims-to-predict-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Breathalyzer Aims to Predict Cancer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like Animals, Plants Also Camouflage Selves For Protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/plants-camouflage-animals-protection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plants may appear still and lifeless to a degree, but they're far craftier than you might believe. A new study finds that many plants use the same camouflage strategies as animals to avoid damage and protect themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying moment bison charges straight at photographer...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5834467/Terrifying-moment-bison-charges-straight-photographer-Yellowstone-National-Park.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just seconds before being charged by a raging bison bull, Willis Chung, 56, took this epic photograph of the beast sizing him up before running in his direction, causing the physician from Denver to leave his gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with 'world's biggest penis' constantly stopped at airport security...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6504682/jonah-falcon-worlds-biggest-penis-sex-a-listers-ruined-acting-career/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ACTOR who claims to have the world’s biggest “natural” penis says it has helped him bed A-listers and Oscar winners – but ruined his own career. In an exclusive interview with Sun Online, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Half human, half dog': 7ft beast leaves man TERRIFIED after savaging his pet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/709097/Mysterious-beast-dogman-leaves-man-terrified-savaging-dog-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation at Six-Year High, Eating Away at Wage Increases...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/u-s-inflation-at-six-year-high-eating-away-at-wage-increases </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. inflation accelerated in May to the fastest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Fined $22,500 -- For Chopping Down Own Tree...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/11/chopping-down-trees-fines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The homeowner says the trees were a danger to his family and property, but local officials say he didn't go through proper channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students clean up act as they turn down drugs to focus on studies...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/06/11/students-clean-act-turn-illegal-drugs-focus-studies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students are no longer dabbling in drugs at university because they are now &amp;ldquo;more hardworking&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;less hedonistic&amp;rdquo;, a study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Congress continues with primary elections in five states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/11/maine-nevada-north-dakota-south-carolina-and-virginia-hold-midterm-primary-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters will pick challengers in several battleground House elections as well as two of the most hotly contested Senate races in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico candidate shot while posing for selfie as killings of politicians continue...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/12/mexico-election-politicians-killed-fernando-puron-selfie </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country braces for further bloodshed as Fernando Purón said to be 112th political candidate killed since September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Tightens Grip on Internet With Data-Storage Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/vietnam-tightens-grip-on-internet-with-data-storage-law-1528799753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vietnam adopted a cybersecurity law that requires internet companies such as Facebook and Google to store their Vietnam-based users’ data on servers in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 boys, no regrets: Michigan family happy the way they are...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/14-boys-no-regrets-michigan-family-happy-way-050832669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEVIEW, Mich. (AP) — A Michigan couple have 14 boys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police question Netanyahu in telecom case for third time...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/police-netanyahu-telecom-case-third-080322123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli police are questioning Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu as part of an investigation into a corruption case involving the country's telecom giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark Head Stuffed With Cigarette Butts Found Impaled On Fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/shark-head-found-impaled-on-australian-fence-1866009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A severed shark head, stuffed with cigarette butts and ocean debris, was found impaled on a fence at an Australian marine rescue organisation's office, with the gruesome discovery drawing criticism on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA BEACH CONDOS, HOTELS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5834437/They-great-beaches-Trump-showed-Kim-iPad-video-North-Koreas-future.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump said part of his hard sell to Kim Jong-un about giving up his nuclear weapons was a video that showed the economic benefits of shaking off the chains of near-global economic sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I DO TRUST HIM'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/exclusive-trust-trump-opens-kim-historic-summit/story?id=55815265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview, ABC News George Stephanopoulos spoke to President Donald Trump about his historic meeting with Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sits down with Stephanopoulos...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/president-trump-sits-george-stephanopoulos-transcript/story?id=55831055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump sat down for an exclusive one-on-one with ABC News chief anchor George Stephanopoulos after the president's summit with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un on Tuesday in Singapore. Among a host of topics, Trump said he trusts Kim to follow through on his pledge to denuclearize,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landlords Practically Giving Malls Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/owners-of-fading-malls-on-their-knees-as-buyer-pool-evaporates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landlords have malls they’d like to unload. But who’d want to buy them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denuclearization details scant...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2018/06/12/asia-pacific/politics-diplomacy-asia-pacific/kim-trump-set-meet-one-one-first-ever-u-s-north-korean-leaders-summit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a vaguely worded agreement signed at their unprecedented summit Tuesday in Singapore, U.S. President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for somebody? Dems lack heir apparent this time...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/391737-ready-for-somebody-dems-lack-heir-apparent-this-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no Ready for Elizabeth super PAC. Nor is there a Prepping for Kamala, Begging for Booker or Salivating for Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ready to write new chapter'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5833959/Were-ready-write-new-chapter-two-nations-Trump-says-Kim-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong-un affirmed an 'unwavering commitment to complete denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula' in a sign document on Tuesday, President Donald Trump says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back-slapping summit legitimizes Kim, say critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/back-slapping-trump-summit-legitimises-kim-critics-094441163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A historic handshake in front of US and North Korean flags, a solemn signing ceremony and back-slapping compliments: critics charge that US President Donald Trump has legitimised Kim Jong Un on the world stage. The photo opportunity the world was waiting to see -- the two leaders clasping hands -- has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces halt to US-SKorea 'war games'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2d80cb7d512c49978e69853a7daa4d5c/After-summit,-Trump-announces-halt-to-US-SKorea-'war-games'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — President Donald Trump and North Korea's Kim Jong Un concluded an extraordinary nuclear summit Tuesday with the U.S. president pledging unspecified "security guar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINGAPORE SMILES!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180612092751-k7ae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (WRAPUP 18, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 18-Trump, Kim agree on denuclearisation, but deal seen symbolic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's hyperinflation at new dizzying high...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuelas-hyperinflation-dizzying-high-210340144.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caracas (AFP) - Venezuela's sky-high inflation soared to 24,571 percent in the past 12 months, lawmakers said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitch McConnell's  Senate reign enters record books...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mitch-mcconnells-us-senate-reign-enters-record-books-013617680.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday, the 76-year-old Kentuckian becomes the longest serving Republican Senate leader ever, surpassing Bob Dole's 11-plus years in charge. It is a remarkable run for a lawmaker with one of the lowest approval ratings in the United States, and all the more impressive given the tumult in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing off with Trump, Trudeau dons cape of 'Captain Canada'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/facing-off-trump-trudeau-dons-cape-captain-canada-203855363.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Normally a conciliatory, charming figure, Justin Trudeau is being forced to transform himself into a kind of "Captain Canada" in order to fight a trade war with Donald Trump that has the potential to be as destructive as it is surprising. "Canadians, we're polite, we're reasonable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After battling Silicon Valley, Pai requires 24-hr security...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fcc-chairman-still-receiving-threats-over-net-neutrality-1528756697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Ajit Pai liberates the Internet, his family still requires 24-hour protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murky U.S. drone-strike policy threatens to backfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/11/us-drone-strike-policy-threatens-backfire-nations-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid proliferation of military drone technology is reaching the point that other nations — and even non-state actors such as Mexican drug cartels — could engage in the kinds of deadly strikes that the U.S. pioneered more than a decade ago and has increased under presidents of both political parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's happiest seaside town: Ocean City, NJ... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2018/06/11/americas-happiest-seaside-town-ocean-city-nj/691495002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Coastal Living" ranks the best small coastal towns for its annual "Happiest Seaside Town in America" issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA: Humans 'absolutely' could live on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/11/could-humans-live-mars-nasa-expert/690476002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans will "absolutely" be in Mars in the future, NASA chief scientist Jim Green told USA TODAY. And, the first person to go is likely living today, he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumb and dumber: Why we're getting less intelligent...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/dumb-and-dumber-why-we-re-getting-less-intelligent-80k3bl83v </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IQ scores of young people have begun to fall after rising steadily since the Second World War, according to the first authoritative study of the phenomenon. The decline, which is equivalent to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT ON THE BRINK?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6505185/the-sun-says-great-britain-brexit-vote-betrayal-leave-remain/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REBEL Tory MPs could today destroy their Prime Minister, their Government and the Brexit the 17.4million majority voted for. A “peace” deal struck last night for 15 knife-edge Commons votes is stil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  CNN TOP NEWS SITE; DRUDGE OVER NYT; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quest of Laurene Powell Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/lifestyle/article/What-does-billionaire-Laurene-Powell-Jobs-want-12985854.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurene Powell Jobs - like the inventors and disrupters who were all around her - was thinking big. It was 2004, and she was an East Coast transplant - sprung from a cage in West Milford, NewJersey, as her musical idol Bruce Springsteen might put it - acclimating to the audacious sense of possibility suffusing the laboratories, garages and office parks of Silicon Valley. She could often be found at a desk in a rented office in Palo Alto, California, working a phone and an Apple computer. There, her own creation was beginning to take shape. It would involve philanthropy . . . technology . . . social change - she was charting the destination as she made the journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSTATE CANCER SALIVA TEST REVOLUTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/lifestyle/health/simple-10-saliva-test-identify-12684555 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A simple saliva test can identify the one in 100 men with a 50% chance of getting the disease and could be offered on the NHS to all men over 40 in a few years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea continues Nazi-style prison camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2016/11/30/asia/north-korea-prison-camps-new-satellite-images/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly-released satellite images show that North Korea's prison camp system may be expanding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUDLOW HEART ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/11/white-house-economic-advisor-larry-kudlow-suffers-heart-attack-trump-tweets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House economic advisor Larry Kudlow suffered a heart attack and is in good condition at Walter Reed Medical Center, the White House said on Monday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  COMCAST bid for FOX coming if AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER  approved...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/11/comcast-announcing-fox-bid-on-wednesday-if-att-time-warner-approved.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast will formalize its all-cash offer for Disney on Wednesday if AT&amp;T's bid for Time Warner is approved Tuesday, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAGARDE: Clouds Over Global Economy Getting Darker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/06/11/lagarde-says-clouds-over-global-economy-are-darker-by-the-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMF’s Lagarde says risks to global economy rising as major industrial nations sharpen threats of a trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elton John condemns social media companies for failing to stem flow of 'hate'... </title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-44421195 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sir Elton John says social media giants should be boycotted if they do not tackle homophobic hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Hurricane targets Mexico... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/major-hurricane-bud-to-target-mexico-with-heavy-rainfall-dangerous-seas-this-week/70005186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddlers eating more sugar than max recommended -- for adults!</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1302201/american-toddlers-are-eating-more-sugar-than-the-amount-recommended-for-adults/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study shows their diet contains more sugar than the maximum amount recommended for adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLINTON: Norms of 'What You Can Do to Someone Against Will' Have Changed...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/bill-clinton-norms-of-what-you-can-do-to-someone-against-their-will-has-changed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Handshake...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-handshake-trump-kim-jong-un-meet-greet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I am very happy to meet you here in Singapore’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia building 'laser cannon' death ray...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/11/russia-building-space-gun-laser-death-ray-terrifying-sounds-7621352/ https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DfcIPT2XkAAzDnZ.jpg </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid gold rush could earn everyone on Earth $100 billion!?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/11/new-asteroid-gold-rush-earn-everyone-earth-75-billion-7622439/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s predicted to create the first trillionaire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body language reveals nerves...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-kim-confident-body-language-reveals-nerves-first-022110411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Sam Holmes and Miral Fahmy SINGAPORE (Reuters) - In their first moments of meeting each other, U.S. President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un both sought to project a sense of command as they began a historic summit in Singapore, according to a body language expert. Karen Leong,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire California ghost town on sale for $1 million...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2018/06/11/for-sale-1-california-ghost.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For sale: (1) California ghost town</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Kim hold historic summit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4a5201ceceb44f896e2e497537ba116/Trump,-Kim-arrive-for-historic-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — President Donald Trump and North Korea's Kim Jong Un came together for a momentous summit Tuesday that could determine historic peace or raise the specter of a gr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voluntarily vagrant, homeless young people put extra strain on liberal cities...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/06/11/voluntarily-vagrant-homeless-youth-crusty-urban-challenge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known by many names – “crusty punks,” “crusties,” gutter punks,” “crumb bums” and “dirty kids,” to list but a few – this group of young adults has rejected a more traditional lifestyle in favor of train hopping, panhandling and voluntary homelessness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's my honor, we will have terrific relationship'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/defense/391749-trump-its-my-honor-to-meet-kim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump predicted he and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un will have a “terrific relationship” as the two leaders started their historic summit in Singapore on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KELLYANNE HUSBAND DEFENDS MUELLER...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/391725-conways-husband-penned-article-defending-constitutionality-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House counselor Kellyanne Conway's husband on Monday released an article defending the constitutionality of special counsel Robert Mueller's probe into alleged ties between the Trump campaign and Russia's election meddling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENNIS RODMAN CRYING;  WEARS MAGA HAT...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/391752-dennis-rodman-weeps-with-joy-over-trump-kim-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA Hall of Famer Dennis Rodman gave an emotional, bizarre TV interview on Tuesday reacting to the highly anticipated summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile launch? Mysterious object over Washington state raises questions...</title>
      <link>http://q13fox.com/2018/06/11/missile-launch-lens-flare-mysterious-object-spotted-over-whidbey-island-raises-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;q13fox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious object was spotted by a local photographer over the skies of Whibey Island early Sunday morning, leading to lots of speculation and questions, but no solid answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: VICE $5.7B Valuation Built On Bluff...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2018/06/inside-vice-media-shane-smith.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For almost 25 years, Shane Smith’s plan was that, by the time the suckers caught on, he’d never be stuck owning the company he co-founded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINGAPORE SMILES!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180612021557-zfi30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (WRAPUP 6, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 6-Trump tells Kim a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope to narrow differences...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180612012523-fz770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (WRAPUP 4, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 4-Trump, Kim meet for historic U.S.-North Korea meeting</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
