<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Millions in South brace for another tornado outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/03/24/severe-storms-tornadoes-forecast-south-thursday/6981342002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several long-track, strong tornadoes, large hail and damaging wind gusts are possible across the South Thursday and Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suez Canal Stays Blocked Despite Efforts to Free Stuck Ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/suez-canal-stays-blocked-despite-efforts-to-free-stuck-ship/ar-BB1eUym8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescue teams are working to dislodge a giant vessel from the Suez Canal in an effort to get traffic moving again in one of the world’s most important waterways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech, Big Cash: Washington's New Power Players...</title>
      <link>https://www.citizen.org/article/big-tech-lobbying-update/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.citizen.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook and Amazon are now the two biggest corporate lobbying spenders in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk announces TESLAs can now be bought with Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90618478/elon-musk-announces-teslas-can-now-be-bought-with-bitcoin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But due to the volatility of bitcoin, a customer could receive “significantly less” than they originally paid if they want a refund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry Texans say 500 migrant youths housed at all-inclusive $33m 'man camp'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9389205/Angry-Texas-residents-tell-Biden-administration-housing-500-migrants-near-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 500 migrant youth are being housed at a 'man camp' in Midland, Texas that was constructed in 2012 to temporarily house workers in the oil industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare sneakers. Bots. Insider connections. This scandal has it all...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rare-sneakers-bots-insider-connections-120016331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Nike executive and her shoe reseller son face the wrath of sneakerheads, who think the shoe game is rigged against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: MEDIUM offers entire editorial staff buyouts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/544699-medium-offers-entire-editorial-staff-buyouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editorial staff at the self-publishing platform Medium are being offered buyouts and its vice president of editorial content is leaving the company as it once again retools its approach to creating its own journalistic content, CEO Ev Williams ann</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'cyclone' of brain fog many long-haulers still experiencing...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/inside-cyclone-brain-fog-covid-19-long-haulers/story?id=76615851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 long-haulers are experiencing a huge litany of symptoms, including potential cognitive and neurological issues like brain fog, memory issues and tremors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59ft tapeworm emerges from man after complained of flatulence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/gigantic-59ft-tapeworm-emerges-mans-23788329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors said the parasite was the longest tapeworm they had seen in Thailand for 50 years. They believed the man had ingested raw beef that contained infected larvae</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens more elephants die under mysterious circumstances in Botswana...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9397581/Botswana-says-preliminary-probe-rules-bacterial-infections-latest-elephants-deaths.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary investigations into the fresh wave of deaths in the Moremi Game Reserve have ruled out anthrax and bacterial infections, Botswana's environment ministry said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg suggests how to tweak tech's liability shield...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/zuckerberg-facebook-section-230-shield-liability-ac9cfb3d-c98d-473b-b80a-722c79e68568.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg wants to make protections for unlawful content conditional on platforms' ability to meet best practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 SCENARIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-election-results-what-comes-next-government-f9c1d51c-f098-4df5-9748-1a64b0894673.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu still has cards left to play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New videos show attack on Officer Sicknick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/544693-new-videos-show-attack-on-officer-brian-sicknick-during-jan-6-riot-nyt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New videos published by The New York Times on Wednesday show the moments that Capitol Police Officer Brian Sicknick was attacked with chemical irritants during the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL ref's career over after hot-mic call on PREDS penalty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nhl-nashville-john-hynes-nashville-predators-viktor-arvidsson-f6a3328aa61ec8adcf4d2ccb0919de67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Tim Peel's career as an NHL referee is over after his voice was picked up by a TV microphone saying he wanted to call a penalty against the Nashville Predators. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of Southern Baptist women question roles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/beth-moore-baptist-southern-baptist-convention-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-sexual-abuse-3e665b36cb35f471598f3491ab10701a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emily Snook is the daughter of a Southern Baptist pastor. She met her husband, also a pastor, while they attended a Southern Baptist university Yet the 39-year-old Oklahoma woman now finds...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First image of black hole gets polarizing update that sheds light on magnetic fields...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/first-black-hole-image-polarized-m87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope cuts salaries for cardinals, clerics in move to save other jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-salaries/pope-orders-salary-cuts-for-cardinals-clerics-to-save-jobs-of-employees-idUSKBN2BG1LG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has ordered cardinals to take a 10% pay cut and reduced the salaries of most other clerics working in the Vatican in order to save jobs of employees as the coronavirus pandemic has hit the Holy See's income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ship-stuck-suez-canal-risks-090032715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It may take days for salvage crew to move the giant container vessel that’s clogging the Suez Canal out of the way, according to two people familiar with the situation.The vessel, Ever Given, is well and truly stuck in the embankment along the canal, according to two people familiar with the situation, who asked not to be identified discussing private details. The ship has been jammed length-ways across the canal early Tuesday in Egypt, leaving at least 100 vessels gridlocked.Salvage efforts have been underway, but at least one attempt to re-float the ship was unsuccessful due to the weight of the ship and small size of the tug boats operated by authorities, the people said. A further attempt is re-float the ship is taking place on Wednesday morning local time, and the ship’s owners are in talks to hire SMIT Salvage B.V. to assist in operations, one of the people said. A spokesperson for SMIT declined to comment.Larger salvage tugs with bigger horsepower may be required to pull the ship -- which has one of the biggest container carrying capacities in the world -- out of the ground, the people said. Images of the stuck vessel showed excavators trying to dig the ship out.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human penises shrinking because of pollution, warns scientist...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/human-penises-are-shrinking-because-of-pollution-warns-scientist-12255106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Shanna Swan has found that chemicals called phthalates are causing human babies to be born with malformed genitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scared To Death? Patients With Serious Diseases Dying From Fear Of COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/patients-dying-from-fear-of-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the same mix of non-COVID inpatients are entering hospitals, these people are much sicker and close to death than in pre-pandemic days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Holding Grudge Harmful To Mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hold-on-to-negativity-well-being/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychologists at the University of Miami say the longer negative emotions linger in the human brain, the worse it is for your mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson credits 'greed' and 'capitalism' for jab success, sparking debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Boris-Johnson-reportedly-credits-greed-and-16049231.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson reportedly credited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTY IN 'FREE FALL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-politics-idUSKBN2BG1DI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Support for German Chancellor Angela Merkel's conservatives has slumped three percentage points in a week to its lowest in over a year, a poll released on Wednesday showed, with the ecologist Greens just four points behind them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12,500-year-old wooden sculpture 'unique and unparalleled find' in human history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/12500-year-old-wooden-sculpture-23786198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Shigir Idol is over 12,500 years old and is regarded as the earliest known work of ritual art that could change the way we see human history but decay has kept others from being found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carcinogen Found in Hand Sanitizers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/carcinogen-found-in-hand-sanitizers-that-plugged-pandemic-gap/ar-BB1eUO2Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some widely available hand sanitizers that American consumers snapped up last year to ward off coronavirus infection contain high levels of a chemical known to cause cancer, a testing firm’s analysis found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry has another new role; Joins 'fight against misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/24/media/prince-harry-aspen-institute-commission-on-information-disorder/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voicing concern about an "avalanche of misinformation" in the digital world, Prince Harry is joining the Aspen Institute's new Commission on Information Disorder as a commissioner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former 'Warp Speed' chief fired from board over sex harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/24/moncef-slaoui-fired-from-galvani-bioelectronics-board-of-directors-over-sexual-harassment-allegations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moncef Slaoui, who headed the Covid vaccine development effort Operation Warp Speed was fired as board chairman of Galvani Bioelectronics sexual harassment claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache of 29 Million Doses in Italy Raises EU Suspicions...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/24/cache-of-29-million-astrazeneca-doses-in-italy-raises-e-u-suspicions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS — A stockpile of 29 million doses of AstraZeneca’s Covid-19 vaccine that were found languishing in a facility in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent byproduct of pandemic: Stress causing spike in chipped, cracked teeth...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2021/03/24/covid-pandemic-stress-causing-teeth-grinding-cracked-tooth/4796180001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 70% of dentists surveyed are seeing an increase of patients with teeth grinding and clenching problems associated with stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India detects 'double mutant' variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-india-cases/india-detects-double-mutant-coronavirus-variant-in-western-state-idUSKBN2BG1QB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India has detected a "double mutant variant" of the novel coronavirus in 206 samples in the worst-hit western state of Maharashtra, a senior government official said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese threat to Taiwan 'closer than think,' top US admiral says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/24/asia/indo-pacific-commander-aquilino-hearing-taiwan-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is quickly amassing weapons and systems to militarily overwhelm Taiwan, an action it could be poised to take within the next six years, the admiral chosen to be the next commander of US forces in the Pacific warned Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab Islamist could choose next PM...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-israel-benjamin-netanyahu-4e0b0aa9800b3a7cff9184964c09a8d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — After a hard-fought election, an Arab Islamist could choose Israel's next prime minister. You read that correctly. Tuesday's elections have left a razor-thin margin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With vaccinations rising, religious groups eye bigger gatherings at upcoming holidays...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/With-vaccinations-rising-religious-groups-eye-16048884.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the country came to a near standstill a year ago, most houses of worship closed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After backlash, Merkel ditches stricter Easter lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210324105529-ah80y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-After backlash, Merkel ditches stricter Easter lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After backlash, Merkel to drop Easter closure plans...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210324095952-a12w3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-After backlash, Merkel to drop Easter closure plans -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Facing Coffee Deficit in Supply Chain 'Nightmare'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coffee-trade-reeling-virus-faces-180243966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Coffee supplies in the U.S. are shrinking and wholesale prices are surging, with the hard-hit market bracing for further fallout from a global shortage of shipping containers that’s upended the food trade.Coffee stockpiles have sunk to a six-year low in the U.S. even with Brazil’s record crop, and a large drop in output after a drought in the South American country is expected to shift the world balance to a deficit in coming months just as demand rebounds.“Everybody is feeling the pinch,” said Christian Wolthers, the president of Wolthers Douque, an importer in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, who estimates that shipping costs have more than doubled from Latin America. “These bottlenecks are turning into a container nightmare.”While cargo-market disruptions have played havoc the global food trade generally, the problems in the coffee market show food inflation already on the rise could be exacerbated as economies reopen. For now, roasters are able to draw on inventories rather than raise prices, but with stockpiles sliding and a smaller Brazilian crop coming, the strains are expected to persist.Arabica-coffee futures in New York have risen about 24% since the end of October following the damage to Brazilian groves. In February, American green, unroasted bean inventory slid 8.3% from a year earlier to the smallest since 2015, industry data showed Monday.The lower inventories mean less of a buffer to cushion the expected decline in Brazil’s crop, aggravating market tightness and lending continued support to prices, analysts say.Marex Spectron this month increased its estimate for a global coffee deficit to 10.7 million bags in 2021-22, compared with its previous projection of 8 million bags, citing lower Brazilian arabica output after adverse weather damaged crops. Goldman Sachs Group Inc. said in a report that if production in Central America doesn’t improve in coming years, the market will enter a structural deficit given the rebound in demand.In the facilities of Dinamo, one of Brazil’s largest coffee warehouses operators, there’s a lot of product stuck waiting for containers. In the company’s unit in Machado municipality, in the coffee heartland of Minas Gerais, beans are awaiting the arrival of 18 empty containers, said Luiz Alberto Azevedo Levy Jr., a director at Dinamo. “These containers will probably take about 15 more days to get here amid bottlenecks at the port,” he said.The situation, which got even more dire in March, will probably reduce the volume of coffee exported by Brazil, Levy Jr. said.“Logistics have been a headache, dealing with lack of space and containers,” said Marco Figueiredo, trader and partner at the Florida-based Ally Coffee, a specialty coffee merchant that imports beans from countries including Colombia, Guatemala, and Brazil. “We are monitoring the situation and talking to clients, making them aware of the rising costs.”Denmark’s A.P. Moller-Maersk A/S, the world’s largest shipping company, said containers and charter vessels are temporarily unavailable for purchase or lease, increasing congestion and bringing delays at ports. The company has tried to purchase or rent all available containers, and is keeping aging units in operation. It’s also repairing ones that it usually wouldn’t at higher costs, Maersk said in an e-mailed response to questions from Bloomberg.“This is a temporary situation, both in terms of purchasing patterns and availability of vessels,” the company said. “We expect things to return to normal during the first half of 2021.”For now, many merchants are trying to hold the line on price increases as they work to lure customers back to cafes and restaurants. There’s steady growth in coffee, though the out-of-home segment could take two to three years to return to pre-Covid levels, according to David Rennie, head of Nestle SA’s coffee brands.Stefano Martin, sales and marketing export manager at Italy-based cafe chain Diemme, said the business isn’t yet feeling the full impact because it’s still operating under contracts made prior to the shipping disruptions. That could change as those contracts are renewed, he said. The company has 26 restaurants and coffee shops, and typically imports 30,000 bags in around 90 shipping containers from Brazil, Colombia, El Salvador, Honduras, Tanzania and India.“There is no impact on our side yet as we have closed all contracts before the prices increased,” he said. “But most probably next batch of contracts will be charged to us.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would have shut supermarkets!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-angela-merkel-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-64baf934e39a94e2ef635676b92222cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Chancellor Angela Merkel on Wednesday dropped plans for a five-day shutdown in Germany over Easter, which had prompted confusion and criticism. She called the idea a mistake and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'disturbing influence' of presidential news conferences...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-dwight-eisenhower-coronavirus-pandemic-dd244a717c67c27cb4b0fd907ab1cb55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — He'd led allied armies in the defeat of Nazi Germany only to find himself, a decade later, a tad intimidated before the cameras in an echoey room of the Old Executive Office...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk announces TESLAs can now be bought with Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90618478/elon-musk-announces-teslas-can-now-be-bought-with-bitcoin?icid=dan902:754:0:editRecirc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But due to the volatility of bitcoin, a customer could receive “significantly less” than they originally paid if they want a refund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Much High-Intensity Exercise Bad for Health...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/24/too-much-high-intensity-exercise-may-be-bad-for-your-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If high-intensity exercise is good for us, is more necessarily better? Maybe not, according to an admonitory new study of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Rally Poses Question: When Does Bull Become Bubble?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/23/stock-rally-poses-question-when-does-a-bull-become-a-bubble/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bull market turned a year old on Tuesday, a testament to the unbridled enthusiasm that let investors shrug off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Covid Patients Left With Ringing Ears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/23/some-covid-19-patients-say-theyre-left-with-ringing-ears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suicide of Kent Taylor, the founder and chief executive of the Texas Roadhouse restaurant chain, has drawn attention to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deeply Polarized Israel Fails to Anoint Leader Once Again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-naftali-bennett-middle-east-coronavirus-pandemic-benjamin-netanyahu-d80e4932e9d6c8e5f5ed60cb72907a45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Uncertainty hovered over the outcome of Israel's parliamentary election Wednesday, with both Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and sworn political rivals determined to depose him...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MENTAL ILLNESS'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2569098/boulder-suspect-ahmad-al-aliwi-family-issues-shooting-mental-health/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOULDER massacre suspect Ahmad Al Aliwi Alissa is believed to have had “issues” with his family prior to his alleged killing spree, The Sun can reveal. Law enforcement officials are also investigat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's 24-hour deaths surpass 3,000 for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/brazils-24-hour-covid-deaths-surpass-3000-first-time-3167886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's 24-hour Covid deaths surpass 3,000 for first time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia markets fall again as virus fears hit confidence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asia-markets-fall-again-virus-025941374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian markets extended losses Wednesday as renewed virus and vaccine fears returned to haunt investors as Europe faces a fresh spike in infections and lockdowns that could knock the economic recovery off course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Destroyers Swarmed By Mysterious 'Drones' Off California...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39913/multiple-destroyers-were-swarmed-by-mysterious-drones-off-california-over-numerous-nights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disturbing series of events during the summer of 2019 resulted in an investigation that made its way to the highest echelons of the Navy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concussions can now be diagnosed through a saliva test...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Concussions-can-be-diagnosed-through-a-saliva-16048076.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they can diagnose concussions accurately using a biomarker in saliva, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black leaders say Miami Beach overreacting with curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Black-leaders-say-Miami-Beach-overreacting-with-16048258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH - City leaders here were on the defensive Tuesday amid charges from Black...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social distancing dispute leads to 'hate crime' charges against doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/social-distancing-dispute-leads-hate-crime-charges-against-florida-doctor-n1261820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jennifer Wright is accused of using "anti-Hispanic ethnic slurs" and physically attacking a man after he mentioned "his Covid-19 spacing concerns."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adults under 50 spur rise in Spring Break hubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/weeks-into-spring-break-adults-under-50-spur-covid-19-rise-in-florida-tourism-hubs/ar-BB1eTnP2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Florida’s pandemic month of March has been defined by the dueling dynamics of a mass vaccination effort focused on older people and a tourism surge to the metro areas of Miami, Tampa and Orlando, among other locales. Those forces appear to have come to a head over the last week, with a rise in cases among people under 50 after months of decline, driving an uptick in the number of tests ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Two spring breakers in FL bitten by sharks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-spring-breakers-bitten-by-sharks-incidents-may-be-linked-to-large-shark-migration-expert-says/ar-BB1eTvVq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two out-of-town visitors to South Florida were bitten by sharks last week, and both wounds are suspected to have been inflicted by blacktip sharks, according to media reports. Blacktips don’t seek interaction with humans, according to Stephen Kajiura, a professor of biological sciences at Florida Atlantic University. But those who venture into the water should be aware that one of the world’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO MAYOR ISSUES NEW WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-headed-in-the-wrong-way-as-younger-adults-drive-uptick-in-covid-19-cases-health-commissioner-warns/ar-BB1eToqj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Chicago public health Commissioner Dr. Allison Arwady warned the city, particularly its younger adults, on Tuesday that coronavirus metrics were once again creeping into a danger zone that resembled a previous second surge during last October. She echoed Mayor Lori Lightfoot’s Monday remarks that cautioned the city will lose its recent gains under its reopening plan if younger adults ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds bust Cuban migrant smuggling ring operating out of Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/feds-say-they-busted-cuban-migrant-smuggling-ring-operating-out-of-the-keys/ar-BB1eSUFu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Federal agents arrested three men Sunday in the Florida Keys as a boat was being lowered by one of them down a ramp at a local marina in an alleged scheme to smuggle migrants out of Cuba. Agents with U.S. Homeland Security Investigations say the men ran the operation out of a house in Key Largo. Shortly after the arrest at the Harry Harris Park marina in the Upper Keys area of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGTV star scammed in house deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/detroit-mayor-duggan-says-hgtvs-nicole-curtis-was-scammed-in-house-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit Mayor Mike Duggan said HGTV star and Metro Detroit native Nicole Curtis was 'scammed' when she bought a blighted home from someone who wasn't the owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted PARLER CEO sues company, alleges stake was taken...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Ousted-Parler-CEO-sues-company-alleges-stake-was-16047747.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - The founder and former CEO of right-leaning social media site Parler is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell's living hell, filibuster-less Senate foretold...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mconnell-filibuster-nuclear-winter-scorched-earth-senate-7850cb51-3661-41ce-8f90-b686e2d45740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's threatening a "nuclear winter," with incessant roll calls and other inconveniences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Degrowth' movement going mainstream: Shrink economy to save planet!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/degrowth-economic-growth-climate-change-pandemic-774933af-9209-4b74-89fb-b4a783a87305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Degrowth — deliberately shrinking the global economy to avert climate change — could leave billions in poverty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA isn't seeing covid spikes like NY and FL. Can state stave off another wave?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-isnt-seeing-covid-19-172045517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as the state's numbers remain comparatively positive, officials are urging caution, saying California can ill afford to see its progress reverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Beats FOXNEWS in Total Viewership in Q1 for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cable-news-ratings-msnbc-wins-quarter-in-total-viewers-for-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC will win the quarter in total viewers for the first time with an average of 1.404 million viewers, according to Nielsen Media Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Heat to open vaccinated-only sections for fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/31123421/miami-heat-open-vaccinated-only-sections-fans-april-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami Heat will open two sections in their lower bowl for only fully vaccinated fans starting with an April 1 game against Golden State. Masks will still be required, but social distancing rules will be slightly relaxed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first digital NFT house sells for $500,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/digital-nft-mars-house-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having spent so much time at home over the last year, many people are craving a change in their surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas reverts to its former glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9393253/Sin-Citys-swing-Nevada-Gov-rolls-COVID-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people descended on Sin City over the weekend after Nevada governor Steve Sisolak allowed casinos, bars and restaurants to reopen at 50 per cent capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY 'Black Widow', 'Cruella' to stream on same day as theatrical releases...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/disney-postpones-black-widow-shang-chi-1234935874/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As moviegoing slowly begins to rebound in the U.S., it appears Hollywood studios aren’t yet ready to release their biggest blockbuster hopefuls on the big screen. All that is to say Disney ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF accidentally reveals location of secret bases online...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/idf-accidentally-reveals-location-of-secret-bases-online-662933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The map was detailed enough to include boundaries and names of the bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ refers Capitol riot prosecutor for internal investigation after '60 MINS' interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/23/politics/capitol-riot-michael-sherwin-60-minutes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department has referred former acting Washington US Attorney Michael Sherwin's unapproved interview with "60 Minutes" on Sunday about the Capitol riot cases to its Office of Professional Responsibility, a department lawyer said in court on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble with the Ghislaine Maxwell case?</title>
      <link>https://technofog.substack.com/p/trouble-with-the-ghislaine-maxwell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;technofog.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New filing shows potential issues with the government's case against Maxwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounded 'Mega Ship' Blocking Suez Canal in Both Directions...</title>
      <link>https://gcaptain.com/grounded-mega-ship-blocking-suez-canal-in-both-directions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gcaptain.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ultra-large containership is aground and blocking ship traffic in the Suez Canal. AIS data shows the MV Ever Given is stuck sideways within the canal, preventing ships from passing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii tourist spots packed...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/hawaii/article/Hawaii-tourist-spots-packed-spring-break-covid-16047204.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii saw 28,000 travelers enter the state on Saturday, the highest number since the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian Americans seek greater political power after killings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-race-and-ethnicity-biden-cabinet-shootings-immigration-60413e240dffeb52bf709a71ad3d64ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Speaking on the floor of the Georgia state Senate last week, Michelle Au implored her colleagues to “stand up” to the hatred aimed at Asian Americans that's increased during the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland launches guaranteed pay plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-oakland-poverty-stockton-f3c3891bd8b359695ca4c6dc9ba3f8ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The mayor of Oakland, California, on Tuesday announced a privately funded program that will give low-income families of color $500 per month with no rules on how they can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS wants 2 Texas military posts to house unaccompanied minors, Pentagon says...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/23/hhs-seeking-military-posts-unaccompanied-minors-477669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon press secretary John Kirby said Tuesday that the military has received a request for the use of Joint Base San Antonio-Lackland and Fort Bliss in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea launches multiple short-range missiles over weekend...</title>
      <link>https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20210324000500325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.yna.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON, March 23 (Yonhap) -- North Korea has resumed short-range missile testing in a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP: THISCLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-parliament-elections-benjamin-netanyahu-5aab7aac65d1e84c013ce37f7fbdbf74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Exit polls indicate there is no clear winner in Tuesday’s Israeli election, leaving Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s fate uncertain and signaling continued political deadlock....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Drivers Forced to Sign 'Biometric Consent' Form or Lose Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dy8n3j/amazon-delivery-drivers-forced-to-sign-biometric-consent-form-or-lose-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new cameras, which are being implemented nationwide, use artificial intelligence to access drivers' location, movement, and biometric data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT POLLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-elections/netanyahu-clinches-61-majority-on-right-on-way-to-victory-exit-polls-662919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three polls give Netanyahu's bloc 61 seats with Yamina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BIBI?  Israel Votes for Fourth Time, Deeply Divided by Netanyahu's Rule... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-public-opinion-coronavirus-pandemic-benjamin-netanyahu-elections-5aab7aac65d1e84c013ce37f7fbdbf74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Exit polls indicate there is no clear winner in Tuesday’s Israeli election, leaving Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s fate uncertain and signaling continued political deadlock....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking hazardous to your health in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/walking-is-hazardous-to-your-health-in-florida-the-deadliest-state-for-pedestrians/ar-BB1erVSM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — You take your life in your hands when you're on foot in Florida, the deadliest state in the nation for pedestrians. Walking can be hazardous to your health in the Sunshine State, which retained its notorious No. 1 ranking as the place where a pedestrian is most likely to be struck and killed by a driver in the United States, according to the 2021 "Dangerous By Design" report from Smart ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI declares 'ZOOM-Free' Fridays amid pandemic work fatigue...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citi-declares-zoom-free-fridays-190336408.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citi will institute "Zoom-Free Fridays" and establish an employee day-off in May as firms seek to restore work-life balance amid the pandemic, the bank's new chief executive announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Saudi official issued death threat against UN's Khashoggi investigator...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/23/top-saudi-official-issued-death-threat-against-uns-khashoggi-investigator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior official twice threatened to have Agnès Callamard ‘taken care of’ in meeting with UN colleagues in Geneva in January 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT art is so hot now, even robots are trying to cash in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/nft-art-is-so-hot-now-even-robots-are-trying-to-cash-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sophia the robot will sell her art on the same NFT marketplace where Grimes sold artwork. "As one creates a piece of art, a mysterious, enigmatic, and magical event occurs," the robot says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER Begins Human Trials of New Pill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/pfizer-begins-human-trials-of-new-pill-to-treat-coronavirus/ar-BB1eSHnp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer Inc. said it has begun human safety testing of a new pill to treat the coronavirus that could be used at the first sign of illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Gov Given Warning After Trapping, Killing Of Yellowstone Wolf...</title>
      <link>https://www.boisestatepublicradio.org/post/montana-governor-given-written-warning-after-trapping-killing-yellowstone-wolf#stream/0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boisestatepublicradio.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana's newly elected Republican governor violated state hunting regulations when he trapped and shot a collared wolf near Yellowstone National Park in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish writer facing prison for calling president 'moron'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-media-poland-social-media-059e5db66925f01119c746625b9071e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A popular Polish writer is facing a potential sentence of up to three years in prison for calling the nation's president a “moron” on social media. Jakub Zulczyk had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON pushing alarming myths targeting China, Jewish people...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/qanon-now-pushes-alarming-conspiracy-120001897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online conspiracy theorists have pivoted their focus to a "new world order" - a cabal of global elites they say include vaccine proponents, Biden and Gov. Newsom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Soldiers transporting vaccines held at gunpoint ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wafb.com/2021/03/22/national-guard-soldiers-transporting-vaccines-held-gunpoint-west-texas-suspect-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wafb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona man has been arrested after he cut off and held at gunpoint a caravan of National Guardsmen transporting COVID-19 vaccines to Matador, Texas around 7 a.m. this morning, according to Idalou Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authors fear the worst if BERTELSMANN takes over SIMON &amp; SCHUSTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2021/mar/22/authors-fear-the-worst-if-bertelsmann-takes-over-simon-schuster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: if Bertelsmann, owner of Penguin Random House, buys US publisher, writers expect smaller deals and less choice for readers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MENTAL ILLNESS'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/boulder-colorado-cops-identify-king-soopers-supermarket-massacre-suspect-as-ahmad-alissa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police also identified the 10 people who lost their lives when the 21-year-old gunman allegedly opened fire on Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eating Processed Meat Significantly Raises Risk Of Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-bacon-processed-meat-increases-dementia-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the other hand, study authors reveal eating unprocessed red meat may actually lower the chances of developing the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sometimes-fuzzy $400,000 threshold...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-sometimes-fuzzy-400-000-threshold-in-Biden-s-16046525.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even supermarkets could close!</title>
      <link>https://www.spiegel.de/politik/deutschland/corona-angela-merkel-plant-radikalen-lockdown-inklusive-supermaerkte-a-b8744b25-8499-437a-93ab-786e8a63eef0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nach SPIEGEL-Informationen hat sich Kanzlerin Merkel mit den Länderchefs Söder und Müller sowie Vizekanzler Scholz auf neue, schärfere Corona-Maßnahmen verständigt. Ab 1. April könnten selbst Supermärkte schließen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland Warns Far-Right Terror Threat Growing as Plans Detected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/finland-warns-far-right-terror-threat-growing-as-plans-detected/ar-BB1eRO3n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extreme right-wing terrorism is becoming a growing threat in Finland, the Finnish Security and Intelligence Service said, citing attack preparations it has detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's commune of venomous cottonmouths on NC coast, and they have FACEBOOK page...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/there-s-a-commune-of-venomous-cottonmouths-on-the-north-carolina-coast-and-they-have-a-facebook-page/ar-BB1eRRTQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. — If North Carolina has such a thing as celebrity wildlife, it would include a group of 100-plus venomous cottonmouths living in a secret spot near the coast. This bunch of pit vipers are the stars of their own Facebook page — Cottonmouth Acres. The page has nearly 1,500 followers and a bold approach to the things shared online. Nothing is held back. Posts in recent months have ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden prepares massive infrastructure bill with universal pre-K, free community college, climate measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-team-preparing-up-to-3-trillion-in-new-spending-for-the-economy/ar-BB1eQspQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden’s economic advisers are pulling together a sweeping $3 trillion package to boost the economy, reduce carbon emissions and narrow economic inequality, beginning with a giant infrastructure plan that may be financed in part through tax increases on corporations and the rich. After months of internal debate, Mr. Biden’s advisers are expected to present the spending proposal to the president and congressional leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two visitors allegedly drugged, raped woman. She was found dead in hotel room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/two-spring-breakers-allegedly-drugged-raped-woman-in-miami-beach-she-was-found-dead-in-a-hotel-room/ar-BB1eRBFL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said two men from Greensboro, N.C., drugged a 24-year-old woman visiting from Pennsylvania, sexually assaulted her and then stole her credit cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUBIO: 'There's Stuff Flying Over Military Installations' We Can't Identify...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/marco-rubio-talks-to-tmz-about-ufos-and-the-possibility-of-alien-life-theres-stuff-flying-over-military-installations-we-cant-identify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Marco Rubio (R-FL) shared his thoughts on aliens with TMZ -- revealing he is worried about UFOs flying near United States military bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Huntsman, of prominent Utah family, files fraud lawsuit against Mormon church...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/James-Huntsman-of-prominent-Utah-family-files-16046024.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Huntsman, of a prominent Mormon family from Utah, filed a federal lawsuit Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE searches for 'hope' and 'prayer' peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishnews.com/magazine/technology/2021/03/23/news/google-searches-for-hope-and-prayer-peak-while-party-and-festival-slump-2264673/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Trends search data gives an insight into the public's interests and mood over the past 12 months of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists can implant false memories -- and reverse them...</title>
      <link>https://www.inverse.com/mind-body/how-to-reverse-false-memories-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inverse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;False memories can be implanted through suggestion. Now, new research suggests they can be reversed too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC's 'TONIGHT SHOW' Brings Back Live Studio Audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/nbcs-tonight-show-starring-jimmy-fallon-brings-back-live-studio-audience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move, which also saw the host return to his longtime home of Studio 6B, makes it likely the first nightly, network late-night program to bring back a live audience since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado man livestreams supermarket slaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/colorado-man-livestreams-boulder-supermarket-shooting/article_cd29be28-87e1-5464-9b1a-4870c5d44ddb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boulder, Colorado, man who livestreamed the shooting scene at the King Soopers grocery store on Monday afternoon drew sharp criticism from some, and praise from others, for his actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza rocket hits near city as PM campaigns there...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-gaza-rocket-hits-near-southern-israeli-city-as-netanyahu-campaigns-there-1.9647662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First news conference big test...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Biden-s-first-news-conference-is-a-test-for-him-16046313.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first news conference of a new administration is always a high-stakes affair for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Hike Details...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/sarahhansen/2021/03/23/new-biden-tax-hike-details-are-out-heres-what-we-know-now/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts increasingly warn against manipulating natural systems...</title>
      <link>https://www.downtoearth.org.in/blog/climate-change/why-geoengineering-is-still-a-dangerous-techno-utopian-dream-74828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.downtoearth.org.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have increasingly warned against manipulating Earth&amp;rsquo;s natural systems&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting suspect had previously attacked classmate, court records show...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/03/23/boulder-shooting-suspect-ahmad-al-aliwi-alissa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old Arvada man arrested in Monday’s mass shooting at a Boulder King Sooper’s previously attacked a classmate at Arvada West High School, according to court records and the Colorado Bure…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AHMAD AL ALIWI ALISSA CHARGED IN RAMPAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9393669/Gunman-21-charged-murder-shooting-killing-10-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alissa, who has lived most of his life in the US, is now in custody and has been charged with 10 counts of murder. At 2.40pm, he opened fire on King Soopers grocery store in Boulder, killing ten people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pushes immediate gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/boulder-colorado-shooting-3-23-21/h_1f11eb1535df9ebb5a3723e2b7a9d945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people, including a police officer, were killed Monday after a gunman opened fire in a grocery store in Boulder, Colorado. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL: We are in new pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/we-are-in-a-new-pandemic-due-to-virus-variant-merkel-01616466604 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist behind 'VIEW' tell-all takes aim at 'APPRENTICE'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/the-apprentice-book-donald-trump-1234936339/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Variety executive editor and New York Times bestselling author Ramin Setoodeh is writing a reported nonfiction book about “The Apprentice,” the TV show that single handedly changed the course of Am…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET Intel? Scientists Discover Clues to Emissions of Intergalactic Radio Bursts...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202103231082426789-et-intel-scientists-discover-clues-to-emissions-of-intergalactic-fast-radio-bursts-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have arrived at the most precise time estimates to date pertaining to the mystery of so-called "fast radio bursts" (FRBs), which are abrupt pulses from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To escape pandemic and lockdowns, Californians resettle in Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/escape-pandemic-lockdowns-californians-resettle-100000745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the start of the pandemic, scores of Angelenos have moved to Taiwan, where they have roots and coronavirus spread has been kept in check.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disgraceful' sex acts in parliament rock Australia's government...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/disgraceful-parliament-sex-acts-rock-020555748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked videos of staff from Australia's conservative government performing sex acts in parliament, including one man masturbating over a female MP's desk, left Scott Morrison's administration facing yet another major scandal Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo reports record 1,021 deaths in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323130726-nvlaa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French hospitals 'violent shock'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323073328-fx3ez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfing pet goat coolly rides waves at California beach...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323012710-l1iqs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Satisfaction with direction of country increases...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/341675/satisfaction-continues-improve-march.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satisfaction with the direction of the U.S. improved again in March, to 32%. This is the second monthly increase Gallup has recorded after the measure fell to its lowest point in nearly a decade in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK SPIRAL:  Miami Beach Business Owners Opt To Remain Closed Than Deal With 'Crime Zone'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/22/miami-beach-business-owners-residents-have-had-enough-spring-break-crowds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone who lives or works in Miami Beach is hoping for a much calmer week and weekend ahead. Still, the tumultuous couple of days of spring break trouble has been more than enough for some people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry Lands Gig At Silicon Valley Startup...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/prince-harry-silicon-valley-startup-betterup-meghan-markle-1234719966/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry won’t have to rely entirely on streaming services for an income – he’s joined a Silicon Valley coaching and mental health services company called BetterUp as its chief impact officer. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Putin's vaccination to be kept out of public eye...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vladimir-putin-immunizations-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-russia-0ca9d03310c85097422fc28181efc831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin will be getting his first vaccination against COVID-19 on Tuesday, but out of sight of the cameras, his spokesman said, prompting questions about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRA Jab Faces Fresh Setback as Feds Question Trial Data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-a98ef616f4e861a4b7568891d06b7da8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — AstraZeneca may have included “outdated information” in touting the effectiveness of its COVID-19 vaccine in a U.S. study, federal health officials said Tuesday in an unusual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Illinois city 1st to offer Black residents reparations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-chicago-discrimination-recreational-marijuana-slavery-752a6fe83c560117523d7f8abba1bfb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVANSTON, Ill. (AP) — Using tax money from the sale of recreational marijuana, the Chicago suburb of Evanston has become the first U.S. city to make reparations available to its Black residents...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR AT BOULDER  SUPERMARKET</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/colorado-supermarket-shooting-10-dead-3da92f0d3db65afdb373cc6bb534a711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOULDER, Colo. (AP) — Police on Tuesday identified a 21-year-old man as the suspect who opened fire inside a crowded Colorado supermarket, and court documents showed that he purchased an assault...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration releases video from inside crowded detention facilities...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-administration-releases-video-inside-crowded-migrant-detention/story?id=76618644</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has now released its first official images from inside two Texas migrant detention facilities. ABC News got an exclusive first look.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
