<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana AG sues reporter over records request...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/intimidation-measure-louisiana-ag-criticized-for-suing-reporter-over-records-request/ar-BB1dt6RU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Allegations of sexual harassment that turn out to be unsupported, inaccurate and unfounded can destroy marriages, damage employee’s children, wreck families and ruin reputations," staff for the attorney general wrote to a reporter who requested complaints against a top deputy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDakota AG Killed a Man. Everything Else Is Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-dakota-attorney-general-killed-095845266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg/GettyOn a remote section of highway in a sparsely populated part of South Dakota, the state’s highest-ranking law enforcement official struck and killed a man while returning from a Republican Party dinner one night in late summer.In the months since, Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg hasn’t missed a day of work—and has not faced any charge in connection with the death of Joe Boever.Many South Dakotans are growing restless, including Boever’s family. Markers indicating a death went up at the crash site on Highway 14 in Hyde County last week, a grim reminder of the tragedy that had cousin Nick Nemec in tears.“I’m very disappointed,” he told The Daily Beast during a video call. “Next week will mark five months since the crash. I’ve prepared myself mentally for some sort of guilty plea to a minor traffic violation on the order of ‘crossing the white line.’”Gov. Kristi Noem, like Ravnsvorg a Republican elected in 2018, has also questioned why it is taking so long for the investigation to conclude.“We continue to call it a great disservice to the victim’s family,” Noem said at a Jan. 21 press conference. “I am disappointed that we haven’t seen some action taken by the states attorney involved and hope certainly that they soon will.”Noem cannot remove or even suspend Ravnsborg, according to the governor’s communications director, Ian Fury.“Since the attorney general is a separately elected constitutional official, she has no such authority,” Fury said.The person who will decide what if any charges will be filed is Emily Sovell, the Sully County state’s attorney and the Hyde County deputy state’s attorney. Sovell is handling the case for her father, Hyde County State’s Attorney Merlin Voorhees, who is not involved in the investigation or the charging decision. No reason for that has been provided. (Voorhees, who was disbarred in 1980 for his role in a cattle feedlot scheme, was reinstated to the bar in 1987. He has served as state’s attorney in both Sully and Hyde counties.)Sovell has not responded to requests for comment left with both county attorneys’ offices and has not spoken a word on the case publicly, even as questions about the investigation have piled up.Mike Deaver, a veteran public relations consultant and strategist from Salt Lake City, has been serving as Ravnsborg’s personal spokesman. He said the attorney general wants the investigation to end and would prefer more transparency.“I would say, the attorney general shares the governor’s sentiment and would like to see this come to a conclusion, or at least remarks from the investigators on the time forecast on when this might be wrapped up,” he said last month.In the course of her probe, Sovell has sought the counsel of Beadle County State’s Attorney Michael Moore and Pennington County State’s Attorney Mark Vargo, as well as the Minnehaha County State’s Attorney’s Office.Moore said the prosecutor has four options in this case.“When dealing with an automobile accident that results in a death of another person, the law provides four different actions of an operator of the motor vehicle,” he said. “Negligent, careless, reckless, and intentional. Vehicle homicide and vehicle battery require the operator to be under the influence and also operating the vehicle in a negligent manner.“In order for the operator to be criminally responsible for the death (if they are not under the influence) their actions must be reckless or intentional,” Moore said. “The South Dakota Legislature, I believe in 2019, rejected a negligent homicide law, thus leaving reckless or intentional actions as the only means of an operator to have criminal liability.”‘I hit something’The 911 call Ravnsborg made after the crash was released a month later. He mentioned his title right away when the dispatcher answered.“This… well… Ally, I’m the attorney general. And I am… I don’t know… I hit something.”Dispatcher: “You hit something?”Caller: “By Highmore. Highmore. And it was in the middle of the road.”The location remains under dispute. A South Dakota Highway Patrol report states that Ravnsborg’s car was actually on the north shoulder when he struck Boever.The crash site is on the west edge of town. A convenience store is nearby, as are a gas station, a machinery business, and a state Department of Transportation shop. All have lights that are on all night, so the fatal crash didn’t happen in the darkness of a prairie night.“I’ve driven the highway in the middle of the night many times since Joe's death,” Nemec told The Daily Beast. “The area between two reflector posts is lit up from your headlights bright enough to see a mouse running across the road.”The speed limit increases to 65 mph a few feet from where Ravnsborg struck Boever, who was apparently walking back to town. He had driven his pickup off the road earlier in the evening—the cause will never be known—and struck a large round bale in the ditch.Boever, 55, who had worked in nursing homes and a grocery store and as a farm hand, called his cousin and friend Victor Nemec, who lives nearby and came to pick him up. They left and planned to return in the morning to repair and retrieve the truck.A few hours later, for some reason, Boever decided to walk to his pickup, carrying a light. As he returned, and just a minute or two before he would have turned off Highway 14 to walk down Iowa Avenue, Highmore’s wide main thoroughfare, he was struck and killed.That’s when things got weird.After Ravnsborg called 911, Hyde County Sheriff Mike Volek, who lives at a nearby rural address, responded. Ravnsborg claims he didn’t know what he struck, but the dispatcher suggested it could have been a deer. They are common sights in the countryside, and vehicle-on-deer crashes are regular events.Ravnsborg, 44, said he used the flashlight app on his cellphone but could not find the object he had struck. His car was not drivable, with the passenger side front and the windshield extensively damaged.At the crash scene, tire marks clearly showed Ravnsborg’s car had moved sharply to the north and come to a stop 100 feet or less from where Boever’s body, later identified by his cousins, was discovered. Nick Nemec, in red, and his brother, Victor, at the site where their cousin Joe Boever was struck and killed by South Dakota Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg on Sept. 12. Courtesy Tom Lawrence It’s unclear how hard Volek, who has refused to speak to the media, looked for the deer or whatever the attorney general had struck. A tow truck was called, and the driver removed the 2011 Ford Taurus, which was Ravnsborg’s personal car.While all this activity was underway, Boever’s body was on the side of the road on the north shoulder, inches from the westbound land. There it would remain for approximately 10 hours.Was he killed immediately? Could help have been summoned? Those are just two of the unanswered questions surrounding this case.Ravsnborg had been in Redfield, a small town 70 miles away, where he had appeared at a GOP gathering. He was returning home to Pierre, the state capital, when he hit Boever.Ravnsborg said he had not consumed any alcohol that day. The manager of Rooster’s Bar &amp; Grill in Redfield, where the event had been held, declined to answer this reporter in September when asked if Ravnsborg had been served a drink, saying it was “an open investigation.”Volek did not give Ravnsborg a blood-alcohol test. In fact, he loaned the attorney general, whom he knew, his private car so he could drive home to Pierre.Then another truly bizarre twist unfolded.Early Sept. 13, Ravnsborg was returning the sheriff’s car, accompanied by Tim Bormann, his chief of staff and a former Faulk County state’s attorney, in another vehicle. Ravnsborg said he spotted a body on the side of the road and alerted the sheriff.“I discovered the body of Mr. Boever in the grass just off the roadway,” Ravnsborg said in a statement released Sept. 14. “It was apparent that he was dead,” he added.At this point, around 15 hours after the accident, Ravnsborg did have a blood test, which showed no sign of alcohol.The crash was investigated by the South Dakota Highway Patrol, which is under state Secretary of Public Safety Craig Price’s supervision, with assistance from other law enforcement agencies.‘A minute either way’Price said evidence indicates Ravnsborg was distracted, but he has not provided details. Was he on the phone? Was he adjusting his radio? Why did he not see Boever, who was dressed in dark clothing?The attorney general has a history of driving offenses, including six speeding tickets in South Dakota and two in Iowa between 2014 and 2018. He also was cited for a seat belt violation and driving without a proper muffler and exhaust system. In all cases, he pleaded guilty and paid small fines.Ravnsborg—a lieutenant colonel in the Army Reserves who has served 24 years in uniform—sought the Republican nomination for a U.S. Senate seat in 2014. He lost to former Gov. Mike Rounds, who was elected to his second term in the Senate in November.Deaver said while Ravnsborg has been through difficult situations before, he has been deeply impacted by this.“Absolutely, I talk to him on a very regular basis,” he said in January. “This is tough on him personally, and he certainly feels for the family and for the public and wants it to be concluded.”Nick Nemec said he fears Boever has been forgotten in all the discussion about Ravnsborg.“I’m afraid so. He was a mild-mannered guy and often overlooked in life,” he said last month. “Although I was pleased to have many people come forward to me who said he was kind to them at his grocery store job, and always remembered their name and details.”To Nemec’s mind, the fatal crash could have so easily been avoided.“Yeah, a minute either way would have made the difference,” he said, wondering what Boever might have done differently. “Had he stopped to take a leak by a ditch bale, the AG would have missed him. He might have driven in the ditch 100 yards before Joe got there—and Joe would have helped him get out of the ditch.”The Nemecs, both area farmers, said they just want the truth to emerge. Nick, a former Democratic state legislator and Public Utility Commission candidate, has another wish.“I will do all I can to try to ensure Jason Ravnsborg is never elected to another public office,” he said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece's #MeToo leads to calls for reckoning on incest...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/greeces-metoo-movement-leads-calls-113710824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece's emerging #MeToo movement, sparked by an Olympian's taboo-breaking decision to go public with allegations of sexual abuse, has raised hopes it can also uncover long-hidden stories of incest in the patriarchal country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-rich find supertall skyscraper an uncomfortable perch...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2021/feb/07/supertall-skyscraper-new-york-432-park-avenue-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy residents of 432 Park Avenue have complained of leaks, malfunctions and wind sway – much to the delight of earthbound New Yorkers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High cost of missed school...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/schools-pandemic-economic-cost-9f54405e-95f1-4e7b-bef1-988d72155af0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy could lose trillions due to coronavirus-induced learning loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope appoints first woman to senior synod post...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/feb/07/a-door-has-opened-pope-francis-appoints-first-woman-to-senior-synod-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s Nathalie Becquart, undersecretary of synod of bishops, is first woman to hold the rank which gives voting rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI net closes on Maga mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/06/us-capitol-insurrection-fbi-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge investigation has so far arrested 235 people, including far-right militants, members of the military – and otherwise unremarkable Trump fans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop fired for harassing, mocking co-worker's virus fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/officer-fired-for-physically-harassing-a-co-worker-mocking-her-fear-of-covid-19-police-say/ar-BB1ds2q0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida officer is accused of ridiculing his co-worker as a “germaphobe” and touching her personal items while saying that he didn't have the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Trial May Pause For Sabbath...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-lawyer-asks-to-pause-impeachment-trial-if-it-runs-into-sabbath/ar-BB1dsemi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats and Republicans eager to tidily conclude former President Donald J. Trump’s impeachment trial within a week may have a fresh obstacle in front of them: the biblical commandment to keep the Jewish Sabbath. One of the lead defense lawyers for Mr. Trump has informed Senate leaders that he is an observant Jew who strictly adheres to the commandment against working on the Sabbath, and thus would be unable to participate in any proceeding...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Dubai is paying the price for letting in tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/dubai-tourism-crackdown-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opening up to everyone around the world, Dubai has reaped the profits. But after rising tide of Covid-19 cases, the emirate is rethinking its tourism strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain will not introduce COVID vaccine passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-britain-passport/britain-will-not-introduce-covid-19-vaccine-passports-idUSKBN2A7097</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain will not introduce COVID-19 vaccine passports, but people will be able to seek proof from their doctor if needed for travel to other countries, vaccine deployment minister Nadhim Zahawi said on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if you test positive abroad?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/what-if-you-test-positive-for-covid-19-abroad-here-e2-80-99s-what-travelers-need-to-know/ar-BB1drR05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most travelers assume their rapid tests will return negative and they’ll head home. But that’s not always the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican operative arrested on child porn charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-former-gop-and-senate-staffer-27-has-been-arrested-on-child-pornography-charges/ar-BB1dsPS5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruben Verastigui, a pro-life campaigner, was arrested on Friday on charges of distributing, receiving, and possessing images of child pornography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of cyberbullying extradited to Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.tricitynews.com/local-news/man-accused-of-cyberbullying-amanda-todd-extradited-to-face-charges-in-bc-3358621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tricitynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday, the BC Prosecution Service confirmed the man was transferred to B.C., where he remains in custody and faces five charges, including extortion, two counts of possession of child pornography, communication with a young person to commit a sexual offence and criminal harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Sale: London's Thinnest House...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/sale-londons-thinnest-house-3139563</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For sale: London's thinnest house</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE moves away from cookies to track users...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-moves-away-diet-cookies-041325414.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is weaning itself off user-tracking "cookies" which allow the web giant to deliver personalized ads but which also have raised the hackles of privacy defenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Crackdown Chills Protests That Threaten Two-Decade Rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putins-crackdown-chills-protests-that-threaten-two-decade-rule/ar-BB1dsfCj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyudmila Shtein, a 24-year-old Muscovite and municipal deputy, is under house arrest until May and risks a two-year jail term for encouraging people to join a protest last month. She’s among more than 11,000 people rounded up in the past two weeks after the biggest show of defiance toward President Vladimir Putin in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under fire for deportation uptick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-team-under-fire-for-deportation-uptick-backing-moise-as-haiti-tensions-multiply/ar-BB1ds4cs?bep_ref=1&amp;bep_csid=23025&amp;ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They arrived back in Mexico without shoes, identification documents or even children's diapers. Held by U.S. immigration officials in detention over several days, the group of over 100 Haitian asylum seekers were sent back across the border earlier this week carrying little more than the clothes on their backs, according to immigration advocates and a memo shared with the Miami Herald. The ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT Boom-and-Bust Shines Light on Market Bubble Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/frothy-markets-spark-worries-of-bubbles-in-european-assets/ar-BB1drmCd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The almost uninterrupted rally in European stocks and corporate bonds over the past year has sent valuation metrics to frothy levels, setting the stage for potential pull-backs as Europe struggles with its vaccine rollout which could imperil the region’s economic recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden doubles down on normal at White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/537418-biden-doubles-down-on-normal-at-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first weeks of President Biden's administration have been a striking contrast with the chaos and turmoil of the Trump administration, bringing a sense of normality back to the White House and government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme regimen that keeps Tom forever young...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/tom-brady-diet-fitness-routines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the superstrict food and fitness regimen that enables Tom Brady, 43, to play like a 25-year-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if you test positive abroad?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/what-if-you-test-positive-for-covid-19-abroad-here-e2-80-99s-what-travelers-need-to-know/ar-BB1drR05?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most travelers assume their rapid tests will return negative and they’ll head home. But that’s not always the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Republicans fined for bypassing security...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/two-republicans-fined-for-bypassing-security-just-days-after-house-approved-the-new-penalties/ar-BB1dslji?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawmakers, Representatives Louie Gohmert of Texas and Andrew Clyde of Georgia, appear to be the first members punished under a new rule approved by the House on Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major push for LGBTIQ rights abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/biden-opens-major-push-for-lgbtiq-rights-abroad/ar-BB1dsmfC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has quickly launched a campaign to support LGBTIQ people abroad, putting their rights higher on the US foreign policy agenda than ever before. Elevating a 2011 initiative launched by his former boss Barack Obama -- and reversing a turnaround under Donald Trump -- Biden is expanding the scope of US efforts on LGBTIQ rights while also adjusting based on lessons learned over the past decade. In his first foreign policy speech,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene is just the latest 'radical White woman poisoning politics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/Marjorie-Taylor-Greene-is-just-the-latest-radical-15929884.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene's vitriolic, conspiracy-laden, violent (anti-Semitic, white...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN DANGER OF LOSING MONSTER LAWSUIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Lou-Dobbs-and-the-most-problematic-claims-Trump-15930038.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Lou Dobbs is out at Fox Business, just a day after the voting machine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI WARNS NO PARTY</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/brady-mahomes-set-super-bowl-013649861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady and Patrick Mahomes go head-to-head on Sunday in a potential Super Bowl classic that pits the greatest quarterback in NFL history against the pretender to his throne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Senate trial, will Trump face criminal charges?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senate-trial-donald-trump-face-014810763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's little chance Donald Trump will be convicted by the US Senate of inciting an insurgency but his legal troubles won't end with the conclusion of his second impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEVADA: Bill would allow tech companies to create local governments...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/politics-and-government/2021-legislature/bill-would-allow-tech-companies-to-create-local-governments-2272887/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’ve got enough money, acres upon acres of undeveloped land and an “innovative technology,” you soon could form a new local government in Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANCELED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/06/media/lou-dobbs-fox-news-last-show/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing unusual happened when Lou Dobbs hosted his Fox Business show on Thursday evening. His hour was full of Fox's usual themes about "radical Dims" (Democrats) and Big Tech "abusing their power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF THE AGES!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-florida-ff43fd00abece142e06bb32c412c272e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone will make history Sunday in a Super Bowl so filled with storylines it would fill a season of TV programming. Tom Brady, already the true Game of Thrones king, going for a seventh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election fraud falsehoods have cost taxpayers $519 million -- and counting...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trumps-election-fraud-falsehoods-have-cost-taxpayers-519-million-and-counting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald Trump's onslaught of falsehoods about the November election misled millions of Americans, undermined faith in the electoral system, sparked a deadly riot - and has now left taxpayers with a large, and growing, bill. The total...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kansas City, hope for victory comes with fear of celebratory gunfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/in-kansas-city-hope-for-a-super-bowl-victory-comes-with-fear-of-celebratory-gunfire/article_22499404-c418-5cfd-b8c0-9549ae339337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. — While many in the Kansas City area will be cheering Sunday for the Chiefs to win another Super Bowl, there is one thing that police hope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba opens door to most small business initiatives...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210206130955-iure3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUBA-ECONOMY/REFORM (PIX):Cuba opens door to most small business initiatives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Once-Scorned Vaccine Now Favorite...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putins-once-scorned-vaccine-now-favorite-in-pandemic-fight/ar-BB1drjfv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin’s announcement in August that Russia had cleared the world’s first Covid-19 vaccine for use before it even completed safety trials sparked skepticism worldwide. Now he may reap diplomatic dividends as Russia basks in arguably its biggest scientific breakthrough since the Soviet era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Tweeting on Saturday Morning -- But Something is Different...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/the-president-is-tweeting-on-saturday-morning-but-something-is-different/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden was tweeting Saturday morning, but not the sort of tweeting that Americans and the media became accustomed to over the past four years and two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year of the space station?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/537658-2021-year-of-the-space-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International Space Station, aging and with an uncertain future, is about to get a huge publicity boost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book reveals worst about famed news anchors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/06/new-book-reveals-worst-about-famed-news-anchors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right after getting hired at “60 Minutes,” Ira Rosen witnessed one of Mike Wallace’s signature meltdowns.  It was 1980 and Rosen, then 26, was on his first assignment for the legendary news pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Rally Takes Crypto Market Value to New Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/musk-helps-crypto-market-value-044155880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin topped $40,000 in a rally that helped the market value of digital tokens scale a new peak.The largest cryptocurrency rose more than 7% to $40,658 at 12 p.m. in New York Saturday, taking it closer to early January’s all-time high of almost $42,000. The value of more than 6,000 tokens tracked by CoinGecko hit about $1.23 trillion.The jump comes after another volatile week in cryptocurrencies marked by Elon Musk’s support for Bitcoin and a record runup in Ether, the second-largest token. Billionaire Musk also posted tongue-in-cheek tweets about Dogecoin -- a Shiba Inu-themed unit that began as a joke -- stirring buying that drove its market capitalization past $6 billion.The developments provide more evidence of the way the casino-like gyrations of digital coins are seeping into the mainstream. High-profile proponents of Bitcoin like Musk say it’s winning broader acceptance in the finance community. Regulators, meanwhile, are stepping up warnings of volatility that could wipe investors out.“Investor perception is at an all-time high at both the retail and hedge fund levels,” said Jehan Chu, managing partner with blockchain advisory firm Kenetic Capital in Hong Kong.Even so, many investors still view digital coins as a treacherous sector. That was underlined in the U.S., where the 24-year-old founder of two New York-based cryptocurrency hedge funds with more than $100 million in investments pleaded guilty Thursday to securities fraud.Bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency, is up about 24% this week. The token may be consolidating before heading toward $50,000, which would imply a market value of about $1 trillion, said Mike McGlone, commodities strategist with Bloomberg Intelligence.Meanwhile, Ether’s eightfold rally over the past year faces possible turbulence from the impending launch of CME Group Inc. futures next week. The contracts may open the door for bearish investors. The digital coin was at $1,693 as of 12 p.m. in London on Saturday.(Updates prices starting from second paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn Re-emerges Pushing QANON, Stolen Election...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/06/pushing-qanon-and-stolen-election-lies-flynn-re-emerges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Washington’s respectable circles, Michael T. Flynn, the former national security adviser, is a discredited and dishonored ex-general, a once-esteemed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>115 inmates take over section of downtown St. Louis jail... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/115-inmates-take-over-section-downtown-st-louis-jail-n1256932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A corrections officer was injured and inmates broke windows and set a small fire at the facility, Mayor Lyda Krewson's spokesman said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of quakes, including 4.2-mag, rattle Oklahoma, geologists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/nation-world/national/article249045035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least a dozen earthquakes rattled Oklahoma, including a 4.2-magnitude temblor, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Ivanka?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/965029/senator-ivanka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her political future is far from a sure thing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS assistant coach investigated for crash after 'drank and took Adderall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-9230969/Kansas-City-Chiefs-coach-Britt-Reid-involved-multi-car-crash-ahead-Super-Bowl-LV.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britt Reid, 35, is in hospital with undisclosed injuries and could be there for days, according to reports from ESPN, after the incident which has left a young child with life-threatening injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robert Maxwell rose from poverty -- and corrupted daughter Ghislaine...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/how-robert-maxwell-rose-from-poverty-and-corrupted-daughter-ghislaine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within 72 hours of her birth, Ghislaine Maxwell’s life was twisted by tragedy. Baby Ghislaine was the ninth child born to Robert Maxwell, the self-made millionaire publisher, and his wife Betty. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NISSAN 'office pod' imagines new kind of remote working...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/nissan-concept-office-pod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inspired by the new realities of the Covid-19 era, the concept camper features a retractable office for remote workers and digital nomads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: Migrants Force Biden to Confront Border Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/06/migrant-families-force-biden-to-confront-new-border-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — President Biden’s first immigration crisis has already begun as thousands of families have surged toward the southwestern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race is on...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/learn-on-mars-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;February is a big month for Mars exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Deficit, Met Considers Selling Art to Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/05/facing-deficit-met-considers-selling-art-to-help-pay-the-bills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a potential shortfall of $150 million because of the pandemic, the Metropolitan Museum of Art has begun conversations with auction houses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald's Senate Trial to Be Held With Signs of Siege All Around...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-senate-trial-to-be-held-with-signs-of-siege-all-around/ar-BB1drCOo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s Senate trial will be enveloped by a thick security cordon of razor-wire-topped fencing, National Guard troops and armed police officers protecting lawmakers -- a stark reminder of the violent assault on the Capitol that touched off his unprecedented second impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Thinking we are unique is arrogant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210206-harvard-astronomer-argues-that-alien-vessel-paid-us-a-visit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard astronomer argues that alien vessel paid us a visit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutated virus may reinfect people already stricken once...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/mutated-virus-may-reinfect-people-already-stricken-once-with-covid-19-sparking-debate-and-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trial of an experimental coronavirus vaccine detected the most sobering signal yet that people who have recovered from infections are not completely protected against a variant that originated in South Africa and is spreading rapidly, preliminary data presented this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED PLANET: China probe sends back first image of Mars; Landing nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210206-china-s-space-probe-sends-back-first-image-of-mars-ahead-of-this-year-s-landing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Tianwen-1 probe has sent back its first image of Mars, the national space agency said, as the mission prepares to touch down on the Red Planet later this year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
