<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Makes Contingency Plans in Case Russia Uses Its Most Powerful Weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/u-s-makes-contingency-plans-in-case-russia-uses-its-most-powerful-weapons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has assembled a team of national security officials to sketch out scenarios of how to respond if Russian President Vladimir Putin unleashes his stockpiles of chemical, biological or nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Defense Minister 'Vanishes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putins-defence-minister-vanishes-26536281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergei Shoigu has not been seen for 12 days and old footage or pictures have been shown of him on TV, say reports in opposition media - he was mentioned in a Kremlin report on March 18 but no visuals of him were shown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activist Publishes Redacted Version of Classified Military UFO Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7dnex/activist-publishes-redacted-version-of-classified-military-ufo-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The classified version of the much-hyped UFO report describes the “shapes” of UFOs, is far more interesting than the one released to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Scott Tallies Her Donations So Far: $12 Billion to 1,257 Groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mackenzie-scott-tallies-her-donations-so-far-12-billion-to-1-257-groups/ar-AAVqeGr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Caught Checking TWITTER Mentions After Dustup...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/ted-cruz-caught-checking-his-twitter-mentions-minutes-after-performative-hearing-dustup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Ted Cruz went full Ted Cruz during the confirmation hearings of Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson which he followed by checking his Twitter mentions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hong Kong Went from 'Zero' to World's Highest Death Rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dgaz3/hong-kong-zero-covid-china-highest-death-rate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city is now reporting more COVID-19 deaths every day than it did over the first two years of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The people cloning pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220322-why-dont-we-hear-about-cloning-anymore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From duplicate dogs to modern mammoths, cloning has come a long way since Dolly the sheep took her first tentative steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to recuse from HARVARD race case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-supreme-court-pick-jackson-202159213.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Supreme Court nominee Ketanji Brown Jackson on Wednesday said that if confirmed to the lifetime job she would recuse herself from a major upcoming case challenging the race-conscious admissions policy Harvard University uses to increase its number of Black and Hispanic students. Jackson, President Joe Biden's nominee to become the first Black woman to serve on the high court, made the comment during the third day of her Senate Judiciary Committee confirmation hearing. Jackson is a Harvard graduate and a current member of the Ivy League school's Board of Overseers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho law bans abortion after 6 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/idaho-governor-signs-bill-banning-abortion-weeks-modeled/story?id=83629542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Brad Little questioned whether the law would withstand legal challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA formally declares 'war crimes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/23/politics/us-russia-war-crimes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government has formally declared that members of the Russian armed forces have committed war crimes in Ukraine, Secretary of State Antony Blinken said in a statement Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside rare meeting with general in Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/23/politics/us-russia-general-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare face-to-face meeting between Russian and US military officials last week led to an "outburst" of emotion from a normally stoic Russian general, a "revealing moment" that the Americans present believe hinted at larger morale problems in Russia's military, according to a closely held US military readout of what transpired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 House GOPers to cohost fundraiser for Cheney challenger...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/23/republicans-fundraiser-liz-cheney-challenger-00019758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheney faces a Trump-backed GOP primary challenge in Wyoming from Harriet Hageman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Silicon Valley Prophet Sees on Horizon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/23/what-the-silicon-valley-prophet-sees-on-the-horizon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stewart Brand paused near the end of a steep trail just a quarter of a mile short of a cactus-laden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic relief money spent on hotel, ballpark, ski slopes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-business-florida-new-york-1c54ec32b2e31ed10bb1628379763425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Thanks to a sudden $140 million cash infusion, officials in Broward County, Florida, recently broke ground on a high-end hotel that will have views of the Atlantic Ocean and an 11,000-square-foot spa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange marries long-term partner in ceremony at UK prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220323-wikileaks-founder-assange-marries-long-term-partner-in-ceremony-at-uk-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange married his long-term partner Stella Moris inside a British high-security prison on Wednesday at a small ceremony attended by just four guests, two official witnesses…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000 killed, wounded, captured or MIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/23/up-to-40000-russian-soldiers-killed-wounded-captured-or-mia-nato-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has previously denied confirming any reported estimates on the number of Russian troops that have been removed from battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. says The Don asked him to 'rescind '20 election'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/23/mo-brooks-says-trump-asked-him-to-rescind-election-remove-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Mo Brooks says Donald Trump suggested a plan to oust Joe Biden from the White House and call a new election that could restore Trump to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 hospitalized after London Olympic pool chlorine gas leak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-sports-health-europe-london-e1bc16f34dcd0287f1dc48693808f45a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A swimming pool in London's Olympic park was evacuated Wednesday and several people were treated by ambulance workers after an incident involving the “release of a gas.” The Queen Elizabeth Olympic Park in east London, built for the 2012 Games in London, said on Twitter that the incident took place at the Aquatics Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body composting: 'Green' burial trend takes root in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20220323-body-composting-green-burial-trend-takes-root-in-usa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No paycheck for popes, Francis says...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220323-no-paycheck-for-popes-francis-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is rash, bad at football and sometimes frustrated at not having his own cash to spend: Francis may wear papal cassocks, but they hide a normal man beneath, he says in a new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker Says PA Should Move To 4-Day Workweek...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2022/03/22/pennsylvania-4-day-32-hour-workweek/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A state representative says it’s time for Pennsylvania to consider a 32-hour workweek for state employees – and the rest of us, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson defends record anew on day 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ketanji-brown-jackson-hearing-day-3-live-updates-067237399cff8c056beeb410c34c4ff9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court nominee Ketanji Brown Jackson is returning to the Senate for a third day of hearings. Live updates here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Losses exceed Soviet losses in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-702073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland's special services asked the foreign ministry on Wednesday to expel 45 Russian diplomats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS PRICE STIMULUS CHECKS NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-price-stimulus-checks-proposals-head-to-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are a few proposals that could involve Americans getting a stimulus check to ease the pain of the rising gas prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100 MONTHLY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stimulus-check-gas-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of bills in Congress would offer stimulus payments and rebates to help Americans cope with soaring gas prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland expelling dozens 'pretending to be diplomats'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/russia/599353-poland-expelling-dozes-of-russians-pretending-to-be-diplomats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland has expelled dozens of Russians who were "pretending to be diplomats,” the country's interior minister announced Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>570K chickens to be destroyed in Nebraska fight against bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/599352-570k-chickens-to-be-destroyed-in-nebraska-fight-against-bird-flu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nebraska Department of Agriculture (NDA) announced on Tuesday that it has confirmed a case of the highly contagious bird flu in a commercial flock of 570,000 broiler chickens and that the birds will be "humanely depopulated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New-Home Sales Decline for Second Month...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-home-sales-declined-february-140914503.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sales of new U.S. homes fell in February for a second month, suggesting high prices and rising mortgage rates may be keeping prospective buyers on the sidelines.Most Read from BloombergWhere Mornings Would Get Darker Under Permanent Daylight Savings TimeChina Jet’s Nosedive From 29,000 Feet Baffles Crash SpecialistsChina Plane Crash Update: Voice Recorder Sent for AnalysisUkraine Update: Zelenskiy Will Join NATO Summit Via Video LinkPurchases of new single-family homes decreased 2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Cup Of Cranberries A Day Keeps Heart Disease Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-cranberries-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eating just 100 grams of cranberries per day contributes to particularly robust cardiac functioning in healthy men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO to bolster troops in Bulgaria, Hungary, Romania, Slovakia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/23/nato-leaders-slated-to-bolster-troop-presence-in-bulgaria-hungary-romania-and-slovakia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine, which has sought NATO membership since 2002, is bordered by four NATO allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Troops Turning on Each Other: 'Sh*tshow'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sh-tshow-russian-troops-now-112804337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irina Rybakova/Press Service of the Ukrainian Ground Forces/Handout via ReutersTwo Russian soldiers have been caught venting about Putin’s “bullshit” war against Ukraine in an intercepted phone call as devastating losses reportedly led one soldier to drive over his colonel with a tank.“Basically, it’s a shitshow here, I’ll put it that way,” an unnamed soldier near Mykolaiv in southern Ukraine can be heard telling a colleague in a recording released by Ukraine’s Security Service late Tuesday.Afte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Satellite Hack Has Victims Far Beyond Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/viasat-internet-hack-ukraine-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest hack since Russia’s war began knocked thousands of people offline. The spillover extends deep into Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witch-hunt among inner circle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10642949/Furious-Putin-begins-witch-hunt-inner-circle-growing-wary-close-allies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergei Shoigu's public appearances have been significantly curtailed in the past week, while his younger daughter Ksenia, 31, was seen posing in Ukrainian colours of blue and yellow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic mushrooms' could follow in footsteps of cannabis...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/23/psychedelics-magic-mushrooms-cannabis-legalization-00016995</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of states are considering bills to expand research or access to the drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subvariant could go 'wild' in Europe before going global...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/23/omicrons-subvariant-bapoint2-could-spread-wildly-in-europe-epidemiologist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise in cases across the continent is being driven by several causes including the spread of the omicron subvariant, BA.2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adviser Quits and Flees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-adviser-chubais-quits-over-ukraine-war-and-leaves-russia/ar-AAVpfPN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney Ridicules 'Off Course' Attacks From Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/mitt-romney-ridicules-off-course-attacks-of-judge-jackson-from-gop-senators-there-is-no-there-there/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitt Romney (R-UT) believes a number of his GOP colleagues were "off course" in their attacks of Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson during Tuesday's confirmation hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squads ordered to kill deserting soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4956617/putin-orders-execution-squads-kill-own-men-desert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has allegedly ordered execution squads to kill his own men if they try to desert his Ukraine invasion. The Russian tyrant expected a swift quick victory when he ordered the invasion …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR ON BORDER: Cartel member spotted 'aiming AK47 at Texas patrol chopper'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4955386/escalating-violence-texas-mexico-border-cartel-shootout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIOLENCE at the US border is escalating as a cartel member has been filmed aiming an AK-47 at a Texas patrol helicopter. The helicopter caught footage of a suspected gunman pointing the weapon in t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for utopian metaverse city with no rules, cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4953398/plan-utopian-metaverse-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN architecture firm has plans to design a metaverse centering around self-governance. Zaha Hadid Architects (ZHA) – one of the world’s most prominent architecture firms – has shared plans to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad ally warns of nuclear dystopia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-ally-says-united-states-075006672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of President Vladimir Putin's closest allies warned the United States on Wednesday that the world could spiral towards a nuclear dystopia if Washington pressed on with what the Kremlin casts as a long-term plot to destroy Russia. Dmitry Medvedev, who was president from 2008 to 2012 and is now deputy secretary of Russia's Security Council, said the United States had conspired to destroy Russia as part of an "primitive game" since the 1991 fall of the Soviet Union. "It means Russia must be humiliated, limited, shattered, divided and destroyed," Medvedev, 56, said in a 550-word statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Bond Plunge Wipes Out $2.6 Trillion, Exceeding Losses of Financial Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/now-worst-drawdown-record-global-005215542.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global bond markets have suffered unprecedented losses since peaking last year, as central banks including the Federal Reserve look to tighten policy to combat surging inflation.Most Read from BloombergWhere Mornings Would Get Darker Under Permanent Daylight Savings TimeChina Jet’s Nosedive From 29,000 Feet Baffles Crash SpecialistsChina Plane Crash Update: One Black Box Located; Pilot DetailsUkraine Update: Zelenskiy Will Join NATO Summit Via Video LinkThe Bloomberg Global Aggreg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Docs Show DOJ Spying on 'VERITAS' Journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/22/project-veritas-feds-secretly-accessed-emails-00019247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer for hidden-camera-sting producer says prosecutors misled court, improperly prolonged gag orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurch co-founder resigns over complaints of unwelcome behavior to women...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/australian-megachurch-co-founder-resigns-over-complaints-of-unwelcome-behavior-to-women/ar-AAVoy4F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hellscape' in Mariupol where 100,000 trapped...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220323-live-hellscape-in-mariupol-where-100-000-trapped-biden-heads-to-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were injured and buildings damaged in Russian strikes on a residential area of the Ukrainian capital, officials said on Wednesday. US President Joe Biden is heading to Europe on Wednesday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large tornado strikes New Orleans, causing serious damage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tornadoes-storms-new-orleans-hurricanes-weather-1b01d30a0719a44489b159cd6ba92a45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARABI, La. (AP) — A tornado tore through parts of New Orleans and its suburbs Tuesday night, flipping cars, ripping roofs off homes and killing at least one person in an area of Louisiana pummeled by Hurricane Katrina 17 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham asks her to rate religious faith 'on scale of 1 to 10'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sen-graham-presses-ketanji-brown-jackson-to-rate-her-religious-faith-e2-80-98on-a-scale-of-1-to-10-e2-80-99/ar-AAVnsBI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissent Brews Over Putin Leadership...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/22/as-russia-stalls-in-ukraine-dissent-brews-over-putins-leadership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In January, the head of a group of serving and retired Russian military officers declared that invading Ukraine would be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks new sanctions, help for Ukrainians in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-biden-migration-world-war-ii-warsaw-606513344e8f0d96152e43f5ee82b75a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With Europe facing its most precarious future since World War II, President Joe Biden will huddle with key allies in Brussels and Warsaw this week as the leaders try to prevent Russia’s war on Ukraine from spiraling into an even greater catastrophe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
