<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How deadliest ever female sniper 'Lady Death' shot 309 Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3550775/sniper-lady-death-world-war-2-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS GERMAN troops poured into the Soviet Union in the midst of World War 2, Lyudmila Pavlichenko rushed to join the Red Army. Out-of-touch recruiters found the prospect of a 24-year-old woman joinin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One person turns up at anti-lockdown protest in Auckland...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/27/new-zealand-police-break-up-one-person-anti-lockdown-protest-in-auckland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram account had called on people to get involved in the Queen Street demonstration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darthgator nearly ripped trainer's arm off. She can't wait to work with him again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-alligator-named-darthgator-nearly-ripped-his-trainer-e2-80-99s-arm-off-she-can-e2-80-99t-wait-to-work-with-him-again/ar-AANOewg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m the one that made a mistake,” the trainer said. “Darthgator was just an alligator doing alligator things.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress hit with $46 million tax fine as China targets celeb culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-actress-hit-with-46-mn-tax-fine-as-china-targets-celebrity-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress hit with $46 mn tax fine as China targets celebrity culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive California fire creeps toward Lake Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/videos-f85b2d338bb942eb8d8e7f4310cdbca1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually impaired Paralympian hit by self-driving bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-visually-impaired-paralympian-hit-by-self-driving-bus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visually impaired Paralympian hit by self-driving bus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where World's Superyachts Are Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/superyachts-sail-to-europe-for-summer-as-covid-restrictions-ease</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where the World’s Superyachts Are Right Now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse dewormer flying off shelves as remedy despite FDA warnings, side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/ivermectin-flying-off-north-texas-shelves-as-a-covid-19-remedy-despite-fda-warnings-side/article_53527e72-ee9d-5ea5-a9fa-5c229499dc81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — For the past month or so, store manager Noah Krzykowski has watched new customers trickle into the Irving Feed Store, all looking for the same thing — ivermectin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing scrutiny over Elder roils election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569458-growing-scrutiny-over-elder-roils-california-recall-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flood of scrutiny over conservative radio host Larry Elder’s California gubernatorial recall bid over past conduct and controversial remarks is giving Republicans headaches and Democrats hope in the surprisingly close contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to Strike Louisiana Exactly 16 Years after Katrina?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/26/tropical-depression-9-could-become-hurricane-ida/5598203001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Ida is aimed at the Gulf Coast and could be a major hurricane when it arrives, possibly by the end of the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Trims Flying Schedule After Worker Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/southwest-airlines-trims-flying-schedule-after-worker-outcry/ar-AANMOub?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines Co. will reduce its flight schedule for the last four months of the year after employees assailed the discount carrier for understaffing operations during a summer marred by delays and cancellations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN NIGHMARE CHOICE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9930749/Biden-decide-leave-Americans-risk-U-S-deaths-Kabul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden on Thursday said he would hunt down the ISIS-K terrorists behind the Kabul attacks, but must do so with limited intelligence capabilities in Afghanistan following his withdrawal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=89VvlmoNKko</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce furious after unwittingly wearing 'blood diamond'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3547464/beyonce-disappointed-angry-after-unwittingly-wearing-tiffany-blood-diamond/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEYONCE was said to be “disappointed and angry” last night after a £22.9million gem she was pictured wearing was compared to a “blood diamond”. She became the first black woman, and only the fourth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer who shot Ashli Babbitt during Capitol riot breaks silence: 'I saved countless lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officer-who-shot-ashli-babbitt-during-capitol-riot-breaks-silence-n1277736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with NBC News, Lt. Michael Byrd said he opened fire only as a “last resort” after the rioters failed to comply with his commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/the-unbearable-summer/ar-AANLeQ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disastrous environmental events are converging like never before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prisons to close amid staff shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/special-reports/florida-prisons/article253769043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Department of Corrections will soon close multiple prisons in North Florida, a last-ditch effort to grapple with severe staff shortages, according to a union representative who talked to Corrections Secretary Mark Inch about the move on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Dressing Up Like FedEx and Arresting People for Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/26/cops-are-dressing-up-like-fedex-guys-and-arresting-people-for-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known agreement allows police officers to seize packages at FedEx sorting centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 TROOPS KILLED</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3544925/kabul-airport-explosion-taliban-afghanistan-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIRTEEN US troops and at least 90 Afghans have been killed in ISIS suicide bomb attacks at Kabul Airport. Two explosions rocked the airport in Afghanistan yesterday just hours before the evacuatio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. provided names of Americans, Afghan allies to evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/26/us-officials-provided-taliban-with-names-of-americans-afghan-allies-to-evacuate-506957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Basically, they just put all those Afghans on a kill list,” said one defense official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS CLAIMS RESPONSIBILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/large-explosion-at-abbey-gate-at-the-kabul-airport-report-677790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terror group ISIS-K claimed responsibility for the suicide bombing attacks near Kabul airport that have killed over 70 civilians and 13 US troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISASTER</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/inside-seth-moulton-secret-kabul-trip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials condemned the unauthorized mission as a reckless stunt. But the congressman says it was critical oversight of a crisis he tried to prevent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR AT KABUL AIRPORT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-evacuations-kabul-9e457201e5bbe75a4eb1901fedeee7a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Two suicide bombers and gunmen attacked crowds of Afghans flocking to Kabul's airport Thursday, transforming a scene of desperation into one of horror in the waning days of an airlift for those fleeing the Taliban takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen 'taken shots' at military aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42151/american-troops-confirmed-killed-in-kabul-airport-terror-bombing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A complex attack on the heart of America's evacuation operation in Kabul has caused the deaths of multiple U.S. servicepeople and even more Afghans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time's Up CEO resigns in wake of Cuomo scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/26/tina-tchen-times-up-ceo-resigns-in-wake-of-andrew-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time’s Up CEO Tina Tchen resigned Thursday in the wake of revelations that leaders of the sexual harassment victims’ advocacy group advised former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on how to handle allegations made against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's MICROSOFT Hack May Have Had Bigger Purpose Than Just Spying...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/26/1013501080/chinas-microsoft-hack-may-have-had-a-bigger-purpose-than-just-spying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China broke into tens of thousands of email accounts in January. Now officials fear the breach wasn't just about spying. It was to build the next generation of artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida adds 901 deaths, largest single-day increase in pandemic history...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article253766203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida on Thursday reported 21,765 more COVID-19 cases and 901 deaths to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, according to Miami Herald calculations of CDC data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden Art Dealer Served Jail Time, Allegedly Defrauded Investor...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/hunter-biden-art-dealer-served-jail-time-and-allegedly-defrauded-investor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The art dealer who the White House has tapped to vet Hunter Biden’s art sales for ethical conflicts was sentenced to three months in jail in 1998 for threatening to stab a man to death and was later accused of defrauding an investor in a messy 2016 lawsuit, raising alarms with ethics watchdogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Dakota AG gets fines, but walks in pedestrian death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/south-dakota-0ec1a028f08df4b63718cf12c9d232da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT PIERRE, S.D. (AP) — South Dakota Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg pleaded no contest Thursday to a pair of misdemeanor traffic charges over a crash last year that killed a pedestrian, avoiding jail time despite bitter complaints from the victim’s family that he was being too lightly punished for actions they called “inexcusable.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 remain as clock ticking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-business-kabul-dc2898e1ff9907f3be86347876ed6b52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Joe Biden is set to speak following the deadly explosions outside the airport in Kabul that killed 12 U.S. service members and scores of Afghans. The White House says Biden will address the nation from the White House at 5 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking hearts and minds: The strategy of surrender...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/opinion/commentary/2021/08/24/breaking-hearts-and-minds-the-strategy-of-surrender/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is more than just an issue of international credibility, it is also one of national security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell barricaded herself in prison conference room, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9929661/Ghislaine-Maxwell-barricaded-prison-conference-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have claimed that Ghislaine Maxwell tried to 'barricade' herself in the video conference room in prison with a cart of legal documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas, Missouri fighting for nurses as beds fill up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-bidding-war-kansas-missouri-hospitals-fighting-for-travel-nurses-as-beds-fill-up/ar-AANMyVp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shifts are often long, the locations unfamiliar. No family or friends may be nearby. But the demand for travel nurses has skyrocketed as the COVID-19 case surge spawned by the delta variant is crushing hospitals across the United States. At a moment when the number of nurses at a facility may determine how many patients can be treated, advertised positions in Kansas and Missouri top $5,600 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man High On Mushrooms Shoots 2 At Miami Beach Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/25/miami-beach-shooter-chose-victims-at-random/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 22-year-old man told Miami Beach police he felt empowered and chose to shoot two people at random Tuesday evening, killing one and wounding another, after getting high on mushrooms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gain of function' experiments with supercharged pathogens lack controls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-science-in-the-shadows/ar-AANLOZ0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key policy revisions have loosened oversight of NIH-funded "gain of function" research despite some experts' fears it could inadvertently cause a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of dating jerks? Army here to help...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/08/26/tired-of-dating-jerks-the-army-is-here-to-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take your dating game up a notch with this Army workshop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many More Deaths?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-6df4471c64e40e7e319ae368d4c1db0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is projected to see nearly 100,000 more COVID-19 deaths between now and Dec. 1, according to the nation's most closely watched forecasting model. But health experts say that toll could be cut in half if nearly everyone wore a mask in public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Capone's granddaughters selling his possessions, fearing wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/mobster-al-capone-s-granddaughters-are-selling-his-possessions-partly-out-of-fear-of-wildfires/ar-AANKihu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women feared that a wildfire could threaten their Northern California homes and destroy the 174 family photographs and knickknacks they say show a warmer side to the infamous mob boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett-Biden meeting delayed due to Kabul attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/kabul-bombing-currently-not-affecting-bennett-biden-meeting-report-677799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett is in Washington on his first visit since becoming prime minister in June and was expected to meet Biden this afternoon at 6 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,811 recovered Israeli patients got reinfected...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/4811-recovered-israeli-covid-patients-got-reinfected-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women warned to stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3545871/taliban-tell-women-to-stay-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Taliban has warned women not to go out to work as militants now ruling the streets need “equality training” to know how to speak to them. The jihadi militants have already promised …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters cover Buckingham Palace fountain in BLOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3545151/extinction-rebellion-activists-cover-buckingham-palace-fountain-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACTIVISTS linked to Extinction Rebellion have covered a Buckingham Palace fountain in fake blood in a protest against the Queen and the royal family. Shameless eco-warriors clutching signs reading …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Diana biopic drops trailer......</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3539354/spencer-movie-trailer-kristen-stewart-princess-diana-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KRISTEN Stewart’s fans are blown away by the stunning new teaser trailer and poster for the actress’ upcoming Princess Diana movie, Spencer. The 31-year-old transformed into the late royal in the n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Mad-Dough: Is MSNBC Host Worth $30 Million Year Without Nightly Show?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rachel-maddow-msnbc-30-million-deal-worth-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry insiders say MSNBC is taking a "gamble," but agree the star primetime host is worth the network's money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASTY BONE AT CITY'S POPULAR DOG PARK WAS HUMAN, COPS SAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article253756298.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They didn’t say if a dog found it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Cook Poised to Get $750 Million Payout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/apple-ceo-poised-to-get-24750-million-final-payout-from-award/ar-AANLP9h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Cook, Apple Inc.’s chief executive officer, will this week collect the 10th and final tranche of the pay deal he received a decade ago after he took over the top job from co-founder Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who was hospitalized with virus comes home to find infected husband dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-woman-hospitalized-with-covid-19-comes-home-to-find-husband-dead-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Central Florida woman fought for her life in the hospital, survived, and thought she'd seen the worst of COVID -- until she went home and made a shocking discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Natural immunity superior to Covid vaccine?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/bombshell-study-finds-natural-immunity-superior-to-vaccination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major study conducted by Israeli researchers into natural immunity has found that immunity acquired via infection from Covid-19 is superior to immunity from the Pfizer vaccine. Researchers at Maccabi Healthcare and Tel Aviv University compared the outcomes of over 76,000 Israelis in three groups: the doubly vaccinated (with the Pfizer vaccine), the previously infected [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Rise Has Own Party Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/larry-elders-california-recall-rise-has-even-republicans-uneasy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELS..</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/09L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/refresh/AL092021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/144701_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Major hurricane threat developing for US Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/major-hurricane-ida-threat-gulf-coast-louisiana-alabama-texas-mississippi/1006485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say the likelihood is increasing that a storm -- still only a depression as of Thursday morning -- could rapidly develop into a Category 3 hurricane and threaten the U.S. in a matter of days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN:  APPLE PRIVACY DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edwardsnowden.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Under His Eye,” she says. The right farewell. “Under His Eye,” I reply, and she gives a little nod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW SULLIVAN</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To see what is in front of one's nose needs a constant struggle," - Orwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Storm Threatens to Roil Gulf, Hit Texas or Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxan.com/weather/weather-blog/first-warning-tropical-system-may-develop-in-gulf-of-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it develops into a tropical storm, it would be named Ida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Rise Has Own Party Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-26/larry-elder-s-california-recall-rise-has-even-republicans-uneasy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular conservative radio talk show host’s entry into California’s gubernatorial recall race has upended predictions for the outcome as both Democrats and some Republicans now work to defeat him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows militants taking joyride in Black Hawk helicopter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/26/taliban-appear-to-take-joyride-in-us-made-helicopter-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It remains unclear exactly how many former Afghan military aircraft are under Taliban control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Nearly Collides With Plane At Logan Airport...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/25/iteam-drone-plane-near-collision-nahant-beach-logan-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A near-collision between a plane and drone near Logan Airport put the Massachusetts State Police Air Wing on alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery jellyfish-shaped object filmed entering atmosphere...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3544462/mystery-jellyfish-shaped-object-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS “jellyfish-shaped object” which suddenly appeared in the Earth’s atmosphere has stunned local Russians.   Residents in the Amur Oblast region spotted the glowing object flying overhead…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Cook Poised to Get $750 Million Payout...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/apple-ceo-poised-to-get-750-million-final-payout-from-big-award</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook will this week collect the 10th and final tranche of the pay deal he received a decade ago after he took over from Jobs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
