<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REVOLUTION ON LEFT</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Sanders-ascent-forces-reckoning-for-Democrats-15078704.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders has seized a commanding position in the Democratic presidential race, building a diverse coalition that is driving his liberal movement toward the cusp of a takeover of a major political party.  The senator's ascendancy, though years in the making, is forcing a sudden reckoning in the Democratic Party's hierarchy as centrist politicians and their wealthy benefactors grapple with the upheaval brought by an electorate not only hungry to defeat President Donald Trump but also clamoring for radical change.  After Sanders' resounding victory in Saturday's Nevada caucuses, and with polls showing him on the rise, Democrats are entering a season of open warfare over whether Sanders, I-Vt., is equipped to beat Trump in what could be a brutal general election. The senator and his allies insist he could, but his detractors say he is too polarizing to win in November - and could severely cost Democrats in congressional or state races if Republicans use Sanders' self-description as a Democratic socialist to paint all Democrats as extreme.  The Sanders insurgency is the culmination of angry grievances that have simmered for the past decade among liberals who say Washington has all but ignored the problems of income inequality, health-care access and climate change.  "The party has shifted to the left, and I don't think many of the more traditional, legacy leaders of the party got it," said Andrew Stern, a longtime former president of the Service Employees International Union. "The good news for Bernie Sanders is he's like a broken clock. He's been in the same place for 35 or 40 years in terms of his positions, and the times have found him."  A headstrong, 78-year-old senator, Sanders has galvanized his supporters with an unwavering commitment to their shared cause and rageful critiques of the "billionaire class." They...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies Roger Stone's effort to disqualify her...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/23/roger-stone-judge-berman-jackson-117066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Berman Jackson accuses the defense of abusing the court’s docket with claims of bias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua's last newspaper dared to criticize the government. Then it lost its ink and paper...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/nicaraguas-last-newspaper-dared-to-criticize-the-government-then-it-lost-its-ink-and-paper/ar-BB10iga7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents warn kids against YOUTUBE 'killer Jump Trip Challenge' after deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/parents-warn-kids-against-youtube-21563313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mums and dads have taken to social media to warn kids about the Jump Trip Challenge or Skull-Breaker which has appeared on YouTube and TikTok</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab monkeys infected with coronavirus in desperate bid to find vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/lab-monkeys-infected-coronavirus-desperate-21559290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US monkeys were treated with a new experimental drug to combat the respiratory disease, which has spread across the globe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SET FOR SPIRAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/us-futures-coronavirus-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of 9:45 p.m. ET Sunday, Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 392 points lower, pointing to an implied opening plunge of 385.41 points for the index on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie reveals free childcare plan for preschoolers...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bernie-sanders-60-minutes-free-childcare-plan-d500ce83-7b95-4e03-89aa-c08ecde9bc5c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have a tax on wealth to pay for that," he told Anderson Cooper on "60 Minutes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPING:  Three Weinstein accusers could send producer to prison for life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-weinstein-accusers-could-send-195906337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the jurors in Harvey Weinstein’s sexual assault trial wrestle with a pair of charges that could send the fallen movie mogul to prison for life, the testimony of three women who don’t even appear in his indictment could help seal his fate.They’re known as Molineux witnesses in New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz Memorial Rips Bezos &amp; Pacino TV Series For Fake History... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/auschwitz-memorial-hunters-amazon-prime-nazi-hunters-1202866536/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: Hunters creator and executive producer David Weil has responded to the backlash in regards to the new Amazon series about a band of Nazi hunters in 1977. As Weil pointed out, the new series…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drives Jeep off 6-story roof of Los Angeles-area garage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95409b68a3659f250aadbcb13c4659d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA MONICA, Calif. (AP) — A man drove his Jeep off the the sixth floor of a Los Angeles-area parking garage early Sunday and was taken to a hospital in critical condition, authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd person in days killed by Mardi Gras float in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/556c18effc1de332d6cb3b970946d4a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — A man was struck and killed by a Mardi Gras float during a raucous weekend street parade in New Orleans, becoming the second person in days killed along a parade route during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000 bees attack police, firefighters in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article240565296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body found hanging lifeless from tree in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-central-park-body-hanged-tree-20200223-mtwcoo4yjvg4ngdmkctk3key6e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops responded to the scene inside the park near Fifth Ave. and E. 74th St. as shocked onlookers passed by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens shortages of 150 drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-threatens-drug-shortage-318c9e7b-5d92-4a5e-b992-2478023c6d01.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is a huge supplier of the ingredients used in many drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims results 'plagued with errors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/buttigieg-campaign-nevada-errors-inconsistencies-dd412de1-066e-4f59-858d-9de61684a9aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign said it received more than 200 incident reports from precincts around the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Matthews faces calls for resignation after comparing victory to Nazi invasion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/484237-chris-matthews-faces-calls-for-resignation-after-comparing-sanders-victory-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Chris Matthews is under fire after comparing Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders' path has echoes of Trump's 2016 campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfcd0845c5bc45c2103832d55d0fed3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A burn-it-down candidate is topping a splintered field of more moderate contenders and setting the party’s establishment wing on edge. It’s how Donald Trump began his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Speakers 'Accidentally' Recording Conversations 19 Times Per Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/dont-worry-alexa-and-friends-only-record-you-up-to-19-times-a-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you ever wondered how often your smart speaker accidentally activates itself? A study from Northeastern University tried to find oiut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia braces for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/politics/federal/no-need-for-face-masks-business-as-usual-says-australia-s-chief-medical-officer-20200223-p543gf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Brendan Murphy said there had been no community transmission of coronavirus in Australia, but warnings have been issued about a possible Victorian pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics Could Be Moved or Canceled Due...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5786657/tokyo-olympics-coronavirus-asia-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hypothetical situation is slowly becoming more tangible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Shorter Men More Likely To Develop Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/height-advantage-taller-young-men-have-lower-risk-of-developing-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that men who are taller than average in early adulthood have a lowered risk of developing dementia later in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye, Out West...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/23/style/kanye-west-cody-wyoming.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is the superstar doing in Wyoming?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Were these 6 Chinese trespassers confused tourists or spies? FBI wants to know...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/were-these-six-chinese-trespassers-confused-tourists-or-spies-fbi-n1140496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI counterintelligence agents are probing whether the spate of incidents at Trump's Mar-a-Lago club and a military site might be part of a coordinated espionage effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil 'Mad' Mike Hughes killed in homemade rocket crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/23/mad-mike-hughes-dies-homemade-rocket-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-styled daredevil “Mad” Mike Hughes died Saturday after a rocket in which he launched himself crashed into the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks quarantine in CA city...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/23/costa-mesa-california-coronavirus-quarantine-block/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge issued a temporary restraining order to halt the transportation of anyone who has tested positive for the new coronavirus to Costa Mesa, California, a city of 110,000 in the heart of Orange County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle campaign headquarters vandalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/23/bernie-sanders-seattle-campaign-headquarters-vanda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after someone threw a large rock through a glass door at Bernie Sanders’ Seattle presidential campaign headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviscerates conventional wisdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/22/bernie-sanders-nevada-2020-election-116762</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Nevada, he exposed his main rivals as weak, divided, and grasping at increasingly tenuous arguments about their viability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Tax Fight Emerges as Global Economic Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/digital-tax-fight-emerges-as-global-economic-threat/ar-BB10hgDC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grenell now highest-ranking openly gay official in US govt history...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/22/richard-grenell-now-highest-ranking-openly-gay-official-in-us-government-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump made history this week after appointing Richard Grenell to serve as acting Director of National Intelligence. The new job, a cabinet-level position, makes Grenell the highest servin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How bizarre, monster fish hoodwinked researchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/22/hoodwinker-sunfish-discovery-north-america-citizen-scientists/4503250002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bizarre sunfish washed up in California last year and created a worldwide furor: Scientists were shocked to find the hoodwinker so far from home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS whistleblower during Obama era found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/philip-haney-dhs-whistleblower-during-obama-era-found-dead-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department of Homeland Security (DHS) whistleblower and Fox News contributor Phil Haney was found dead in Amador County, Calif., on Friday, according to a press release from local authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyson Fury appears to lick blood off Deontay Wilder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/23/tyson-fury-appears-to-lick-blood-off-deontay-wilders-neck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did Tyson Fury lick Deontay Wilder’s blood? That appeared to be the case during his seventh-round TKO victory on Saturday night at the MGM Grand Garden in Las Vegas. In the sixth round, Fury …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says 'enemies' used virus to sabotage as death toll rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-accuses-enemies-using-virus-sabotage-vote-090204026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran confirmed eight deaths from the novel coronavirus on Sunday, the highest toll of any country outside China, as the supreme leader accused foreign media of trying to use the outbreak to sabotage a general election. The final results of the parliamentary election are due on Sunday, two days after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big jump in virus cases in Italy despite lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bda63e372d4d0e5f393744e2cff6fdf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy's number of cases of the new corona virus leaped upward, with dozens of new confirmed cases reported in Lombardy, the northern region which includes the country's financial...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow targets Chinese with raids amid fears...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/moscow-targets-chinese-raids-amid-virus-fears-69157387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian authorities are going to significant lengths to keep the virus in China from surfacing in Moscow</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
