<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Putin New Year letter to Trump: Moscow open for dialogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-usa-dialogue/putin-in-new-year-letter-to-trump-says-moscow-is-open-for-dialogue-idUSKCN1OT07W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, in a New Year letter to his U.S. counterpart D...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FACEBOOK sorry for banning Franklin Graham...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/living/religion/article223714480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook banned Franklin Graham for 24 hours, the North Carolina evangelist posted. The social media giant described the 2016 post about Bruce Springsteen’s opposition to HB2, the bathroom bill, as hate speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside erotic New Year's Eve 'Illuminati Ball'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/29/inside-this-sexy-eyes-wide-shut-style-new-years-eve-bash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this day and age, risqué can be risky. But Cynthia von Buhler is bringing sexy back to NYC. The illustrator has thrown, by her own estimation, hundreds of over-the-top parties over almost three …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several Injured After Jet Bridge Collapse At BWI Airport...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/12/29/reports-of-jetway-collapse-at-bwi-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jetway has reportedly collapsed at Baltimore-Washington International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Original Woodstock site to host 50th anniversary concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/13cc53be5d4547d09ca5ded3c6b6ca16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHEL, N.Y. (AP) — A three-day music festival will be held in August 2019 at the original Woodstock concert site to mark the 50th anniversary of the historic event. The Bethel Woods Center for the Arts, a concert venue built on the original Woodstock site, announced Thursday that it will host the golden anniversary event Aug. 16-18. The center says performers will include "prominent and emerging artists spanning multiple genres and decades." The venue says talks by "leading futurists and retro-tech experts" will also be featured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Overdose? What Happened to KTLA Anchor Found Dead in Motel?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/28/what-happened-to-l-a-tv-anchor-chris-burrous-43-found-dead-from-possible-drug-overdose-at-suburban-days-inn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Los Angeles media, the death of 43 year old news anchor Chris Burrous is being described as “he died.” In the New York papers, where we’re awake, the Post and the Daily News ac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious space sounds picked up in eerie recording by remote Antarctic base...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1064700/Space-sounds-Antarctic-base-BAS-aliens-mysterious</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS working at a remote research station in Antarctica have recorded “eerie” sounds from space when trying to pick up lightning activity signals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSAULTS CUSTOMER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6538155/Vape-shop-worker-launches-furious-rant-against-Trump-supporter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump supporter Ian Furgeson, 36, filmed himself getting kicked out of a vape shop in Georgia where the employee launched a hysterical and expletive rant against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New laws putting California further at odds with president...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3444b71e2ede48e99f6d6e9d58d6fd56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California Gov. Jerry Brown is leaving office Jan. 7 after signing more than 1,000 laws in his last year, further positioning the state as a bastion of liberal activism and goad to President Donald Trump. The laws, most of which take effect Tuesday, ease criminal sentences, tighten gun restrictions and address climate change, gender discrimination and sexual harassment. The Democratic governor approved 1,016 laws, the most in any of his last eight years in office. His 201 vetoes also were the most during his final two terms, as lawmakers passed a record number of measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family demands answers as former National Guardsman's body returns from China...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/29/family-demands-answers-as-former-national-guardsmans-body-returns-from-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of a National Guardsman-turned-health care exec who died on a business trip to China is expected to arrive today at JFK. And his family plans to conduct an autopsy to determine the ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell at center of shutdown impasse -- uncharacteristically disengaged...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/McConnell-at-center-of-shutdown-impasse-but-13497233.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The federal government has been partially shut down for a week, hundreds of thousands of workers are furloughed, but there's no sign of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, the veteran dealmaker who's brokered an end to so many Washington impasses. McConnell is home in Kentucky, and the senator's spokesman, Donald Stewart, said it's up to President Donald Trump and the Democrats to come up with a deal to end the stalemate over funding for Trump's border wall. In other words, in McConnell's view, it's not on him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Racist Motherf*cker!'</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-unhinged-leftist-has-mental-breakdown-refuses-service-to-trump-supporter-in-vape-shop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vape shop has since fired the irate employee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in UFO sightings...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1064489/TR-3B-UFO-sightings-military-experiments-US-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE has been a shocking rise in alleged TR-3B triangular UFO sightings across the world - with the most recent footage showing the bizarre aircraft close to a US airbase in Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice Cooper: Want my shows far away as possible from politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/dec/29/alice-cooper-i-want-my-shows-to-take-you-as-far-away-as-possible-from-politics-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The musician, 70, on avoiding politics, cheating at golf and having understanding parents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Venezuelans stalking open seas as economy collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/29/pirates-caribbean-venezuelans-stalking-open-seas-economy-collapses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With rich Caribbean fishing grounds on their doorstep, the villagers of Cedros in Trinidad are never short of fishermen's tales to tell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's president-elect plans decree allowing wider gun ownership...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-guns/brazils-president-elect-plans-decree-allowing-wider-gun-ownership-idUSKCN1OS0HN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's far-right President-elect Jair Bolsonaro said on Saturday he plans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Body found in ocean near U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/body-found-ocean-near-u-s-mexico-border-n952936 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body was found near Border Field State Park, the edge of which runs up along the border and includes fencing that stretches into the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Navy couple recreate iconic New York WWII kiss...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6537905/Gay-Navy-couple-recreate-iconic-New-York-WWII-kiss-face-brutal-backlash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Woodington, 33, and husband Kenneth, 30, recreated the iconic WWII kiss. Bryan, a Navy sailor, was returning home to Florida after seven months in the Persian Gulf and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV chef loses prime-time show after 'horsesh*t' Chinese food diss...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/12/28/tv-chef-in-hot-water-after-horsesh-t-chinese-food-diss/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zimmern responded,“I am completely responsible for what I said and I want to apologize to anyone who was offended.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PK-mnbH4s74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vape shop clerk in Atlanta has epic meltdown and assaults based Chad Trump supporter who trolls him mercilessly - calls him the "N word" in front of a Black ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vape Shop Clerk Epic Meltdown Over Trump T-Shirt; Assaults Customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/12/update-xhale-city-vape-shop-fires-racist-trump-hating-liberal-after-screeching-meltdown-caught-on-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FLU SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/28/health/flu-activity-cdc-report-bn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flu activity is increasing in the United States, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong undersea quake reported near Philippines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/davao-oriental-philippines-earthquake-tsunami-warning-today-2018-12-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center lifted its warning for a potential tsunami that could hit coastal areas of the southern Philippine and Indonesia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots to be implanted with REAL BRAINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748890/robots-ai-human-rights-legal-status-eu-proposal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore trying to stem decades-long disappearing act...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c852e9751cd744b7a27fa9333c14d1a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — LaShelle Rollins' rental house in West Baltimore is wedged between a line of derelict properties valued only by street gangs, drug addicts and firefighters conducting arson drills. And even though her family's $700-a-month address sits across from a public school, they are among the only occupants of this desolate block. Life in an emptied-out, rundown cityscape is a slog and Rollins is worn out by all of it: The sounds of late-night interlopers stomping down the stairs of a musty wreck next door; a constant fear of fire set by vandals; the social isolation; the rats. With no faith in a prompt police response, they keep a bat at the ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court ruling puts police murder case of Black Panther back in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/459a3d6e25bd4bcdacc7fc3c7db627b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A court ruling this week puts the police murder case of former Black Panther Mumia Abu-Jamal back in the spotlight years after it drew the attention of Amnesty International, Hollywood celebrities and death penalty opponents worldwide. Abu-Jamal, a one-time taxi driver and radio reporter, emerged over four decades in prison as a vocal critic of the American justice system, especially the racial bias he saw at the heart of his 1982 trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Original Woodstock site to host 50th anniversary concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/408e4eeb26c247eabe7cf2f1566197bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump and Democrats are trading blame for the partial government shutdown but doing little substantive talking with each other as the disruption in federal services and public employees' pay slogs into another weekend. Trump upped the brinkmanship by threatening anew to close the border with Mexico to press Congress to cave to his demand for money to pay for a wall. Democrats vowed to pass legislation restoring the government as soon as they take control of the House on Thursday, but that won't accomplish anything unless Trump and the Republican-controlled Senate go along with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP poll shows high job approval for Trump from veterans...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3b0264d3b4db4c899d98ab3df9902fe4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 6 in 10 military veterans voted for Republican candidates in the November midterm elections, and a similar majority had positive views of President Donald Trump's leadership. But women, the fastest growing demographic group in the military, are defying that vote trend. That's according to AP VoteCast, a nationwide survey of more than 115,000 midterm voters — including more than 4,000 current and former service members — conducted for The Associated Press by NORC at the University of Chicago. It found that veterans overall approved of Trump's job performance, showing high support for the president's handling of border security and his efforts to make the U.S. safer from terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old favorites, outdated attitudes: Can entertainment expire?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3b753464a4e24746a59ffbed5682a4b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The 1940 movie "The Philadelphia Story" opens with a case of domestic assault played for laughs — Cary Grant shoving Katharine Hepburn to the ground by her face while a jaunty musical score plays. Eight decades later, the movie is clearly two things: uneasy fare for a post-#metoo culture — and an enduring American classic. And it's far from the only example of such things. They exist throughout society's pop-culture canon, from movies to TV to music and beyond: pieces of work that have withstood time's passage but that contain actions, words and depictions about race, gender and sexual orientation that we now find questionable at best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia's Volatile Volcano Collapsed -- Now More Explosive...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/indonesias-volatile-child-of-krakatau-collapsed-but-now-its-more-explosive-11546084803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The volcano that unleashed a tsunami and killed more than 400 people has collapsed to about a third of its previous height and is ejecting superheated magma into the sea, magnifying the power of the eruptions and sending ash more than a mile into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Tax State Exodus...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/high-tax-state-exodus-11546037709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growth-friendly states gain population, and it isn’t just the weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIEGEL suspends two senior editors after fake news scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/1229/1019468-spiegel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influential German news weekly Der Spiegel said it has suspended two senior editors following the scandal involving a reporter who admitted faking stories for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirees try to keep cool as stocks tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stockmarket-retirees/u-s-retirees-try-to-keep-cool-as-stocks-tumble-idUSKCN1OR1BW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Farrington, a retiree who turns 75 next month, admits to being in a consta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS MIGRANT RELEASE CONTINUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/texas-shelters-grapple-with-more-migrants-released-by-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shelter director in the Texas border city of El Paso says his agency has served 1,300 people in the last five days after they were released by U.S. immigration authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC launches probe in wake of nationwide 911 outage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/centurylink-outage-that-hit-911-service-spurs-fcc-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disruption affected 911 emergency services nationwide. FCC Chairman Ajit Pai called the problem "particularly troubling" in its "breadth and duration."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt police 'kill 40 militants' in raids after tourist bus blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46708695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The raids follow Friday's deadly tourist bus bombing near the Giza pyramids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living paycheck to paycheck disturbingly common...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/jobs/labor/i-see-no-way-out-living-paycheck-paycheck-is-disturbingly-common-20181228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In light of the partial government shutdown, a heated discussion on Twitter about what it means to get by in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS THROWN A LIFELINE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/28/sears-chairman-eddie-lampert-submits-bit-for-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday was the deadline for buyers to put in their offers to save Sears. The owner of Kmart and Sears filed for bankruptcy in October.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
