<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Alive Inside: How to reach 'vegetative' patients -- aware of everything...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/alive-inside-how-do-we-reach-vegetative-patients-when-tests-show-theyre-aware-of-everything</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not clear how much Jeff Tremblay knows about the role he’s playing in a revolution in the treatment of the catastrophically brain injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs process numbers, count their treats...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/a-new-study-shows-dogs-can-process-numbers-and-theyre-counting-their-treats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Our work not only shows that dogs use a similar part of their brain to process numbers of objects as humans do — it shows that they don’t need to be trained to do it’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New BOEING docs show 'very disturbing' concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-boeing-737max/new-boeing-737-max-documents-show-very-disturbing-employee-concerns-u-s-house-aide-idUSKBN1YS1BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co documents under review by a U.S. congressional panel appear to point t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake, Dangerous Kids Products For Sale On AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/12/24/warning-fake-dangerous-kids-products-are-turning-up-for-sale-on-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was advertised to look like a high end brand, but this car seat is a copycat. Legitimate sellers say it's one of many potentially dangerous kids products sold on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crop duster spreads 100 gallons of holy water on Louisiana town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/crop-duster-spreads-100-gallons-holy-water-louisiana/story?id=67914735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crop duster spread holy water on a Louisiana town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the REDSKINS Plummeted to Rock Bottom...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/nfl/2019/12/24/21035742/washington-redskins-rock-bottom-dan-snyder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The professional football team in the nation’s capital was the hottest ticket in town for decades. But under Dan Snyder’s ownership, the franchise has lost a lot of games and managed to alienate even some of its most dedicated fans. What made one of most unshakable fandoms in America give up on its team?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA plans to dramatically shrink Navy destroyer fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2019/12/24/pentagon-proposes-big-cuts-to-us-navy-destroyer-construction-retiring-13-cruisers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pentagon proposal sent to the white house would cut five destroyers out of the budget over the next five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI iooking into former KY gov's pardons...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/23/matt-bevin-pardons-fbi-asking-questions-situation/2737842001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are looking into former Kentucky Gov. Matt Bevin's last-minute pardons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WEINSTEIN CASES BEING REVIEWED BY LA DA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/harvey-weinstein-cases-review-1203451578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein is set to go on trial next month in New York on charges of rape and sexual assault. But no matter how that case turns out, he will still face criminal jeopardy in Los Angeles. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God Has Me Right Where He Wants Me': Bieber Announces New Single 'Yummy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/24/god-has-me-right-where-he-wants-me-justin-bieber-announces-new-single-called-yummy-for-january-3rd-2020-tour-dates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber released a video announcement today for new music and tour dates. His single, “Yummy,” comes January 3rd. He says, “As humans we are imperfect. My past, my mistakes,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Exploited Prison Labor to Make 2020 Campaign Phone Calls...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/12/24/mike-bloomberg-2020-prison-labor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bloomberg campaign said it ended the arrangement after learning of the prison call centers from an The Intercept inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan could release Fukushima radioactive water into environment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japan-could-release-fukushima-radioactive-water-environment-072000457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Japanese government agency has proposed releasing radioactive water from the stricken Fukushima nuclear plant into the environment, as storage space runs out. About a million tonnes of contaminated water has built up since then and the tanks that hold it are almost full. An extensive pumping and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloomy Christmas Eve on the 20th day of French strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gloomy-christmas-eve-20th-day-french-strike-131303722.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas Eve 2019 was an unusually gloomy one for France, as the 20th day of a transport strike left many scrambling Tuesday to reach their loved ones for the traditional family feast, while others simply gave up. The protest against pension reform has led to thousands of trains being cancelled or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAUGHTY OR NICE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0c322ada689cc214d75e6b9a2f91720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — President Donald Trump said Tuesday that North Korean leader Kim Jong Un may be planning to give him “a nice present" such as a “beautiful vase” for Christmas rather than a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser-Linked Satellites Could Deliver Worldwide 'Internet from Space'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/12/laser-linked-satellites-could-deliver-internet-space/162009/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such a network could potentially reach remote and underserved areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Accused of Humiliating Needy For Throwing Cash at Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/rapper-blueface-accused-humiliating-needy-after-throwing-large-amounts-cash-homeless-people-1478965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News Moments That Defined the 2010s...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/best-decade-ever-the-cable-news-moments-that-defined-the-2010s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 2010s come to a close, it's an interesting exercise to consider how future historians will help explain just what the hell happened over the past decade, which so happens to coincide neatl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren embraced high-dollar fundraiser circuit for years -- until just before her presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-embraced-the-high-dollar-fundraiser-14929335.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chase Williams grinned broadly as he stood for a photo next to Sen. Elizabeth Warren, chatting briefly with the Massachusetts Democrat before moving on so someone else could have their turn.  It was the kind of moment that has become a ubiquitous part of Warren's presidential campaign and its long "selfie lines," where supporters wait for hours to pose with her at no charge.  But this shot, taken in October 2017, was at an entirely different kind of event: an exclusive "backstage" reception that took place in the vault of a former Cleveland bank. And that was the day's low-rent affair - donors who agreed to pay more attended an even more exclusive shindig with Warren that day, according to two people familiar with her schedule.  The events were part of a high-dollar fundraising program that Warren had embraced her entire political career, from her first Senate run in 2011 through her reelection last year. Warren was so successful at it that she was able to transfer $10 million of her Senate cash to help launch her presidential bid.  But in the past year Warren has undergone a transformation, moving from one of the Democratic Party's biggest draws at high-dollar fundraisers to a presidential candidate who has sworn them off as sinister attempts to sell access.  In a debate last week, Warren criticized rival Pete Buttigieg for having an exclusive fundraiser in a crystal-filled wine cave in Napa Valley, prompting the South Bend, Indiana, mayor to respond that she shouldn't issue "purity tests you cannot yourself pass."  Williams, who supports Buttigieg in the presidential race, said Warren's position was "disingenuous."  "I am frustrated because she said, 'I don't do this. This isn't something I do.' And two years ago she very much did do that, and I was in the room," said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia unveils new 'unstoppable' 7,000mph hypersonic missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-unveils-new-unstoppable-7000mph-21158649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The undetectable high speed Russian missile can now be launched from land, sea or air and travel at a quite extraordinary 7,000mph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917' Star on Filming Best War Movie in 20 Years -- in One Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/1917-star-george-mackay-on-filming-the-best-war-movie-in-over-20-yearsin-one-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Mendes’ new war epic is being hailed as “the best war film since ‘Saving Private Ryan.’” Star George MacKay talks the arduous task of filming the whole thing as just one take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The surge is real': Klobuchar makes late push in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/24/amy-klobuchar-iowa-089646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her strong debate performance and Midwestern sensibility raises hopes of a surprise showing in Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S BEATINGS: Brawls break out in malls across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7823773/Brawls-break-malls-minute-shoppers-try-score-deal-Super-Saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American shoppers spent a record $34.4billion on Super Saturday, the biggest single day in American retail history, but the weekend was marred by violent incidents at several locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite image heightens concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/satellite-image-of-construction-at-north-korea-factory-hikes-concerns-about-possible-icbm-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new satellite image shows construction at a factory where Pyongyang makes military equipment for such long-range missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Kaepernick shoe sells out in day...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/475821-new-kaepernick-shoe-sells-out-in-a-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike’s new sneaker featuring former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick was sold out by Tuesday, a day after its release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania silently forges path through ordeal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/887f8e64ba46b92c9c4daf5cc74ea604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hillary Clinton spent the morning of her husband's impeachment visiting Capitol Hill to rally Democrats to his side. Pat Nixon kept assuring reporters her husband wouldn't quit —...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Embeds TESLA Key In Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/tesla-model-3-key-implant-hand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I guess you could call that brand loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NKorea likely to test long-range missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/24/north-korea-missile-test-seems-likely-soon-as-tensions-with-us-return.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States needs to stop expecting North Korea will just "surrender," said Harry Kazianis, senior director at D.C.-based think tank, Center for National Interest. The more achievable goal is to mitigate tensions with Pyongyang using economic solutions and collaboration with China he suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fog grounds all flights at Chicago O'Hare, Midway airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/weather/ct-dense-fog-flights-canceled-20191224-dhyuahrhondeboscvxlw7bzidq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overnight, “dense, freezing fog” developed throughout the city and its surrounding suburbs, leading to travel difficulties both in the air and on-ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: God did not elect Trump, people did...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/475685-god-did-not-elect-trump-people-did</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who share his values and priorities let’s stop the sanctimony and religious gymnastics. Let’s recognize the difference between the sacred and the profane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says leading world in hypersonic weapons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4e05956217d895594bcef491083e950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — President Vladimir Putin said Tuesday that Russia is the only country in the world that has hypersonic weapons. Speaking at a meeting with top military brass, Putin said that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple reports of object 'travelling at 1,000mph' over Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/multiple-reports-ufo-travelling-1000mph-21157050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gigantic object has sparked claims a secret Space Force craft has been caught on camera, having been caught near an Air Force base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First measles case reported in Austin in decades...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/475809-first-measles-case-reported-in-austin-texas-in-20-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in Austin, Texas are warning residents they may have been exposed to measles after the first diagnosed case was reported in the city in more than 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*ck off!': New Yorkers react to being named 'rudest city'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/24/f-k-off-new-yorkers-react-to-being-named-rudest-city-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you believe these shmucks?! Americans think New Yorkers are the biggest jerks in the country, according to a new survey — released just days before Christmas, no less. The slap-in-the-face Busi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glittering symbol of press, Newseum set to close its doors...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/glittering-symbol-press-newseum-set-close-doors-012838678.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just steps from the US Capitol, the Newseum's gleaming glass-and-steel structure has for over a decade been a shining symbol for the press and free expression. The museum, with exhibits covering the September 11 attacks and the Berlin Wall as well as a daily display of front pages from around the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist intends to prove he found life on Mars in 1976...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/science/life-mars-viking-rosalind-franklin-rover-1349002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Quietly Masking Efforts to Calm Market?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-may-quietly-masking-extent-171616740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wall Street sleuths are wondering whether the Federal Reserve is quietly doing more to calm the U.S. repo market than just the headline-grabbing liquidity injections that have captivated observers for months.The New York Fed runs something called the foreign reverse repo pool, a place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian mag raises issue of 'unconditional loyalty'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191224023342-ynppd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RELIGION (PIX):Christianity Today again slams Trump, raises issue of 'unconditional loyalty'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothers charged with obstructing GirlsDoPorn investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/courts/story/2019-12-23/brothers-charged-with-obstructing-girlsdoporn-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators suspect duo removed computers from home of Michael Pratt before he fled the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passionate but dwindling crowds mark the decline of Tijuana bullfights...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2019-12-23/passionate-fans-but-dwindling-crowds-at-tijuana-bullfights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tijuana once hosted bullfights in a 22,000-seat arena. But with fewer crowds, the aficionados now watch from a 3,000-seat plaza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABERNATHY:  In age of Trump, it's OK to be [deeply] conflicted... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/In-the-age-of-Trump-it-s-OK-to-be-deeply-14928014.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILLSBORO, Ohio - Considering recent reports chronicling the decline of Christianity in the United States, the level of outrage expressed over President Donald Trump's offhand comment that the late congressman John Dingell, D-Mich., might be "looking up," presumably from hell, is somewhat surprising. Suddenly, at least for a day or two, everybody got religion.  To be fair, Trump first suggested that Dingell was "looking down" from heaven. But the president couldn't resist his little joke, and the resulting anguish it caused Rep. Debbie Dingell, the congressman's widow, was entirely understandable. Trump should apologize.  He won't, of course. Not that Trump's lack of contrition will cost him any support. The president's devotees long ago accepted his callousness as a character flaw that is offset by his frontal assault on a corrupt and complacent Washington swamp. The local Republican Party county chair told me last week she had just returned from Dayton, where the printer claims to be working around the clock to keep up with the demand for Trump fliers, pamphlets and memorabilia. There is no abatement in enthusiasm, he told her.  The blowback from the pundit class over Trump's musings on the fate of someone's eternal soul would be more meaningful if the same empathy was accorded the president when it is predicted that he will burn in hell. Such insinuations are regularly made, and similar hopes expressed in emails I receive. There are even fine art prints of "Trump's Arrival in Hell" available online ($30 unframed), but widespread disgust over such an affront to our president has yet to be observed.  Despite the Bible's observation that the path to heaven is narrow and few will travel it, while the road to hell is wide and much more populated, it is still improper in polite society to suggest that anyone will end up in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They came to the US on raft from Cuba, then built 'vast empire of fraud,' feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article238654813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN:  GOODBYE, 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1220676/queens-speech-christmas-message-queen-news-2019-brexit-royal-family-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has spoken publicly for the first time about the Royal Family’s “bumpy” year. In her Christmas Day message, she admits 2019 has not been a vintage year for them – or the UK. The monarch, who has repeatedly tried to heal divisions within the royals and the nation, describes “how small steps taken in faith and in hope can overcome long-held differences to bring harmony and understanding”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA TALKS UP WARREN BEHIND CLOSED DOORS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/475576-obama-talks-up-warren-behind-closed-doors-to-wealthy-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren has spent her presidential campaign railing against the donor class, making it known she doesn't want their help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversies under Prince Mohammed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-controversies-under-prince-mohammed-130921138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has been engulfed by a series of controversies since Mohammed bin Salman was named crown prince and heir to the throne in June 2017. The brutal murder of critic Jamal Khashoggi and the increased repression of dissidents have overshadowed the prince's efforts to modernise the economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising popularity of Chinese medicine threatens wildlife populations, say conservation groups...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rising-popularity-chinese-medicine-threatens-173018089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing popularity of traditional Chinese medicine is ravaging global populations of donkeys, tigers and other many other animals, conservation groups say.  Poachers target various species for their organs and treatments are offered for a variety of ailments, from arthritis to erectile dysfunction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government proposes release of Fukushima water to sea or air...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e60f93b7f7de2ff7b5b015fb5167dd9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan's economy and industry ministry proposed on Monday the gradual release or evaporation of massive amounts of treated but still radioactive water being stored at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeling of doom envelops Coach Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d69c8a113ff966376647eef871135b51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though the Dallas Cowboys still have a path to the playoffs, there's a feeling of inevitability in one of the most disappointing seasons for Jerry Jones in 30 years as owner and general...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/23/us-futures-point-to-cautiously-higher-open.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks climbed higher on Monday, hitting new records, as the year-end rally continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell NOT closing door on trial witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e8550f1b1469b642d221c457d281df0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Monday that he was not ruling out calling witnesses in President Donald Trump's impeachment trial — but indicated he was in no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tests internet -- to work if cut off from worldwide web...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191223181421-ew39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/INTERNET:Russia checks its internet can work if cut off from worldwide web</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Excess Belly Fat Worsens Ability To Think...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-your-belly-affects-your-brain-as-we-age-excess-body-fat-worsens-fluid-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that extra belly fat may hurt one's ability to think and react to new situations on the fly, referred to as "fluid intelligence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans leaving the House at record pace. Why?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/republicans-are-leaving-the-house-at-a-record-pace-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far this year, 22 Republicans in the U.S. House have announced that they will not run for reelection next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON exec killed by van delivering company's packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/kenbensinger/amazons-race-to-build-a-fast-delivery-network-the-huma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more US sniffer dogs to Egypt, Jordan after deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-more-us-sniffer-dogs-egypt-jordan-deaths-210300202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has temporarily stopped sending bomb detecting sniffer dogs to Jordan and Egypt after several of the animals died due to what US officials say was lack of care. "Any death of a canine in the field is an extremely sad event and we will take every measure possible to prevent this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God always chose people that had flaws'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/evangelicals-stand-with-trump-god-always-chose-people-that-had-flaws/ar-BBYh0li</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke bomb simulation shows how blast would destroy 6 US cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/how-nuclear-attack-would-destroy-us-cities-2019-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City would have the most fatalities from a nuclear blast. San Francisco would have the least.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDUP: FEDEX Driver Caught Tossing Packages Into Ditch...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/12/21/fedex-driver-ditches-packages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FedEx employee in Mercer County was caught throwing packages into a ditch after indicating he had delivered them to their destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military warns: DNA kits pose 'personal, operational risks'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-warns-military-members-dna-kits-pose-personal-and-operational-risks-173304318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is advising members of the military not to use consumer DNA kits, saying the information collected by private companies could pose a security risk, according to a memo co-signed by the Defense Department’s top intelligence official.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
