<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ricI5t66cj8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See the full news release: https://www.projectveritas.com/2019/07/24/current-sr-google-engineer-goes-public-on-camera-tech-is-dangerous-taking-sides You can ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael 'squatter' ex-boyfriend arrested for smashing up star's mansion!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9572544/fadi-fawaz-arrest-george-michael-london-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s ex Fadi Fawaz was dramatically arrested after going berserk and allegedly smashing up the late singer’s £5million house. Cops swooped on the London property last night after …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea launches 'short range missile' in defiance of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9578494/north-korea-launch-missile-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Jong-un tonight launched two short-range military missiles in a shocking show of defiance to Donald Trump. Military leaders in neighbouring South Korea say the surprise launch took place in the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: NFL star deep in debt despite earning $99 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jul/24/adrian-peterson-nfl-debt-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial problems continue to mount for Washington running back Adrian Peterson, who is being sued for failure to repay a $5.2m loan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions Between Sanders, MSNBC Boil Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-war-between-bernie-sanders-and-msnbc-reaches-a-new-peak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator’s campaign sees the cable news network as part of a brewing problem that allows vague and unverified claims to go unchecked on air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMASKY:  He Delivered the Goods!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-mueller-delivered-the-goods-will-dems-feast-on-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our system of government as it now exists is just not equipped to handle someone who lies with blasé alacrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats getting fatter...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fat-cats-literally-new-study-finds-felines-are-getting-chubbier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term "fat cat" is thrown around quite frequently, but usually not to describe actual cats. Well, a new study out of the University of Guelph finds that cats are indeed getting fatter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns of ongoing election interference...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Mueller-parries-questions-in-highly-anticipated-14119850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Former special counsel Robert Mueller III, in quiet and occasionally halting testimony, warned Congress on Wednesday that Russia is still interfering with American democracy and offered some sharp criticism of President Donald Trump.  "They're doing it as we sit here, and they expect to do it in the next campaign," Mueller said of the Russians, during roughly six hours of highly anticipated testimony before two House committees about his investigation of Russian election interference and Trump's possible obstruction of justice.  Mueller's appearance offered the prospect of pulling back the curtain on his secretive investigation, but the former prosecutor and FBI director strove - by day's end successfully - not to reveal any details beyond his staff's 448-page report.  Some Democrats had hoped his testimony would lead to a fresh groundswell of support to begin impeachment proceedings, but that seemed unlikely in the immediate aftermath of the hearings, which produced no blockbuster revelations. Mueller seemed reluctant to even utter the word "impeachment."  Republicans pronounced the matter dead, and Trump declared victory.  "We had a very good day, the Republican Party," the president told reporters at the White House. "There was no defense of what Robert Mueller was trying to defend . . . this ridiculous hoax, this witch hunt."  He called Mueller's performance "horrible."  Mueller, who only hours earlier had specifically denied his investigation was a hoax or a witch hunt, appeared grim and determined in the packed hearing room but also at times confused or unable to hear the questions being asked - particularly in the morning, when the House Judiciary Committee questioned him about whether the president obstructed justice by attempting to impede Mueller's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron gambles on IVF for lesbians...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-reform-ivf/macron-gambles-on-cultural-shift-with-bill-allowing-ivf-for-lesbians-idUSKCN1UJ20A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government on Wednesday sent to parliament draft legislation that wou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Departure From His Once-Fabled Stamina...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/24/us/politics/mueller-hearings-performance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As special counsel, Mr. Mueller adopted a more hands-off style than when he was F.B.I. director, and it was on display Wednesday in his congressional appearances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN 'INJURED' IN JAIL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Jeffrey-Epstein-Found-Injured-in-NYC-Jail-Cell-After-Possible-Suicide-Attempt-or-Assault-Sources-513174311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused pedophile and financier Jeffrey Epstein was found apparently injured and in a fetal position inside his cell at an NYC jail, sources said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live-tracking deflections...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/robert-mueller-house-testimony-tracker-july-2019-n1033166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former special counsel testified in front of two House committees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico gov resigns after weeks of protests over obscene chats..</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/embattled-puerto-rico-gov-ricardo-rossell-resigns-amid-public-outcry-n1033241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Ricky, te botamos!" ("Ricky, we threw you out!") the jubilant crowd exclaimed after the governor's announcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlogger dies live-streaming himself eating poisonous centipedes and lizards...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-35-dies-live-streaming-18763663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese vlogger, named only by his surname Sun, was reportedly found lifeless in his flat after the bizarre stunt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Outright liars' made it hard to complete...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article233059602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing strikes ominous tone, saying military could intervene in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-07-24/beijing-strikes-ominous-tone-saying-military-could-intervene-in-hong-kong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong protesters are now directly challenging the Chinese government while pro-Beijing thugs have gone on a rampage, beating bystanders, journalists and protesters in public. China's state media is stirring nationalist sentiment with rhetoric that has been used in the past to pave the way for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino 'HOLLYWOOD' big summer gamble. Will it pay off?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-07-23/quentin-tarantinos-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-is-sonys-big-summer-gamble-will-it-pay-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony Pictures fought hard to land Quentin Tarantino's first film after Weinstein. Will the $90-million bet on originality and star power pay off?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror site told readers to 'hunt' gays. Then activist stabbed to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-horror-movie-themed-website-told-readers-to-14118182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frightening Russian website promoted it as a "game" - identify gay people, upload their photos and information to a database and then proceed to hunt them down and torture them, like the gruesome "Saw" movies that inspired the site's name.  The page was blocked in Russia last week, but not before the names of prominent journalists and activists began appearing there. Yelena Grigorieva was among them. The 41-year-old was a fierce advocate for LGBTQ rights, and on Saturday she was found dead near her home in St. Petersburg with eight stab wounds and signs she'd been strangled.  One suspect has been arrested, local media reported.  The grisly attack is the latest in a spate of violence and threats against the gay community in Russia, where in 2013 the government outlawed so-called "gay propaganda" - a ban that a European court later said "reinforced stigma and prejudice and encouraged homophobia."  "This tragedy is yet another painful episode in the ongoing plague of anti-LGBTQ violence and atrocities that have been taking place in Russia and the region," Jay Gilliam, global director of the Human Rights Campaign, told The Washington Post.  Grigorieva's killing prompted protests in Russia's second largest city on Tuesday and demonstrators there connected her death to her activism.  "Yelena was killed because she was not afraid to tell the truth about the subjects that are traditionally silent in Russia and on the country's state TV channels," attendee Marina Ken told the Associated Press.  Grigorieva, who was also active in a number of other causes, regularly received death threats and reported them to the police, who her friends say didn't take them seriously, the Moscow Times reported. Officials at the Human Rights Campaign, which is the largest LGBTQ rights organization...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein splashed out $18M for SECOND Caribbean island...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7282441/Jeffrey-Epstein-paid-18M-SECOND-Caribbean-island-building-compound-prison.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein has big plans for the latest addition to his already sizable real estate portfolio, with a schematic showing his plans to build a massive compound on the property - despite being in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eat last meal at 2pm to lose weight?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7280855/Eating-meal-2pm-help-lose-weight-suppresses-appetite.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study at the University of Alabama Birmingham tested Early Time-Restricted Feeding (eTRF), which is a type of fasting where dinner is eaten in the afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA shares plunge as it reports big loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/24/tesla-earnings-q2-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Tesla reaffirmed its full-year delivery guidance and said it still expects return to profitability in the third quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKS ON NECK; SEMI-CONSCIOUS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/24/jeffrey-epstein-injured-in-federal-jail-in-manhattan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein was on the floor of his cell in a fetal position, was semi-conscious and had marks on his neck, sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNISM: Cuba Running Out of Medicine...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/health/2019/07/24/cuba-the-healthcare-darling-of-the-international-left-is-running-out-of-medicine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Healthcare authorities in Cuba blamed a "complex situation" Tuesday for growing shortages of basic medicines that many need to stay alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC Slap on Wrist for Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/47f5f7fd9e0941a880b929af081a37a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1b98bfdbea19426faf1be2006ac9334f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>105&amp;#176;  IN PARIS?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/paris-on-alert-for-record-breaking-temperatures-as-heat-wave-grips-spain-to-germany/461396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explains decision not to subpoena president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/454575-mueller-explains-decision-not-to-subpoena-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Sean Patrick Maloney (D-N.Y.) on Wednesday pressed former special counsel Robert Mueller on why he did not subpoena President Trump for an interview during his investigation into Russian election interference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADER: Trump will 'defeat himself' if goaded...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/454421-ralph-nader-trump-will-defeat-himself-in-2020-if-hes-goaded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s been dubbed an election “spoiler” by countless critics, but Ralph Nader says there’s one person likely to spoil President Trump’s 2020 reelection hopes: Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare rhinos among more hundreds of animals killed by India floods...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-07-rare-rhinos-animals-india.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating floods have killed more than 200 wild animals—including 17 threatened one-horned rhinos—in one of India's best-known national parks, officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGES: Man Poses As 'GMA' Producer, NYTIMES Reporter To Obtain Govt Docs...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/07/24/nikolaos-hatziefstathiou-poses-good-morning-america-producer-new-york-times-reporter-obtain-government-documents-da-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say they contacted the journalists and they say they did not send those emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Disaster ends impeachment talk...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/24/muellers-testimony-equals-end-of-any-trump-impeachment-talk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among his talents, Donald Trump has a special gift for driving his detractors so crazy that they do really stupid stuff. The decision by Democrats to force Robert Mueller to testify before Congress…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside reports of deaths, sickness that have consumed Dominican Republic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/24/inside-the-reports-of-deaths-sickness-that-have-consumed-dominican-republic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s fear surrounding the Dominican Republic these days. In just the past few months, the beach oasis has been battered by a steady stream of disturbing reports about tourist deaths, sudde…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: NIKE sneakers sell for record $437,500...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/over-moon-nike-sneakers-sell-record-437-500-225653835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new world record for a pair of sneakers was set at auction on Tuesday when an avid collector splashed out $437,500 on Nike's 1972 "Moon Shoe," Sotheby's said. The sale smashed the previous record of $190,373 spent in 2017 on a pair of signed Converse worn by Michael Jordan in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING reports biggest-ever loss as 737 MAX grounding drags on ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boeing-reports-2-9-bn-loss-2q-biggest-004917350.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing reported its biggest loss ever on Wednesday as the 737 MAX crisis drags on, and the company warned it could be forced to temporarily halt production of the plane if the grounding is extended much longer. Getting the MAX back in the air is a "complex" multi-regulator process "that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTAGE:  Medical students less likely to become primary care doctors...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/american-medical-students-less-likely-to-choose-to-become-primary-care-doctors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only 41.5% of internal medicine positions were filled by U.S.-trained fourth-year students getting traditional medical degrees, the lowest share on record. Similar trends were seen this year in fam…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COULD YOU REPEAT QUESTION?'</title>
      <link>https://grabien.com/story.php?id=244735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Can you repeat the question, sir?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Shelter Used Gas Chamber To Euthanize Pets...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/07/23/wyoming-animal-shelter-using-gas-chamber-euthanize-pets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animal welfare advocates say gas chambers are cruel because death often doesn't happen quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HBO Series Has Redford As POTUS and White Supremacy Ruling The Land...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/watchmen-white-supremacy-theme-damon-lindelof-regina-king-tv-series-alan-moore-hbo-tca-1202652928/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dropping an Easter egg-rich new Watchmen trailer during the spotlight of Comic-Con, Damon Lindelof today tore right into the heart of the upcoming HBO series based on Alan Moore and Dave Gibb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>