<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Deportations under Trump still lower than Obama, ICE report shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Deportations-under-Trump-are-on-the-rise-but-13467316.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Amid President Donald Trump's push for tighter immigration policies, the United States deported more than 256,000 illegal immigrants in 2018 - the highest number since the Obama administration, new data shows. U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement Deputy Director Ronald Vitello announced Friday that in the past fiscal year, which ended in September, ICE has detained "a record number" of illegal immigrants and that the number of those deported has risen about 13 percent since 2017. The data, which comes from a new agency report, shows that 145,262 of those who were deported were convicted criminals and that 22,796 had criminal charges pending against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Secretary Zinke to Step Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/trump-s-interior-chief-said-to-step-down-amid-ethics-inquiries#gs.zXDR264</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's Interior Chief to Step Down asÂ Pressure Mounts From Ethics Inquiries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beauty queen makes history as first trans Miss Universe contestant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/7988219/stunning-beauty-queen-first-transgender-miss-universe-contestant/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOR the first time in the Miss Universe’s 66-year history, there is a transgender contestant in the competition. Angela Ponce, who is Miss Spain, will be making history as she takes part in the fin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMACARE, RIP</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/federal-judge-texas-strikes-strikes-down-affordable-care-act-n948306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a ruling sure to be appealed to Supreme Court, Texas court says the ACA, also known as Obamacare, can no longer stand without the penalty against the uninsured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE DECLARES UNCONSTITUTIONAL WITHOUT TAX</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/12/14/texas-federal-judge-obama-health-care-law-unconstitutional/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in Texas threw a dagger on Friday into the Affordable Care Act, ruling that the entire health-care law is unconstitutional because of a recent change in federal tax law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHN OF GOD: Brazil faith healer ruled fugitive...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-healer-abuse/brazil-faith-healer-accused-of-sexual-abuse-ruled-a-fugitive-idUSKBN1OE0NO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian faith healer accused of sexual abuse by more than 300 women is now c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waves in San Fran could reach 50 feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/weather/high-surf-warning-for-the-bay-area-beaches-waves-up-to-50-feet-expected/1660969148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service issued a high surf warning from Sunday morning into Monday night with waves breaking between 25 to 46 feet down the Bay Area coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI soldiers 'defy orders'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/748360/ai-news-killer-robots-soldiers-technology-latest-future-predictions-ian-pearson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi gets her swagger on...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/421487-pelosi-gets-her-swagger-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Nancy Pelosi has her swagger back after a stellar week for the California Democrat, who is expected to make history next month by beginning a second Speakership in the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AQUAMAN' Crosses $200 Million Without US Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/15/box-office-aquaman-has-200-mil-already-without-us-release-animated-spider-man-looks-at-30-mil-weekend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. was very smart with “Aquaman.” Still not open in the U.S., the DC Universe underwater extravaganza will cross $200 million this weekend– and it’s not even open …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises closure: 'Rest in peace!'</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/421537-trump-praises-closure-of-weekly-standard-rest-in-peace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday praised the shuttering of the Weekly Standard, a conservative magazine critical of him, one day after the publication announced that it would close and lay off staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could America's 'Deep Underground Seismic Scar' Be Re-Awakening?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-13/could-americas-deep-underground-seismic-scar-be-re-awakening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SHED MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stocks-drop-as-chinese-economy-falters-11544776971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All three major U.S. stock indexes are in correction territory for the first time since March 2016, with disappointing economic data from China and the eurozone sparking Friday’s nearly 500-point fall in the Dow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEADSPACE vs. CALM: Meditation Battle That's Anything but Zen...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/headspace-vs-calm-the-meditation-battle-thats-anything-but-zen-11544889606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of apps preach relaxation to millions of customers—but still badly want to beat each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Lab-Grown Meat Poses New Questions for Religious Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/emergence-of-lab-grown-meat-poses-new-questions-for-religious-leaders-11544834277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lab-grown meat is raising new questions for religious leaders, including Rabbi Yuval Cherlow, who is considering whether meat grown from animal cells in a petri dish will fit into the kosher tradition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUTANTS: Deformities Alarm Scientists Racing to Rewrite Animal DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/deformities-alarm-scientists-racing-to-rewrite-animal-dna-11544808779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists around the world are editing the genes of livestock to create meatier pigs, cashmere goats with longer hair and cold-weather cows that can thrive in the tropics. But amid some successes, disturbing outcomes are surfacing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. troops will now stay in Syria indefinitely, controlling third of country...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/middle-east/in-america-s-hidden-war-in-syria-troops-face-peril-on-many-fronts-1.560780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruined, fearful city of Raqqa was once the Islamic State's capital, the showcase of its caliphate and a magnet for foreign fighters from around the globe. Now it lies at the heart of the United States' newest commitment to a Middle East war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New media hits stumbling block, scaring away investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/New-media-hits-stumbling-block-scaring-away-some-13466790.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As legacy news companies suffered tremors over the past decade, money from venture capitalists poured into upstarts that promised to leverage a keener understanding online reading habits to create a giant-killing class of new media ventures. Today, the money is starting to dry up. Big ambitions have been downsized. And the tremors that continue to shake many newspapers are now moving through new-media companies. Among those facing headwinds are BuzzFeed, Vox and Vice. Another one, Mic, last week abruptly laid off most of its staff -- and the company that a year ago was valued at $100 million garnered a fire-sale offer of $5 million for its remnants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic Clothing Dominates Fashion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/15/fashion/warcore-fashion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Safety-orange jumpsuits, face masks, tactical vests: So-called war-core clothing is hot during these anxious times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff digs into Trump's personal finances...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2018/12/24/adam-schiffs-plans-to-obliterate-trumps-red-line</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Democrats controlling the House, Schiff’s congressional investigation will follow the money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temple 'poisoning': Eleven dead, 90 sick after eating religious food offering...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/india-temple-poisoning-eleven-dead-13736379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people have been arrested and investigators believe a dispute prompted the deliberate food poisoning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water shortages ahead? Sierra Nevada snow pack on track to shrink 79%...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/12/15/water-shortages-ahead-sierra-nevada-snow-pack-on-track-to-shrink-79-percent-new-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the current rate the climate is warming, runoff from Sierra snow into California’s largest reservoirs is heading for a dramatic decline, according to a new study from Lawrence Berkeley Nat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Brexit referendum gaining traction...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/A-second-Brexit-referendum-was-once-a-pipe-dream-13468802.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - Not long ago, staging a second Brexit referendum was a fringe idea - a pipe dream of a handful of "remoaners" who had voted to remain in the European Union, cheered on by unpopular figures from yesteryear, such as former prime minister Tony Blair. But the once barely imaginable is now becoming remotely possible. The British may be headed toward one of history's greatest do-overs - another vote to ask do they really, really want to leave the E.U., after all they know now about breaking up being hard to do. For crazy, chaotic Brexit, nothing would be more crazy and chaotic than another vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'ROMA' be victim of NETFLIX curse? </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/entertainment/article/Will-Roma-be-a-victim-of-the-Netflix-curse-13466559.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm so glad "Roma" hits Netflix on Friday, because it gives me another chance to talk about "Mudbound." "Mudbound" is the Netflix film that was briefly released in theaters last year to make sure it qualified for the Oscars. "Mudbound," about two families - one white, one black - living in post-WWII Mississippi, is one of the great modern American films. Its theme goes to the core of race relations in America. The cinematography is breathtaking, the performances are stunning and Dee Rees' direction is both sensitive and brutal. But the film got absolutely screwed at the Oscars, receiving only four nominations (and best picture wasn't one of them).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unearths tomb of ancient high priest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181215-egypt-unearths-tomb-ancient-high-priest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt unearths tomb of ancient high priest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP NAMES MULVANEY 'ACTING' CHIEF OF STAFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mick-mulvaney-to-replace-john-kelly-as-chief-of-staff-trump-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday named White House budget director Mick Mulvaney as his new “acting” chief of staff, saying the former South Carolina Republican congressman will replace John Kelly as his top aide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naples supervolcano showing 'signs' of  'Vesuvian-style eruption'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1059446/Volcano-eruption-warning-Italy-Naples-Campi-Flegrei-supervolcano-Mount-Vesuvius</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITALY'S Campi Flegrei volcano has, for the first time in nearly 400 years, been “showing a type of unrest” which could indicate it is “getting ready for another eruption”, volcano expert Christopher Kilburn has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bionic eye to be implanted in humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748251/bionic-eye-world-first-blindness-cure-robot-unsw-sydney-phoenix-99-human-trials-release</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence in Paris as police clash with protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6498733/Up-8-000-police-bolster-streets-Paris-Yellow-Vest-protesters-plan-chaos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fighting erupted in central Paris today as thousands of protesters took to the streets for the so-called 'Act V' Day of Rage. It's the fifth consecutive week rioters have protested in the French streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 300 Women Accuse 'Miracle' Healer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/over-300-women-accuse-famous-spirit-medium-as-metoo-hits-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 300 Women Accuse Famous Spirit Medium as #MeToo Hits Brazil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Super Bowl Halftime Show Became Music's Least Wanted Gig...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/music/news/maroon-5-super-bowl-halftime-show-1203089706/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who would have thought that the Super Bowl Halftime show, an American institution watched by more than 100 million people, would become the least wanted gig in music? But thanks to the ongoing cont…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah to impose nation's strictest DUI limit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/421525-utah-to-impose-nations-strictest-dui-limit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah is set to become the state with the strictest limit for alcohol consumption before driving, dropping the standard for blood alcohol content (BAC) from the nationwide standard of .08 to .05.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news vs fact in online battle for truth...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-12-fake-news-fact-online-truth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since US President Donald Trump weaponised the term "fake news" during the 2016 presidential election campaign, the phrase has gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle-aged man pledges frat; Paddled 200 times...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/14/middle-aged-man-pledges-frat-claims-he-was-paddled-200-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that’s “Old School!” A middle-aged Brooklyn man told cops he paid a painful price for pledging a fraternity at the ripe old age of 45 — by getting whacked on the backside hundreds of times with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'MULE' Clint Eastwood's second-best opening as actor...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/spider-man-into-the-spider-verse-mortal-engines-clint-eastwood-the-mule-weekend-box-office-1202520137/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5th Update/Writethru, Saturday AM, after Friday 11:26AM post: Saturday AM estimates see Sony’s Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse with a solid weekend start of $37.2M after a $12.6M Friday at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden team discusses 2020 run with Beto...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adc92878ae0044868176760aff44e3cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he considers running for president, Joe Biden is talking with friends and longtime supporters about whether, at 76, he's too old to seek the White House, according to several sources who have spoken with the former Democratic vice president. The discussions suggest Biden is aware that his age may be the biggest hurdle to launching another bid for the Democratic presidential nomination, especially in an era when many in the party yearn for a new generation of leadership. He would be the oldest person to ever be elected president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decorated Green Beret charged with murder of suspected Taliban bombmaker...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/green-beret-charged-murder-suspected-taliban-bombmaker/story?id=59825579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former U.S. Army Green Beret has been charged with the 2010 murder of a man he suspected of being a Taliban bombmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Zuckerberg Lost $15 Billion This Year; More Than Any of 500 Richest...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/money/5478554/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-loss-net-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial year was costly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinal choir boy abuse case raises questions about gag orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/the_new_gatekeepers/australian-sexual-abuse-gag-order.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $500 brownie...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/food/try-this-$500-brownie-covered-in-gold/4894016/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chef Jason Harley, owner of Baby J's Burgers, has a brownie you can buy for $500.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
