<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NHC: Storm system on track to Gulf Coast up to 80% chance of development...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/weather-news/article234994772.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sunherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk plans first orbital testflight of Mars-bound spacecraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-spacex-starship-mars-space-nasa-a9102486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN NEW TARGET</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/it-s-elizabeth-warren-s-debate-1.1315146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts senator is right where she wants to be as 10 Democrats prepare to spar in Houston. Who can slow her down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Tracking $90M Opening...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/09/joker-box-office-opening-weekend-projections-1202732548/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips’ R-rated DC villain movie Joker arrived on tracking today with an indexed first choice among all audiences in the low 20s among moviegoers that exceeded a mix of both superhero …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious object from interstellar space 'approaching our solar system'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9912329/interstellar-space-object-solar-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS object from deep space is fizzing towards the Solar System – and scientists have no idea what it is. Dubbed “C/2019 Q4”, the high-speed body appears to be on a path origina…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos show violent world of soccer hooligans and die-hard Ultras...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/9912353/flares-fireworks-fighting-riot-police-ultras-hooligans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE violent world of football hooliganism has been captured in pictures in a new book. Ultras: A Way of Life attempts to bring a cultural understanding to the shocking scenes witnessed in football …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Spending Time With Friends Lowers Dementia Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/spending-time-with-friends-every-day-may-lower-dementia-risk-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that maintaining an active social life into our 50s and 60s can help lower one's risk of developing dementia later on in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel approves impeachment parameters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/12/politics/impeachment-investigation-vote-house-judiciary-committee/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee on Thursday approved a resolution defining the rules of the panel's impeachment investigation, the first vote the committee has taken related to the potential impeachment of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief executives of 145 companies urge Senate to pass gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/12/chief-executives-of-145-companies-urge-senate-to-pass-gun-control-laws.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaders of 145 companies wrote a letter to the Senate Thursday, urging the governmental body to take action on gun safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rebel' Saudi women shun obligatory abaya robe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rebel-saudi-women-shun-obligatory-abaya-robe-023336310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her high heels clacking on marble tiles, a defiant Saudi woman turned heads and drew gasps as she strutted through a Riyadh mall -- without a body-shrouding abaya. Last year, de facto ruler Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman hinted during an interview with CBS that the dress code may be relaxed, saying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Can Mass-Produce Human Embryoids...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/09/11/757072996/scientists-create-a-device-that-can-mass-produce-synthetic-human-embryos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers hope large numbers of very primitive, embryo-like structures will lead to new insights into early human development and ways to prevent miscarriages and birth defects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson: What Does It Say That 'Conservatives Nicer to Me'?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/marianne-williamson-slams-liberals-in-hot-mic-moment-what-does-it-say-that-conservatives-are-nicer-to-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What does it say that Fox News is nicer to me than the lefties are?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPhone creep out? Tiny holes scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Does-the-new-iPhone-creep-you-out-Scientists-14433714.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Apple debuted its newest iPhones on Tuesday, a striking new feature took center stage: a three-lens setup that puts a near-professional camera in the hands of anyone who can afford the $999 to $1099 devices. Three lenses are a lot better than two - unless they send you reeling in disgust.  That's the unexpected reaction thousands of Apple fans shared on social media as images spread of the back of the new phone, where the trio of lenses are crowded into a small square near the top left corner.  "The new iPhone is creeping me ... out with the 3 little cameras," one Twitter user wrote.  The backlash comes from people who say they suffer from an obscure and perplexing condition called "trypophobia" - a fear of clusters of small holes like those found in shoe treads, honeycombs and lotus seed pods. Essex University Professor Geoff Cole, a self-diagnosed trypophobe and researcher in the United Kingdom who studies the condition calls it "the most common phobia you have never heard of."  The phobia isn't recognized in the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders, which psychologists and psychiatrists use to diagnose patients. But self-described sufferers and some researchers claim the images can evoke a strong emotional response and induce itching, goose bumps, and even nausea and vomiting.  Trypophobia was only named in 2005 after the word began appearing on Reddit and in other online forums, like in a post by an Irish woman named Louise who belonged to an online community of self-described "weirdoes who have an irrational fear of HOLES."  Over the next decade, though, thousands of people have reported suffering from trypophobia. Support groups have popped up on social media. In 2016, Kendall Jenner raised the condition's profile when she wrote a blog post saying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris braces for massive public transit strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190912-paris-braces-major-strike-public-transport-system-friday-ratp-metro-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 10 metro lines closed and interruptions to bus and RER train lines, public transport in Paris will be “extremely disrupted” on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB sets home run record at 6,106...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/mlb-sets-new-home-run-record-at-6106-and-counting-with-2-12-weeks-still-to-play/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home run records continue to fall in major-league baseball</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNISM: Cuba warns energy cutbacks looming...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/750a923bea224d5aba11c0ea5dcbb6e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — Cuba's president warned Wednesday night that the country faces a looming energy crisis due to lack of diesel fuel, but he hopes to avoid blackouts in coming days. President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans deaths take toll in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0cde7fc74be84e3cbcff676a5097ed5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LUMBER BRIDGE, N.C. (AP) — "Okay, Mommy. I love you." That was Brenda Scurlock's last text from her son, Avery, before he was shot eight times, his body abandoned in a field in eastern North...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy Garland's wild final years of drugs and cruelty...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/11/judy-garlands-wild-final-years-of-drugs-and-cruelty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Onstage and on screen, Judy Garland boasted big, beautiful eyes and one of the most iconic singing voices in Hollywood history. She was Dorothy in “The Wizard of Oz” and Esther in “A Star Is Born,”…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: Lone Star Showdown...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190912093544-ad0li</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEBATE (PIX):Biden, Warren to share stage for first time at U.S. Democratic presidential debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: USA Exports More Oil Than Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-beats-saudi-arabia-to-become-top-oil-exporter-on-shale-boom-1.1314948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. briefly became the world’s No. 1 oil exporter as record shale production found its way to global customers, and there are prospects for more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lovers of Modena' skeletons holding hands were both men...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49672855 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The male skeletons, buried in Roman times, have been holding hands for around 1,500 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: Lone Star Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/461004-three-way-clash-set-to-dominate-democratic-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden will be flanked by progressive heavyweights Sens. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) at the next Democratic debate Thursday in Houston, marking the first time the sharp ideological divide among the top Democratic contenders will be on full display.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Calls For Whites to be Shot; 'Take As Slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2019/09/12/swedish-rapper-calls-for-white-people-to-be-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia carries out mass raids on Kremlin critic Navalny's supporters...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190912082209-4008q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/OPPOSITION (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia carries out mass raids on Kremlin critic Navalny's supporters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel accused of planting mysterious spy devices near White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/12/israel-white-house-spying-devices-1491351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The likely Israeli spying efforts were uncovered during the Trump presidency, several former top U.S. officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Pacific Nation Making Go of Own Digital Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/tiny-pacific-nation-is-making-a-go-of-its-own-digital-currency/ar-AAH9f1K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt 'silently monitoring snake-like UFOs' seen across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/government-is-silently-monitoring-snake-20026203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A former police detective believes the US government is well aware of the mysterious objects that have appeared over several different states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Generation of Aircraft Will Track Bathroom Visits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/the-next-generation-of-aircraft-will-track-your-bathroom-visits-1.1314946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airbus sees a big market in digitally aware cabins that may speed your flight—and save airlines lots of money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK sanctions Netanyahu page over hate speech violation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9401a7eb8c3f44e1b67a22cb4305f004 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Facebook says it has sanctioned the page of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu because of a violation of the company's hate speech policy. Facebook said on Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuits. Possible bankruptcy. Declining members. Is there future for Boy Scouts? </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/social-issues/lawsuits-possible-bankruptcy-declining-members-is-there-a-future-for-the-boy-scouts/2019/09/11/54699d6a-ce53-11e9-8c1c-7c8ee785b855_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the new school year begins, Scout leaders on the ground are vying for the future of an organization facing threats from all sides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Trump ordered NOAA statement supporting claim that Alabama was at risk from Dorian...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2019/09/11/trump-ordered-noaa-statement-supporting-claim-that-alabama-was-at-risk-from-dorian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers, Commerce Department launch investigations into NOAA’s decision to back President Trump over forecasters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor dissents...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/461014-sotomayor-dissents-trump-asylum-ban-comes-when-stakes-could-not-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Sonia Sotomayor on Wednesday took issue with the Trump administration's tendency to turn to the Supreme Court for relief from lower court injunctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquito trials raise hopes of defeating dengue...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mosquito-trials-raise-hopes-defeating-dengue-174108758.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Mosquito Program (WMP) has pioneered a method where male and female Aedes Aegypti mosquitoes are infected with the disease-resistant bacteria called Wolbachia before being released into the wild. In a matter of weeks, baby mosquitoes are born carrying Wolbachia, which acts as a disease buffer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>da Vinci's mechanical lion goes on display in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/leonardo-da-vincis-mechanical-lion-goes-display-paris-220821315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo da Vinci's famous mechanical lion on Wednesday went on display in Paris for a month, in a tribute to the Renaissance master 500 years after his death. The lion, which is two metres (six feet, seven inches) high and three metres long and made of wood with a metal mechanism, is a reconstruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  California law on rideshare drivers may hurt gig economy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-law-rideshare-drivers-may-hurt-gig-economy-160849946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark bill was approved 29-11 late Tuesday in the state senate, with the assembly -- which has already approved the measure -- expected to send it to California Governor Gavin Newsom. The legislation, which is being closely watched in other states, responds to critics who argue that companies like</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms 150th Trump judicial nominee...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/11/senate-confirms-150th-trump-judicial-nominee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Senate confirmed President Trump’s 150th judicial nominee Wednesday, helping to fulfill the president’s campaign promise to remake the federal bench with a conservative bent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOUGHEST YET...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/supreme-court-allows-enforcement-trump-asylum-limits-n1052751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit to stop the new policy is still working its way through the lower courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al-Qaida leader urges attacks against the West on Sept. 11 anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/al-qaeda-leader-urges-attacks-on-the-west-on-911-anniversary/ar-AAH9fwm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration bars access to immigration tent courts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-administration-bars-access-to-immigration-tent-courts/ar-AAH9ggY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People drowned in their attics...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/nation/2019/09/11/people-drowned-attics-dorian-submerged-whole-houses/40114001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teams of dog handlers from the U.S., Canada and Belgium are uncovering more and more bodies among the debris of Bahamas homes hit by Hurricane Dorian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN TOPS POLL</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/864229/joe-biden-elizabeth-warren-are-tied-26-percent-new-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) is going nowhere but up. The 2020 candidate pulled off a rare showing in an Economist/YouGov poll published Wednesday, tying the largely untouchable former Vice President Joe Biden with 26 percent support among registered voters. It marks one of the few polls where Biden is within danger of losing his frontrunner status, and contains a dismal prediction for Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.). Biden has only had a few close calls in previous polls, but Warren's 2020 rise has seemingly been eating away at his support as well as Sanders'. In a late August poll from Monmouth University, Sanders and Warren topped the pool with 20 percent support, and Biden was just behind at 19 percent. In this Economist/YouGov poll, Biden is back up, but so is Warren, both leaving Sanders a full 10 points behind at 16 percent. Sen. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) meanwhile has largely lost her post-debate spike, tying South Bend, Indiana Mayor Pete Buttigieg at 6 percent. And former Texas Rep. Beto O'Rourke, once a frontrunner himself, joins the 1 percent crowd at the bottom of the barrel. 2020 National Democratic Primary:Warren 26%Biden 26%Sanders 16%Buttigieg 6%Harris 6%Booker 2%Yang 2%Bennet 1%Bullock 1%Castro 1%Gabbard 1%Klobuchar 1%O'Rourke 1%Williamson 1%@YouGovUS/@TheEconomist 9/8-10https://t.co/pzE25Io89q pic.twitter.com/UEdcNIs0hK â€” Political Polls (@Politics_Polls) September 11, 2019 The Economist/YouGov surveyed 1,500 American adults from Sept. 8â€“10, who were selected via an opt-in Internet panel. The margin of error for registered voters was three percent. Find the whole poll here. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Edit DNA in Attempt to Cure Man's Cancer, HIV...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinese-scientists-edit-dna-attempt-210000310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chinese researchers safely treated a man with leukemia and HIV using gene-edited stem cells, a step forward in a field that was shaken last year when another Chinese scientist used the same technology to create the world’s first genetically-edited babies.The man’s medical case, published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes Back Trump Asylum Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a817cf3affb04f3d8ad3c4940366a5fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court is allowing nationwide enforcement of a new Trump administration rule that prevents most Central American immigrants from seeking asylum in the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUUL threw million$ at Washington. Hasn't bought much....</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/11/juul-vaping-lobbying-washington-1491029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump just delivered a big blow to the dominant vaping company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-Editing May Offer Path To Cure For HIV, First Published Report Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/09/11/759369190/crispr-gene-editing-may-offer-path-to-cure-for-hiv-first-published-report-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers safely used CRISPR gene-editing techniques in a patient with HIV. The research provides evidence the approach may be promising for treating HIV infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive rally for Catalonia's secession in Barcelona...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0c327d45bb8e4df1ae64e248231b9e40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Hundreds of thousands of Spaniards who support the secession of Catalonia gathered in Barcelona on the region's main holiday Wednesday, just weeks before a highly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm banks reconsider long-held promises to donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/09/11/consumer-dna-tests-sperm-donor-anonymity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of consumer genetic tests is forcing sperm donation clinics to confront the fact that it's virtually impossible to guarantee anonymity to clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters pause in remembrance...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests-idUSKCN1VW0DT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong activists called off protests on Wednesday in remembrance of the Sept....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA health director resigns after anti-vaxxer outburst...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/jennifer-kent-resignation-medical-vaccines-14431584.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's director of the Department of Health Care Services has resigned after writing a Facebook post that slammed anti-vaccine advocates.  Jennifer Kent announced Tuesday she was stepping down from her role with the department, a position she has held since 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State could soon ban sale of new fur products...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-11/fur-sale-ban-california-passes-legislature</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California lawmakers vote in favor of outlawing new mink coats and other new items made from the fur of undomesticated animals, including mink, rabbit and coyote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>32-year-old caught impersonating 81-year-old to board US flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-49667290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, 32, disguised himself with a dyed white beard, large glasses and a wheelchair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since 2010, 96% of all U.S. counties saw decline in share of white population...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/americas-race-diversity-population-1d8b2664-860d-4c9f-84a6-416af8421601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data shows expanding diversity will be the theme of this century's demographic shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro feeding via nasal tube following surgery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-feeding-via-nasal-tube-following-surgery-190209092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors treating Brazil's President Jair Bolsonaro said Wednesday he was feeding via a nasogastric tube due to intestinal problems which prevented him from taking food normally following abdominal surgery. The president experienced "slow intestinal transit and abdominal distention" over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange alien world found to have water...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/strange-alien-world-found-have-water-vapor-possibly-rain-clouds-ncna1052486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exoplanet K2-18 b lies in the habitable zone of its host star some 110 light-years from Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman found guilty of trespassing at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article234961982.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown Met Rape Accuser at Bible Study...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/11/antonio-browns-rape-accuser-britney-taylor-met-him-at-bible-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personal trainer accusing star New England Patriots wideout Antonio Brown of rape is a former gymnast who first met the athlete at Bible study — and she claims she has passed a lie-detector tes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create near-extinct rhino embryos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0e1236b18b394650a37bfe8e43a388e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CREMONA, Italy (AP) — Scientists announced Wednesday they have succeeded in creating two embryos of the near-extinct northern white rhino as part of an international effort to save the species,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: WASH POST shuts commuter newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Express-commuter-newspaper-published-by-The-14431419.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Express, the free newspaper published weekdays by The Washington Post for Metro riders and other commuters, will shut down on Thursday, ending 16 years of publication, the company said Wednesday.  Managers of the paper cited its deteriorating financial condition for the decision to cease publishing. Although they declined to cite specific figures, they said the printed paper had recently begun to lose money.  Colorful and lively, Express was designed to be a fast read for public-transit commuters each morning, especially people who didn't subscribe to The Post. It featured eye-catching and sometimes cheeky cover illustrations that highlighted a single news story or trend, often one underplayed by The Post or ignored by TV newscasts.  It also contained a mix of news stories and features drawn from The Post and original stories and opinion columns produced by its own staff, now numbering 20 journalists. They will be laid off as a result of the paper's closure.  The publication was distributed free of charge each morning via old-fashioned newspaper hawkers (who numbered around 75) at Metro stations and via newspaper boxes. At its peak in 2007, it was distributed to around 190,000 people per day, said Dan Caccavaro, its executive editor. At that point, it was handsomely profitable, he said, and so popular that there was discussion of publishing an afternoon edition for the ride home.  But its circulation has declined in recent years, falling to around 130,000 copies a day this year. The drop reflected, in part, falling Metro ridership, which has been driven by a switch to home telework, riding-sharing services and other means of transportation, Caccavaro said.  In the end, however, Express may have been done in by a technological change within the Metro system itself: WiFi. The wiring of the transportation system has enabled...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T. Boone Pickens Dead at 91...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/2019/09/11/t-boone-pickens-larger-than-life-energy-tycoon-and-osu-diehard-dies-at-91/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T. Boone Pickens, legendary energy executive, philanthropist, ardent Oklahoma State University supporter and one of America's most famous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water discovered for first time in atmosphere of habitable exoplanet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/water-discovered-first-time-atmosphere-habitable-exoplanet-172956870.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water has been discovered for the first time in the atmosphere of an exoplanet with Earth-like temperatures that could support life as we know it, scientists revealed Wednesday. Eight times the mass of Earth and twice as big, K2-18b orbits in its star's "habitable zone" at a distance -</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under fire for trying to give Iraq oil money to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/biden-tried-to-buy-putins-support-for-iraq-war-with-promise-of-oil-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden sought out Russian President Vladimir Putin before the 2003 invasion of Iraq to propose a deal in which Russia would be given the oil profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ministry leaders charged with forced labor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c4813ac83d874fe08de8b61032be5c11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL CENTRO, Calif. (AP) — A dozen leaders of a California-based ministry were arrested on charges that they used homeless people as forced labor, holding them in locked group homes and forcing them...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President weighs ban on flavored e-cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/11/trump-weighs-ban-on-flavored-e-cigarettes-1489507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes as lawmakers are seizing on an outbreak of a vaping-related illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Fed should cut rates to zero 'or less'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/11/trump-says-fed-boneheads-should-cut-interest-rates-to-zero-or-less-us-should-refinance-debt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Wednesday continued his verbal assault on the Federal Reserve, who he blames for slowing the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  White House Pressed Agency to Repudiate Weather Forecasters Who Contradicted Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/460909-mulvaney-pushed-noaa-to-disavow-forecasters-who-contradicted-trump-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House Chief of Staff Mick Mulvaney instructed Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross to have the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) support President Trump’s comments on the threat of Hurricane Dorian to Alabama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/09/11/allegheny-county-district-attorney-antonio-brown-rape-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Allegheny County District Attorney's Office says they will be looking into the sexual assault allegations leveled against former Pittsburgh Steelers wide receiver Antonio Brown in a federal lawsuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Deletes Tweet Saying 'Airplanes Took Aim' at Towers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ny-times-updates-deletes-tweet9-11-airplanes-took-aim-twin-towers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We've deleted an earlier tweet to this story and have edited for clarity," Times says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now ineligible to play?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/NFL-will-consider-placing-Antonio-Brown-on-paid-14431061.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL will give serious consideration to placing Antonio Brown on paid leave via its commissioner's exempt list, according to multiple people familiar with the situation, after he was accused in a federal lawsuit in Florida of rape and sexual assault.  The wide receiver would be ineligible to play for the New England Patriots if he's placed on the exempt list by the league.  Placing Brown on the exempt list is "possible" and something that the NFL is "going to have to focus on," said one of the people close to the situation, who spoke on the condition of anonymity because of the sensitivity of the topic.  The league is investigating the allegations but it's unclear whether a decision about the exempt list will be made this week, before the Patriots are scheduled to play again. Brown has not been charged with a crime, so the NFL does not have to be concerned, at this point, about interfering with a criminal investigation. It is not clear yet if or when the league's investigators will be able to arrange interviews with Brown's accuser and other potential witnesses.  If the league opts to put Brown on paid leave, it also would have to decide under what conditions he would be permitted to come off the exempt list and how it would react, for example, to a prospective settlement of the civil lawsuit. Brown has denied the allegations through his attorney.  NFL leaders planned to meet Wednesday about the matter. The league potentially could allow Brown to begin playing for the Patriots while its investigation proceeds, and then place him on paid leave at some point if NFL officials believe that is warranted.  Brown was at the Patriots' facility Wednesday with the expectation that he would participate in meetings and practice, ESPN reported.  He agreed to a one-year contract with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority Trust Gov't to Use Facial Recognition Responsibly...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/analytics-data/2019/09/study-more-half-americans-trust-law-enforcement-use-facial-recognition-responsibly/159770/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pew Research Center’s study is the latest to conclude Americans are growing more comfortable with having their faces scanned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL ST:  STOP HER!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jim-cramer-says-wall-street-execs-are-panicking-about-elizabeth-warren-presidency-shes-gotta-be-stopped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC host Jim Cramer gave Massachusetts Senator and Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren an unintentional boost when he said that Wall Street executives are privately telling him that &amp;q</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT RISING:  Biden agenda far more liberal than Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article234890482.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New tech takes aim at $74 billion in real estate broker commission...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-buying-and-selling-a-home-could-soon-be-as-simple-as-trading-stocks-2019-09-11 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence in housing won’t just eliminate Realtors. It could completely change the way we buy, sell and live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gets Prison for Family Curse Scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Psychic-gets-federal-prison-time-after-14425923.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman who claimed to be a psychic healer with a direct line to God was sentenced to more than three years in federal prison after she swindled a woman she met at the Galleria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths of first responders on rise... </title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/deaths-of-first-responders-from-ground-zero-related-illnesses-are/article_d272ed73-bafd-5905-b8c3-70a1b58bdab4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most first responders, former New York City detective Tom Frey is a master of understatement — even when it comes to talking about the World Trade Center terror attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC:  He can't fudge GDP number to boost election chances...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/experts-say-trump-probably-cant-manipulate-economic-data-for-2020-bid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and former top economic officials say the economic data that underpins major government programs and forms the basis for private financial forecasts is likely safe from presidential interference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Faces Dozens of Investigations by House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-ramp-trump-inquiries-080000189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Heading into his re-election campaign, President Donald Trump faces months of inquiries by House Democrats beyond a potential impeachment probe.The scrutiny extends from Trump’s personal finances to decisions made by the White House on issues such as health care and immigration, his alleged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch doctor acquitted in landmark euthanasia trial...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-09-dutch-court-doctor-landmark-euthanasia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch doctor was acquitted Wednesday in a landmark trial that prosecutors and physicians hope will help clarify how the country's 2002 euthanasia law can be applied to people with severe dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War still raging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d3aeafcdf97451680cfb439982d3ca7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On his third Sept. 11 anniversary as president, Donald Trump on Wednesday remembered the victims, first responders and U.S. troops that have battled in Afghanistan, and he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS GATHER FOR TEXAS DEBATE</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/10-qualifying-candidates-share-debate-stage-1st-time/story?id=65389784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, every candidate who qualified for the DNC debate will be on the same stage, this time in Houston for the debate hosted by ABC News and Univision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fake News' Fears: 95% 'Troubled' by State of Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fake-news-fears-95-of-americans-troubled-by-current-state-of-media-poll-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study finds that 67% of people think journalistic ethics will be worse during the 2020 election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of World's Biggest Porn Sites Branching Into Fine Art...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/one-of-the-world-s-biggest-porn-sites-is-branching-into-fine-art-1.1314466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub is sponsoring a show at the Maccarone gallery in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
