<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/refresh/AL192020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/215703_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Satanist anarchist wins Republican nomination for county sheriff...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1463548/transsexual-satanist-anarchist-wins-nomination-new-hampshire-sheriff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARIA DiMezzo, a “transsexual Satanist anarchist,” has nabbed the Republican nomination in the sheriff’s race of a New Hampshire county while running with the campaign slogan “F**k the Police.” DiMe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Trump battle for women who sided with president last time -- and now regret it... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Biden-and-Trump-battle-for-women-who-sided-with-15562688.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From her home in the Philadelphia suburbs, Nin Bell works for an answering service, taking calls from people trying to reach more than 10,000 funeral homes and end-of-life companies. As the coronavirus began to sweep the country earlier this year, the number of calls related to new deaths tripled.  Caller after caller told her about losing a loved one to covid-19, as well as to suicides and drug overdoses. They provided an overwhelmingly painful window into just how badly the country was suffering.  And then Bell would hear President Donald Trump - whom she voted for in 2016, helping him win Pennsylvania - downplay the severity of the pandemic.  "He was telling everybody it wasn't a big deal - but I knew it was a big deal because of my job. I'm like: 'Why am I taking 60 coronavirus deaths in one day, on one shift, when I used to only take 20 death calls a day?'" said Bell, 47, the mother of two teenage boys who lives in Parkside, about 20 miles southwest of Philadelphia."He made a lot of mistakes. He just runs his mouth. . . . He's the president, he can't get away with that, especially when people's lives are in danger."  Bell "definitely, 100 percent" plans to vote for Joe Biden for president - and she has been urging others to do the same.  She's part of a group of White women, especially those who are middle- or working-class, who didn't vote for Hillary Clinton in the last election but are determined to vote for Biden this year.  Those women, who have been targeted by both campaigns, loom large in a presidential race that could, like 2016's, be decided by shifts among a few sets of voters in the highly polarized nation.  Although Clinton won the majority of votes from women in 2016, she lost to Trump among White women. Since then, however, polls have shown Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke plumes unlike anything previously seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/californias-wildfire-smoke-plumes-are-unlike-anything-previously-seen/ar-BB18Y54b?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas turms ghost town where even strippers put up signs saying, 'Sorry, we're clothed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8726053/Las-Vegas-ghost-town-strippers-signs-saying-Sorry-clothed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the shadow of Covid-19, Las Vegas is on its own losing streak. Casinos, hotels and shows which last year generated $60 billion (£48 billion) in tourist revenue are either almost empty or shuttered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WB HIDES 'TENET' BOXOFFICE DATA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/box-office/warner-bros-tenet-box-office-studios-1234767113/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who closely follow box office earnings have noticed a surprising lack of transparency surrounding ticket sales for “Tenet,” the $200 million-budgeted sci-fi epic from director Ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial resumes after 'unexplained illness'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vaccine-trial-resumes-virus-continues-225916843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinical trials of one of the most advanced experimental Covid-19 vaccines resumed Saturday after a brief safety pause, as infection numbers continued to march upward in countries across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli protesters keep up pressure on Netanyahu over alleged corruption...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200912182400-pha5g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-PROTESTS (TV, PIX):Israeli protesters keep up pressure on Netanyahu over alleged corruption</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro says Venezuela caught Marine-turned-CIA spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1462920/maduro-venezuela-caught-usa-marine-cia-spy-target-oil-refineries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA’S President says authorities caught a U.S. Marine-turned-CIA spy with ‘special weapons’ meant to target the nation’s oil refineries President Nicolás Maduro said t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's smoke plumes unlike anything previously seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-s-wildfire-smoke-plumes-are-unlike-15562222.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 3.1 million acres have burned in California this year, part of a record fire season that still has four months to go. A suffocating cloud of smoke has veiled the West Coast for days, extending more than a thousand miles above the Pacific. And the extreme fire behavior that's been witnessed this year hasn't just been wild - it's virtually unprecedented in scope and scale.  Fire tornadoes have spun up by the handful in at least three big wildfires in the past three weeks, based on radar data. Giant clouds of ash and smoke have generated lightning. Multiple fires have gone from a few acres to more than 100,000 acres in size in a day, while advancing as many as 25 miles in a single night. And wildfire plumes have soared up to 10 miles high, above the cruise altitude of commercial jets.  Scientists have been scrambling to collect as much data on these wildfires as possible, hoping to unlock the secrets to their extreme behavior and fury. Among them is Neil Lareau, a professor of atmospheric sciences in the department of physics at the University of Nevada at Reno. Lareau closely studies pyrocumulus clouds, towering explosion-like plumes of heat that develop above intense blazes.  He retrieved data from the National Weather Service's network of Doppler radars, which scan the skies every few moments at up to 15 different vertical angles. By stitching these different elevation "slices" together, he was able to produce a three-dimensional model of each smoke plume.  The Creek Fire, which burned nearly 200,000 acres in the Sierra Nevada Mountains, was only 6% contained on Friday. On Sept. 5, a day after it was first ignited, its smoke plume soared to 55,000 feet. That's taller than many of the tornadic thunderstorms that roll across Oklahoma and Kansas each spring.  Such clouds are both indicators of and contributors to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco may soon allow 16-year-olds to vote!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/major-american-city-may-soon-allow-16-year-olds-vote-n1239955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the proposition passes, San Francisco would become the first large city to give 16- and 17-year-olds the right to vote in local elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Unvetted Vaccine Next?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-pressed-for-plasma-therapy-officials-worry-is-an-unvetted-vaccine-next/ar-BB18Y5jc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Sued for Packing NFL Charters With Young, Blond Crews...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/united-sued-for-packing-nfl-charters-with-young-blond-crews/ar-BB18X2Wi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France and Spain sets daily infection record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/france-sets-daily-record-more-22673308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second wave of Covid-19 in France showed no signs of slowing as a record 10,561 new infections were announced, the first time the daily number has topped 10,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LULULEMON, which is worth $40 billion and sells $128 yoga pants, promotes 'resist capitalism' event...</title>
      <link>https://notthebee.com/article/lululemon-which-is-worth-40-billion-and-sells-128-yoga-pants-promotes-resist-capitalism-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;notthebee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROFL 🤣</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WATCH GULF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/884d6693c5ebb9c9a1b7b440d39d6022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — Tropical Storm Sally formed Saturday off south Florida, becoming the earliest 18th-named storm on record in an Atlantic hurricane season as it enters the Gulf of Mexico...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY VALLEY  HEARTBREAK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/56216039822719d0760198f4560c0030</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — Wildfire smoke that posed a health hazard to millions choked the West Coast on Saturday as firefighters battled deadly blazes that obliterated some towns and displaced tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOMADLAND' WINS VENICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nomadland-wins-golden-lion-award-at-venice-film-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting awards went to Vanessa Kirby and Pierfrancesco Favino at the scaled-down festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Unvetted Vaccine Next?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/12/us/politics/trump-coronavirus-treatment-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details of how the president has demanded faster action from health agencies help explain the intensifying concern that he could demand pre-Election Day approval of a vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tries his luck in Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/trump-tries-luck-nevada-161700024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the clock ticks down to Election Day, President Donald Trump is spending valuable time this weekend in Nevada — a state he lost in 2016, but that his campaign sees as a critical part of a backup path to re-election, as his current electoral odds continue to narrow in states he won narrowly that year. Trump was scheduled to hold a high-dollar fundraiser in Las Vegas, and rallies in Las Vegas and Reno. Both sets of plans nod to the campaign's challenges this cycle — the fundraisers come amid home stretch money concerns, while the public events were still in flux late in the week due to pandemic-related challenges that have dogged similar rally plans this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENICE WINNERS LIST...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/venice-film-festival-winners-2020-golden-lion-full-list-1234575829/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Refresh for latest…: Following a successful two weeks that marked the first major international industry event in the pandemic era, the Venice Film Festival draws to a close tonight as Cate B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsonists arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1461447/four-arrested-intentionally-starting-blazes-wildfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR people have now been arrested on the West Coast for deliberately starting blazes as wildfires rage. Cops detained two men in Washington, man in Oregon and woman in California as the desperate …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek and Turkish ships playing chicken at sea. There's already been one crash....</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Greek-and-Turkish-ships-are-playing-chicken-at-15562178.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last weekend, Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan demanded that Greece engage in talks over escalating tensions in the eastern Mediterranean, warning that "They're either going to understand the language of politics and diplomacy, or in the field with painful experiences." The Greek government, meanwhile, announced further steps this week to bolster the country's defenses.  New tensions between the two longtime rivals flared up in mid-August, when Turkey deployed the research vessel Oruç Reis, flanked by two warships, to explore for oil and gas in contested waters between the islands of Crete and Cyprus. Greece accused Turkey of violating its sovereign rights -- and dispatched warships of its own, precipitating a collision between a Greek frigate and a Turkish warship.  How Greece and Turkey interpret international maritime law is key to understanding what's going on in this contested part of the Mediterranean, a conflict that risks drawing in other countries, including Germany, France and the UAE. Here's what our research tells us.  - Parties are doubling down on dueling interpretations of the law of the sea. The U.N. Convention on the Law of the Sea (UNCLOS) asserts that countries may claim a territorial sea extending up to 12 nautical miles (nm) from their coasts, including sovereignty over the offshore oil under those waters. UNCLOS also grants nations the right to claim "sovereign rights and jurisdiction" over the waters, seabed and subsoil of an exclusive economic zone (EEZ) extending up to 200 nm, as well as a continental shelf extending up to 350 nm in certain circumstances.  This might sound straightforward, but in semi-enclosed seas like the Aegean and Mediterranean, geographical limitations and overlapping claims make it near-impossible for any country to stake out its full jurisdiction. For this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot who witnessed declassified UFO says object committed 'act of war' during encounter...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/usa/500504-declassified-ufo-act-of-war-radar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the former fighter pilots who encountered a mysterious flying object off the coast of California in 2004 says the unidentified phenomena committed an “act of war” in the unexplained encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran executes champion wrestler who was 'tortured into confessing to murder'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/iran-executes-champion-wrestler-who-22671125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navid Afkari, convicted of fatally stabbing a security guard during anti-government protests in Shiraz, Iran, was supported by the likes of Donald Trump and FIFA amid calls for Tehran to spare his life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advantages of incumbency crumbling away for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-advantages-of-incumbency-are-crumbling-away-15562130.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump had a bad week: That was the week before last. He had another one this past week. For someone trailing former vice president Joe Biden in the presidential race, Trump remains the biggest obstacle to reelection, an embattled incumbent who is frittering away the advantages of incumbency.  The week before last it was an article in the Atlantic by Jeffrey Goldberg that portrayed the president using derogatory language about military personnel killed or wounded in action. It was based on several unnamed sources and Trump - and others now or formerly in the administration - vigorously disputed the account. Prominently absent from those publicly defending Trump were former defense secretary Jim Mattis and, critically, former White House chief of staff John Kelly.  This past week it was an entirely different issue for the president - a self-inflicted problem that was the result of his many hours of taped, on-the-record conversations with Washington Post associate editor Bob Woodward, whose book "Rage" will be published this week.  Trump's own words plunged him into a controversy about how early knew about the dangers of the coronavirus and why he didn't share that with the public. Because he couldn't disclaim what was on the tapes, he offered as a defense that he didn't want to panic the public - though as The Post's Phil Rucker pointed out, the president has repeatedly played on fear as a political weapon.  Throughout his presidency, Trump has been skillful at creating diversions when things go awry. Today it's more the case that events are creating distractions from his ability to deliver a consistent and effective campaign message. This is one more example of the reality that, since the beginning of the year, he has seen the advantages of incumbency erode or disappear.  Before the pandemic, the economy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice gears up to award masked Golden Lion winner...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200912-venice-film-festival-gears-up-to-award-masked-golden-lion-winner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice film festival gears up to award masked Golden Lion winner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside hyper-violent cartel who 'now outgun El Chapo's criminal empire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-hyper-violent-mexican-cartel-22663888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jalisco New Generation Cartel has become a dominant force in Mexico's ceaseless drug war. Its members carry out horrifying acts of violence and push their products across the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 families buy 97 acres of land in Georgia to create city safe for Black people...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/12/us/freedom-black-cooperative-toomsboro/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Welcome to Freedom!" exclaims real estate agent Ashley Scott as she surveys the nearly 97 acres of land that she and a group of 19 Black families purchased in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Sanders shows concerns over campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Sanders-shows-concerns-over-Biden-campaign-15562057.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., is privately expressing concerns about Joe Biden's presidential campaign, according to three people with knowledge of the conversations, urging Biden's team to intensify its focus on pocketbook issues and appeals to liberal voters.  Sanders, the runner-up to Biden in the Democratic primary, has told associates that Biden is at serious risk of coming up short in the November election if he continues his vaguer, more centrist approach, according to the people, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe sensitive talks.  The senator has identified several specific changes he'd like to see, saying Biden should talk more about health care and about his economic plans, and should campaign more with figures popular among young liberals, such as Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y.  Asked for comment, Sanders's team provided a statement from Faiz Shakir, the senator's former campaign manager in the presidential race, saying that Sanders is "working as hard as he can" to get Biden elected but has advised some strategic adjustments.  "Senator Sanders is confident that Joe Biden is in a very strong position to win this election, but nevertheless feels there are areas the campaign can continue to improve upon," Shakir said. "He has been in direct contact with the Biden team and has urged them to put more emphasis on how they will raise wages, create millions of good paying jobs, lower the cost of prescription drugs and expand health care coverage."  Shakir said Sanders "also thinks that a stronger outreach to young people, the Latino community and the progressive movement will be of real help to the campaign."  The Biden campaign declined to comment.  Sanders led a surging liberal faction during the Democratic primaries and scored early successes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Pelosi? Don't underestimate what she might do in office...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/515839-president-nancy-pelosi-dont-underestimate-what-she-might-do-in-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A delay in voting results and potential voter fraud could put the House Speaker temporarily in the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The coming wave of defaults...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/516032-the-coming-wave-of-defaults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We face a new wave of mortgage and rental delinquencies, much of which will come in the next few months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan warns Macron not to 'mess with Turkey'...</title>
      <link>https://www.trtworld.com/turkey/erdogan-warns-macron-not-to-mess-with-turkey-39702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.trtworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments come after France’s Macron criticism of Ankara over the current tensions in the eastern Mediterranean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE?</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvertiser.com/story/news/2020/09/12/tropical-storm-sally-depression-19-nhc-update-saturday-louisiana/5772291002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Depression 19 is forecast to turn into Tropical Storm Sally over the weekend, ahead of approaching the Gulf of Mexico. Get the latest updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Democracy in America plunges to new low...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/democracy-america-new-low-2020-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll finds large declines among several principals including protections of free speech and the tolerance of peaceful protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC star McGregor arrested in Corsica for indecent exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/other-sports/mma/breaking-conor-mcgregor-arrested-alleged-22672332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former two-weight UFC champion has been training for a 180km voyage to raise awareness of water safety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic orange glow slowed blaze?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/12/apocalyptic-glow-may-have-helped-quell-california-wildfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apocalyptic orange skies seen in Northern California earlier this week actually helped quell the devastation from the massive wildfires, but death and devastation lie beneath the ashes. The smo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dakotas lead virus growth as both reject mask rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4988865f4fad739e099b17707f8727f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — Coronavirus infections in the Dakotas are growing faster than anywhere else in the nation, fueling impassioned debates over masks and personal freedom after months in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican water wars: Dam seized, troops deployed, at least 1 killed in protests about sharing with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/mexican-water-wars-dam-seized-troops-deployed-at-least-1-killed-in-protests-about-sharing/article_c4306e29-9cc0-58f0-9db6-62c75cf810fe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — Mexico's water wars have turned deadly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar-tipped road movie 'NOMADLAND' races between global festivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-nz/entertainment/news/oscar-tipped-road-movie-nomadland-races-between-global-festivals/ar-BB18Xjlu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian prosecutor set for 'historic' anti-mafia court battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/italian-prosecutor-set-for-historic-anti-mafia-court-battle/ar-BB18XQwh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Sued for Packing NFL Charters With Young, Blond Crews...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/united-sued-for-packing-nfl-charters-with-young-blond-crews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In so doing, the airline bases the value of workers entirely on their racial and physical attributes, and stereotypical notions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onslaught Falls Short of Breakthrough...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/12/trump-onslaught-against-biden-falls-short-of-a-breakthrough/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s weekslong barrage against Joseph R. Biden Jr. has failed to erase the Democrat’s lead across a set of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest Concerns Don't Translate Into Surge for President...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/12/in-wisconsin-poll-unrest-concerns-dont-translate-into-surge-for-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The key battleground of Wisconsin, which President Trump carried in 2016 by talking up trade, the economy and doubts about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctica still free of COVID-19. Can it stay that way?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d99c49fbd77540fac433cb7c644c6974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — At this very moment a vast world exists that’s free of the coronavirus, where people can mingle without masks and watch the pandemic unfold from thousands of miles...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy shaken up by brutal beating death of young Black man...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16b6a0dafbc7d11e8ab09be48805e6cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Hundreds of people in Italy walked in a funeral procession Saturday for a young Black man whose brutal beating death has shaken up the country and drawn condemnation from the highest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL WATCH GULF...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/121154.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAnon spreads across globe, shadowing COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/516102-qanon-spreads-across-globe-shadowing-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The QAnon movement is spreading around the world, turning an outlandish conspiracy theory revolving around President Trump into one of the nation’s most dangerous exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran executes wrestler who Trump, others urged country to spare...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/516123-iran-executes-wrestler-who-trump-urged-country-to-spare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has reportedly executed a wrestler accused of murder after President Trump asked authorities to spare him from the death penalty, according to the country’s state TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY VALLEY  HEARTBREAK</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Half-a-million-Oregonians-more-than-10-percent-15559123.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAPPY VALLEY, Ore. - Wildfires across the West Coast have killed at least 19 people in California and have ravaged more than a million acres of land in Oregon, where dozens of people were missing and tens of thousands of residents evacuated their homes amid some of the most dangerous air conditions in the world.  Oregon officials said they believe the wildfires could have claimed numerous lives because of how many structures have burned, but they said a death toll is unclear as they began to survey the destruction. Fires continued to rip through more than 1,500 square miles in the state on Friday.  "We know we're dealing with fire-related death, and we're preparing for a mass fatality incident based on what we know and the number of structures that have been lost," said Andrew Phelps, director of Oregon's Office of Emergency Management. Phelps said he could not confirm how many deaths had occurred from the fires, but a state-run dashboard recorded at least five fatalities.  After days of high temperatures and dry winds, cooler weather on Friday allowed firefighters to begin to contain some of the 16 fires across the state. But they had barely begun to make headway when dense smoke limited firefighters' ability to fly, said Doug Grafe, chief of fire protection for the Oregon Department of Forestry. Eight of the 16 fires will be on the map until fall rains arrive, Grafe said.  A cluster of fires grew dramatically across a swath of 56 miles southeast of Portland, burning about 440,000 acres in an area of the state unaccustomed to wildfires of this magnitude, Grafe said. A blanket of smoke covered the sky even in downtown Portland, where officials opened up the Oregon Convention Center for evacuees.  "We have not seen the likes of this fire in this state, this integrated with our communities, ever before," Grafe said. "We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mx_RZIPC3M0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani claims 'no reason to believe' his Ukraine contact is spy despite sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-giuliani-ukraine-russian-spy-trump-20200911-2xllriyagzgthpbje2hyopcunm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Americans commemorated the 19th anniversary of 9/11, NYC's former mayor talked about his active dislike for de Blasio and Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL WATCH MIAMI...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/112055.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump made promise to save coal in 2016. He couldn't keep it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trump-made-a-promise-to-save-coal-in-2016-he-couldnt-keep-it/ar-BB18Gm7N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN to Televise 'Black National Anthem'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2020/09/10/espn-to-televise-protesting-players-and-singing-of-black-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The players have said they will protest and, if they do, ESPN says they will televise it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE '75% CHANCE OF WINNING'...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecast of the 2020 presidential election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of San Quentin inmate who contracted virus files wrongful death claim...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/family-san-quentin-inmate-contracted-032703943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family of San Quentin inmate dead after getting COVID-19 files death claim cites transfer of infected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising deaths and lost hope...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-staggering-fire-toll-record-110053322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With months of fire season ahead, blazes across California explode in size, taxing resources. Ten are reported dead in fire sweeping Butte and nearby counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of structures destroyed in CA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/10-killed-californias-deadliest-blaze-184704800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Complex fire near Oroville in Butte County is now blamed for 10 deaths, placing it among the deadliest wildfires in state history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials battle online misinformation along with wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d294693de30f859f6c028122fd99bf11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Emergency responders in the Pacific Northwest are fighting misinformation along with raging wildfires as people spread unsubstantiated social media posts blaming coordinated groups...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL players booed as racial justice stand sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/561c74297aef243e58ac573afe4d8e26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — The NFL’s new stance encouraging players to take a stand against racial injustice got its first test as some fans of the Super Bowl champion Kansas City Chiefs booed during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OREGON SCORCHED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/429f97bdf66aaa28a4dd43879a412503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — Hundreds of firefighters battled two large wildfires Friday that threatened to merge near the most populated part of Oregon, including the suburbs of Portland, and the governor...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
