<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules law prohibiting secret recording of govt officials is unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/news/boston/index.ssf/2018/12/federal_judge_rules_mass_law_p.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal court judge Monday ruled a Massachusetts General Law prohibiting the secret recording of police or government officials is unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK: Get-Trump talk now campaign finance, not Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-sudden-shift-in-get-trump-talk-now-its-campaign-finance-not-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors investigating President Trump made big news Friday, but it wasn't about Russia. Rather, in their sentencing recommendation for fixer Michael Cohen, lawyers with the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York wrote that in the final weeks of the 2016 campaign, candidate Trump…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False statement charges abound, contrast to Clinton case...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/false-statement-charges-abound-in-mueller-probe-discouraged-in-clinton-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation is abounding with false statement charges against Trump campaign associates, but a Justice Department inspector general report revealed that the FBI and federal prosecutors discouraged charging witnesses under the same offense in the bureau’s probe into Hillary Clinton’s private email server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO: Masked man shoots livestreaming campaign door-knocker...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/man-recovering-from-being-shot-while-campaigning-for-15th-ward-political-candidate/4872789/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxwell Little, also known on social media as Maxwell Omowale Justice, is recovering after being shot in the leg while campaigning for 15th Ward aldermanic candidate Joseph Williams on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman plotted mass murder, corresponded with SC church shooter...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/news/ohio-woman-who-plotted-mass-murder-corresponded-with-dylann-roof/article_e84839b4-fcb8-11e8-ae4f-cb4da1e387eb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio woman accused of plotting what she referred to as an "upscale mass murder" at a Toledo bar had glorified Dylann Roof and corresponded with the self-avowed white supremacist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKEDIN billionaire backs voter data project in 'existential threat' to Democratic Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/10/linkedin-reid-hoffman-dnc-voter-data-1054857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;DNC’s top leaders have been telling people that Hoffman’s project represents an “existential threat&amp;quot; to the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NISSAN Million-Dollar Supercar...</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/news/25359/nissan-opens-orders-for-1-1-million-710-hp-gt-r50-italdesign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it Nissan's farewell to the R35 GT-R, or is it a glimpse of the R36? Doesn't matter—it's both gorgeous and knock-your-socks-off fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socials outpace print as news source for adults...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/12/10/social-media-outpaces-print-newspapers-in-the-u-s-as-a-news-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One-in-five U.S. adults often get news via social media, slightly higher than the 16% who often do so from print newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star under fire after calling moon landing fake...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/warriors/article/steph-curry-fake-moon-landing-podcast-13454284.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Curry says he does not believe humans have been to the moon, a stance which is clearly unsupported by facts and hopefully just a joke.  Curry made the proclamation on The Ringer's podcast "Winging It" with teammate Andre Iguodala and hosts Vince Carter and Kent Bazemore; you can hear the exchange around the 46-minute mark. There's some talking over each other that makes it hard to hear, but when the discussion turns to the moon landing, almost everyone seems to agree we've never been to there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record count for mysterious paralyzing illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6cc9d8f3a9c4c84b72a9f45c3a335ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — This year has seen a record number of cases of a mysterious paralyzing illness in children, U.S. health officials said Monday. It's still not clear what's causing the kids to lose the ability to move their face, neck, back, arms or legs. The symptoms tend to occur about a week after the children had a fever and respiratory illness. No one has died from the rare disease this year, but it was blamed for one death last year and it may have caused others in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs officers searching more travelers' devices...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54497b1d5f5541efb96dc25d11ee66a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. Customs and Border Protection officers are searching the electronic devices of travelers more often, and did not always follow proper protocol, a new watchdog report has found. The report made public Monday found there were 29,000 devices searched at a port of entry out of 397 million travelers to the U.S. in budget year 2017, up from 18,400 the year before from 390 million travelers. Customs and Border Protection officials note it is less than 1 percent of all travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE announces new security flaw, closes social network...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/google-announces-new-security-flaw-closes-social-network-early-n946201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Plus received its initial kiss of death in early October, when the company revealed that a security bug had exposed the information of 500,000 users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for plotting synagogue attacks in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-man-arrested-for-plotting-synagogue-attacks-in-toledo-ohio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI says Damon Joseph planned to carry out mass shooting during Shabbat services on behalf of Islamic State, told undercover agent he was inspired by Pittsburgh massacre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gets Wedding Ring Back -- After Flushing It Down Toilet 9 Years Ago!</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/10/woman-gets-wedding-ring-back-after-flushing-it-down-toilet-9-years-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paula Stanton was sure the diamond-encrusted gold ring was lost forever after she noticed it wasn't on her finger while she was cleaning her bathroom nearly a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters save 100 snakes from house fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article222894925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters in Texas rescued more than 100 pythons, boa constrictors and other snakes from a home that caught fire over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusion, Despair in Hinterlands...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-france-high-school-students-protests-yellow-vests&gt;Students vow 'Black Tuesday' protests...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows NYC police pulling toddler from mother's arms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dc2801bde5e8423c85ab058bede17858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Outrage built Monday over a video showing police officers violently yanking a toddler from his mother's arms at a Brooklyn food stamp office, with public officials expressing horror and clients of the facility complaining it is indicative of how the city treats social-services recipients. A witness said a security officer confronted the woman, Jazmine Headley, who had sat on the floor of the crowded office for two hours because of a lack of chairs. Police were called when she refused to leave. The woman ended up lying face-up on the floor during a tug of war over the child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt restricts yellow vests sales to avoid copycat protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/38a1a03c66234372b2149f3013f642ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Egyptian authorities have quietly introduced restrictions on the sale of yellow reflective vests, fearing opponents might attempt to copy French protesters during next month's anniversary of the 2011 popular uprising that toppled autocrat Hosni Mubarak, security officials and retailers said Monday. They said industrial safety equipment dealers have been instructed not to sell yellow vests to walk-in buyers and to restrict business to wholesale sales to verified companies, but only after securing police permission. They were told offenders would be punished, the officials said without elaborating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron promises tax relief...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/216f4fe17e85429a82ee088ed2a73b41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on anti-government protests in France (all times local): 8:15 p.m. Facing exceptional protests, French President Emmanuel Macron is promising to speed up tax relief for struggling workers and to scrap a tax hike for retirees. The actions were the pledges Macron made on Monday night in his first public comments since protests against his presidency devolved into rioting in the French capital. The French leader reiterated earlier promises to raise the minimum wage and pledged to abolish taxes on overtime pay starting Jan. 1, several months before schedule. He also said a tax hike pensioners faced would be scrapped. All of the measures offered had been demanded by the yellow-vested protesters who have led four weeks of increasingly radicalized demonstrations against Macron's presidency, seen as favoring the rich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Licensed Content Remains Majority of Total Streams...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/netflix-original-series-licensed-viewing-friends-the-office-1203085230/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Netflix moving fast enough to bulk up on originals to offset programming that’s about to get pulled by studios like Disney, Fox and WarnerMedia? Original content accounted for 37% of Netfl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-BLOOMBERG Execs to Be Charged in Construction Fraud Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/10/nyregion/bloomberg-construction-fraud-kickback.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a dozen executives at the company are expected to be arrested on Tuesday by the Manhattan district attorney on fraud, theft and bribery charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of allegations in fundamental Baptist churches across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article222576310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation into US fundamental Baptist churches found more than 400 sexual misconduct allegations. More than 160 pastors, ministers and Christian leaders have been accused of committing crimes against children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Threatens Vehicle Attacks Near U.S. Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-magazine-for-millennials-threatens-vehicle-attacks-near-u-s-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debut issue of The Youth of the Caliphate called for attacks in Australia; a month later, a jihadist conducted a deadly stabbing attack in Melbourne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONIC employees allegedly laced kid's meal with ecstasy...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/sonic-employees-accused-of-lacing-kids-meal-with-ecstasy/4871425/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say two Sonic employees and their manager were arrested after ecstasy was reportedly found in a child's meal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, rebels discussing term limits for party leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/10/pelosi-party-leader-term-limits-1054789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several members of the anti-Pelosi group discussed the potential deal on a conference call Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's visit to Baltimore called off...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-trump-visit-cancelled-20181210-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A planned visit by President Donald Trump to Baltimore on Wednesday has been called off and a discussion of the administration’s urban revitalization policies will take place at the White House instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Pamphlets With KKK Logos Distributed Across Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/12/09/pittsburgh-anti-semitic-materials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Pittsburgh are investigating hate-filled material that is being distributed in city neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers leap to sign John Kelly to $15 million tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6479553/Publishers-leap-chance-John-Kelly-tell-book-deal-time-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top publishers said they 'would kill' to publish John Kelly's tell-all book about his time as Trump's Chief of Staff. One editor said they reached out to him before the formal announcement was made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Voyager 2 Leaves Solar System, Enters Interstellar Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/voyager-2-probe-moves-into-interstellar-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;11 billion miles from Earth, NASA's Voyager 2 spacecraft has moved into interstellar space, joining Voyager 1 in the realm between the stars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of Honduras, El Salvador, Domincan Republic want to leave; USA top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/158-million-migrants-want-to-move-to-the-us-worlds-top-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is the top pick – by far – for migrants seeking a new home despite reports that President Trump’s policies are scaring people away and making countries like Canada and some in Europe the preferred choice, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayers walks away from White House...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/09/politics/ayers-white-house-chief-of-staff/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Ayers, the leading candidate to replace John Kelly as President Donald Trump's chief of staff, announced Sunday he will not be taking the job, reviving discussions about who will succeed the retired Marine general when he leaves at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli troops raid office of Palestinian news agency...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181210162908-cagcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/RAID (TV, PIX):Israeli troops raid office of Palestinian news agency - Wafa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese court bans sale of most iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/apple-falls-after-qualcomm-injunction-in-china-bans-most-iphone-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese court ordered a ban on most iPhone sales in the country as part of two preliminary injunctions. Qualcomm sought the injunctions, alleging Apple violated two of its patents. Apple denies any patent violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY DELAY!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181210154633-ygpjh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 9-UK's May pulls vote on her divorce deal, thrusting Brexit into the unknown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/wall-street-faces-stomach-churning-swings-as-economic-uncertainty-grows/18053902/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a trade war broke out between the world’s two largest economies in June, investors barely blinked. After the Federal Reserve raised interest rates — often a reason for investors to sell stocks — the markets kept climbing. As some of the world’s largest economies began to slow down, U.S. markets largely shrugged it off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY DELAY!</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/may-pulls-parliamentary-vote-on-her-brexit-deal-idUSKBN1O90X1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May on Monday abruptly pulled a parliamentary vot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLD:  Pharrell Williams mocked for excessively thanking AMERICAN EXPRESS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/12/10/pharrell-williams-mocked-for-excessively-thanking-american-express/?_ga=2.243566861.96299170.1544457139-1073313886.1542905213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is an amazing concert, but how many times is he contractually obligated to thank Amex?” a spy asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM PULLS BREXIT VOTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa2ff4d861a24db9a1fa717d9fdc9adb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — The Latest on the debate over Britain's impending departure from the European Union (all times local): 5:15 p.m. British opposition leader Jeremy Corbyn has challenged Prime Minster Theresa May's decision to delay a vote on Brexit in the House of Commons, arguing that her government is in "complete disarray." Labour lawmakers shouted "Resign! Resign!' as May wrapped up her remarks Monday, adding further insult to the humiliation of failing to deliver on her signature piece of legislation, the Brexit divorce deal from the European Union. Corbyn described the situation as unprecedented and serious. He says "the government has lost control of events and is in complete disarray." Even members of May's own party were quick to further criticize the way she's handled the negotiations. Conservative Party lawmaker Jacob Rees-Mogg sharply rejected May's "undeliverable deal," saying it risked paving the way for a Labour Party government led by Corbyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court gives victory to PLANNED PARENTHOOD in Medicaid case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-leaves-legal-victory-place-planned-parenthood-n945946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dispute did not involve abortion, but rather a legal battle over whether states could block Medicaid patients' access to other health services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'John of God' hit with sex abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://www1.folha.uol.com.br/internacional/en/brazil/2018/12/twelve-women-accuse-medium-john-of-god-of-sexual-abuse.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.folha.uol.com.br&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twelve women have come forward with allegations of sexual abuse against world-famous Brazilian medium and spiritual healer João de Deus (John of God). According to the victims, he abused them when they sought spiritual healing in the House of Dom Inácio de Loyola, in Abadiânia (GO), where thousands of people from all over the world go searching for spiritual treatments and counseling to every week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve Women Accuse...</title>
      <link>https://www1.folha.uol.com.br/internacional/en/brazil/2018/12/abuse-allegations-against-john-of-god-shock-small-goias-town.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.folha.uol.com.br&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silence. The word, repeated exhaustively as an order in pictures and posters hanging on walls at Casa Dom Inácio de Loyola, in Abadiânia (GO) describes what part of the small town's 15,000 residents have been going through since the press reported several allegations of sexual abuse involving João de Deus (John of God), one of Brazil's most famous psychics.On the streets, few people talk freely about the scandal, since the town's economy relies heavily on the activities of Casa Dom Inácio, João de Deus spiritual healing center, open since 1976. They say they are afraid of retaliation and also because the medium hasn't talked about it yet.On Saturday (8th), 13 women told newspaper O Globo and TV Globo's late night talk show "Conversa com Bial" that the psychic had been sexually abused them during spiritual healing sessions in his private quarters inside Casa Dom Inácio, where more than a thousand people pass every week, from Wednesdays to Fridays.The news reports changed Abadiânia's routine. On Sunday (9th) morning, tourists and residents were feeling unsettled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Summons U.S. Ambassador Over HUAWEI...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-09/china-foreign-ministry-summons-u-s-ambassador-over-huawei</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Roger Ailes documentary earns less than $13K at boxoffice...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/420507-roger-ailes-documentary-earns-less-than-13k-at-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new documentary on former Fox News CEO and Chairman Roger Ailes earned just $12,431 on Friday and Saturday after its release, according to ComScore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's Turn in Hot Seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-ceo-faces-hot-seat-in-washington-1544446801 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai is expected to face questions at a Congressional hearing on a range of topics, including the company’s handling of user data and its development of a search engine that would comply with China’s strict internet censors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking two languages may help aging brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Speaking-two-languages-may-help-the-aging-brain-13453980.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even when you're fluent in two languages, it can be a challenge to switch back and forth smoothly between them. It's common to mangle a split verb in Spanish, use the wrong preposition in English or lose sight of the connection between the beginning and end of a long German sentence. So does mastering a second language hone our multitasking skills or merely muddle us up? This debate has been pitting linguists and psychologists against one another since the 1920s, when many experts thought that bilingual children were fated to suffer cognitive impairments later in life. But the science has marched on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Jews feel under threat, think of emigrating: EU survey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-antisemitism/european-jews-feel-under-threat-think-of-emigrating-eu-survey-idUSKBN1O91RA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one in three European Jews have considered emigrating over the past fi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human SOUL' to be scanned?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/747335/powerful-mri-scanner-china-human-soul-consciousness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW TUMBLES AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/09/dow-futures-drop-200-points-as-sell-off-is-set-to-continue-in-new-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded lower in a volatile session as investors feared an intensifying trade war between the United States and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese military official urges plan to attack American naval vessels in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3592985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.taiwannews.com.tw&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-business optimism dips...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/small-business-optimism-dips-over-fears-of-an-economic-slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although tax cuts and regulatory rollbacks this year fueled small-business optimism to hit its highest level in decades, the latest CNBC/SurveyMonkey Small Business Survey, released Monday, reveals small-business confidence is starting to cool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusion, Despair in Hinterlands...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/riots-reveal-disillusion-and-despair-in-french-hinterlands-1544450282</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In small cities and towns like Montluçon, French who watched with silent skepticism as President Emmanuel Macron racked up political victories are now rising against his vision for remaking the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUALCOMM wins import ban against iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/china-court-grants-qualcomm-injunction-against-apple.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President defends hush money payments as 'private transaction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia/trump-defends-hush-money-payments-as-simple-private-transaction-idUSKBN1O91JW </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump on Monday defended hush money payments reported by his former lawye...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students oppose Clarence Thomas building -- but don't know why...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I haven’t done much research on this..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to kill you': Nicaragua's brutal crackdown on press freedom..</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/dec/10/nicaragua-journalists-press-freedom-crackdown-ortega</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists have been beaten, arrested, and robbed in the wake of the civil revolt that paralysed the country earlier in the year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next worry: Shrinking profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-earnings/the-next-worry-for-u-s-stocks-shrinking-profit-forecasts-idUSKBN1O91B0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing ranks of stock market Eeyores now have another reason to stay glum: ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Spy Cameras In Vacuum Cleaners...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-08/dea-spy-cameras-vacuum-cleaners-surveillance-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMILIATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7942076/theresa-may-brexit-deal-house-of-commons-vote-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May is today set to SCRAP the Commons vote on her Brexit deal in a humiliating climbdown. MPs were due to vote on the withdrawal agreement tomorrow night. But facing a huge defeat with doze…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Disappearing From Airwaves, COURT TV Will Get Another Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/after-disappearing-from-airwaves-court-tv-will-get-another-trial-1544443200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal network is being relaunched by E.W. Scripps, which bets on consumer demand for true-crime media. It will offer viewers 24/7 trial coverage, along with analysis and commentary from legal experts and documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants in Tijuana trickling over and under wall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4defb351a1e4b5982688b07d8bb9958</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico (AP) — A steady trickle of Central American migrants have been finding ways to climb over, tunnel under or slip through the U.S. border wall to plant their feet on U.S. soil and ask for asylum. In recent weeks, Honduran migrant Joel Mendez fed his 8-month-old son, Daniel, before handing him over to his partner, Yesenia Martinez, who had crawled through a hole in the rain-softened soil under the wall. A group of young people hoisted themselves over the wall to San Ysidro, California, hoping that their ticket to a better life was finally within reach. One migrant offered a hand to help the others jumping down onto U.S. territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY DELAYS BREXIT VOTE?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/12/10/brexit-latest-news-vote-theresa-mays-deal-air-rivals-eye-leadership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May will delay the vote in Parliament on her Brexit deal, multiple sources have told The Telegraph, while she has held an emergency conference call with her Cabinet this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Dispatching Bombers to Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/russia-dispatching-blackjack-bombers-venezuela/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is deploying nuclear-capable Tu-160 Blackjack bombers to Venezuela as part of an increasingly provocative pattern of bomber training flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Masculine faces seen as more competent...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/women/masculine-competence-faces-gender-bias-study-association-for-psychological-science-a8675686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaunt, Filthy Kids Roam Streets of Caracas in Packs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/gaunt-filthy-and-scared-kids-roam-streets-of-caracas-in-packs#gs.HdLkBvY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaunt, Filthy Kids Roam Streets of Caracas in Packs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps Know Where Were Last Night -- and Not Keeping It Secret...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/your-apps-know-where-you-were-last-night-and-theyre-not-keeping-it-secret-5486582/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The database reviewed by The New York Times, a sample of information gathered in 2017 and held by one company, reveals people’s travels in startling detail, accurate to within a few yards and in some cases updated more than 14,000 times a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Christians snatched in overnight raids in Sichuan province...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/2177263/100-snatched-china-church-raids-overnight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worshippers taken from their homes and off the streets in coordinated crackdown across Chengdu in Sichuan provincePastor among those arrested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron addresses France; Too late?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e3788b2dc7b14229be0eaadc7cc8b450</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron is preparing to speak to the nation Monday at last, after increasingly violent and radicalized protests against his leadership and a long silence that aggravated the anger. Many protesters only want one thing: for him to declare "I quit." That's an unlikely prospect. Instead Macron is expected to announce a series of measures to reduce taxes and boost purchasing power for the masses who feel his presidency has favored the rich. He's being forced to act after four weeks of "yellow vest" protests that started in struggling provinces and spread to rioting in the capital that has scared tourists and foreign investors and shaken France to the core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU court offers way out...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/may-pushes-brexit-deal-eu-court-offers-way-092920857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May on Monday began a final push to persuade parliament to back her Brexit deal as the European Court of Justice ruled Britain was free to halt withdrawal from the bloc unilaterally. The court ruling will fuel calls for a second referendum to stop Brexit and comes on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58% adults NEVER do muscle-strengthening...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-Big-Number-58-percent-of-U-S-adults-never-13452687.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just getting moving that is important for better health. Health experts say people should have a muscle-strengthening component to their exercise, too. Yet 58 percent of American adults don't do any muscle-strengthening exercise, according to research. Among the activities that qualify are lifting weights and exercising with elastic bands, both of which create resistance that you must work against, as well as push-ups, situps, climbing stairs, cycling, hiking up hills. Still, the researchers - who analyzed data on nearly 400,000 people ages 18 to 80, representing all U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market's severe drop could be ominous sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-stock-market-pullback-20181209-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones industrial average plunged 4.5% for the week, ending with a 559-point rout Friday that left the index in negative territory for the year. So is this the end of the decade-long bull market? Or is it the sort of normal, healthy pullback that often follows lengthy gains?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Status of NYC's most elite buildings sinking...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/08/behind-the-price-drops-at-new-yorks-famed-good-buildings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People talk about whether somebody lives in a good building or not,” says Muffie Potter Aston, a philanthropist and longtime resident of 765 Park Ave. (a classic good building). “It’s sort o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SETS ALL-TIME TOUCHDOWN RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/09/tom-brady-nfl-all-time-touchdown-record-patriots-dolphins-week-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another week, another record for Patriots quarterback Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive War Drill Over Nevada...</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/25380/conga-lines-of-usaf-airlifters-filled-the-night-sky-across-u-s-for-joint-forcible-entry-drill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, those lights in the sky aren't Santa and company on a dry run. They're the U.S. Air Force practicing to make good on its own naughty or nice list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Bezos Earns More In 30 SECONDS Than Average Worker Makes In Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-26/jeff-bezos-earns-more-30-seconds-average-worker-makes-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soy sauce 'colon cleanse' hoax leaves woman brain dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7937420/soy-sauce-colon-cleanse-hoax-wrong-woman-brain-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DOCTOR has outlined a shocking case in which a woman was left brain dead after a case of coeliac disease went horribly wrong. The medical episode, outlined on medical YouTube channel Chubbyemu, i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNSTEIN:  HE IS CORNERED...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watergate-journo-bernstein-for-the-first-time-in-his-life-trump-is-cornered-due-to-mueller-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' Named Best Picture By LA Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/la-film-critics-association-voting-under-way-1167808</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Hawke, Olivia Colman, Steven Yeun and Regina King won the acting prizes in the vote, which took place Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milestone reached in efforts to clear mines from Jesus baptism site...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181209-milestone-reached-efforts-clear-mines-jesus-baptism-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milestone reached in efforts to clear mines from Jesus baptism site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage in Egypt over sex on top of Great Pyramid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6476529/Danish-photographer-posts-picture-having-sex-Great-Pyramid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danish photographer Andreas Hvid posted the explicit snap on his website and it was also featured in a video he posted on YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/media/2018/12/09/bernstein-trump-led-a-criminal-conspiracy-rs.cnn/video/playlists/reliable-sources-highlights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carl Bernstein has described the Nixon years as a "criminal presidency." So Brian Stelter asks him if the same term applies to President Trump. "I don't think we know completely yet," Bernstein says. But "I think it's very obvious that there has been a criminal conspiracy led by the president of the United States to obstruct justice. It's hard to see otherwise in the filings that have been made public thus far."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA PUSH IMPEACHMENT</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-media-demand-trump-impeachment-following-cohen-sentencing-fi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Democracy at stake' if Dems don't pursue impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi sues Mueller, illegal grand jury leaks alleged...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/09/corsi-mueller-lawsuit-klayman-stone-wikileaks-1054204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit also accuses Mueller of trying to badger Jerome Corsi into giving false testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVY SNOW POUNDS SOUTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/live-updates-over-1-000-flights-canceled-hundreds-of-accidents-reported-as-snowstorm-buries-carolinas-southern-virginia/70006840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty Seats Outnumber Fans in NFL Stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2018/12/09/weak-14-empty-seats-outnumber-fans-many-nfl-stadiums/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Buffalo Bills said they had 59,119 spectators at New Era Field on Sunday (capacity 71,870 seat maximum) when the New York Jets came to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation of generic 'cartel' grows to 300 drugs, 16 companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Probe-of-generic-cartel-grows-to-300-drugs-13453234.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executives at more than a dozen generic-drug companies had a form of shorthand to describe how they conducted business, insider lingo worked out over steak dinners, cocktail receptions and rounds of golf. The "sandbox," according to investigators, was the market for generic prescription drugs, where everyone was expected to play nice. "Fair share" described dividing up the sales pie to ensure that each company reaped continued profits. "Trashing the market" was used when a competitor ignored these unwritten rules and sold drugs for less than agreed-upon prices. The terminology reflected more than just the clubbiness of a powerful industry, according to authorities and several lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Shift Focus to Family Business...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/done-with-cohen-federal-prosecutors-shift-focus-to-trump-family-business/18053541/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When federal prosecutors recommended a substantial prison term for President Donald Trump’s former lawyer, Michael Cohen, they linked Trump to the crimes Cohen had committed in connection with the 2016 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA tourism: Travelers flocking to ancestral homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/better/pop-culture/why-dna-travel-may-be-big-travel-trend-2019-ncna942161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A family tree used to take years of painstaking research. But with the advent of DNA testing, more people are discovering their roots and the travel industry is taking notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans load up spending bill before Dems take control...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/9/republicans-load-spending-bill-democrats-take-hous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the clock ticks down in Congress, Republican lawmakers are racing to load up the end-of year spending legislation with their own priorities, figuring this is their last chance to push their agenda while they control both chambers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Transparency? AI expert warns: Lose jobs over THOUGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1056533/ai-warning-brain-transparency-lose-jobs-thoughts-nita-farahany-tedtalks-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LEADING expert on the ethical, legal and social implications of bioscience has revealed her concerns over handing over the control of our minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt probes x-rated video, pics at top of Giza Pyramid...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/egypt-investigates-explicit-video-and-photos-at-top-of-great-pyramid-11574849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors will consider action after footage is widely shared of a Danish photographer appearing to have sex on the monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica resorts covered up, silenced victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2018/11/30/jamaica-resort-sexual-assault-sandals/2048055002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamaican resorts have silenced sexual assault victims for years with agreements, free trips and cash refunds. But many victims are speaking out now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking study...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/groundbreaking-study-examines-effects-of-screen-time-on-kids-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 Minutes goes inside a landmark government study of young minds to see if phones, tablets and other screens are impacting adolescent brain development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screen Time Changes Structure of Kids' Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/screen-time-changes-structure-of-kids-brains-60-minutes-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen Time Changes Structure of Kidsâ€™Â Brains, â€˜60 Minutesâ€™ Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVY SNOW POUNDS SOUTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/live-updates-over-100-000-without-power-as-heavy-snow-ice-pounds-carolinas-and-virginia/70006814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER STORM CANCELS 1,700 FLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2018-12-09-diego-snow-impacts-carolinas-georgia-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's a complete rundown of Winter Storm Diego's preparations and impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who will run West Wing?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pence-chief-of-staff-nick-ayers-wont-be-next-white-house-staff-chief-1544389556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Ayers, a top Trump campaign consultant and administration staffer, won’t be the next White House staff chief, after he and the president failed to agree on a time-frame for the job, White House officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI MIRACLE: Wild final play lifts Dolphins past Pats...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/sports/nfl/miami-dolphins/article222873205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hook and lateral for the win! Dolphins pull of a stunner, beating the Patriots on an insane final play from Tannehill to Kenny Stills to DeVante Parker to Kenyan Drake to keep their playoff hopes alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succession Plan Disrupted...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ayers-won-t-be-trump-s-chief-of-staff-white-house-official-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ayers and Trump werenâ€™t able to agree on a plan for Ayers to stay in the job for two years as the president wanted, said sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Ayers out of running to be White House chief of staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7a5a0eb3f15c4f4a9f7fd34680c1bc68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's top pick to replace chief of staff John Kelly, Nick Ayers, is no longer expected to fill the role. Ayers, who is chief of staff to Vice President Mike Pence, was seen as the favorite for the job when Trump announced Saturday that Kelly would leave around year's end. But a White House official said Sunday that Trump and Ayers could not reach agreement on Ayers' length of service and that he would instead assist the president from outside the administration.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
