<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China building nuke power plant in Argentina as turns to Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3166763/china-building-nuclear-power-plant-argentina-it-looks-latin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New deal is the latest Chinese effort to engage with countries in the region using its cutting-edge clean energy technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic seed vault to receive rare deposits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arctic-seed-vault-receive-rare-101008106.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Svalbard Global Seed Vault, on Spitsbergen island halfway between mainland Norway and the North Pole, is only opened a few times a year to limit its seed banks' exposure to the outside world. On Monday, gene banks from Sudan, Uganda, New Zealand, Germany and Lebanon will deposit seeds, including millet, sorghum and wheat, as back-ups to their own collections. The International Center for Agricultural Research in Dry Areas (ICARDA), which moved its headquarters to Beirut from Aleppo in 2012 because of the war in Syria, will deposit some 8,000 samples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb Security Beef Up; Violent Crime Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/02/13/super-bowl-private-security-help-protection-celebrities-la-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private security companies are seeing an uptick in requests in Los Angeles for Super Bowl weekend, as a result of recent violence in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Case of Evaporating Sub-Neptune World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-mysterious-case-of-the-evaporating-sub-neptune-world/ar-AATMzfR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Seeds of Political Violence Being Sown in Church...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/the-seeds-of-political-violence-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new insurrection is being organized, in a sanctuary near you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Soda Tax -- Great for Beer Sales?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/12/study-seattles-soda-tax-has-been-great-forbeer-sales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is pouring cold beer on Seattle's soda tax. The study, published in the peer-reviewed journal PLoS ONE, reveals...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of pandemic restrictions fast coming to end...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/02/12/world/science-health-world/covid-restriction-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the world has changed since early 2020 and new approaches to restrictions are justified, health officials warn that the coronavirus remains part of our reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding love for $300,000: Behind scenes of luxury matchmaking business...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/finding-love-300-000-behind-130035301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can't put a price on love, but Amber Kelleher-Andrews has put a price on finding it: $30,000 to $300,000 a year for her elite matchmaking services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's most expensive home attracting royal interest and could sell for $500m...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/americas-most-expensive-home-attracting-26210319</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 21 bedrooms and 42 bathrooms, it's being marketed as the 'biggest and most expensive modern home in America'. It includes a nightclub, beauty salon and sweet shop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURROW SEEKS HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.sportingnews.com/us/nfl/news/joe-burrow-super-bowl-heisman-college-championship/pfp6kmfx6equuz9gfgddtleb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportingnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Burrow has achieved tremendous success at the collegiate and NFL levels. He's one step away from achieving an unprecedented achievement among quarterbacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car dealers raising prices due to low supplies. Automakers retaliating. Consumers stuck in between...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/car-dealers-are-raising-prices-due-to-low-supplies-automakers-are-retaliating-consumers-are-stuck-in-between/ar-AATLANL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER-BOWL BLOCKBUSTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-nz/sport/more-sports/rams-bengals-brace-for-super-bowl-blockbuster/ar-AATKIV7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles Rams team bristling with star-power will seek to deny the giant-killing Cincinnati Bengals a Hollywood ending in the Super Bowl on Sunday as an NFL season full of plot twists reaches its climax. The first NFL championship game of the post-Tom Brady era sees the Rams play host at their gleaming $5.5 billion SoFi Stadium against a Bengals side chasing a first Super Bowl crown. Around 100 million Americans are expected to tune in for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul urges truckers to disrupt Super Bowl, come to DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Rand-Paul-urges-truckers-to-disrupt-Super-Bowl-16913168.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As many anti-vaccine and anti-mandate protesters in trucks continue to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA snowboard coach accused of taking pictures of naked athletes, racer investigated for N-word...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/peter-foley-us-snowboard-coach-racer-hagen-kearney-misconduct-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former snowboardcross rider Callan Chythlook-Sifsof, a member of the 2010 Olympic team, made the accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling Trump: Profitable Post-Presidency Like No Other...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/12/selling-trump-a-profitable-post-presidency-like-no-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early December, Donald J. Trump put on a tuxedo and boarded the private jet of a scrap-metal magnate and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory issues for older people could be result of 'clutter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/memory-issues-older-people-result-clutter-rcna15133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you run out of brain space? That’s the wrong way to visualize memory, scientists say. Instead, older people face the challenge of sifting through more information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 33-year-old left USA for Bali and lives 'life of luxury' on $2,233 a month...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/12/this-33-year-old-left-the-us-for-bali-now-he-lives-on-74-a-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olumide Gbenro his remote marketing and public relations business in 2018. Now, he makes about $140,000 a year through his business and investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken producers warn about fast-spreading bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/11/chicken-producers-warn-about-fast-spreading-bird-flu-spreading-across-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US poultry producers are tightening safety measures for their flocks as disease experts warn that wild birds are likely spreading a highly lethal form of avian flu across the country. Indiana on We…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz gets Walk of Fame star as rival says he's too 'Hollywood'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-mehmet-oz-oprah-winfrey-congress-celebrity-3031911c3f7f115607b3817048e01050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — Mehmet Oz, the celebrity heart surgeon who recently ended his daytime TV “Dr. Oz Show” to run for U.S. Senate in Pennsylvania, got a star Friday on the Hollywood Walk of Fame — just as he was being attacked 2,000 miles away in a rival's TV ad saying he's too “Hollywood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk slammed over NEURALINK project that could see brains hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4669936/elon-musk-deadly-neuralink-project-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEURALINK CEO Elon Musk is facing scrutiny for experiments that allegedly left monkeys dead, ahead of human clinical trials. The internet is shunning Elon Musk after the Physicians Committee for Re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Violence Rises in West Bank, Settler Attacks Raise Alarm...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/12/as-violence-rises-in-the-west-bank-settler-attacks-raise-alarm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURIN, West Bank — The Israeli settlers streamed down the hill toward Palestinian farmland, some waving sticks, some throwing stones,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear hunter kills self after accidentally shooting brother...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/man-takes-life-after-accidentally-26198875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police deputies were dispatched to a property in an unincorporated community in Oregon, US, to reports a man had accidentally shot his brother while loading a gun after being startled by a black bear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden weighs appeal of 3 top candidates for high court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/stephen-breyer-joe-biden-us-supreme-court-congress-judiciary-235cba1d2bfb1466e10b17ffd637843f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden had zeroed in on a pair of finalists for his first Supreme Court pick when there were rumors last year that Justice Stephen Breyer would retire. But since the upcoming retirement was announced late last month, it has come with the rise of a third candidate, one with ready-made bipartisan support that has complicated the decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI Program Can Spot Rare Diseases By Analyzing Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ai-facial-analysis-rare-diseases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say a new facial analysis program can actually detect the warning signs of rare diseases by examining the features of a person's face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will record warmth favor RAMS?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/sports/will-record-warmth-favor-the-rams-in-super-bowl-56/1140672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl this year is not just the hottest ticket it town -- in could also feature the hottest game-time temp ever for the big game. What do some fans think about how that will affect the two teams facing off?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burrow crossover appeal inspires Namath comparisons...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/12/nice-fit-joe-burrow-belongs-to-everyone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Burrow strode into Arrowhead Stadium two Sundays ago for the A.F.C. championship game clad in a black turtleneck, rimless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing maximum pressure from Russia, Zelensky refuses to blink...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-maximum-pressure-from-russia-zelensky-refuses-to-blink-at-the-negotiating-table/ar-AATKLBA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear gas fired as convoy enters Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/police-stop-50-vehicles-heading-paris-protest-convoy-2022-02-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police fired tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs Elysees avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a "Freedom Convoy" protesting against COVID-19 restrictions made it into the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Huge, Silent' Earthquake Caused Mysterious Global Tsunami...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/how-huge-silent-earthquake-caused-mysterious-global-tsunami-1678486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "hidden" earthquake caused a tsunami recorded over 6,200 miles from the epicenter, researchers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS backlog hits 24 million returns, further imperiling tax filing season...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/taxes/irs-backlog-hits-nearly-24-million-returns-further-imperiling-the-2022-tax-filing-season/ar-AATKL3A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE INVASION IMMINENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10505243/The-Anglo-Saxons-need-war-Russia-blames-WEST-Putin-decides-invade-Ukraine-WEDNESDAY.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Antony Blinken is on a call to Russian diplomat Sergey Lavrov after 'extremely detailed' invasion plans stoked fears of war in Eastern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CALLS PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-emmanuel-macron-europe-moscow-1f353699f0be1609da5435c98cfc8022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin and U.S. President Joe Biden are to hold a high-stakes telephone call on Saturday as tensions over a possibly imminent invasion of Ukraine escalated sharply and the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Canada police arrive to remove protesters at border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-united-states-justin-trudeau-blockades-f3368c041216343175d255a2ce23eb84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDSOR, Ontario (AP) — Canadian police moved in Saturday to remove protesters who have disrupted Canada-US trade at a major bridge border crossing. Protesters at the busiest crossing between the United States and Canada remained overnight despite new warnings to end the blockade that has disrupted the flow of goods between the two countries and forced the auto industry on both sides to roll back production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR WARNING: RUSSIA INVASION IMMINENT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-news-02-11-22/h_26bf2c7a6ff13875ea1d5bba3b6aa70a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between Moscow and Kyiv are at their highest in years, with a large Russian troop buildup near the shared borders of the two former Soviet republics. Follow for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL SPIKES: $95</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/11/oil-jumps-amid-escalating-tensions-between-russia-and-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices jumped amid escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia, with the U.K. advising British nationals to leave Ukraine immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREIGNERS FLEE UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60355295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden and Vladimir Putin to talk as the US says Russia could invade Ukraine "at any time".</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
