<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Robot Dogs Now Have Rifles Mounted On Backs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42717/robot-dogs-can-now-have-6-5mm-assault-rifles-mounted-on-their-backs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot dogs have been met with equal parts fascination and fear by the public, but their utility for military applications is becoming undeniable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half of Bay Area residents plan to leave permanently...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/576496-more-than-half-of-bay-area-residents-plan-to-leave-permanently-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of the residents living in the San Francisco Bay Area say they are considering moving out of the area permanently, according to a poll from Joint Venture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uEhdlIor-do</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Shepard’s 18th mission, NS-18, will lift off on Wednesday, October 13, carrying four astronauts, Dr. Chris Boshuizen, Glen de Vries, Audrey Powers, and W...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious financial problems afflict 40% households...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/oct/12/us-households-financial-problems-medical-care-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Households struggle to afford medical care and food, with figure rising to 59% for those with income under $50,000 a year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The VR porn revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10084523/Tracey-Cox-says-virtual-reality-porn-norm-2026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most new things with technology, VR seems sci-fi right now, but it will quickly become the norm for many people in the next few years, according to Tracey Cox, who says it's the next big sex trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WV program to pay people $12k to move to coal country gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/courage-strength-optimism/full-steam-ahead-west-virginias-program-to-pay-people-12k-to-move-to-coal-country-gains-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGANTOWN, West Virginia — Quintina Mengyan needed some air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's top 'tech cop' ready to take on Big Tech with America...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/13/global-insider-margrethe-vestager-big-tech-515851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margrethe Vestager says the Biden administration is a “dream come true.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrencies could lead to financial instability, author warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/13/cryptocurrencies-could-lead-to-financial-instability-author-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency enthusiasts say the digital money will democratize finance. One economist has some more unsettling predictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early-season snowstorm snarls travel throughout Rocky Mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/rocky-mountains-october-snowstorm/1032344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorful leaves were still clinging onto trees across the Rockies when the region was buried by an early-season snowstorm — one that required a yardstick to measure snowfall totals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security COLA largest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/social-security-cola-increase-4f2cd7b763371b91923227be883e367e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Millions of retirees on Social Security will get a 5.9% boost in benefits for 2022. The biggest cost-of-living adjustment in 39 years follows a burst in inflation as the economy struggles to shake off the drag of the coronavirus pandemic .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish man sentenced to death by antisemitic judge. Now, he could get second chance...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-Jewish-man-was-sentenced-to-death-by-an-16529258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For much of his life, Randy Halprin struggled with his Jewish identity. Throughout...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 GALLON IN NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-prices-hit-5-in-manhattan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eye-popping gas prices have returned to New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Secret Blacklist of 'Dangerous' Groups, People...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/10/12/facebook-secret-blacklist-dangerous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the public deserves to see the list, a clear embodiment of U.S. foreign policy priorities that could disproportionately censor marginalized groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'chaos' as Italy adopts tough Covid pass regime...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fears-chaos-italy-adopts-tough-112444339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy from Friday will require all workers to show a coronavirus health pass, one of the world's toughest anti-Covid regimes that has already sparked riots and which many fear will cause "chaos".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators seek answers from TESLA over lack of recall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-software-881ef270cbfdc6e4f62b88400588686f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — U.S. safety investigators want to know why Tesla didn't file recall documents when it updated Autopilot software to better identify parked emergency vehicles, escalating a simmering clash between the automaker and regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to reopen land borders in November for fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-covid-19-pandemic-travel-4826edefa498139ebd37684e4f64d553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. will reopen its land borders to nonessential travel next month, ending a 19-month freeze due to the COVID-19 pandemic as the country moves to require all international visitors to be vaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest white rhino dies in Italian zoo aged 54...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211013-world-s-oldest-white-rhino-dies-in-italian-zoo-aged-54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World's oldest white rhino dies in Italian zoo aged 54</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to test thousands of Wuhan blood samples in Covid probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/12/asia/china-wuhan-blood-samples-covid-19-probe-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is preparing to test tens of thousands of blood bank samples from the city of Wuhan as part of a probe into the origins of Covid-19, according to a Chinese official. The move comes amid increasing calls for transparency over the emergence of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS closing more stores in San Fran due to organized theft...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/576482-walgreens-closing-more-stores-in-san-francisco-due-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens is closing more stores in San Francisco due to organized retail theft in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burry Posts TWITTER Rant Over Taxing Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/michael-burry-of-e2-80-98big-short-e2-80-99-fame-posts-twitter-rant-over-taxing-the-rich/ar-AAPsyP6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Burry, whose huge, profitable bets against the housing bubble were made famous in “The Big Short,” denounced what he called U.S. class warfare and challenged the notion that the rich don’t pay enough taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen arrested after refusing to wear mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wyoming-teenager-arrested-after-refusing-to-wear-mask-on-school-grounds-family-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;16-year-old Grace Smith says she was arrested at her Wyoming high school after she refused to wear a mask on school grounds. The teen says she's faced three separate two-day suspensions for not abiding by the school's mask mandate, and received $1,000 in trespassing fines for refusing to leave the campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Sees European Crisis as Russia's Golden Chance...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/putin-sees-european-gas-crisis-as-russia-s-golden-opportunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin Sees European Gas Crisis as Russia’s Golden Opportunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Warns of Tougher Response If Beijing Flights Get Too Close...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/taiwan-warns-of-tougher-response-if-china-flights-get-too-close-kup9kjp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan Warns of Tougher Response If China Flights Get Too Close</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used ASTON MARTIN $114,500 Price Tag Attests to Chip Squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/used-aston-martin-114-500-095901111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Like NowNYC's Waldorf Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's OverreachThey Invented the Must-Have Instrument for the Burning Man Set. Now They Want to Kill It OffWhat Comes After GE’s 129 Years of Greenhouse GasUsed-car sellers are enjoying a boom in demand in the U.K. as the pandemic puts a squeeze on the supply of chips f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Meteor Explode Over New Hampshire?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/did-a-meteor-explode-over-new-hampshire-that-may-explain-the-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists said that a bolide, a type of large meteor explosion in the atmosphere, might have been the source of a disturbance that was widely reported on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell gets wake-up call...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/576461-mcconnell-gets-gop-wake-up-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The backlash Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (Ky.) received from fellow Republican senators last week is a wake-up call to the GOP leader that he doesn’t have any more political capital to spend on helping Democrats raise the debt limit aga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100K threaten strikes as unions flex muscles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/576456-more-than-100k-workers-threaten-strikes-as-unions-flex-muscles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers in various industries nationwide are threatening to go on strike in a sweeping effort to secure higher pay and better working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steaks Could Become Luxury...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steaks-could-soon-become-champagne-150022224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The boss of Europe’s top meat processor said beef will become a luxury like champagne because of the climate impact of producing it. Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Like NowNYC's Waldorf Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's OverreachTycoon Behind a Crisis-Era Property Crash Now Sits on a $9 Billion Debt MountainThey Invented the Must-Have Instrument for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Pristine Beach Is One of Japan's Last. Soon It Will Be Filled With Concrete...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/13/this-pristine-beach-is-one-of-japans-last-soon-it-will-be-filled-with-concrete/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KATOKU, Japan — Standing on its mountain-fringed beach, there is no hint that the Japanese village of Katoku even exists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stock Market Malaise With Shadow of '70s-Style Stagflation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/13/a-stock-market-malaise-with-the-shadow-of-70s-style-stagflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine mandates seem to be working, younger children may be approved for shots by Halloween, and the coronavirus appears to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trans activists, comedians grapple with Chapelle special...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/comedians-defending-dave-chapelle-netflix-special-trans-lgbtq-214359105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian was no holds barred in his latest Netflix special, and some comics say that's a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Burn Infected Couple's Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxewa/vietname-dogs-killing-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What started as a heartwarming story of human kindness has within days evolved into a national reckoning on animal abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With flight, more than 20 civilians will have reached space this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-william-shatner-e2-80-99s-flight-more-than-20-civilian-astronauts-will-have-reached-space-this-year/ar-AAPsESJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor will join a private space movement that has picked up speed and outpaced NASA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area woman charged with hosting teen sex parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/los-gatos-woman-charged-with-hosting-alcohol-sex-parties-for-teens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Bay woman has been charged for hosting secret teen parties with alcohol and sex, according to charges filed by the Santa Clara County District Attorney’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART, FEDEX, UPS move to 24/7 model to address bottlenecks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/576463-white-house-says-walmart-fedex-ups-will-move-to-24-7-model-to-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major goods carriers Walmart, FedEx, and UPS will move to working 24 hours a day, seven days a week in order to address the global supply chain bottlenecks, the White House announced on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SQUID GAME' becomes NETFLIX biggest-ever launch hit...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/squid-game-becomes-netflixs-biggest-235059497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dystopian South Korean drama "Squid Game" has become Netflix's most popular series launch ever, drawing 111 million fans since its debut less than four weeks ago, the streaming service said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatner set for blast off...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-william-shatner-science-business-lifestyle-09705724072c0ecad2674c8511f0fcab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VAN HORN, Texas (AP) — Actor William Shatner counted down Wednesday to his wildest role yet: riding a rocket into space, courtesy of “Star Trek” fan Jeff Bezos. Best known for his role as Captain Kirk, the 90-year-old Shatner joined three other passengers for the planned launch from West Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request for Tucker Carlson's Performance Review Is 'Intrusive,' Judge Says...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/2020-election/judge-steers-away-from-dominions-intrusive-requests-for-fox-news-hosts-performance-reviews-in-1-6b-defamation-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delaware judge overseeing a $1.6 billion lawsuit against Fox News has steered away from an attempt by Dominion Voting Systems, Inc. to obtain the internal personnel records of high-profile hosts Tucker Carlson, Sean Hannity, Maria Bartiromo, Jeanine Pirro, and former host Lou Dobbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's Balancing Act in China Gets Trickier During Xi's Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-balancing-act-china-gets-160000957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In less than a year, China has upended the world’s largest internet sphere, throwing its biggest players from Alibaba to Tencent into a tailspin with a storm of regulatory measures to loosen their stranglehold over data and content. Yet Apple Inc., the largest of them all and an American icon, has sailed through mostly unscathed.Most Read from BloombergHow France Turned the Humble Roundabout Into a Showcase for ArtWhat the Front Line of the U.S. Abortion Fight in Kentucky Looks Li</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second whistleblower reports 'potential criminal violations' to Feds...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/10/11/tech/facebook-whistleblower-sophie-zhang-congress/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sophie Zhang, who said she felt like she had "blood on her hands" after working at Facebook, is willing to testify before Congress about her former employer, she told CNN Sunday. She said she had also passed on documentation about the company to a US law enforcement agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DEADLINE NEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/biden-s-vaccinate-or-test-mandate-approaches-questions-arise-over-n1281130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Occupational Safety and Health Administration was already a strained agency before the president announced the new requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Nations Have Deadlier Covid Outbreaks With Same Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/why-some-nations-have-deadlier-outbreaks-with-the-same-vaccines/ar-AAPr6Ho</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRLINES REBUFF TEX GOV</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012200659-vbp9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AIRLINES-VACCINE (PIX):Rebuffing Texas governor, American Airlines, Southwest stand by vaccine mandate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to test vax nasal spray...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012185352-0bl3g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-VACCINE (PIX):Russia to test COVID-19 vaccine in form of nasal spray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies scraping for staff ahead of holidays...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-christmas-shopping-holidays-e7e45190fdf6c9fb138aee565e4c9b58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — All employers want for Christmas is some holiday help. But they might not get their wish. Companies that typically hire thousands of seasonal workers are heading into the holidays during one of the tightest job markets in decades, making it unlikely they’ll find all the workers they need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL BATTLE OVER VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-nba-sports-business-aa6c30fa6270b735acafc69e2ce26766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — With the governor of Texas leading the charge, conservative Republicans in several states are moving to block or undercut President Joe Biden’s COVID-19 vaccine mandates for private employers before the regulations are even issued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPERMAN' actor slams gay reveal: 'It isn't bold or brave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/dean-cain-superman-bisexual-1235030248/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Superman actor criticized the DC Comics storyline about Clark Kent's son, who is now Superman of Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% want to make career change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/why-50percent-of-workers-want-to-make-a-career-change-new-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whopping 76% of workers say they want their company to make work permanently flexible in terms of schedule and/or location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Ranch threatened by wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/ronald-reagan-ranch-alisal-fire-santa-barbara-county-1234854834/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are working to protect the ranch once owned by Ronald Reagan amid the rapidly moving Alisal Fire in Santa Barbara County. The 688-ranch, Rancho del Cielo, served as the vacation home for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART Cartel Reporter Dies in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2021/10/11/breitbart-cartel-reporter-dies-in-mexico-authorities-believe-he-drowned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breitbart News Cartel Reporter Gerry Aranda's body was discovered in the Pacific Ocean in Chiapas, Mexico, on October 4, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCS Boot from Ring of Honor...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/RapSheet/status/1448043568979927042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwayne Johnson Lets Down His Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/10/dwayne-johnson-speaks-his-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A no-holds-barred talk with the megastar and entrepreneur about his volatile childhood, his heartbreaking relationship with his dad, and Vin Diesel’s “bullshit.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Kristof forms committee for Oregon gov run...</title>
      <link>https://www.opb.org/article/2021/10/12/new-york-times-columnist-nick-kristof-oregon-governor-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday, Kristof officially formed a political action committee, a move that will allow him to raise money and hire staff ahead of a likely official announcement of his candidacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Tyga arrested on domestic violence charge...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/10/12/tyga-arrested-on-felony-domestic-violence-charge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper turned himself in Tuesday after refusing to speak with police Monday at his home following Swanson’s allegations and is being held on $50,000 bail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THINGS PEOPLE CAN'T GET'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/americans-may-not-get-some-christmas-treats-white-house-officials-warn-2021-10-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials, scrambling to relieve global supply bottlenecks choking U.S. ports, highways and railways, warn that Americans may face higher prices and some empty shelves this Christmas season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA authorizes first e-cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/consumer-news/2021/10/fda-authorizes-first-e-cigarettes-cites-benefit-for-smokers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heath officials on Tuesday authorized the first electronic cigarettes in the U.S., saying the R.J. Reynolds vaping products can benefit adult smokers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No college degree? More employers than ever don't care...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/11/success/jobs-apprenticeships-college-degrees-feseries/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star banned from team -- until vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/12/nets-announce-kyrie-irving-is-banned-from-team-until-hes-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly one week before the Nets kick off their regular season against the Bucks, the team announced Kyrie Irving will not practice or play with the team – even during away games, where he is allow…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidney transplant canceled because donor wasn't jabbed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/12/mans-kidney-transplant-canceled-because-donor-wasnt-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Ganin, 52, was five days away from his scheduled surgery when he received the news from the Cleveland Clinic about the new policy that would prevent him from accepting the donor’s kidney…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Funding Arm Gave Encrypted App $1.6 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3dawk/wickr-cia-funding-inqtel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The funding solidifies Wickr's position as an encrypted chat platform for government agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp surge in energy prices threatens economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/sharp-surge-in-energy-prices-threatens-economic-recovery-and-is-already-slowing-growth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Energy prices are surging, and the economy is already feeling the pinch of higher fuel costs though it is far from stalling out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Patient With Pneumonia Forced To Wait 20 Hours For Room...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/denver-hospital-patient-wait-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic wears on, hospitals are filling up fast. A normal visit to an emergency room can mean hours of waiting before being admitted to a hospital room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Kim vows to build 'invincible military'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-58880207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks after a series of missile tests, Kim Jong-un says weapons are needed for defence, but not war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMASH MOUTH singer retires after 'chaotic' onstage rant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/12/smash-mouths-steve-harwell-retires-after-wild-onstage-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harwell announced his retirement after a video of himself giving a very chaotic performance went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next big threat isn't ransomware. It's killware...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-next-big-cyberthreat-isn-t-ransomware-it-s-killware-and-it-s-just-as-bad-as-it-sounds/ar-AAPpD7A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers increasingly target infrastructure – from hospitals and water supplies to banks and transit – in ways that could injure or kill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Media Teaming Up With Lawmakers To Sell Ads...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/growing-advertising-model-puts-reporters-and-lawmakers-at-the-center-of-the-corporate-pitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news site Axios in July hosted an event with Rep. Kurt Schrader (D., Ore.), a member of a House subcommittee on health and the sponsor of legislation that would provide federal funding that allows companies to sell knockoff drugs virtually identical to those that originated with their competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Congressman to Retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/blog/meet-press-blog-latest-news-analysis-data-driving-political-discussion-n988541/ncrd1281320#blogHeader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. John Yarmuth, D-Kentucky, chairman of the powerful House Budget Committee, will announce Tuesday that he won't seek re-election in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters Claims TWITTER Account Hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/rep-maxine-waters-claims-twitter-account-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Maxine Waters claimed Monday that her Twitter account had been hacked, and while she did not provide details, she added that she knew the identity of the perpetrator and would "take care" of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Exec Dodges Gunfire in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/crime/cnn-executive-shares-security-camera-footage-of-him-dodging-gunfire-in-washington-d-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN head of strategic communications Matt Dornic dodged gunfire in Washington, D.C., on Monday night, according to video he posted on Twitter on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozzy Osbourne says worshiping Satan protected him from virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/after-family-members-contracted-covid-19-ozzy-osbourne-says-worshiping-satan-protected-him-from-virus/ar-AAPqBDG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What in God’s good name? Ozzy Osbourne is thanking Lucifer for protecting him from coronavirus. The Grammy Award-winning heavy metal icon credited Satan for covering him during the pandemic, even as close family members contracted COVID-19. “My wife had the virus; my daughter had the virus and I never got it,” he told Metal Hammer. “Being a devil worshiper does have its good points!” In ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT warns it blocked  biggest cyberattack ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3840958/microsoft-cyberattack-china-asia-ddos-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICROSOFT has fought off the biggest “DDoS attack” in recorded history. The huge cyberattack involved tens of thousands of computers – most of which were spread across Asia. Cyberattack…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard activated for testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/10/12/metro/facing-staffing-shortages-baker-activates-massachusetts-national-guard-assist-with-covid-19-testing-public-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In response to staffing shortages that caused COVID-19 testing delays in many Massachusetts school districts, Governor Charlie Baker activated up to 200 members of the National Guard on Tuesday to assist with testing in public K-12 schools, according to an administration spokesperson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number leaving restaurant, hotel jobs doubled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-459c0884721a213985cdf0185a1176f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One reason America's employers are having trouble filling jobs was starkly illustrated in a report Tuesday: Americans are quitting in droves. The Labor Department said that quits jumped to 4.3 million in August, the highest on records dating back to December 2000, and up from 4 million in July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Steers Dems Toward Biden Agenda With 'Fewer Things'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pelosi-steers-democrats-toward-biden-agenda-with-e2-80-98fewer-things-e2-80-99/ar-AAPqozr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fractious Democrats are grappling with how to fit their priorities into a shrunken tax and spending bill and House Speaker Nancy Pelosi has signaled she prefers scaling back President Joe Biden’s multi-trillion dollar economic agenda by focusing on fewer, well-executed programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  SOUTHWEST CEO Denies Vax Mandate Causing Massive Delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/southwest-ceo-says-zero-flights-canceled-due-to-vaccine-protests-blames-biden-for-jab-requirements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest CEO Gary Kelly on Monday denied that protests over a Covid-19 mandate played any role in widespread flight cancellations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue Of Christ Outside Miami Church Beheaded...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/10/09/statues-of-jesus-defaced-at-st-marthas-catholic-church-in-miami-shores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time in about a month, the statue of Jesus has been defaced at St. Martha's Catholic Church in Miami Shores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowered by new leverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/a-record-number-of-workers-are-quitting-their-jobs-empowered-by-new-leverage/ar-AAPqmmR?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers were a reflection of the leverage workers have in the current economic market, with job openings outnumbering unemployed workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95:  Queen Elizabeth II in rare outing with walking stick...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10083701/Queen-95-uses-walking-stick-extra-support-Westminster-Abbey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen used a walking stick today as she arrived with Princess Anne for a service of thanksgiving to mark the centenary of the Royal British Legion at Westminster Abbey in London today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Naked Woman Roams Around Denver Airport...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/naked-female-passenger-denver-international-airport-draw-attention-police-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female passenger parading through a Denver International Airport concourse last month without any clothing drew attention from fellow passengers and airport police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 5 OF TRAVEL HELL</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/southwest-airlines-flights-cancelations-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines canceled 87 flights as of 9 a.m. ET, according to flight tracker FlightAware. Meanwhile, more than 190 flights have already been delayed, according to the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Baby Aspirin Use to Prevent Heart Attack or Stroke Should Be Curtailed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/12/health/daily-aspirin-heart-disease-stroke-draft-recommendation-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Preventive Services Task Force is considering making several changes to its guidance on taking a daily aspirin to prevent heart disease and stroke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 4.3 MILLION WORKERS QUIT JOBS IN MONTH!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/a-record-4point3-million-workers-quit-their-jobs-in-august-led-by-food-and-retail-industries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job openings declined sharply in August while hiring also fell and the level of workers quitting their jobs hit the highest level since at least late-2000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PILOTS BLAME AIRLINE</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/southwest-fllght-cancellations-pilots-association-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Southwest passengers have had to pick between paying for other transportation or staying put for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why only him?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/12/jon-gruden-career-assassinated-raiders-leaked-emails-650000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are serious questions surrounding Jon Gruden&amp;amp;#039;s resignation that need to be answered. Why were only his emails leaked?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does internet keep breaking?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-58873472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outages of Facebook and its family of apps now lead to significant disruption for firms worldwide</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
