<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>150 workers in forced quarantine at L.A. hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/150-cannery-workers-are-in-forced-quarantine-at-l-a-hotel-without-pay-suit-claims/ar-BB15Lahe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA LESS MEGA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/trump-s-tulsa-rally-fizzles-as-seats-go-empty/ar-BB15LsJW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Kung Flu' Remark Stirs Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/donald-trump-tulsa-rally-social-media-stunned-president-coronvirus-kung-flu-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's first rally since the start of the coronavirus pandemic in the U.S. was a rundown [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' solar eclipse thrills skywatchers on longest day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ring-fire-solar-eclipse-thrills-skywatchers-longest-day-104709979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers along a narrow band from west Africa to the Arabian Peninsula, India and the Far East witnessed a dramatic "ring of fire" solar eclipse Sunday. Without the coronavirus pandemic, they would have organised a trip to Lake Magadi in southern Kenya where the skies are generally clearer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros conspiracy theories surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f01f3c405985f4e3477e4e4ac27986e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say he hires protesters and rents buses to transport them. Some say he has people stash piles of bricks to be hurled into glass storefronts or at police.  George Soros, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature hits 100 F degrees in Arctic Russian town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/temperature-hits-100-degrees-arctic-russian-town-71370623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Siberian town with the world’s widest temperature range has recorded a new high amid a heat wave that is contributing to severe forest fires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists unearth Galilee Christian town sacked by Persians in 7th century...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/archaeologists-unearth-galilee-christian-town-sacked-by-persians-in-7th-century/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remains of affluent, rural community discovered at Pi Mazuva in 2007 include crosses, pagan-inspired mosaic; new publication illuminates the Christians who lived there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK teens, K-Pop fans take credit...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/TikTok-Teens-and-K-Pop-Stans-Say-They-Sunk-Trump-15355108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign promised huge crowds at his rally in Tulsa, Oklahoma, on Saturday, but it failed to deliver. Hundreds of teenage TikTok users and K-pop fans say they're at least partially responsible.  Brad Parscale, the chairman of Trump's re-election campaign, posted on Twitter on Monday that the campaign had fielded more than 1 million ticket requests, but reporters at the event noted the attendance was lower than expected. The campaign also canceled planned events outside the rally for an overflow crowd that did not materialize.  Tim Murtaugh, the Trump campaign's spokesman, said protesters stopped supporters from entering the rally, held at the BOK Center, which has a 19,000-seat capacity. Reporters present said there were few protests.  TikTok users and fans of Korean pop music groups claimed to have registered potentially hundreds of thousands of tickets for Trump's rally as a prank. After @TeamTrump tweeted asking supporters to register for free tickets using their phones June 11, K-pop fan accounts began sharing the information with followers, encouraging them to register for the rally - and then not show.  The trend quickly spread on TikTok, where videos with millions of views instructed viewers to do the same, as CNN reported Tuesday. "Oh no. I signed up for a Trump rally, and I can't go," one woman joked, along with a fake cough, in a TikTok posted June 15.  Thousands of other users posted similar tweets and videos to TikTok that racked up millions of views. Representatives for TikTok did not immediately respond to requests for comment.  "It spread mostly through Alt TikTok - we kept it on the quiet side where people do pranks and a lot of activism," said YouTuber Elijah Daniel, 26, who participated in the campaign....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Attacks Rise As Extremists Target Protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/06/21/880963592/vehicle-attacks-rise-as-extremists-target-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty people are facing prosecution amid reports of more than 50 vehicle-ramming incidents at protests since late May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden parents fear losing kids if don't send to school...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/coronavirus-sweden-compels-parents-send-kids-to-school-2020-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents say schools or local government have said they may contact social services if the children continue to stay home from school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany riot: Gangs smash shops, attack police...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53126464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A night of mayhem leaves shops smashed up and looted in the industrial south German city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbing rampage in UK park terror attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11916773/reading-attack-terror-cops-confirm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPS have confirmed the Reading bloodbath which left three men dead and three others injured was a terror attack. The 25-year-old Libyan knifeman suspect is still in custody, as police declared the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Warns of Possible Second Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-warns-of-possible-second-coronavirus-lockdown/ar-BB15My6D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was secretive US 'ninja' missile used again in Syria?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/was-the-us-secretive-ninja-missile-used-again-in-syria-saturday-632232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media posts sought to link the strike to a series of other US attacks on al-Qaeda affiliates in northern Syria in which US drones have used such a weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' solar eclipse thrills skywatchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2020/06/21/world/science-health-world/ring-of-fire-solar-eclipse-africa-asia/#.Xu9FdmhKjb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers along a narrow band from west Africa to the Arabian Peninsula, India and the Far East witnessed Sunday a dramatic "ring of fire" solar eclipse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 dead;  25-year-old Libyan knifeman detained...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/uk-stabbing-attack-that-left-3-dead-being-treated-as-terror-incident-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stabbing rampage in a British park that left three people dead is now being treated as a terrorist attack, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic rebounds 90% as commuters avoid public transit...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/traffic-increased-to-pre-pandemic-levels-inrix-report-2020-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have warned that as cities reopen, traffic and congestion could continue to increase past pre-coronavirus levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Kurt Cobain guitar sells for record $6 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/kurt-cobains-mtv-unplugged-guitar-sells-for-staggering-recordsetting-amount-at-auction-002108604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 1959 Martin D-18E acoustic is now the most expensive guitar ever sold, beating the previous record of $3.975 million for a Black Stratocaster owned by Pink Floyd's David Gilmour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake shakes Oklahoma after rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jun/21/earthquake-shakes-oklahoma-after-donald-trump-rall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.2 earthquake shook northern Oklahoma on Saturday and was felt in parts of Tulsa as protesters filled the city’s downtown streets after President Donald Trump’s campaign rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports 30,000 daily cases, highest number since May 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/20/us-reports-his-number-of-daily-coronavirus-cases-since-may-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S reported more than 30,000 new coronavirus cases on Friday, the highest number of daily infections recorded since May 1, according to data compiled by the Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper films brother beating white MACY'S employee; Says he heard n-word...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/man-who-filmed-macys-beatdown-of-white-man-says-attack-was-instinct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flint police launched an investigation after the video was posted on social media and said they are looking for Quay and his brother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood poised for big-screen gamble as theaters reopen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-poised-big-screen-gamble-theaters-reopen-074415398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than three months of coronavirus-mandated limbo, Hollywood is headed back to the big screen -- and hoping that Russell Crowe's road rage thriller "Unhinged" will jump-start the recovery. Christopher Nolan's much-hyped "Tenet" will follow soon after. While top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 11 wounded in Minneapolis shooting, police say... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/21/us/minneapolis-shooting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man was killed and 11 others were injured in an overnight shooting in Minneapolis, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P!nk Shreds Trump Rally: 'I Sold Out That Same Place In Five Minutes'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/pink-shreds-donald-trump-tulsa-rally-attendance-one-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer Pink, a longtime critic of President Donald Trump, mocked him for the smaller-than-expected [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he ordered slower coronavirus testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/At-rally-Trump-blames-media-and-protesters-for-15354941.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. - President Donald Trump promoted his rally here on Saturday as an opportunity to reignite his reelection campaign and move past the coronavirus pandemic, which has killed more than 120,000 Americans and devastated the economy. He claimed that nearly 1 million people had requested tickets and boasted, "We've never had an empty seat, and we certainly won't in Oklahoma."  Instead, he addressed his supporters, most of them unmasked, in a 19,000-seat arena with many spots unfilled, hours after his campaign had announced that six members of the advance team staffing the event had tested positive for the virus.  He used his platform to belittle testing, which public health experts say is required to contain the outbreak. Because the strategy reveals what the president characterized as trivial cases, his direction was to curtail it. "So I said to my people, 'Slow the testing down,' " he said, as the audience cheered.  There was no massive overflow audience; the area outside the arena had emptied out by early evening, and plans for Trump to address the audience outside were quickly scrapped. The campaign blamed protesters; there were only scattered efforts to block entrances, which were resolved by police.  The campaign said quarantine procedures had gone into effect for the infected staff members and those in "immediate contact" with them. Meanwhile, Tulsa County reported 136 new cases Saturday - marking another high for both single-day and average cases - while the state as a whole reported 331 new infections.  Upon entering the rally grounds, attendees were handed blue face coverings - which many chose not to wear - and directed through a maze of metal fencing, which led to a touchless temperature screening conducted by volunteers in purple smocks. Most police officers and National Guard soldiers on the rally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA LESS MEGA</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-campaign-cancels-plans-to-address-overflow-crowd-because-not-enough-people-showed-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign cancelled a planned outdoor rally to the "overflow crowd" in Tulsa, Oklahoma on Saturday after low turnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He was obviously kidding'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621005728-6euqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TRUMP-TESTING:Trump urges slowdown in COVID-19 testing, calling it a 'double-edge sword'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blames media and protesters for empty seats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a59b4efe97f2249d414ae4f0b3c6495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. (AP) — President Donald Trump launched his comeback rally amid a pandemic on Saturday by declaring that “the silent majority is stronger than ever before," but what was meant to be a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p3jkf0LjPjw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday, June 20, 2020: Join RSBN for LIVE all day coverage of President Donald Trump's MAGA/KAG rally at the BOK Center in Tulsa, OK. Our live coverage wil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Epstein 'madam' Maxwell hiding out in luxury Paris Apt.... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1014441/jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-hiding-paris-flat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUGITIVE socialite Ghislaine Maxwell has been hiding out in a sprawling Paris apartment close to Jeffrey Epstein’s £7million paedo pad, we can reveal. Maxwell, one of the world’s most wanted women,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President will no longer speak outside; Overflow crowd fails to materialze...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-rally-tulsa-oklahoma/h_d50f71b9ed7379fc6ac37e6b4ed6a885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus cases rise in Oklahoma, President Trump is hosting a rally in Tulsa on Saturday that is expected to be attended by thousands. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters gather outside McConnell's home: 'No justice, no sleep'...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/protesters-gather-at-mcconnells-home-no-justice-no-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered outside of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell's Kentucky home early Friday, made loud noises, and held signs reading sayings such as, "No justice, no sleep," "Look us in the eyes," "Wake up, Mitch," and, "Breonna couldn't sleep, neither should Mitch."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign staff test positive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23796a826ba86619527363b92ed49a33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's campaign says six staff members helping set up for his Saturday night rally in Tulsa, Oklahoma, have tested positive for coronavirus.  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERSEES TRUMP PROBES</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Barr-says-at-his-request-Trump-has-removed-15354618.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump on Saturday fired the top federal prosecutor in New York, a day after U.S. Attorney Geoffrey Berman had made clear he would resist an effort by Attorney General William Barr to remove him from office.  Barr informed Berman of the president's move in a sharply worded letter, informing Berman that his deputy, Audrey Strauss, will serve as the acting U.S. Attorney in Manhattan until the Senate can confirm his replacement.  Barr wrote that he had hoped for Berman's "cooperation to facilitate a smooth transition" in the office as Trump nominates the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission, Jay Clayton, to fill the job permanently.  Instead, Barr wrote that Berman had chosen "public spectacle" by resisting the effort to remove him. "Because you have declared you have no intention of resigning, I have asked the President to remove you as of today, and he has done so," Barr wrote.  Berman's office did not immediately comment on the letter.  Offering little explanation, Barr announced late Friday that Berman would be replaced on an acting basis by the U.S. attorney in New Jersey, and that Trump would nominate Clayton for the position. Berman issued a remarkable statement in response, insisting he had not resigned and had no intention of stepping aside until the Senate confirms his replacement.  In an email sent to employees early Saturday morning, a copy of which was read to The Washington Post, Berman wrote that his only concern was "protecting this office and your work." On Saturday, Berman reported to work at his office in Manhattan.  The stalemate has generated significant legal and political questions, over how the dispute will be resolved and what's to become of several sensitive investigations involving people close to President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Bolton suggests possible 'obstruction' by Trump in SDNY Turkey investigation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-suggests-obstruction-trump-sdny-turkey-investigation/story?id=71362785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration's ongoing efforts to oust the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York Geoffrey Berman have set off a firestorm in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO suspends show of comedian embroiled in racism row with Mexican president...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-racism-hbo/hbo-suspends-show-of-comedian-embroiled-in-racism-row-with-mexican-president-idUSKBN23R0QO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television network HBO Latin America has suspended the TV show of a Mexican comedian who angered President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and his wife with a remark about their child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to have sweeping powers over Hong Kong security law, stoking concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests-security/beijing-to-have-sweeping-powers-over-hong-kong-security-law-stoking-concerns-idUSKBN23R0FC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will have overarching powers over the enforcement of a new national security law in Hong Kong, according to details released on Saturday that signalled the deepest change to the city's way of life since it returned to Chinese rule in 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime NY congressman tries to fend off challenger from left...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Longtime-N-Y-congressman-tries-to-fend-off-15354455.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAMORONECK, N.Y. - Standing outside a firehouse here, as 10,000 donated face masks were delivered, Rep. Eliot Engel confronted the questions that had put his 31-year congressional career in jeopardy.  How did the longest serving New York congressman suddenly face complaints of ignoring his district? How did Jamaal Bowman, a former middle school principal who has never run for office, turn Tuesday's Democratic primary into a pitched battle over who cared more about the north Bronx and southern swath of Westchester County?  "It's a farce," Engel said. "People know I bring millions of dollars home from Washington. I know virtually everybody in the district. If there are three people in a room and I'm invited, I'm there."  Two years after Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., stunned the political establishment and unseated Joseph Crowley, then the fourth-ranked House Democrat, Engel is trying to fend off the same insurgency from the left. The House Foreign Affairs Committee chairman knew it was coming and has welcomed the help, from the endorsements of Hillary Clinton, Gov. Andrew Cuomo and top congressional Democrats to Republican donors funding a super PAC that backs him.  "I'm grateful to anyone who supports me," said the 73-year-old Engel.  A victory for Engel would humble his party's growing left wing after its favored candidates came up short in the race for the Democratic presidential nomination. A defeat would reveal the limits of a party establishment that, just a few years ago, could keep its incumbents safe with a simple premise: You know them, so why not keep them?  "It's like B.C. and A.D. - before AOC and after AOC," said Ritchie Torres, a liberal state legislator running in the 15th District, which neighbors Engel's. "In the post-AOC world, incumbency is no longer an entitlement, no longer a guarantee of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest woman wearing 'I Can't Breathe' shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-news-live-tulsa-rally-news-speech-coronavirus-protest-update-twitter-a9576876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: HE'LL PAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8442775/Justice-Departments-attempt-block-John-Boltons-tell-book-DENIED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Royce Lamberth denied the request for the former security adviser's book to be canned in a ruling Saturday, saying 'the damage is done' after 200,000 copies have already been released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh crisis for DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/503706-push-to-oust-manhattan-attorney-sparks-fresh-crisis-for-doj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department's push to oust a key U.S. attorney who spearheaded multiple probes involving associates of President Trump has spurred a new crisis for the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump coronavirus 'death clock' truck enters Tulsa ahead of rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/503715-trump-coronavirus-death-clock-truck-enters-tulsa-ahead-of-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Death Clock truck moved in to join the camaraderie in Tulsa, Okla., ahead of President Trump's rally there Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My terrifying five-day stay inside Seattle's cop-free CHAZ'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/my-terrifying-5-day-stay-inside-seattles-autonomous-zone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — On June 8, Seattle police frantically loaded what they could from the east precinct onto trucks and cars. Within hours, they boarded up and abandoned the station. That night, left-wing pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm just here to do my job,' imperiled prosecutor says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9ecba75a9d528ad1de7af33f978f007</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The powerful U.S. attorney in Manhattan who has been overseeing investigations of President Donald Trump's allies showed up at his office to work Saturday, defying the attorney...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As athletes return to campus, what are they signing up for?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9becba20565e275d1d9bd55a62cb4a74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio State calls it the Buckeye Acknowledgment and Pledge, a two-page document the school asked its athletes to sign before they could begin using team facilities during the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Industry Having Major Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-porn-industry-is-having-a-major-meltdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As adult performers realize they can create their own content and make money sans studios or dangerous agents, directors and performers, the future of porn may be worker-driven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSA: Protesters clash with Trump supporters ahead of rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/1012630/tulsa-rally-trump-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUPPORTERS have gathered in their thousands for a Donald Trump rally where the President is set to take the stage for the first time since the coronavirus outbreak. Huge lines of keen Trump support…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump third defeat in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/06/20/trumps-third-and-ultimate-defeat-this-week-judge-rules-john-boltons-book-about-presidents-incompetence-can-be-published-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has ruled that John Bolton’s book about Donald Trump’s incompetent and criminal presidency, “The Room Where It Happened,” can be published by Simon &amp; Schuster. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenin statue unveiled in western Germany after legal battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lenin-statue-unveiled-west-germany-legal-battle-034816604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A divisive new monument to Soviet leader Lenin was unveiled in Germany on Saturday, in the middle of a global row over the controversial background of historical figures immortalised as statues. More than 30 years after the post-World War II communist experiment on German soil ended, the tiny Marxist-Leninist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India, China accuse each other of violating de facto border...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200620095151-h8179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-CHINA/ (PIX):India, China accuse each other of violating de facto border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal barriers, MAGA gear...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e7311038d1c2f32bf9fdd7c727a9cc53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. (AP) — Supporters of President Donald Trump were lining up Saturday outside metal barriers surrounding the Tulsa stadium where the president will hold his first rally in months, ready...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But blasts conduct...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd4d178b8050739c915e455e022347ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge ruled Saturday that former national security adviser John Bolton can move forward in publishing his tell-all book despite efforts by the Trump administration to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Headed to Indoor Trump Rally, Raising Virus Fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07b7fc437494f98596f428dc90140140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of people from many states are converging on Tulsa for an indoor rally and other campaign events Saturday for President Donald Trump, raising concerns that the gatherings could...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
