<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GM strikers worried but determined: 'This is America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/09/21/gm-uaw-strike-one-week-in-strikers-worried-determined/2402195001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While loyalty to GM runs deep, loyalty to one of the most powerful labor unions in America runs deeper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Antonio Brown's deal with PATRIOTS dissolved in days... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/How-Antonio-Brown-s-deal-with-the-Patriots-14458241.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oakland Raiders' Antonio Brown-related pain would become the New England Patriots' gain, it seemed at first.  It took the Patriots, six-time Super Bowl champions, only hours to agree to a contract with Brown after he was released by the Raiders following the craziness over his frostbitten feet, helmet grievances against the NFL, practice-field clash with General Manager Mike Mayock and social-media antics. Surely Brown would become a solid locker-room citizen in Coach Bill Belichick's no-nonsense environment, restore his football reputation and assist quarterback Tom Brady to make the Patriots next to unbeatable, right?  But the relationship between Brown and the Patriots unraveled quickly when Brown's off-field behavior took a more disturbing turn with allegations by two women of rape, sexual assault and intimidation. With the NFL investigating and considering whether to place Brown on paid administrative leave, the Patriots decided Friday to release the seven-time Pro Bowl wide receiver, 11 days and one game after announcing his signing Sept. 9.  That decision came amid two sets of deliberations, one by the team and one by the league, that made it appear inevitable that Brown would be taken off the field soon either by the NFL or the Patriots, in the view of some of those close to the case.  Those people described a league investigation that was progressing, with consideration of the allegations by both women, toward the potential placement of Brown on the commissioner's exempt list. The Patriots, meanwhile, dealt with the controversy and media questioning about the accusations and tried to figure out what was the right thing to do, in general terms, and best for their team.  The outcome is that the Patriots move on without Brown while he faces an uncertain NFL future, with the league signaling to any interested...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. trade regulators approve APPLE tariff exemptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-apple/u-s-trade-regulators-approve-some-apple-tariff-exemptions-amid-broader-reprieve-idUSKBN1W52J2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. trade regulators on Friday approved 10 out of 15 requests for tariff exempt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'When you are in, you can't get out': Women describe how Jeffrey Epstein controlled them...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article235247637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TAUNTS TRUMP: I'LL BEAT HIM LIKE A DRUM</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-accuses-Trump-of-abusing-power-to-smear-him-14458075.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden hit back Saturday after being swept up in President Donald Trump's latest national controversy, providing an early look at how he'll respond to Trump's attacks.  Last week, The Washington Post reported that Trump pressured Ukraine's president to investigate a company with ties to Biden's son Hunter. Trump's request seemed designed to elicit damaging information about a political rival ahead of the 2020 election.  Biden, the top-polling 2020 Democratic presidential candidate who beats Trump in head-to-head matchups in battleground states and nationwide, said Saturday that if the president did that, it's only because "he knows I'll beat him like a drum."  Biden also challenged Trump to release a transcript of his phone call with the Ukrainian leader.  Biden found himself at the center of a massive political scandal that includes unfounded accusations spread by Trump and his allies that Biden used his influence as vice president to help his son with a business deal.  Trump and his allies reportedly asked Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to look into Biden's efforts in 2016 to convince Ukraine to fire its top prosecutor, who at the time was also investigating a natural gas company that employed Hunter.  Biden said he knew nothing of his son's business deal and was acting on behalf of the United States, which saw the prosecutor as ineffective at stamping out corruption.  The Biden campaign sent a lengthy memo to reporters Saturday listing quotes from various news outlets, including the Kyiv Post in Ukraine, discrediting Trump's attack.  The memo seems part of a larger Biden campaign effort to get ahead of the story and keep history from repeating itself - if Trump keeps peddling the story, it could dog his campaign just as Hillary Clinton's emails dogged hers. . ..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong a 'police state'... </title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/hong-kong-a--police-state---prominent-protesters-tell-afp-11931406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Swiss protest 5G wireless over health fears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thousands-swiss-protest-5g-wireless-over-health-fears-201051081.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people protested in the Swiss capital Bern Saturday over the roll-out of a 5G wireless technology across the country, which they fear could damage people's health. The protesters, many carrying placards, gathered in front of the Swiss parliament building, in a bid to stop the construction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politics turn nasty in Canada as Trudeau and rivals get personal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/politics-turn-nasty-canada-trudeau-061201888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For polite Canada, the latest federal election campaign is turning out to be pretty nasty.Even before bombshell pictures of Prime Minister Justin Trudeau in blackface makeup surfaced on Wednesday, his Liberals and their main opposition Conservatives had foregone the usual niceties in favor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's Record-Setting Homicides, Slugglish Economy Test AMLO...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mexico-record-setting-homicides-slugglish-192331196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mexico’s homicides in August show the nation remains on pace to break last year’s record, while a national poll showed President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador’s approval falling as the economy teeters on the brink of a technical recession.Murders rose 3.3% in the first eight months of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RASMUSSEN:  PRESIDENT HITS 52% APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_sep20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  HAS TRUMP FINALLY GONE TOO FAR?</title>
      <link>http://theoneworldnews.com/analysis-comment/opinion-trump-walks-a-crooked-mile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theoneworldnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Everyone here is keyed up for the Big One. The One that’s going to finally bring Donald Trump down. As soon as the news broke Wednesday night in The Washington Post that a whistle-blower had accused the president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon deploys troops to Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/u-s-deploy-military-forces-saudi-arabia-after-drone-attacks-n1057216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The president has approved the deployment of U.S. forces which will be defensive in nature," Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER:  WE'RE DOOMED!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/21/why-ann-coulter-loves-to-hang-out-on-the-upper-east-side/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ann Coulter was leaving the Comedy Cellar in Greenwich Village at 3 a.m. when she was set upon by mob. “They were animals, they were physical,” she said, recalling the group of nearly a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Fed to pump $75 BILLION into markets daily through Oct 10...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-fed-pump-75-bn-money-markets-daily-154943871.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Federal Reserve Bank said Friday it will inject billions into the US financial plumbing on a daily basis for the next three weeks in an effort to prevent a spike in short-term interest rates. The Fed will offer up to $75 billion a day in repurchase agreements -- exchanging secure assets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TAUNTS TRUMP: I'LL BEAT HIM LIKE A DRUM</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/video/5934168/trump-knows-ill-beat-him-like-a-drum-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch Trump knows ‘I’ll beat him like a drum’: Biden Video Online, on GlobalNews.ca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump heads to UN with long list of deals he's yet to close...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/786ad62e3220495089537ae95c699055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump, a self-described deal-maker, is saddled with a long list of unresolved foreign policy deals he has yet to close heading into his U.N. visit this coming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems blast latest Trump crisis. But what will they do?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4418b7894e37420aa537cdf167d77a76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars crushed by falling bricks in Albania after 5.6-mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/cars-crushed-in-albania-following-powerful-5-6-magnitude-earthquake/538522 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ABUSE OF POWER'</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/21/biden-trump-ukraine-whistleblower-scandal-1507053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An angered Joe Biden accused President Donald Trump of “using every element of his presidency to try and smear me,” and called for an investigation into Trump’s phone call with the Ukrainian president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker's last days?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/cory-booker-memo-may-not-be-race-much-longer-if-n1057196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential candidate's campaign manager warned the NJ senator might not stick around if he can't raise nearly $2M in days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo 'being tortured in hellhole prison'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/el-chapo-being-tortured-just-20091114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin Guzman, 62, was jailed for life last month and placed in the Colorado Super Max</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PLAYS NICE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/462406-warren-avoids-attacks-while-building-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren is employing a strategy in the Democratic primary her rivals aren’t: She's not taking swipes at them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery towers going up all over Cincinnati area...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcpo.com/money/consumer/dont-waste-your-money/mystery-towers-going-up-all-over-cincinnati-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcpo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strange cylinder-like towers are popping up around the region, and homeowners have a lot of questions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Picasso painting had never been seen before. Until neural network painted it...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/614333/this-picasso-painting-had-never-been-seen-before-until-a-neural-network-painted-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With help from a neural network, researchers reconstructed an image the artist created and painted over during his Blue Period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Biden, Whistle-Blower Complaint Could Cut 2 Ways...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/21/for-biden-whistle-blower-complaint-could-cut-2-ways/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - CEDAR RAPIDS, Iowa — Since President Trump defeated them nearly three years ago, Democrats have warned, in increasingly alarmed terms, that Mr. Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-generated faces look like real life humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/ai-generated-faces-eerily-look-20137964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new artificially-intelligent headshots have left the internet freaked out over how realistic they are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: Genteel 'DOWNTON ABBEY' Takes Out Brad Pitt, Stallone...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/09/21/box-office-genteel-downton-abbey-takes-brad-pitts-ad-astra-and-stallones-rambo-gives-studio-highest-debut-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gentility and peak TV won the day at the box office Friday, and should command the weekend as well. Julian Fellowes’ delightful “Downton Abbey” transfer to the big screen knocked …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of dead cats found in home...</title>
      <link>https://www.recordonline.com/news/20190920/dozens-of-dead-cats-found-at-montgomery-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recordonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY - Montgomery and county officials are investigating the deaths of dozens of cats found at a Town of Montgomery home following the former</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald eagles have found themselves new home: Suburbia...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-18/bald-eagles-have-found-themselves-a-new-home-suburbia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bald eagles are choosing to nest close to human activity, but no one knows why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAFT WAS ENRAGED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7488575/Patriots-owner-Robert-Kraft-fired-Antonio-Brown-threatening-texts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kraft became enraged on Friday afternoon when he learned of 'intimidating and threatening' text messages that Brown sent to one of the women accusing him of sexual misconduct, sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charge against airline mechanic highlights 'insider threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ce13931c2dae4bd482d9ace2ce28db92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steak, beer and politics: 2020 Dems descend on Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1898c4fbb23f4625921e116f90417eda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Video shows hundreds of shackled, blindfolded prisoners in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/chinas-detention-of-uighurs-video-of-blindfolded-and-shackled-prisoners-authentic-11815401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights groups say China is holding one million people, mostly ethnic Uighurs, at detention camps - a charge Beijing denies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young conflicted about internet and well-being...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/internet-use-mental-health-youth-survey/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We surveyed Mashable readers. You might be surprised by how they responded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String of shootings at high school football games continues...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/string-shootings-high-school-football-games-continues-teens/story?id=65764590 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For at least the fifth week in a row, a shooting has taken place during a high school football game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Bankrupt Illinois Cities Cut Services To Fund Pensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/bankrupt-illinois-cities-forced-cut-services-fund-pensions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors build new tongue out of woman's arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/doctors-build-new-tongue-out-20135144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Patterson, from Rushcliffe, had just gotten engaged when she was diagnosed with tongue cancer in April 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER OVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27662788/brown-pats-cut-wr-amid-field-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown's brief stint with the Patriots is over, as the team released him Friday. "We feel that it is best to move in a different direction at this time," the Patriots said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Perfectly real' deepfakes in 6 months?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/hao-li-perfectly-real-deepfakes-will-arrive-in-6-months-to-a-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Soon, it's going to get to the point where there is no way that we can actually detect [deepfakes] anymore, so we have to look at other types of solutions," says Hao Li.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAFT WAS ENRAGED...</title>
      <link>https://theathletic.com/1228966/2019/09/20/how-robert-kraft-and-bill-belichick-arrived-at-decision-to-cut-antonio-brown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theathletic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kraft, who was on a business trip, and Belichick spoke and decided Friday to officially release Brown just 11 days after the Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranoia Written All Over Stocks in Struggle Back to Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/paranoia-written-over-p-500-110001512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The relentless drive into defensive stocks is a logical way to cope for investors beset all year by signs a recession is at hand. It’s also a tough way to set a fresh stock record.Buoyed by a supportive Federal Reserve and strong economic data, the S&amp;P 500 climbed within points of an all-time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland Best Place To Settle?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iceland-yes-iceland-best-place-153104626.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello, northern lights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS CUT BROWN...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/20/patriots-release-antonio-brown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown's Patriots career is over after one game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT: Killer robots 'unstoppable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/09/21/microsoft-chief-brad-smith-says-rise-killer-robots-unstoppable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of killer robots is now unstoppable and a new digital Geneva Convention is essential to protect the world from the growing threat they pose, according to the President of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest technology company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing States Lose Most Factory Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-u-swing-states-lost-161444923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the U.S. presidential campaign heats up, Democratic candidates may want to look at two Rust Belt states that narrowly helped deliver Donald Trump’s victory in 2016: Pennsylvania and Wisconsin.The two swing states lost the most manufacturing jobs in the past 12 months, bucking the national</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran issues 'battlefield' warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-issues-battlefield-warning-us-deploys-troops-110024302.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any country that attacks Iran will become the "main battlefield", the Revolutionary Guards warned Saturday after Washington ordered reinforcements to the Gulf following attacks on Saudi oil installations it blames on Tehran. Tensions escalated between arch-foes Iran and the United States after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freeze on Ukraine aid draws new scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-freeze-on-ukraine-aid-draws-new-scrutiny-amid-push-for-biden-investigation/ar-AAHBu9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFI:  KELLYANNE GOES WITHOUT GEORGE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/462427-clarence-thomas-joe-manchin-rudy-giuliani-among-guests-at</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various political and government figures turned out at the White House on Friday as President Trump hosted Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison for an elaborate state dinner, only the second formal state visit so far during Tr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian ravioli served with lemon-cheese emlusion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fox-marvel-executives-among-guests-232207438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Fox Corp. Chief Executive Officer Lachlan Murdoch and Marvel Entertainment Chairman Isaac Perlmutter were among those attending President Donald Trump’s second State Dinner on Friday, in honor of Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison.The guest list included a number of conservatives</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
