<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RTpWYWIfP7Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us July 11th for our first fully crewed rocket powered test flight, and the beginning of a new space age. Aboard #Unity22 will be our team of two pilots...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troop Request Presents Hard Choice for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/haiti-s-troop-request-presents-hard-choice-for-biden/ar-AAM0eis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti’s request for U.S. troops to help stabilize the country following the assassination of its president presents a difficult choice for President Biden: send forces to aid a neighbor even as he is trying to pare down America’s military footprint overseas, or refrain and risk allowing the chaos unfolding there to escalate into a refugee crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Staggering Depth Of 196 Feet, World's Deepest Pool Opening...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/10/1014801508/with-a-staggering-depth-of-196-feet-the-worlds-deepest-pool-is-opening-in-dubai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 196 feet deep, Deep Dive Dubai has set the record for the deepest diving pool. Visitors can explore, play pool and chess, and visit an underwater library.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New polling shows Democrats alarmed about crime, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/714321/new-polling-shows-democrats-alarmed-about-crime-too/?unlock=URUO654OJ2WRART4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By listening to activists more than their own party’s voters, Democrats have been complacent in dealing with rising violence in American cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenner Jeered at CPAC: 'Sick freak'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/transphobic-abuse-hurled-caitlyn-jenner-095436808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A heckler filmed himself shouting 'sick freak' at Caitlyn Jenner as she attends the Conservative Political Action Conference in Dallas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High potency weed linked to psychotic episodes, mysterious vomiting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/high-potency-weed-linked-psychotic-episodes-mysterious-vomiting-illness-young-n1273463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It felt like Edwards Scissorhands was trying to grab my intestines and pull them out,” a Colorado man told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Woman duct-taped to seat after trying to open airplane door...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/11/video-shows-woman-duct-taped-to-seat-after-trying-to-open-airplane-door-on-american-airlines-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a TikTok video captured by a fellow passenger, an American Airlines passenger was duct-taped to her seat after the woman allegedly bit a flight attendant and attempted to unlock the aircraft&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White spite: NYC principal 'conspired to oust Caucasian teachers'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/10/washington-heights-school-staffers-have-no-confidence-in-principal-paula-lev-after-race-flap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The faculty of High School for Law and Public Service is rebelling against their principal, charging that she has “flagrantly but unsuccessfully attempted to divide our school by race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority of Brazilians support impeaching Bolsonaro...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/majority-brazilians-support-impeaching-bolsonaro-poll-shows-2021-07-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, a majority of Brazilians support impeaching President Jair Bolsonaro, according to a poll released on Saturday, as serious graft allegations related to vaccine procurement hit the right-wing leader's already battered image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Afghan pullout, USA ditches 'forever wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210711-with-afghan-pullout-us-ditches-forever-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Afghan pullout, US ditches 'forever wars'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida men say plan was to arrest, not kill, Haiti's president...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida/2021/07/10/florida-men-say-plan-was-to-arrest-not-kill-haitis-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief of Haiti’s national police force doubts their story: “They wanted to kill him. They knew what they were doing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA alarmed as Saudi lawsuits threaten to expose secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210711-us-alarmed-as-saudi-lawsuits-threaten-to-expose-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US alarmed as Saudi lawsuits threaten to expose secrets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old infected with 'two variants at once'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210710-90-year-old-infected-with-two-virus-variants-at-once</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;90-year-old infected with 'two virus variants at once'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel maid prevents 'Vegas style' massacre at All-Star Game...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/11/hotel-maid-prevents-potential-shooting-at-mlb-all-star-game-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hotel maid is being hailed for her role in preventing what police fear could have been a “Las Vegas style shooting” at the upcoming MLB All-Star Game in Denver, a report said Saturday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record temperatures strain power supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/heat-wave-set-new-high-temperature-records-strains-power-supply/ar-AALZLvn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California authorities urge people to conserve electricity as the heat wave taxes the power grid. Heat warnings are in place through 8 p.m. Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA records 20,000 new cases 3 days in row for first time since May...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9776815/US-records-20-000-new-COVID-cases-day-row-time-May.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials say that the fast-spreading Delta variant first identified in India is racing through areas with low vaccination rates, eroding gains made in beating back the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocker: Team USA falls to Nigeria in pre-Olympic basketball loss...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-nba-olympic-games-nigeria-olympic-team-7afdd39c0551bccd2f5cd35a41349978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — This is not how USA Basketball expected to open its Olympic summer. Nigeria probably didn’t expect it, either. If there was any expectation of invincibility for the Americans heading into the Tokyo Olympics, it’s already gone — after Nigeria beat the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star Mingo arrested for indecency with child...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3257726/falcons-barkevious-mingo-arrested-indecency-child-sexual/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA Falcons linebacker Barkevious Mingo was arrested earlier this week for “indecency with a child, sexual contact.” Mingo, 30, was arrested on July 8 by the Arlington Police Depart…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vow to tackle industry giants confronts consolidation wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/biden-vow-to-tackle-industry-giants-confronts-consolidation-wave/article_e6450522-b9ef-5d3c-8c63-290807dd8531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Joe Biden’s vow to take on the U.S. economy’s most dominant companies faces a monumental task: combating years of consolidation that have left industry after industry controlled by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. has more than 1,000 new virus cases in day, highest in months...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/la-county-has-more-than-1000-new-coronavirus-cases-in-a-day-highest-in-months/ar-AAM0aaP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time L.A. County reported more than 1,000 new cases in a single day was due to a backlog of cases in late May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As people flock to theme parks, series of accidents plagues popular rides...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/as-people-flock-to-theme-parks-this-summer-series-of-accidents-plagues-popular-rides/article_f6c0c83d-f600-51b3-9ab2-d36e9143c2cb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. — Headlines across the country have been abundant with news of shocking theme park accidents in the last several weeks, some of them fatal. Last month, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wounded wife speaks out...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210710-wounded-wife-of-assassinated-haitian-leader-speaks-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wounded wife of assassinated Haitian leader speaks out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI, DHS sent in...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210709162804-ybnch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-PRESIDENT/USA-WHITEHOUSE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. sending FBI, DHS law enforcement to Haiti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti asks US for troops after assassination...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-caribbean-haiti-election-2020-011ce271fe57211c29ffb0e5eef9c506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — Haiti’s interim government has asked the U.S. and U.N. to deploy troops to protect key infrastructure as it tries to stabilize the country and prepare for elections in the aftermath of President Jovenel Moïse’s assassination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England aim to be Euro 'Top Guns' after call from Tom Cruise...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210710-england-aim-to-be-euro-top-guns-after-call-from-tom-cruise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;England aim to be Euro 'Top Guns' after call from Tom Cruise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaxxed 'BOND' Actress May Miss Fest After Catching Covid...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/french-actor-lea-seydoux-may-cancel-trip-to-cannes-after-testing-positive-for-covid-exclusive-1235016470/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French actor Lea Seydoux is supposed to be the toast of this year’s Cannes Film Festival with four films, including three in competition. But sources say that the French star may cancel her t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought-hit New Mexico town eyes economic liftoff from GALACTIC launch...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210710153355-eaxv6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-EXPLORATION/VIRGINGALACTIC-TOWN (TV, PIX):Drought-hit New Mexico town eyes economic liftoff from Virgin Galactic space launch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Tax Overhaul Gains Steam as G20 Backs New Levies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/562309-g-20-finance-heads-endorse-global-tax-overhaul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finance officials in the Group of 20 (G-20) on Saturday endorsed “key components” of a framework for an international tax overhaul that is a top priority of the Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel preparing for civil war in West Bank?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/561845-is-israel-preparing-for-the-inevitable-civil-war-in-the-west-bank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International attention is focused on fighting in Gaza, but Hamas is looking ahead to opportunities to take over the West Bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On This Farm, Cows Are Coequals...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/10/on-this-german-farm-cows-are-in-charge-or-at-least-coequals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUTJADINGEN, Germany — Tom will lay his head in the lap of anyone who sits down to rub his neck,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers deplaned...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3256589/fort-lauderdale-airport-evacuated-passengers-deplaned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT Lauderdale Airport is being evacuated and passengers told to deplane over a “security investigation” amid “bomb threat” fears. Areas of Terminals 2 and 3 at Fort Lauder…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/fl-ne-ftl-airport-terminal-evacuated-20210710-covfs3n7pjavvaqrqi24hinhh4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A security investigation has caused the evacuation of Terminals 2 and 3 at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport, officials said Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Terminals at Fort-Lauderdale-Hollywood Airport evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/officials-evacuate-terminals-at-fort-lauderdale-hollywood-intl-airport-as-they-investigate-security-related-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE-HOLLYWOOD INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT, FLA. (WSVN) - Officials have evacuated terminals at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport as they investigate a security-related incident.Portions of Terminals 2...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
