<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Toxic 'forever chemicals' found in drinking water throughout US...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/01/23/pfas-toxic-forever-chemicals-found-drinking-water-throughout-us/4540909002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report found that 20 cities and regions nationwide — including Washington, D.C., Philadelphia, Miami and Louisville — contained high PFAS levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney becomes top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/23/mick-mulvaney-trump-impeachment-102758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats say the acting White House chief of staff is the most important potential witness in Trump's trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Connection: Inside 9/11 Case That Divided the FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-saudi-connection-inside-the-9-11-case-that-divided-the-fbi/ar-BBZfp1C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN cancels Dem presidential town halls because of impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/23/politics/cnn-cancels-iowa-2020-town-halls/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has canceled the Democratic presidential town halls scheduled to take place next week ahead of the Iowa caucuses because of the ongoing impeachment trial, a CNN spokesperson said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators Play With Toys, Read Books...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/23/gop-senators-kids-toys-fidget-spinners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, Republican senators are passing the time during the impeachment trial with fidget spinners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Biden's rivals can't break his lock on black voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/23/joe-biden-black-voters-support-south-carolina-102365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His opponents have tried for a year to chip away at his African American support in South Carolina. But nothing's working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state medics monitor 16 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7919851/Washington-coronavirus-patient-contact-16-people-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington state heath officials have predicted that the number of Americans infected would likely grow as the coronavirus continues its spread at a faster rate than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue NYPD cops using sketchy facial-recognition app...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/rogue-nypd-cops-are-using-sketchy-facial-recognition-app-clearview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rogue NYPD officers are using a sketchy facial-recognition software that it’s own facial recognition unit doesn’t want to touch because of concerns about security and potential for abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'war zone' city...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/inside-wuhans-quarantine-zone-amid-viral-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soldiers wearing face masks screened people Thursday for the coronavirus in Wuhan, China — where doctors wore hazmat suits to treat patients sickened by the mystery illness, photos from insid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamic leaders make 'groundbreaking' visit to Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2aee1fb2ac13e4ed26a41e0096bac46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Muslim religious leaders joined members of a U.S. Jewish group at Auschwitz on Thursday for what organizers described as “the most senior Islamic leadership delegation" to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bernie 12-point lead in NH...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbur.org/news/2020/01/23/new-hampshire-bernie-sanders-lead-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbur.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden, Buttigieg and Warren are clumped in a close battle behind the Vermont senator, with less than three weeks until the New Hampshire primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM LEHRER DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/press-releases/from-judy-woodruff-longtime-pbs-newshour-anchor-and-co-founder-jim-lehrer-has-passed-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, DC (January 23, 2020) -- It is with great sadness that I share the news that co-founder and longtime anchor of the PBS NewsHour Jim Lehrer died today, Thursday, January 23, 2020, peacefully in his sleep at home. Lehrer, born May 19, 1934, served as anchor of the NewsHour for 36 years before retiring in 2011. Lehrer and Robert MacNeil founded the program in 1975, out of their 1973 coverage of the Senate Watergate Hearings on PBS. "I'm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING CANCELS NEW YEAR EVENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hongkongfp.com/2020/01/23/wuhan-virus-hong-kong-holiday-camps-become-quarantine-zones-lunar-new-year-festival-cancelled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hongkongfp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;by Jerome Taylor &amp; Xinqi Su Hong Kong has turned two holiday camps, including a former military barracks, into quarantine zones for people who may have come into contact with carriers of the Wuhan virus, officials announced Thursday. The international financial hub has been on high alert for the virus, which has killed 17 people since …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's reelection looks more like long shot than slam dunk?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/479078-trumps-reelection-looks-more-like-a-long-shot-than-a-slam-dunk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's approval rating is dismal, and partisans are highly engaged and unlikely to stray from their respective party nominees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani claims he has goods on Biden, threatens to go public...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/23/rudy-giuliani-threatens-to-go-public-with-biden-corruption-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, the personal attorney for President Trump, threatened Thursday to go public with information that would expose corruption by 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden. “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK  after 3 seconds!</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/how-will-we-know-whos-winning-streaming-war-if-every-service-counts-views-differently/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As viewers shift from traditional TV to streaming, services like Netflix have less incentive to share a common metric for sharing what counts as a "view"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Groupthink, Self-Censorship Making Journalism Lifeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/01/packer-hitchens/605365/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A writer who’s afraid to tell people what they don’t want to hear has chosen the wrong trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Egyptian mummy 'brought back to life' by scientists who recreated voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/ancient-egyptian-mummy-brought-back-21342577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Egyptian priest, known as Nesyamun, hasn't spoken in more than 3,000 years, but now his voice has been synthesised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ education now mandatory in New Jersey schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/education/nj-lgbtq-education-curriculum-lesson-plans-mandate-20200120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators in a dozen N.J. public school districts, including Haddon Heights, are testing a pilot curriculum to include instruction about the contributions of lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and disabled people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Prosecutors Paint Picture of Serial Predator... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/annabella-sciorra-testifies-harvey-weinstein-raped-her-1272310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Sopranos' actress is one of four primary witnesses testifying for the prosecution about Weinstein's conduct toward them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother caught with 200 pounds of meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/grandmother-caught-with-200-pounds-of-meth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 65-year-old grandmother is accused of trying to sneak more than 200 pounds of methamphetamine into the U.S. at a border crossing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected people seen dead in streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/infected-people-seen-dead-streets-21345585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Disturbing images on Instagram from inside Wuhan show residents dropping to the floor following a lockdown of the city by Chinese authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds:  Man stole $10 million from investor to bankroll Vegas gambling, lavish lifestyle...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/criminal-justice/ct-chicago-sports-gambler-fraud-charges-20200122-uruvy3ao4jf7xeeumtrg4jp4su-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Gorodetsky, who made a name for himself as a maverick in the Las Vegas sports betting scene with a seemingly bottomless bankroll and the guts to lay it all on the line, was charged Tuesday in federal court in Chicago with a massive fraud scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant parents deported without their children make historic return to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/migrant-parents-deported-without-their-children-make-historic-return-to-the-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the U.S. separated thousands of migrant families in 2018, it deported hundreds of parents without their children. Nine of them were allowed to return to U.S. to see their children once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 40% of Americans don't have $1,000 for an emergency!</title>
      <link>https://www.bankrate.com/banking/savings/financial-security-january-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bankrate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When in a pinch, those who lack emergency savings turn to other methods to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touches highest levels of American power...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jeff-bezos-phone-back-mbs-saudi-arabia-amazon-d9f15cf8-6f1b-4a6e-974b-3b37a0b10181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He owns one of the country's biggest companies and most influential news outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOPRANOS' Actress Stuns Courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-annabella-sciorra-rape-trial-1202838739/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annabella Sciorra recounted to a jury how Harvey Weinstein burst into her apartment sometime in the winter of 1993-94, pinned her on a bed and raped her, leaving her so traumatized that she began t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems face risks and limits in impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5dbd0f2716438d40395b36f054f7d55d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The challenge is becoming increasingly clear for House Democrats prosecuting President Donald Trump's impeachment case as the Senate convenes for a second day of arguments in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami PD suspends white officer who begins identifying as 'black'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/miami-pd-suspends-white-officer-who-begins-identifying-as-black-male/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A controversial Miami cop was suspended with pay after he argued at a Miami City Commission meeting last week that he identifies as a black male, despite his Caucasian complexion. #BREAKING: @MiamiPD Capt. @OrtizFOP tells city commission “I am a black male” after he was caught lying about his race on 2014 lieutenant’s exam and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot the Robot Dog Trots Into the Big, Bad World...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/spot-the-robot-dog-trots-into-the-big-bad-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Dynamics' creation is starting to sniff out its role in the workforce: as a helpful canine that still sometimes needs you to hold its paw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Goes Off After FOX AND FRIENDS Airs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-goes-off-on-mini-mike-bloomberg-after-fox-and-friends-airs-attack-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump fired back at Democratic candidate Michael Bloomberg in response to his new campaign ad -- airing on Fox &amp; Friends -- slamming the president's behavior as "erratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to move, Californians tour top destination: Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-01-22/californians-looking-to-leave-tour-their-destination-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of California voters have considered moving out of state. Many who do choose Texas, where lower housing costs come with trade-offs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NETFLIX New Ratings Math Sacrifices Clarity for Flashy Numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/netflixs-new-ratings-math-sacrifices-clarity-flashy-numbers-1272214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer's change to the way it measures viewers means it's harder to tell how many people actually watch a show as opposed to just sampling it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS SCARE LAX</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/lax-passenger-quarantined-after-showing-potential-coronavirus-symptoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger arriving on an American Airlines flight to Los Angeles International Airport from Mexico City was hospitalized and quarantined after showing what health officials called “disturbing" symptoms, that indicate the patient may have been exposed to the deadly coronavirus,  it was announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA student jailed in China over tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-arrests-university-minnesota-twitter-e495cf47-d895-4014-9ac8-8dc76aa6004d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student had posted images of a cartoon villain resembling Xi Jinping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg ad blasts Trump treatment of military leaders...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479529-nationwide-bloomberg-ad-blasts-trumps-treatment-of-military-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg released a new nationwide television advertisement for his presidential campaign on Thursday, blasting President Trump over his reported treatment of military leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TAUNTS TRUMP ON TWITTER: 'OBSESSED MUCH?'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/23/mike-bloomberg-trump-obsessed-much/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg taunted President Donald Trump in a tweet Thursday, accusing him of being &amp;quot;obsessed&amp;quot; with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein trial turns to accusers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/83025aa11d457221eaa7a260faeab504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A ctress Annabella Sciorra confronted Harvey Weinstein in court Thursday after keeping her rape accusation against the former Hollywood honcho largely hidden for decades....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
TARANTINO: I am in combat with blockbuster franchises...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/jan/23/quentin-tarantino-blockbusters-originals-star-wars-franchises-superhero-movie-martin-scorsese-marvel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino says ‘original movies’ are in a ‘war’ with superhero and Star Wars franchises, echoing Martin Scorsese’s attack on Marvel films</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with 'identical human appearance' unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-identical-human-appearance-21343768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RealDoll's flagship Harmony sex robot was paraded at the AVN Adult Entertainment Expo at Las Vegas' Hard Rock Hotel and Casino. It is capable of holding conversations with people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Epstein 'madam' emails hacked; Powerful friends exposed?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/23/ghislaine-maxwells-private-emails-reportedly-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell’s private emails have been hacked — and she may have been targeted in a search for damning information on her powerful network of pals, according to new court papers. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Vesuvius blast turned ancient victim's brain to glass...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8ffb49731526ee1b1741798ff0e9a7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The eruption of Mount Vesuvius turned an incinerated victim's brain material into glass, the first time scientists have verified the phenomenon from a volcanic blast, officials at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan crosses into Mexico without resistance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ccbbe21522c8771ca00afec50a9015f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Hundreds of Central American migrants crossed the river into Mexico from Guatemala Thursday after a dayslong standoff with security forces. Carrying U.S. and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Dogs found eating body of owner who hadn't been heard from for days...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/5872579/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said it's very likely the man died of natural causes and the dogs were starving after not having been fed for a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My night with male sex doll'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/9721275/two-bendy-willies-and-a-brief-moment-of-passion-my-night-with-a-male-sex-doll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HENRY is tall, dark and handsome, doesn’t answer back and is always up for sex. Only thing is he isn’t real, he’s a male sex doll. Increasing numbers of British men – and women – are se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAKES COULD BE SOURCE</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/chinese-coronavirus-outbreak-traced-back-to-snakes-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers appear to have zeroed in on how the coronavirus in China first spread to humans: exposure to snakes at a wholesale market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are all extremely vulnerable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/how-jeff-bezos-iphone-x-was-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It most likely began with a tiny bit of code that implanted malware, which gave attackers access to Jeff Bezos’ photos and texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVER-UP FEARS MOUNTING</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Wuhan-quarantine-expands-as-Chinese-fear-14997682.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - The central Chinese city of Wuhan pulsated with fear and anger Thursday, as 11 million people awoke to news that they were being confined to a metropolis-sized quarantine zone designed to contain a widening coronavirus outbreak.  The quarantine is also spreading with nearby Huanggang and Ezhou announcing they were shutting down travel networks, effectively confining some 20 million people to their municipalities.  In Wuhan, train and bus stations were abruptly closed, hundreds of flights were canceled, and some roads were blocked to stop people from leaving the city Thursday, a day when transportation networks should have been heaving with passengers heading to their hometowns for the official start of the Lunar New Year holiday on Friday night.  But experts warned that it would not be enough to stop the spread of the pneumonia-like virus, which has now killed 17 people in Wuhan and surrounding Hubei province. The number of people infected in China stood at 617 on Thursday afternoon.  "A bigger outbreak is certain," said Guan Yi, a virologist who helped identify Severe acute respiratory syndrome in 2003. He estimated - "conservatively" - that this outbreak could be 10 times bigger than the SARS epidemic because that virus was transmitted by only a few "super spreaders" in a more defined part of the country.  "We have passed through the 'golden period' for prevention and control," he told Caixin magazine from self-imposed quarantine after visiting Wuhan. "What's more, we've got the holiday traffic rush and a dereliction of duty from certain officials."  Authorities had initially said that the virus, which began in a Wuhan food market selling exotic animals for consumption, was mild and could not be transmitted between humans. But that changed this week when the numbers of people infected by the virus, which has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted GRAMMYS CEO speaks out on bombshell allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/culture/story/deborah-dugan-speaks-filing-lawsuit-recording-academy-68460397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deborah Dugan spoke out for the first time since filing a lawsuit against the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, which does the Grammys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg copies Trump -- to beat Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mike-bloomberg-2020-campaign-operation-donald-trump-eafc685c-fd07-44a7-9c3a-c8b55b471291.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His campaign is trying to learn from what the president did in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW IMMERSIVE PLANE CRASH EXPERIENCE TO OPEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/plane-crash-simulator-performance-flight-flying-darkfield-nottingham-a9298516.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recording Academy imploding week of GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-Recording-Academy-is-imploding-the-week-14996152.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a lineup of in-demand performers including Ariana Grande, Rosalía, Lizzo and pop-goth wunderkind Billie Eilish, the upcoming Grammy Awards will, for the third time in as many years, take place amid turmoil within its ranks.  Last week, the Recording Academy, which puts on the annual ceremony, announced that its chief executive Deborah Dugan had been placed on administrative leave following a "formal allegation of misconduct by a senior female member" of the organization. Dugan's suspension arrived less than six months into her tenure as the academy's first female chief executive and president - and just days ahead of the Jan. 26 ceremony.  Dugan responded Tuesday in a 44-page complaint filed with the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, alleging gender discrimination, sexual harassment and unequal pay on the part of the academy. The complaint, officially known as a charge of discrimination, also claims that the organization retaliated against Dugan after she raised concerns - in an email to a senior human resources executive - that the academy was operating under a "'boys' club' mentality."  In her email, Dugan accused Joel Katz, an entertainment lawyer who serves as the academy's general counsel, of sexually harassing her. She also referenced alleged sexual misconduct by her predecessor, Neil Portnow, who called the allegations "ludicrous, and untrue" in a statement to media outlets Wednesday.  Dugan's lawsuit signals a reckoning for the embattled 63-year-old organization, which has faced mounting criticism in recent years over the Grammys' failure to properly recognize female artists and artists of color. Here are some answers to questions you might have about the lawsuit - and how it might affect the Grammys going forward.  - When did the controversy start?  According to Dugan's lawsuit, she emailed the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOT DOCTOR TREATING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/robot-doctor-treating-first-coronavirus-21342199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patient taken in a sealed "isopod" to space-age specialist pandemic containment facility in Washington hospital which has never been used before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-democrats-detail-trump-ukraine-timeline-in-opening-arguments-2020-01-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House managers presented an exhaustive account of the president's efforts to pressure Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in far-Right visits to former Nazi concentration camps...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/rise-far-visits-former-nazi-114929792.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Nazi concentration camps in Germany are experiencing a disturbing rise in visits by the far-Right and Holocaust deniers, the head of the memorials at two of the most notorious camps has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING CANCELS NEW YEAR EVENTS...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beijing-cancels-events-curb-virus-120920839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARS fighter returns to spotlight...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200123094324-u6r80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/DOCTOR (PIX):China SARS fighter returns to spotlight in coronavirus battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATIENTS PUT IN BOXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/passenger-infected-coronavirus-wheeled-out-21341307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows a man - who showed potential coronavirus symptoms - wearing a protective suit, mask and gloves as he is wheeled to a waiting ambulance outside the airport in Fuzhou in south-eastern China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAME KILL RATE AS SPANISH FLU?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/professor-warns-new-coronavirus-has-same-kill-rate-as-the-spanish-flu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish flu killed 20-50 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAKES COULD BE SOURCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/22/health/snakes-wuhan-coronavirus-outbreak-conversation-partner/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snakes -- the Chinese krait and the Chinese cobra -- may be the original source of the newly discovered coronavirus that has triggered an outbreak of a deadly infectious respiratory illness in China this winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468376-1/us-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate impeachment trial of President Trump continues with opening arguments from House managers. Other legislative work is also possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA QUARANTINES CITIES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-warns-virus-could-mutate-spread-death-toll-030352863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China locked down nearly 20 million in two cities at the centre of a deadly virus outbreak on Thursday, banning planes and trains from leaving in an unprecedented move aimed at containing the disease which has already spread to other countries. The respiratory virus has claimed 17 lives since emerging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CASES RISE SHARPLY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed98662865c3c2eafc1733c827111ab2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China decided Thursday to lock down three cities that are home to more than 18 million people in an unprecedented effort to try to contain a deadly new viral illness that has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury hears defense cite accuser's email saying 'I love you' years after alleged rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Harvey-Weinstein-used-his-power-and-prestige-to-14995261.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Women accusing Harvey Weinstein of sexual assault at his criminal trial will have to answer for two realities - the stories they will tell on the witness stand and the starkly different record preserved in emails and other records from before and after the alleged assaults.  That was the argument made by his attorney Damon Cheronis on Wednesday as he presented to the jury emails between Weinstein and the woman he allegedly raped at a Doubletree Hotel in Manhattan in 2013.  Cheronis said accuser Jessica Mann, an aspiring actress, maintained a five-year relationship with the movie tycoon and sent flirty, warm messages throughout. At one point she referred to him as her "casual boyfriend."  "I love you, I always do. But I hate feeling like a booty call. ;)" Mann wrote in a 2017 message to Weinstein - which was put up on a large TV screen at the back of the room in Cheronis' opening statement.  "Ladies and gentlemen, that's not how you talk to your predator," the lawyer said. "That's not how you talk to your rapist."  Cheronis said the district attorney's office wants to convey that the women were "weak" and "couldn't stand up for themselves," that they "were lured in by Harvey Weinstein [and] tricked."  "That's a mirage, and don't take my word for it," the lawyer told the jury.  Weinstein was hunched over at the defense table during his lawyer's moment in the spotlight, chewing his way through a roll of Mentos as Cheronis offered the first official counternarrative to the depiction of Weinstein as a monster and predator that has taken hold in the media since allegations against him started the #MeToo movement in October 2017.  "The truth doesn't change when an article comes out in 2017," Cheronis told the panel, referring to some of the coverage that prompted scores...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  DEEP PARTISAN SPLIT ON REMOVAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.people-press.org/2020/01/22/by-a-narrow-margin-americans-say-senate-trial-should-result-in-trumps-removal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.people-press.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Senate impeachment trial gets underway, about half of Americans say Donald Trump should be removed from office. A 63% majority say Trump definitely or probably has committed illegal acts, either in office or while running for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are all extremely vulnerable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/22/technology/jeff-bezos-hack-iphone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It most likely began with a tiny bit of code that implanted malware, which gave attackers access to Mr. Bezos’ photos and texts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union membership falls to record low of 10.3%...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/479400-union-membership-falls-to-record-low-of-103-percent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of salaried workers in labor unions fell 0.2 points in 2019 to a record low of 10.3 percent, almost half the 20.3 percent rate in 1983 and a 2-point drop from a decade earlier,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators suffer 'digital detox' as they hear case...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122233952-np0dr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-SCENE (PIX, TV):U.S. senators on 'digital detox' as they hear Trump's impeachment trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRIAL UNFOLDS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122233051-0thx7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV):UPDATE 8-Democrats launch first salvo at Trump impeachment trial, say U.S global standing at stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  72% WANT WITNESSES...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122223845-ozj6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-POLL (POLL, URGENT, PIX):POLL-Let them speak: Most Americans want witnesses in Trump impeachment trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 1:  11 million TV viewers...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122221214-885t7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-RATINGS (REPEAT, PIX):RPT-Opening of Trump impeachment trial draws 11 million TV viewers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars flaunt Gaultier creations for designer's finale in Paris...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122202308-8qhc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASHION-PARIS/HAUTE COUTURE-GAULTIER (PIX, TV):Stars flaunt Gaultier creations for designer's finale in Paris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Trump to Attend Anti-Abortion March in First for a U.S. President...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/trump-to-become-first-president-in-history-to-speak-at-march-for-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will deliver an in-person speech on Friday at the March for Life, an annual rally held in Washington protesting the legalization of abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS 'MUTATING'</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10784540/coronavirus-wuhan-china-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVENTEEN people have died from coronavirus as more than 500 cases of the killer strain were confirmed, officials have said. Latest figures reveal 471 cases in China, with four in Thailand, two in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Began With Goodwill Tour, Intimate Dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bezos-hack-began-with-saudi-goodwill-tour-intimate-dinner/ar-BBZerWh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety Over Bolton...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-shows-anxiety-as-arguments-begin-in-senate-impeachment-trial/ar-BBZecI9?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first robot heart will 'end need for transplants'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/worlds-first-soft-robotic-heart-21338696  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "hybrid heart" made of soft artificial muscles and sensors is believed to eventually end the need for transplants from dead humans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graffiti returns to the NYC subway system...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-graffiti-makes-a-bit-of-a-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MTA spends a lot of money every year to clean graffiti from subway cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President breaks daily tweet record... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-twitter-record-impeachment-trial-e2b8f412-e429-4ce3-8d34-77e5334f3595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president reached a total of 141 tweets and retweets by 6 pm ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan, their new neighbors and the paparazzi...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/harry-meghan-neighbors-paparazzi-204051422.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke and Duchess of Sussex have threatened legal action over the pictures, but the photographers are also under fire from locals who say they are not going to tolerate invasions of privacy. "It is a quiet place here," said Kathryn Sandberg, a long-time resident of North Saanich, the tiny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA psychologist defends torture before Guantanamo court...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cia-psychologist-defends-torture-guantanamo-court-214757489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A psychologist who helped design the CIA's "war on terror" torture program after the September 11, 2001 attacks defended the program this week before its victims at the US military prison in Guantanamo, Cuba. James Mitchell was unapologetic Tuesday when he appeared at a hearing to answer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE and APPLE clash over web browser privacy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-apple-clash-over-browser-233257322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Google engineers said a tool Apple Inc. developed to help users avoid web tracking is fundamentally flawed and creates more problems than it solves.The Intelligent Tracking Prevention feature on Apple’s Safari web browser, which is meant to block tracking software used by digital advertisers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein rape trial opens, marking milestone for #MeToo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2d1427a79ef085495b63a45b5f8fb6a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein went on trial Wednesday in a landmark moment for the # MeToo movement, with prosecutors painting him as a sexual predator who used his Hollywood clout to abuse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Grammys CEO says rape allegation 'false and outrageous'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/277fdd6e461fd42c701c763ab2464eec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Former Grammys CEO Neil Portnow said Wednesday that a rape allegation against him aired by his successor in a complaint against the Recording Academy is “false and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson communicated with MBS on WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/01/22/boris-johnson-communicated-saudi-crown-prince-whatsapp-ex-uk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson has been in communication with Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s crown prince over WhatsApp, multiple former UK government figures have told The Telegraph, raising major security concerns in light of the Jeff Bezos hack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Opens Door to Cuts to Medicare, Other Entitlements...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-opens-door-to-cuts-to-medicare-and-other-entitlement-programs/ar-BBZdSGU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff, Nadler tension spills out...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/schiff-nadler-impeachment-tension-spill-onto-senate-floor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment trial of President Donald Trump is highlighting rhetorical and stylistic differences, and at times tension, between two key House chairmen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHUMER: Bolton-Biden trade 'off the table'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/22/senate-trial-hear-house-democrats-argue-case-against-trump/4534581002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House impeachment managers, led by Intelligence Chairman Adam Schiff, D-Calif., have 24 hours, over three days, to argue their case against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle first in USA where residents can vote via smartphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/22/21077358/seattle-king-county-smartphone-voting-mobile-supervisors-board-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting will be easier — and potentially riskier — than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MIAMI HERALD Cuts 70 Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.miaminewtimes.com/news/miami-herald-layoffs-will-affect-70-workers-as-newspaper-closes-printing-plant-11453685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miaminewtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Herald is closing its Doral-based production plant and will soon print at the Sun Sentinel's plant in Deerfield Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> READ: TECHNICAL REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_uk/article/v74v34/here-is-the-technical-report-suggesting-saudi-arabias-prince-hacked-jeff-bezos-phone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motherboard has obtained the report made by FTI Consulting into how Crown Prince Mohammad Bin Salman allegedly hacked Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos's phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The selling of CTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/sports/sports-perspectives/the-selling-of-cte-how-the-concussion-doctor-has-built-a-career-on-distorted-science-1.615744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennet Omalu, a Nigerian American pathologist portrayed by Will Smith in the 2015 film, "Concussion," Omalu is partly responsible for the most important sports story of the 21st century. But the brain science community believes Omalu is dramatically overstating the risks of CTE and contact sports and fueling misperceptions about the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to impose visas restrictions for pregnant women...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4c42c5311ba8a6661855cadd12f0fed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration is coming out with new visa restrictions aimed at restricting “birth tourism," in which women travel to the U.S. to give birth so their children can have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Fires Back With Photo From Khashoggi Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jeff-bezos-cryptically-responds-to-reports-of-saudi-hacking-with-image-from-jamal-khashoggi-memorial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos responded to Saudi Arabia today over reports that his phone was hacked through WhatsApp by crown prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA QUARANTINES WUHAN</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/china-quarantines-wuhan-coronavirus-outbreak-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus has been linked to at least 17 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Fast Track...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29b81fda30045ec649467abb7ee47d28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. Senate began hearing opening arguments Wednesday in President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial with proceedings now on a fast track. First up: Democratic House managers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flips out at reporter: 'Why why why why why why why?!?'   </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/biden-flips-out-at-reporter-why-why-why-why-why-why-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This wasn’t a stutter — he just flipped out. After a campaign event in Mason City, Iowa on Wednesday, Joe Biden was being pursued by CBS reporter Ed O’Keefe, who wanted to know about Biden’s recent kerfuffle with Bernie Sanders. WATCH: After a campaign event in Mason City, Iowa, @joebiden reacts to @edokeefe's question about …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
