<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How tech giants turned 'digital wellness' into marketing ploy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-big-tech-co-opted-time-well-spent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the large tech corporations turned "digital wellness" into a Goopified trend that gives them a new way to market themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 stabbed at UK railway station; Attacker 'shouted Allah!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/greater-manchester-news/manchester-victoria-knife-attack-station-15615253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No trams are currently stopping at Victoria and there's a large police presence outside the station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing face-detecting locks in public housing increases citizen surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/31/beijing-facial-recognition-public-housing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing is using smart locks with facial recognition to prevent abuses of public housing, but at a steep cost to privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON DECLARES: I AM GREATEST EVER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-declares-himself-the-greatest-player-of-all-time-because-of-championship-with-cavaliers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James says his 2016 NBA title with the Cavs made him the best ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi says won't resign if indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-i-wont-resign-if-summoned-for-a-hearing-pending-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Imagine if ultimately the case was closed, and a prime minister had been ousted,' Netanyahu says. That would be 'a terrible blow to democracy'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDES WARN: HILLARY COMPARISONS 'REEK SEXISM'</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/elizabeth-warren-2020-campaign/579214/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her 2020 bid, the senator from Massachusetts wants to reclaim her status as a political outsider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Warren's 'psychiatrist' knows whether she thinks she can win White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-on-whether-warren-thinks-she-can-win-the-presidency-youd-have-to-ask-her-psychiatrist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with "Fox &amp; Friends" host Pete Hegseth set to air during the Fox News New Year's Eve Special, President Trump suggested that only Massachusetts Democratic Sen. Elizabeth Warren's "psychiatrist" knows whether she thinks she can win the White House in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horny passengers 'try to mate' with snake!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/31/cane-toads-python-escape-storm-northern-australia-kununurra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amphibian expert says toads were trying to mate with python, as thousands of the invasive pest are flushed out by rising waters in Kununurra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army rescinds unusually specific order banning sex, cuddling...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/europe/army-unit-in-europe-rescinds-unusually-specific-order-banning-sex-and-cuddling-1.562272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas came late for some Army troops on rotation to Europe when officials canceled an order Wednesday that for nine days banned various sexual acts, including cuddling, for a unit’s soldiers in the rotational barracks at the Grafenwoehr Training Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington On Verge of Legalizing Human Composting?</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/washington-may-become-the-first-state-to-legalize-human-composting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's something beautiful in deciding how one's final moments should be confined to the memory of our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-world-cup-host-qatar-introduce-100-percent-booze-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toads ride on Monty the python to escape storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-31/cane-toads-hitch-ride-on-monty-the-python-back/10675944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A farmer in far north WA captures the bizarre sight of a knot of cane toads hitching a ride on a python in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos fortune drops $40,000,000,000+ from peak, but still grew by $24 BILLION this year...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/magazines/panache/tim-sweeney-jeff-bezos-lei-jun-the-worlds-biggest-billionaire-winners-losers-of-2018/articleshow/67320613.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singaporean billionaires fared the best in dollar terms, gaining $2.5 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winds could make Vegas New Year's Eve fireworks dicey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/winds-could-make-las-vegas-new-years-eve-fireworks-dicey-1562570/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service forecasts a high of 49 degrees Monday with winds kicking up and clouds moving out late morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines President Duterte claims he abused maid as teenager...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/30/asia/rodrigo-duterte-comments-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte has claimed he molested a maid while in high school -- comments his spokesman later said were "made up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 BILLION ROBOCALLS IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stop-robocalling-me-i-didnt-11546261200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans’ growing battle against illegal robocallers has reached a boiling point, with victims of one form of phone-related malfeasance now lashing out at those impacted by a different form: phone-number spoofing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Experiment to Stop Latin America Carnage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/inside-the-experiment-to-stop-the-carnage-in-latin-america-11546275481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few places in Ecuador and Colombia are exceptions to the regional surge in homicides. Efforts include turning gang members into garbage collectors, and firing hundreds of corrupt police officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens steal NYC bus; 4-hour joyride...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-teen-thieves-steal-mta-bus-bronx-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A half-dozen teens stole a parked MTA bus from the Bronx and took it on a three-borough joyride — less than 24 hours after a trio of teenagers stole a city bus in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro follows through on gun, 'anti-Marxist' vows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-follows-gun-anti-marxist-vows-193827024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - On the eve of taking office as Brazil's new president on Tuesday, Jair Bolsonaro is making clear he intends to implement the far-right agenda he promised during his election campaign. The announcements underlined Bolsonaro's desire to break with decades of center-left rule in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican spokesman, deputy resign amid crisis for pope...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vatican-spokesman-greg-burke-deputy-resign-suddenly-111645264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican spokesman, Greg Burke, and his deputy resigned abruptly Monday amid an overhaul of the Vatican's communications operations and a crisis period in Pope Francis' papacy. The departures of Burke and his deputy, Paloma Garcia Ovejero, signaled that problems associated with Francis'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless starts fire in front of MANDALAY BAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/homeless-person-causes-fire-in-front-of-mandalay-bay-police-say-1562386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details were not immediately available from the Clark County Fire Department, but Metropolitan Police Department Lt. David Gordon confirmed about 10:40 p.m. that an unknown number of palm trees had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana made big promises on racial equity -- and fell short...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/legal-marijuana-made-big-promises-racial-equity-fell-short-n952376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time is really up on selling your business dream as a social justice movement,” said the president of the Minority Cannabis Business Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian-American Sentenced to Life for Selling Properties to Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com//Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Palestinian-American-gets-life-in-prison-for-selling-properties-to-Jews-575903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, Isaam Akel, was arrested by the PA last October despite holding an Israeli ID card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says ready to work with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-46714985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's latest statement suggests trade negotiations between the two countries are progressing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice to charge day-trippers for access...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbde03ccc904e618443198adab23979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A measure in Italy's 2019 budget law will allow the local government in Venice to charge day-trippers for access to the city's historic center as a way to help defray the considerable costs of maintaining a popular tourist destination built on water, the mayor said. Venice Mayor Luigi Brugnaro said late Sunday on Twitter that the new visitors' tax would "allow us to manage the city better and to keep it clean" and "allow Venetians to live with more decorum."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Investments of 2018? Art, Wine, Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-best-investments-of-2018-art-wine-and-cars-11546232460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury assets, including wine, art, classic cars and fancy colored diamonds, have outperformed stocks and bonds this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious swamp cancer killing ponies on island famous for them...</title>
      <link>https://www.delmarvanow.com/story/news/local/virginia/2018/12/29/chincoteague-pony-euthanized-swamp-cancer/2438186002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delmarvanow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disease killed three other ponies this year, as well as two in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran TV chief sacked over Jackie Chan sex scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46720733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A regional channel showed Jackie Chan's Shinjuku Incident without censoring an "immoral" part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets stagger towards end of worst year since financial crisis... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-rounds-worst-since-2011-gains-034945504--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World stock markets staggered Monday towards the end of their worst year since the global financial crisis a decade ago, rocked by rising interest rates, the global trade war and Brexit, dealers said. London and Paris wobbled in holiday-shortened trade on New Year's Eve -- but nursed dizzying double-digit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: NO wall money...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51dd72d6d19e4d2eb0b73dcd2c45aa27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the U.S. government shutdown (all times local): 11:45 a.m. House Democrats are unveiling legislation to re-open the government without money for President Donald Trump's border wall. The House is preparing to vote on the package Thursday when the new Congress convenes. This is according to an aide who was not authorized to discuss the plan publicly and spoke on condition of anonymity. It will include one bill to fund the Department of Homeland Security at current levels through Feb. 8, with $1.3 billion for border security. The package will also include six other bipartisan bills to fund the departments of Agriculture, Interior, Housing and Urban Development and others closed by the partial shutdown. Some have already passed the Senate. Those bills will provide money through the remainder of the fiscal year, to Sept. 30. The partial government shutdown is in its second week over Trump's demand for $5 billion for the wall. --Lisa Mascaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hold fast': Mattis bids farewell to Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hold-fast-mattis-bids-farewell-pentagon-153201158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Jim Mattis bade farewell to the Pentagon on Monday, telling the US military to "hold fast" after he quit over a series of fundamental differences with President Donald Trump. Mattis resigned December 20, after Trump stunned the US establishment by ordering a full troop withdrawal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER messages unleashed FBI raid on NSA leak suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/31/nsa-hacking-case-twitter-1077013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge reveals that just before Shadow Brokers advertised a major breach, contractor sent suspicious message: “Shelf life, three weeks”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge funds had miserable 2018; Closures, mediocre performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/hedge-funds-hopes-for-2018-dashed-amid-fund-closures-20181224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year was supposed to be when rising volatility and yields brought back the glory days. Instead, returns fell and investors fled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12,000 police on duty in Paris as 'yellow vests' call protests...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/12-000-police-duty-paris-yellow-vests-call-153929643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 150,000 police are set to be on duty around France on New Year's Eve when "yellow vest" protesters have called for another round of anti-government demonstrations. The French capital will be on high alert after repeated clashes over the last month between security forces and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batten Down the Hatches -- Media Storm Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/batten-down-the-hatches-for-2019-a-media-storm-is-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consolidation, an uncertain economy and an unstable presidency is making people nervous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist filmed snorting cocaine off Escobar's grave getting death threats...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/12/31/brit-filmed-snorting-cocaine-off-pablo-escobars-grave-says-death-threats-8295204/?ito=cbshare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Semmens, 35, has lost his family after being kicked out of Colombia where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis CK leaked standup: Jokes about school shooting, Holocaust, trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6541323/Louis-CK-makes-fun-Parkland-shooting-victims-shocking-leaked-stand-audio.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Louis CK, 51, attacked the Parkland high school shooting victims in leaked audio from his December 16 set at the Governor's Comedy Club in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN GETS READY</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c9f36d36633c43d0bee74859a010850a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Elizabeth Warren on Monday took the first major step toward launching a widely anticipated campaign for the presidency, hoping her reputation as a populist fighter can help her navigate a Democratic field that could include nearly two dozen candidates. "No matter what our differences, most of us want the same thing," the 69-year-old Massachusetts Democrat said in a video that highlights her family's history in Oklahoma. "To be able to work hard, play by the same set of rules and take care of the people we love. That's what I'm fighting for and that's why today I'm launching an exploratory committee for president."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown first battle of new era...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b1ca483bfaa646deba4fff1a968b2ade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi often quotes Abraham Lincoln saying public sentiment is everything. It's a theory that will be put to the test when the new House Democratic majority gavels in this week and votes to end the government shutdown without money for President Donald Trump's border wall with Mexico. The high-stakes move to reopen the government will be the first big battle between Trump and Pelosi as Democrats come into control ready to reassert the power of the legislative branch and confront the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Pence-Schumer showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/31/mike-pence-chuck-schumer-government-shutdown-2018-1076615</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men with no shared history or apparent personal chemistry are charged with ending the shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed man wearing surgical mask headed to church to 'fulfill prophecy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kens5.com/article/news/local/armed-man-headed-to-fulfill-prophecy-at-church-is-from-houston-area/273-625427998</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kens5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 33-year-old man was arrested in Seguin Sunday morning after heading to a church a loaded firearm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500-euro note gets last print run...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-500-euro-note-gets-last-print-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;500-euro note gets last print run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers develop artificial fingerprints; Hack smartphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/28/research-claims-fake-fingerprints-could-hack-a-third-of-smartphones.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Academics at New York University and the Michigan State University have developed images of fingerprints that have the potential to unlock devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BIGGEST WINS AND LOSSES...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/30/trump-biggest-wins-losses-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second full year at the helm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Detains American on Spying Charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russia-detains-american-on-spying-charge-11546255397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian authorities said they had detained a U.S. citizen for alleged spying, setting the tone for more confrontation between the two countries in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Right Wing Woos New Audience: Jewish Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/europes-right-wing-woos-a-new-audience-jewish-voters-11546257601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across Europe, anti-immigration parties with ties to far-right movements have stepped up efforts to recruit supporters in the continent’s small Jewish community, often drawing on perceptions in that community about anti-Semitism among Muslims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WELCOMES 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2018/dec/31/new-years-eve-2018-celebrations-around-the-world-live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow all the celebrations as the clock strikes midnight and countries see out 2018 to welcome in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.D. Salinger at 100: 'CATCHER IN RYE' still relevant?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Is-Catcher-in-the-Rye-still-relevant-on-13499289.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catcher in the Rye By J.D. Salinger Little, Brown. 240 pp. $8.99 - - - Tuesday is J.D. Salinger's 100th birthday, but Holden Caulfield is still 17. The iconic teenager of "The Catcher in the Rye" is forever suspended in the amber of our youthful alienation. Although a few pious schools continue to ban Salinger's only published novel, for millions of adults, a faded copy of "The Catcher in the Rye" is a sweet teenage treasure, as transgressive as a trophy from band camp. Ninth-graders who secretly read the book with a flashlight when it came out in 1951 are now in their 80s. To read it again as an adult is to feel Holden's pain lingering like a phantom limb. His righteous cynicism is adolescence distilled into a sweet liquor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican spokesman, deputy resign suddenly...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-spokespersons/vatican-spokesman-deputy-resign-suddenly-idUSKCN1OU0HG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spokesman for the Vatican and his deputy resigned suddenly on Monday, an off...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminist filmmakers tackle adult movie machismo...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-feminist-filmmakers-tackle-adult-movie-machismo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feminist filmmakers tackle adult movie machismo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spaceship zooms toward farthest world ever photographed...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/nasa-spaceship-zooms-toward-farthest-world-ever-photographed-11075422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA:  A NASA spaceship is zooming toward the farthest, and quite possibly the oldest, cosmic body ever photographed by humankind, a tiny, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOTS COULD MAKE ROAD WORK THING OF PAST...</title>
      <link>https://home.bt.com/news/uk-news/futuristic-micro-robots-could-make-roadworks-a-thing-of-the-past-11364321785449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grants totalling £26.6m will fund projects including the development of tiny devices to repair cracks in pipes without the need to dig up roads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WELCOMES 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/new-years-eve-celebrations-watch-fireworks-world-welcomes-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Year's Eve is upon us - catch up on all the celebrations around the world with our live stream of all the best firework displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injection to halt Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/injection-halt-progress-alzheimers-available-within-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An injection capable of halting the progress of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s could be available to patients within a decade, Britain&amp;rsquo;s leading dementia organisation predicts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year Ends on 10th Day of Shutdown as Pelosi Awaits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/year-ends-on-10th-day-of-partial-federal-shutdown-pelosi-awaits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi is set to reclaim the speakerâ€™s gavel on Thursday, when Democrats take control of the House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser gun burns flesh from half mile away; 'Perfect for assassins'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-laser-gun-burns-flesh-13793411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the first targets of the weapon will know about it is when they drop down dead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lion kills intern at NC conservator center...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimesnews.com/news/20181230/lion-shot-killed-after-killing-one-person-at-conservators-center</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimesnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lion killed a worker Sunday, Dec. 30, at the Conservators Center, then was shot and killed so Caswell County authorities could retrieve the worker.A</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorists risk lives to loot beer truck that shed bottles on busy road...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8087159/motorists-risk-lives-loot-beer-truck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIRSTY motorists ditched their cars on a busy South African motorway to loot a beer truck that dropped thousands of bottles of cider and lager. Putting their own lives at risk the drivers pulled o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young QBs hope to shine in playoff debuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/sports/steelers/2018/12/29/nfl-playoff-picture-week-17-patrick-mahomes-mitchell-trubisky-lamar-jackson-deshaun-watson/stories/201812300086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodgers and Manning (and maybe Roethlisberger) won’t be in the playoffs, but Mahomes, Watson and Trubisky will make their postseason debuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey delivers pizza to photog who found him in hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6540165/Disgraced-Oscar-winner-Kevin-Spacey-breaks-cover-second-time-dog.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey emerged from his $6million hiding place in Baltimore on Sunday sporting a baseball cap that read 'Retired since 2017'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths Level Off -- Even Decline -- in Opioid Hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/deaths-level-offand-even-declinein-some-opioid-hotspots-11546088400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national overdose-fatality rate appears to be leveling off, and states including New Hampshire and Ohio say deaths have decreased, with the overdose-reversal drug naloxone playing a part in easing the crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of churches agreeing to protect from deportation soars...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/30/rosa-gutierrez-lopez-among-church-sanctuary-migran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement, the government’s deportation agency, has fought state and local governments that have enacted sanctuary policies, it has taken a hands-off approach to churches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judges in govt secrecy cases: POTUS tweets are 'speculation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/12/30/trump-tweets-judges-doj-lawyers-foia-lawsuits/2197524002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judges and Justice Department lawyers have rejected President Donald Trump's tweets as a basis to demand the public release of secret documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor 'concerned' as police 'Zika in meth' stunt goes viral...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/new_orleans/news/article_b2875830-0c8c-11e9-8a33-27661950addb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’ve heard that methamphetamine in Louisiana comes with the Zika virus, well, that’s fake news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake-porn videos weaponized to harass, humiliate...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/technology/109671510/fakeporn-videos-are-being-weaponised-to-harass-and-humiliate-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was her face. But it had been edited, without her knowledge or consent, onto someone else's body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie alumni seek meeting to address 'sexual violence' on campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/30/bernie-sanders-campaign-harassment-1077014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The signees are looking to change what they call a pervasive culture of toxic masculinity in the campaign world.&lt;br /&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major NCAA football conference considers private equity partners...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/sports/oregonian/john_canzano/2018/12/want-to-buy-a-stake-in-the-pac-12-conference-its-exploring-taking-on-private-equity-partners.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pac-12 Conference leadership explores taking on private equity partners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On island famous for wild ponies, dangerous infection killing horses...</title>
      <link>https://www.journalnow.com/news/state_region/swamp-cancer-threatens-wild-ponies-at-chincoteague-national-wildlife-refuge/article_88efce24-b9ad-5386-a577-4179ebcd63e4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.journalnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINCOTEAGUE NATIONAL WILDLIFE REFUGE, Va. — In the cold months, this barrier island is a place of austere stillness, its famed wild ponies grazing along brown marshes, their long faces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23-Year-Old Mahomes Joins Brady, Manning in 50 TD Club...</title>
      <link>http://www.sportingnews.com/us/nfl/news/nfl-news-chiefs-patrick-mahomes-record-50-tds-5000-yards-89-yard-td-pass-week-17-raiders/12apmxtsk5u6s1k9brm00o94oz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportingnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mahomes joins Peyton Manning as the only two players to have 50 touchdowns and 5,000 passing yards in a single season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khomeini grandson: No guarantees Iran regime will survive...</title>
      <link>http://english.alarabiya.net/en/News/middle-east/2018/12/30/Khomeini-grandson-warns-No-guarantees-Iran-s-regime-will-survive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.alarabiya.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hassan Khomeini, the grandson of Ayatollah Khomeini, the founder of the Iranian regime, stressed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where in World Is Larry Page?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/where-in-the-world-is-larry-page-11546199677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Google founder sets a good example for fellow CEOs by keeping a low profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family sues UNIVERSAL Orlando Resort over English-only warning signs after man dies at park...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2018/12/30/family-sues-universal-orlando-resort-over-english-only-warning-signs/2444935002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Guatemalan family is suing Universal Orlando Resort after Jose Calderon Arana suffered a fatal heart attack two years ago after going on the "Skull Island: Reign of Kong" ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD To Patrol Times Square With 1,200 Cameras, Drones...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/30/police-new-years-eve-safe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New levels of security are being added to Times Square to protect over a million people that police expect to celebrate the New Year’s Eve ball drop Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DREAMERS' ON TABLE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ce26f76f37bd41bca5fa97ada7e6a4cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three confidantes of President Donald Trump, including his departing chief of staff, are indicating that the president's signature campaign pledge to build a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border would not be fulfilled as advertised. Trump sparked fervent chants of "Build that wall!" at rallies before and after his election and more recently cited a lack of funding for a border wall as the reason for partially shutting down the government. At times the president has also waved off the idea that the wall could be any kind of barrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Mystery: Why Did John Roberts Intervene in Mueller Probe?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/12/30/supreme-court-john-roberts-robert-mueller-investigation-223569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re about to find out why the chief justice of the Supreme Court decided to get involved in the special counsel’s investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE MONDE controversy over 'constructivist' Macron cover...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181230-le-monde-magazine-creates-controversy-with-constructivist-cover-macron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French newspaper Le Monde faced huge criticism on Sunday after it published a highly provocative cover of French President Emmanuel Macron for its Saturday M magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100  volcanoes on cusp of eruption?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1065105/volcano-eruption-warning-update-Ring-of-Fire-Indonesia-Karakatau-Yellowstone-supervolcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s foremost volcanologists has warned that there are around 100 “explosive” volcanoes around the world that could cause devastation at a moment’s notice.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
