<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Will ideas 'radical' for DC seem reasonable to voters?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/01/how-the-media-can-prevent-2020-from-becoming-2016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ultimate bias in journalism is not political. It’s toward controversy, gaffes, and scandal—shiny new things that get ratings and shares and downloads. There’s a rather obvious lesson here for Democrats seeking the White House—and for media elites who are tragically out of touch with how Americans actually consume the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's oldest rock was found by astronauts -- on the Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/24/world/earth-oldest-rock-moon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Apollo 14 astronauts returned samples from the moon's surface, they probably didn't realize that they were reuniting Earth with a bit of its early history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Dimon, GOLDMAN CEO private meets with Maxine Waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/jamie-dimon-and-david-solomon-met-with-wall-street-critic-maxine-waters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimon and Solomon gave Waters their perspectives on a wide range of topics, including where they stand on the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Resistance' Within West Wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/24/exclusive-excerpts-from-team-of-vipers-john-kelly-overheard-undermining-president-trump-on-syria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Kelly was overheard deliberately undermining Trump's strategy on Syria, an excerpt from a forthcoming book alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eat what want and stay slim? Being thin in DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-01-24/eat-what-you-want-and-still-stay-slim-thank-your-genes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxes of used tissues sell for $80: 'Schedule own illness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Odd_News/2019/01/24/Company-selling-boxes-of-used-tissues-for-80/8151548348856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles start-up is offering to let people choose their own illness schedules by buying a box of used tissues for $80.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Bomb Threat Hoax To Avoid Seeing Parents Diverts Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/easyjet-bomb-threat-hoax-flight-diverted-lyon-rennes-student-parents-avoid-a8743021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country sent back to 'dark ages' after underwater Internet cable severed...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/tonga-sent-back-to-dark-ages-after-underwater-internet-cable-severed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the South Pacific nation of Tonga are experiencing a total Internet shutdown after an underwater cable which connects the island to the rest of the world was severed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDERS QB Challenges Critical ESPN Host to Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.times-standard.com/2019/01/23/derek-carr-challenges-max-kellerman-to-a-fight-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.times-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the First Take personality criticized Carr on Wednesday, the quarterback barked right back on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope 'closely watching' Venezuela chaos, but takes no side...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-vatican/vatican-calls-for-end-to-suffering-in-venezuela-but-takes-no-sides-idUSKCN1PI2QM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis is following the situation in Venezuela closely and the Holy See su...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters planning to grill big banks on Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/24/maxine-waters-scrutiny-nations-big-banks-1113148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;It's probably not going to be a real syrupy sweet committee hearing,&amp;quot; said Rep. Emanuel Cleaver, a senior member of the panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of War: Combat artists capture soul of Marines...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2019/01/24/the-art-of-war-how-combat-artists-are-capturing-the-soul-of-the-marine-corps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Go to war, do art” is now the battle cry of the Marine combat artists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL 'DOWN PAYMENT' DEMANDED TO RE-OPEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/white-house-demands-large-down-payment-on-the-wall-as-schumer-and-mcconnell-try-to-reach-shutdown-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement followed the failure of two Senate bills to end the partial government shutdown now in its 34th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16-month undercover sting to catch man illegally selling $90 worth of fish...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/saskatchewans-government-staged-a-16-month-undercover-sting-to-catch-a-first-nations-man-illegally-selling-90-worth-of-fish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seriously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Starts Sending Some Asylum Seekers Back to Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-start-sending-some-asylum-seekers-back-to-mexico-11548362672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration will soon return some asylum-seeking migrants to Mexico to wait until their U.S. immigration court hearing, the first step in implementing a new border policy announced last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke chief: Bought spares for equipment we agreed to destroy...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/irans-nuclear-chief-we-bought-spares-for-nuke-equipment-we-agreed-to-destroy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ali Akbar Salehi says supreme leader was convinced West would renege on 2015 pact, so replacement tubes for nuclear reactor were secretly purchased</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL SecState resigns after blackface photos emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2019/01/24/new-secretary-state-ertel-dressed-blackface-halloween-2005/2649161002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Ertel was captured in a photo wearing blackface at a private party 14 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both Senate Bills Blocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/24/senate-rejects-trump-plan-to-fund-border-wall-and-end-shutdown-1124728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the failure, lawmakers expressed optimism that there's a way out of the impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILITARY BEHIND MADURO</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/venezuelas-military-backs-maduro-11548347862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s military threw its support behind embattled President Nicolás Maduro, a day after the head of the country’s national assembly declared himself legitimate leader and was recognized by the U.S. and most Latin American nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH MERGING WITH BIG BROTHER? </title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/is-big-tech-merging-with-big-brother-kinda-looks-like-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The all-seeing Amazon, Google, and Facebook have every incentive to help the national security state undermine privacy, free speech, and democracy. We’ve read this book before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California city sets fee on disposable cups...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article224951810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berkeley, California, has approved a 25-cent fee on disposable cups city officials say is part of an effort to eliminate restaurant waste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Dem counteroffer on border security!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/426810-pelosi-no-dem-counter-offer-on-border-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) said Thursday that House Democrats are not working behind the scenes to craft a counteroffer to President Trump’s border wall demands as a strategy for ending the history-making partial shutdown. &amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to Launch 'Massive' War Drills...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-to-launch-massive-war-drills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian military leaders announced on Thursday that the Islamic Republic would be launching a "massive" set of war drills later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who owns your face? Social media mobs raise new privacy concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/23/who-owns-your-face-social-media-mobs-raise-new-pri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might own your car, your house, your pet and your 401(k). But you don’t own your own photographic image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren proposes new 'wealth tax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/elizabeth-warren-to-propose-new-wealth-tax-economic-advisor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren's proposal comes alongside other Democrats' plans to raise taxes on the wealthiest Americans to pay for ambitious policy goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD launches teen sex chatbot...</title>
      <link>https://adage.com/article/agency-news/planned-parenthood-launches-roo-a-sexual-health-chatbot-teens/316365/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;adage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risky phone soars, killing Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/01/24/distracted-driving-iihs/2655556002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are using theirÂ phones in riskier ways while driving, worsening the nation'sÂ crash crisis, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos hits turbulence over CEOs' private jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190124-davos-forum-hits-turbulence-over-ceos-private-jets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Davos forum hits turbulence over CEOs' private jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN:  Time for journalists to sign off TWITTER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/24/media/reliable-sources-01-23-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's first male cheerleaders to make Super Bowl debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/lifestyles/nfl-first-male-cheerleaders-make-super-bowl-debut-atlanta/9s5XwRRoBoaN4jRkkg3rNM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quinton Peron and Napoleon Jinnies made history last year when they joined the LA Rams squad, and will do so again at Super Bowl 53 in Mercedes-Benz Stadium on February 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional support alligator helps depression...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6cf8234a7a5a492eabfa4b0e319f2ec3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YORK HAVEN, Pa. (AP) — A Pennsylvania man says his emotional support alligator helps him deal with his depression. Joie Henney, 65, said his registered emotional support animal named Wally likes to snuggle and give hugs, despite being a 5-foot-long alligator. The York Haven man said he received approval from his doctor to use Wally as his emotional support animal after not wanting to go on medication for depression, he told Philly.com .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe Gets Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/mcauliffe-hints-im-going-to-announce-says-trump-has-no-moral-core</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe, who is inching toward a 2020 Democratic presidential bid, launched a full frontal attack on President Trump’s leadership, blaming him for expanding racial division in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No. 1 leaker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/01/trump-aide-recalls-conways-leaking-tactics-in-the-west-wing-vipers-nest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive excerpt from “Team of Vipers,” Cliff Sims recalls how Kellyanne Conway played Trump, saying one thing on Fox News while bad-­mouthing his administration in private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffers brain freezes during address...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/applause-line-nancy-pelosi-repeatedly-tells-mayors-to-clap-for-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi was like a mother hen to America’s mayors on Wednesday, telling them when to clap for her. After thanking a member of her audience, she said, “That’s an applause line! I’ll let you know.” She followed through on her promise. ﻿ After claiming Democrats support “strong border security initiatives,” she said, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SERENITY' review: Year's first gloriously bad movie is here...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/jan/24/serenity-review-the-years-first-gloriously-bad-movie-is-here </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew McConaughey is a gigolo/fishing boat captain alongside Anne Hathaway in a thrillingly awful thriller with one of the most ill-conceived twists in recent history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. warships sail through Taiwan Strait, turning up pressure on Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/2183546/us-warships-sail-through-closely-watched-taiwan-strait-turning-pressure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the fourth time the Navy has publicly admitted to sending surface combatants through the closely-watched strait since the US restarted the practice last summer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff, Waters plan joint DEUTSCHE BANK investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/23/adam-schiff-maxine-waters-deutsche-bank-1108140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two California Democrats have been talking about areas of interest for each committee and where there's common ground, Schiff said in an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS NEW SPEECH IN BORDER STATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/24/donald-trump-still-planning-major-speech-despite-postponing-state-of-the-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is still considering delivering a major speech to the country next week, despite postponing his State of the Union address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antibiotic resistance 'urgent' global threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-46973641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers want drug firms to develop new antibiotics and to stop people overusing existing ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1,000 media jobs lost in 1 day...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/digital-media-layoffs-consolidation-continue-1548289098-d3bd0e23-aef7-4ad5-8778-428391e80ac8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new layoffs show it's not getting any easier to keep media organizations afloat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's shutdown strategy paying off?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/819128/why-trumps-immigration-compromise-shrewd-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How long can Nancy Pelosi and the Democrats hold out in the shutdown standoff?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMP SHOOK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9067168fa95b41099ee5616225f07061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said he is postponing his State of the Union address until the partial government shutdown ends, yielding after a weeklong showdown with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi. Following a high-stakes game of dare and double-dare, Trump conceded Wednesday night that "no venue that can compete with the history, tradition and importance of the House Chamber." He said he was not looking for an alternate option after Pelosi served notice earlier in the day that he wouldn't be allowed to deliver the address to a joint session of Congress next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tripping Teen Goes On School Groping Spree...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/k-12/lsd-school-groping-spree-634789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 24--A 15-year-old student apparently tripping on LSD groped the breasts of three school staffers and tried to strangle a nurse with her stethoscope while yelling “I'm an Avenger,” according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran arrests 7,000 dissidents in 'year of shame'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/24/iran-arrested-more-than-7000-dissidents-last-year-says-amnesty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists, lawyers, minority rights activists and anti-hijab protesters among those held</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soap storm as SAfrican show broadcasts first inter-racial kiss...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/24/interracial-kiss-angers-south-african-viewers-one-countrys-popular/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-five years on from the collapse of apartheid, one of South Africa's most popular TV soap operas has shed stark light on the country's ongoing battle with racism after showing its first on-screen inter-racial kiss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People with tattoos more likely to have higher number of sex partners...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/how-having-tattoos-affects-your-13901764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey by researchers from the University of Miami has revealed that people with tattoos are more likely to take risks - and this has an effect on their sex life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan court upholds 'sterilization' rule for gender change...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190124-japan-court-upholds-sterilisation-rule-gender-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan court upholds 'sterilisation' rule for gender change</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount St Helens warning: Molten rock rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1077163/mount-st-helens-volcano-warning-scientist-molten-rock-rising-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNT St Helens could erupt again as scientists closely monitor a lava dome rising at five metres a day, a bombshell documentary revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machines capable of predicting, manipulating future?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1077096/artificial-intelligence-ai-predict-future-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARTIFICIAL Intelligence is capable of predicting your future thoughts without knowing anything about you, scientists have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking moment 100 illegals caught on camera climbing over border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6626463/Nearly-500-Central-American-migrants-entered-illegally-one-week-AZ.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Customs and Border Protection officials based in Arizona announced on Wednesday that over 100 migrants had been taken into custody after being caught on camera scaling a border wall in Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi not giving an inch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/24/politics/donald-trump-nancy-pelosi-government-shutdown/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi isn't giving an inch. The House speaker, fortified by brutal polling for Donald Trump, refuses to provide the President an easy way out of his own political box as the government shutdown sparked by his demand for a border wall drags into a 34th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne trashed Trump to mainstream reporters, ex-aide recounts...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/819425/kellyanne-conway-secretly-trashed-trump-advisers-mainstream-reporters-extrump-aide-recounts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new excerpt from former White House communications staffer Cliff Sims' new memoir emerged in Vanity Fair, and this one focused on a very special member of President Trump's Team of Vipers: Kellyanne Conway. Sims doesn't appear to be a fan: As I watched Kellyanne in operation over our time in the White House, my view of her sharpened. It became hard to look long at her without getting the sense that she was a cartoon villain brought to life. Her agenda â€” which was her survival over all others, including the president â€” became more and more transparent. [Cliff Sims, via Vanity Fair] In the White House, "Kellyanne managed to land a job with no fixed responsibilities" and a huge office, where she could "just dabble in areas that piqued her interest," Sims writes. And one of those interests was leaking, a fact he learned firsthand while drafting a response on her MacBook to Morning Joe calling her out for being two-faced about Trump: Kellyanne was sitting at her desk texting away. And since her iMesÂ­sage account was tied to both her phone and her laptop, which she must not have even considered, I could inadvertently see every conversation she was having. Over the course of 20 minutes or so, she was having simultaneous conversations with no fewer than a halfÂ­-dozen reporters, most of them from outlets the White House frequently trashed for publishing "fake news." [Sims, Vanity Fair] Conway "bashed" Kushner, Steve Bannon, and Reince Priebus by name and also recounted private conversations with Trump, "talking about him like a child she had to set straight," Sims said. "I was sitting there, watching this, totally bewildered. I was supposed to be writing a statement, defending her against accusations that she had done almost exactly what I was watchÂ­ing her do that very moment." Read more about his impressions of Conway and Trump at Vanity Fair. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegans 'barbecue dog' in street to shock people into ditching meat...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/01/24/vegans-barbecue-dog-street-shock-people-ditching-meat-8383740/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stunt was meant to cause outrage but some said schoolchildren were left 'terrified' by the sight of the charred animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make 'El Chapo' pay?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/make-el-chapo-pay-for-the-wall-say-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen House Republicans proposed a bill this week that would let the Trump administration use billions of dollars seized from drug lord Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman to build the southern border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims lowest since 1969...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-unemployment/u-s-weekly-jobless-claims-lowest-since-1969-idUSKCN1PI1SM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for unemployment benefits fell to mo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax season from hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/24/irs-tax-returns-government-shutdown-1121839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are already signs that some will be no-shows because they’re facing the prospect of working without pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem primary could turn into 'Lord of the Flies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/why-2020-democratic-primary-could-turn-lord-flies-n961236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top party insiders see a real possibility that superdelegates could play a role at a brokered convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX plays peekaboo with ratings. Hollywood isn't amused...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-netflix-ratings-20190124-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With little motivation to become more transparent, Netflix is irking other Hollywood studios and talent agencies, which say they are at a competitive disadvantage because of the streaming entertainment giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Kansas abandon daylight saving time?</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/politics-government/article224747030.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislation to exempt Kansas from daylight saving time raises the question: What happens to Kansas City?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 hides credit or bank account from partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/millions-of-americans-keep-financial-secrets-from-spouses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 1 in 5 Americans in a live-in relationship keeps a secret checking, savings or credit card account</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil accuses US missionary of endangering isolated tribe with disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8268351/american-missionary-arrested-contacted-tribe-amazon-disease/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL’S government has accused an American missionary of exposing an isolated indigenous tribe to deadly diseases which could wipe them out. Steve Campbell, from Maine in the US, was reportedly qu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese app tells you if near someone in debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/tech/chinese-debt-app-wechat-a4046936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google knows a lot about you: what you look like, how you sound, your favourite place to get coffee. But all that information stays within Google, it isn't handed over to the UK government, who can then use it to decide if you deserve a mortgage or can go on holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Longest of long shots.' Can Pete Buttigieg make serious run at White House?</title>
      <link>https://www.southbendtribune.com/news/local/longest-of-long-shots-can-pete-buttigieg-make-a-serious/article_20de2c10-1a1f-5c11-a713-1f3152a88eac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.southbendtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other candidates have higher profiles, more money. But South Bend's mayor says he can 'do something no one else can do.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncharted waters: Scientists to explore Indian Ocean depths...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/uncharted-waters-scientists-to-explore-indian-ocean-depths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREMEVERHAVEN, Germany (AP) — Scientists prepared Thursday to embark on an unprecedented, years-long mission to explore the Indian Ocean and document changes taking place beneath the waves that could affect billions of people in the surrounding region over the coming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican to break with party; Reopen govt without wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/01/23/colorado-cory-gardner-republicans-trump-wall-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado senator’s spokesman said Wednesday night that the senator has long opposed shutdowns, including the 2013 shutdown, and that Gardner will also vote for the second measure to open …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns against Internet 'disinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/pope-francis-warns-against-spirals-of-hatred-on-social-media-96633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his World Day of Social Communications message, Pope Francis said that online discussion is “too often based on opposition to the other.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Urging Govt to Limit Protection for Activist Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/google-urged-the-u-s-to-limit-protection-for-activist-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Urged the U.S. to Limit ProtectionÂ for Activist Workers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach Developer Dismisses Rising Sea Levels as 'Paranoia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/miami-beach-developer-dismisses-rising-sea-levels-as-paranoia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Miami Beach Developer Dismisses Rising Sea Levels as â€˜Paranoiaâ€™</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Votes on Senate bills seen as progress even if fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c468787c58124ffa9153e602fe7875ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate is taking a new approach to ending the partial government shutdown by actually taking votes instead of just pointing fingers. But competing bills appear likely to fail Thursday, caught in a poisonous Washington impasse. Either measure would reopen federal agencies and pay 800,000 federal workers who are days from missing yet another paycheck. Republicans would couple ending the 34-day shutdown with $5.7 billion for President Donald Trump's border wall and revamping immigration laws. Democrats would reopen agency doors for three weeks while bargainers seek a budget accord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, Russia Building Super-EMP Bombs for 'Blackout Warfare'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/china-russia-building-super-emp-bombs-for-blackout-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several nations, including China and Russia, are building powerful nuclear bombs designed to produce super-electromagnetic pulse waves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Saudi produce ballistic missiles? Satellite imagery raises suspicions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Satellite-imagery-raises-suspicion-of-Saudi-13556411.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images suggest that Saudi Arabia has constructed its first known ballistic missile factory, according to weapons experts and image analysts, a development that raises questions about the kingdom's increasing military and nuclear ambitions under its 33-year-old crown prince. If operational, the suspected factory near the missile base in al-Watah, southwest of Riyadh, would allow Saudi Arabia to manufacture its own ballistic missiles, fueling fears of an arms race against its regional rival Iran. Saudi Arabia does not possess nuclear weapons, so any missiles produced at the apparent factory are likely to be conventionally armed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Years of Crisis?</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/Trump-Pelosi-war-intensifies-foreshadowing-two-13556012.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are a few things common to all presidents, whichever party they come from. They all think they get unfair media coverage. They all feel like prisoners of the White House and wish they could just go for a walk by themselves or head down to the corner bar. And they all chafe at the constraints on their power, the fact that despite occupying what appears to be the most powerful office in the world, there are all kinds of forces, institutions and people they can't control and that limit their ability to do what they want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 10,000 Central Americans bound for USA request Mexican visas...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/More-than-10-000-Central-Americans-bound-for-US-13556640.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - Mexico said Wednesday that more than 10,000 people have requested visas to cross its southern border as it seeks to grant legal documents to members of a rapidly growing U.S.-bound migrant caravan from Central America. If the migrants travel together, the convoy could exceed the size of the last such caravan, which became a flash point in U.S.-Mexican relations as President Donald Trump seized on it to argue for building a giant border wall. But the new movement is far less organized than the last caravan. Those migrants traveled together in part to avoid arrest. The current group of migrants, in contrast, will have legal papers and may disperse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benny Gantz, Israel's Reluctant Warrior, Takes Aim at Netanyahu's Post...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/politics/193787-190123-reticent-former-idf-chief-benny-gantz-sets-date-for-party-s-official-campaign-launch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chefs and truck drivers beware: AI is coming for your jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6034c9ce1af347ec8da996e39b29c51b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots aren't replacing everyone, but a quarter of U.S. jobs will be severely disrupted as artificial intelligence accelerates the automation of existing work, according to a new Brookings Institution report. The report, published Thursday, says roughly 36 million Americans hold jobs with "high exposure" to automation — meaning at least 70 percent of their tasks could soon be performed by machines using current technology. Among those most likely to be affected are cooks, waiters and others in food services; short-haul truck drivers; and clerical office workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO PRESIDENTS IN VENEZUELA?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/52bb7f774bc94f439df0606eb96bab4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuelans headed into uncharted political waters Thursday, with the young leader of a newly united and combative opposition claiming to hold the presidency and socialist President Nicolas Maduro digging in for a fight with the Trump administration. Violence flared again Wednesday during big anti-government demonstrations across Venezuela, and at least seven protesters were reported killed in the escalating confrontation with Maduro, who has been increasingly accused of undemocratic behavior by the United States and many other nations in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA BACKS GUAIDO</title>
      <link>https://wctrib.com/news/world/4561031-us-recognizes-venezuelan-opposition-leader-interim-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wctrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela - President Nicolas Maduro on Wednesday faced the gravest challenge to his authority since assuming power in 2013 as the U.S.-backed opposition claimed the legitimate mantle of leadership, and President Donald Trump promptly recognized him as Venezuela's interim president. The dramatic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT 'fake news' filter built into browser...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/449530-newsguard-edge-browser-media-integrated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate and neocon-backed startup NewsGuard is one step closer to its vision of bringing its “unreliable” news rater to every screen after Microsoft makes it an integral part of its Edge mobile browser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$125M Malibu Mansion Hits Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.realtor.com/news/celebrity-real-estate/malibu-mansion-125m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realtor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oceanfront estate in the posh beach community of Malibu is now on the market for $125 million, which, if it holds, could set a sales record for the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NANCY: NO STATE OF UNION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/23/trump-tells-pelosi-he-will-give-state-of-the-union-during-government-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi had said Democrats would block President Donald Trump from giving his State of the Union in the House chamber until the government is open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA RECOGNIZES GUAIDO AS PRESIDENT</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-23/trump-to-recognize-opposition-leader-guaido-as-venezuela-s-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Delays Congressional Testimony;  'Safety Fears'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/23/michael-cohen-postpones-plan-to-testify-at-congress-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen's advisor Lanny Davis cited "ongoing threats" to Cohen's family from Trump and the president's current personal attorney, Rudy Giuliani, in the decision to postpone his Feb. 7 appearance before the House Oversight Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private satellites open uncharted territory in data collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/privately-produced-satellites-open-uncharted-territory-in-data-collection-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company has launched hundreds of small satellites capturing over a million photos of Earth each day for commercial use, offering unimagined possibilities and consequences. Sunday at 7 p.m. ET/PT on CBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated as Latin American nations back Guaido...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-latam/maduro-isolated-as-latin-american-nations-back-venezuela-opposition-leader-idUSKCN1PI01J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Latin American nations recognized Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600-million-year old creature earliest animal ever found...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/mg24132142-700-exclusive-600-million-year-old-blobs-are-earliest-animals-ever-found/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fossils in China suggest that that some of the first animals in existence may have been carnivorous comb jellies similar to some species that still exist today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear gas, vehicles torched, civilians bloodied...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1076882/venezuela-riots-nicolas-maduro-juan-guaido-venezuela-presidential-crisis-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA has plunged into chaos as thousands of people have taken their rage to the streets demanding President Nicolas Maduro to resign while he clings to power and severs diplomatic ties with the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials rescue 80 cockatiels flying inside cramped apartment...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2019/01/23/officials-rescue-83-birds-from-local-1-bedroom-apartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Humane Society helped rescue dozens of birds from their cramped quarters in a San Diego apartment Friday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
