<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi's Grip on Power to Be Tested This Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pelosis-grip-on-power-to-be-tested-this-week-1543147201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi’s hold on her caucus faces its first major test this week, when House Democrats cast initial votes for their leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime San Fran journalist missing in Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Longtime-San-Francisco-journalist-Ray-Taliaferro-13418925.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A longtime Bay Area journalist and radio host last seen near a pizza parlor in Kentucky has been missing for two weeks, according to media reports. Raphael "Ray" Taliaferro, who was a journalist and news anchor for San Francisco's KGO-AM radio and KRON-TV, was last seen near a pizza parlor called "Mellow Mushroom" in Paducah, Kentucky, on Nov. 10, according to media reports. A missing person's flier posted by the Paducah Police Department stated he may have been experiencing "disorientation and signs of dementia," according to a KRON 4 report. Sheriff Ted Holder of the Massac County Sheriff's Office in Illinois told The Chronicle that Taliaferro's wife reported him missing around 9:30 a.m. in Massac County on Nov. 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Big Tech in Big Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/irwin-m-stelzer/facebook-apple-amazon-netflix-and-google-may-get-government-regulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FAANGs (Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix, and Alphabet) have real problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead sea lions washing up on Puget Sound shores -- with bullet holes...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/along-west-seattle-beaches-slain-california-sea-lions-an-unwelcome-sight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, 13 dead California sea lions have been reported, with six confirmed to have been shot, according to Seal Sitters, a volunteer group that responds to reports of stranded or dead marine mammals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS staffers 'furious' Charlie Rose investigation still ongoing...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/24/cbs-staffers-want-answers-after-year-long-charlie-rose-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News staffers are furious that an investigation into sexual harassment at the network is still ongoing, a year after Charlie Rose’s firing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult Leader Plans Sex-Robot Brothel -- With a Twist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/california-cult-leader-uniclone-unicron-plans-sex-robot-brothelwith-a-twist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it happens, the bionic bordello would require that customers obtain consent from the robots. Is that even possible?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to Judge Every Resident Based on Behavior by End of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-21/beijing-to-judge-every-resident-based-on-behavior-by-end-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Plans to Monitor Moods, Movements, and Kids' Home Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/google-reveals-plans-to-monitor-our-moods-our-movements-and-our-childrens-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you think our privacy is compromised now, just wait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions flare after Ukraine claims Russia ship rammed tugboat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9e44a0c2dce40aebfc117e1490c51b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A Russian coast guard vessel rammed a Ukrainian navy tugboat, resulting in damage to the ship's engines and hull, the Ukrainian navy said Sunday The incident took place Sunday as two Ukrainian navy artillery boats and a tugboat were transiting from Odessa on the Black Sea to Mariupol in the Sea of Azov, via the Kerch Strait, a narrow passage between Crimea and the Russian mainland. "Russian coast guard vessels (...) carried out openly aggressive actions against Ukrainian navy ships" during the transit, the Ukrainian navy statement said. It said a Russian coast guard ship damaged the tugboat's engine, hull, side railing and a lifeboat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman rescuing cat gets stuck in tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article222150020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in North Highlands got stuck in a tree and had to be rescued by Sacramento Metro Fire personnel after trying to rescue a cat that was in the tree, according to a tweet from Metro Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas woman dead after trying to get cheap nose job in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/news/2018/11/24/dallas-woman-dead-after-botched-nose-job-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dallas woman who ended up comatose and on life support after a botched nose job in Mexico has died, according to a family member.Laura Avila died...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN LOOMS IN UK PARLIAMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-46334649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than 18 months of negotiations, European leaders agree a deal for the UK to leave the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU BACKS BREXIT DEAL</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7822575/brexit-summit-live-brussels-second-referendum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU leaders have FINALLY given the green light to Theresa May’s Brexit deal this morning at a historic summit in Brussels – and say it now can’t be changed. European Council Presid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUFFING:  Stocks post worst Thanksgiving week decline since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/23/stock-markets-dow-set-for-losses-as-trading-resumes-for-half-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Friday as some of the most popular technology shares were under pressure once again, while a steep drop in oil prices also weighed on equities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-owned broadcaster says it faces intimidation from Poland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6aacb5672cf491e8a2deb55b608bc69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A U.S.-owned broadcaster said it was the target of attempted intimidation by Polish authorities, describing how security agents appeared at the home of a cameraman who went undercover to film neo-Nazis and told him he must appear for questioning on suspicion of propagating fascism. TVN, owned by Discovery, broadcast undercover footage in January that showed members of a Polish neo-Nazi group celebrating Adolf Hitler's birthday in a forest in 2017. It said that on Friday evening, agents with Poland's Internal Security Agency visited the home of the cameraman who had gone undercover, Piotr Wacowski, and gave him the summons to appear in the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan rejects legalizing same-sex unions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a34cf44ef92949d8b31d84090f64c6ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Voters in Taiwan passed a referendum asking that marriage be restricted to one man and one woman, a setback to LGBT couples hoping their island will be the first place in Asia to let same-sex couples share child custody and insurance benefits. The vote on Saturday, organized by Christian groups that make up about 5 percent of Taiwan's population and advocates of the traditional Chinese family structure, goes against a May 2017 Constitutional Court ruling. Justices told legislators then to make same-sex marriage legal within two years, a first for Asia where religion and conservative governments normally keep the bans in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York dog found in Florida 18 months after disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/features/pets/sinatra-a-blue-eyed-husky-from-brooklyn-turns-up-in-seffner-after-18-months-missing-20181123/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog is a family’s link to a teenage daughter who died in a tragic gun accident. The reunion comes thanks to Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clash turns deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/a-border-clash-turns-deadly/article_843b8da1-f071-552b-ae43-8cf40b831f87.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEGUCIGALPA, Honduras — Henry Diaz Reyes and about 1,500 other Central American migrants had just pushed past Guatemalan authorities and onto a border bridge to Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti prime minister promises jobs in answer to unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181124-haiti-prime-minister-promises-jobs-answer-unrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Urges Dems to Unite Ahead of First Leadership Vote...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/11/24/nancy-pelosi-democrats-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi, who’s facing challenges to her possible return as U.S. House Speaker, urged her Democratic colleagues to unite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO FATHERED 200 CHILDREN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/nov/24/sperm-donor-man-who-fathered-200-children</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worried he’d never have a family, Louis became a prolific sperm donor, hoping that his children would one day track him down. And then they did</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Porn's Female Directors Are Putting Hollywood to Shame...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-porns-female-directors-are-putting-hollywood-to-shame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In racking up awards nominations while maintaining creative control over their content, a new crop of female directors are blazing a trail for other women to follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange lawyers blocked from entering Ecuadorian embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/444795-assange-lawyers-refused-entry-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange’s lawyers have been refused entry to the Ecuadorian embassy, WikiLeaks said in a tweet. The news comes amid fears he may soon be kicked out of the embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mummy of 3,000-year-old woman found 'perfectly' preserved inside coffin in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/mummy-3000-year-old-woman-13639066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ancient coffin was one of two discovered in El-Asasef, Luxor, on the bank of the River Nile, by Egyptian authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS BURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1049731/France-protests-paris-riots-police-emmanuel-macron-latest-france-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEAR gas and water cannons have been fired by riot police in France amid a desperate struggle to control violent protests of more than 30,000 residents angry at President Emmanuel Macron over rising fuel prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S BEATINGS! BLACK FRIDAY BRAWLS...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/seasons-beatings-men-brawl-in-walmart-aisle-during-black-friday-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Black Friday, and you know what that means: People trading in their dignity for discounted toys and paper towels. Two men brawled in the aisle of a Walmart on Thanksgiving evening. It’s not clear what the tussle was over, but women jumped in and cursed them out. Watch (NSFW): ﻿ Others wrestled TVs as …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUEL TAX REBELLION</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181124101720-ghrrs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-French police fire tear gas at fuel price protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Deal reached to make asylum seekers wait outside USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-united-states-mexico-asylum-20181124-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has won the support of Mexico's government for a plan to remake U.S. border policy by requiring asylum seekers to wait in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Deal reached to make asylum seekers wait outside USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/deal-with-mexico-paves-way-for-asylum-overhaul-at-us-border/2018/11/24/87b9570a-ef74-11e8-9236-bb94154151d2_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump administration has won support of leftist president-elect Andrés Manuel López Obrador, who takes office Dec. 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for civil war...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d3033b920af449b594e66b51890b517b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French police fired tear gas and water cannons to disperse violent demonstrators in Paris on Saturday, as thousands gathered in the capital and beyond and staged road blockades to vent anger against rising fuel taxes. Thousands of police were deployed nationwide to contain the eighth day of deadly demonstrations that started as protests against tax but morphed into a rebuke of President Emmanuel Macron and the perceived elitism of France's ruling class. Two people have been killed since Nov. 17 in protest-related tragedies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sex doll spa...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/744254/sex-doll-spa-galmato-haven-repairs-realdoll-reggie-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREISAND: If only we could be the way we were...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6410531/Barbra-Streisand-76-felt-compelled-write-album-protest-songs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barbra Streisand mourned the death of her beloved curly-haired Coton de Tulear Samantha 18 months ago ‘as if it were a child’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez, freshmen look to shape party...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ocasio-Cortez-Democratic-freshmen-look-to-shape-13418215.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has rapidly emerged as the de facto leader of a historic class of House Democrats whose diversity and ties to the progressive left will shape the party as it targets President Donald Trump and works to clarify its message ahead of the 2020 elections. Incoming members have quickly exerted their influence on Capitol Hill since the midterm elections, with progressives bolstering Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi's, D-Calif., bid for speaker by declining to endorse an opposition movement led by centrist Democrats. Yet while Rep.-elect Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Every human spawned from single couple 200,000 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6424407/Every-person-spawned-single-pair-adults-living-200-000-years-ago-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from the Rockefeller University and the University of Basel surveyed genetic 'bar codes' of five million animals and deduced that we sprang from a single pair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil records worst annual deforestation for decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/24/brazil-records-worst-annual-deforestation-for-a-decade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 8,000sq kms lost in the year to July amid alarm new president Jair Bolsonaro will make situation worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man covered in face tattoos arrested 54th TIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6424339/Cincinnati-man-charged-kidnapping-woman-arrested-53-times-violent-offenses.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Mann, 35, of Cincinnati wanted a payout of $100 before allowing a woman to go free, according to prosecutors, adding a 54th arrest to his lengthy rap sheet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Warns Brexit Plan Akin to Titanic Heading Toward Doom...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/johnson-warns-brexit-plan-akin-to-titanic-heading-toward-doom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Warns Brexit Plan Akin to Titanic Heading Toward Doom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$86,000 Reward For Snitching On Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-23/china-offers-86000-reward-snitching-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSISSIPPI RUNOFF: Dems target another Senate seat in Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/417930-dems-target-another-senate-seat-in-deep-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are aggressively targeting another Senate seat in the Deep South in next Tuesday’s runoff election after scoring a major win in Alabama last year, as embattled Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith (R) stumbles in deep-red Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes prefer to dine with friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.myscience.org/news/wire/just_like_us_giraffes_prefer_to_dine_with_friends-2018-bristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.myscience.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence on Champs Elysees...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/24/french-gilets-jaunes-protests-turn-violent-on-the-streets-of-paris </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clashes broke out between crowds and police on the Champs Élysées in the second weekend of demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of People Find Texting Daily Source Of Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-texting-source-daily-stress-third-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its earliest days, texting was a simple way to shoot a short message to someone in a jiff. But with photos, videos, emojis, gifs, and countless other bells and whistles causing so many of us to keep our heads buried in our devices constantly, text messaging has become a way of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Saudi prince says CIA cannot be trusted on Khashoggi conclusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi/senior-saudi-prince-says-cia-cannot-be-trusted-on-khashoggi-conclusion-idUSKCN1NT0G5 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Saudi prince cast doubt upon the reported CIA finding that Saudi Crown ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Macron must resign'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/tear-gas-fired-at-furious-protesters-in-france-11561900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a second week of demonstrations, thousands are protesting against the steep rise in diesel prices brought in by the president.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
