<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Maya ritual cave 'untouched' for 1,000 years stuns archaeologists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/culture/2019/03/maya-ritual-balamku-cave-stuns-archaeologists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exploration of Balamku (Cave of the Jaguar God) reveals ancient religious practices—and may hold clues to the rise and fall of the Maya empire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: BUGATTI unveils most expensive new car ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/bugatti-unveils-the-most-expensive-new-car-ever-built.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only one version has been made and is already sold to a mystery owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Where pay most, least taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/2019/03/05/taxes-2019-where-income-sales-and-property-tax-highest-us/39124869/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the checkout counter to the 1040 form due every April, what Americans end up paying in taxes depends largely on where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dressed up, ready for fun: New Orleans celebrates Mardi Gras...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7761daf5827b44d5a08ce994637c8820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — The streets of New Orleans will be filled Tuesday with excited kids catching beads from atop ladders, revelers in fancy costumes walking through the French Quarter and Mardi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Who Couldn't Beat Climate Debate Now Seek to Join It...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/republicans-couldn-apos-t-beat-090000456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s just not worth the fight anymore,” Shimkus said in an interview when asked about his changing stance on climate change. Shimkus is among a number of Republicans who -- after years of sowing doubt about climate change or ignoring it altogether -- are scrambling to confront the science they once</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Trump White House lawyer calls Mueller 'hero'; Probe no witch hunt...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-white-house-lawyer-calls-mueller-american-hero/story?id=61455661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Congressional investigations into the White House, Ty Cobb said, "It's never gonna be over."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths from alcohol, drugs, suicide hit new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/03/05/suicide-alcohol-drug-deaths-centers-disease-control-well-being-trust/3033124002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths from alcohol, drugs and suicideÂ in 2017 hitÂ theÂ highest level since federal data collection started in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This man fasts 17 to 24 hours a day. It's changed his life...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/2019/03/04/weight-loss-approach-uses-intermittent-fasting-app-inspiration/2978617002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life Fasting Tracker app from LifeOmic helps users practice intermittent fasting, which advocates say helps with weight loss and increased wellness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Weighs Ending Phone Surveillance Program Exposed by Snowden...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nsa-weighs-ending-phone-surveillance-program-exposed-by-snowden-11551752806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency is considering ending a once-secret surveillance program that annually collects hundreds of millions of telephone call records, including those belonging to Americans, because it lacks operational value, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRODIGY lead singer found dead in home...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8561534/prodigy-keith-flint-suicide-marriage-split-home-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRODIGY star Keith Flint killed himself days after putting his beloved home up for sale — following a devastating split from his wife. The rave legend, 49, died at the Essex farmhouse he shared wit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron blasts Brexit as cause of Europe's biggest crisis since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6771177/Emmanuel-Macron-calls-Brexit-irresponsible-lie.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his most ferocious attack on Brexit to date, the French President said Britain's withdrawal was peddled by 'anger mongers and fake news' and 'offers nothing'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Calls for Online Jihad...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-supporters-around-the-world-rally-for-steep-escalation-in-online-jihad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jihadists urged to hit sites including Reddit, LinkedIn, Pinterest, Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Vine, and Snapchat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OPENS OBSTRUCTION PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1c319d8e4c943a482d03195d069e92a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats launched a sweeping new probe of President Donald Trump on Monday, an aggressive investigation that threatens to shadow the president through the 2020 election season...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of autosexual: People attracted to selves...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/shortcuts/2019/mar/04/age-of-the-autosexual-the-people-sexually-attracted-to-themselves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you turned on when you look in the mirror, and enjoy nothing more than a steamy night at home alone? You could be an autosexual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed keeps GDP growth view at 0.3%...</title>
      <link>https://www.streetinsider.com/Fed/Atlanta+Fed+leaves+U.S.+first+quarter+GDP+growth+view+at+0.3+percent/15211588.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.streetinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - The U.S. economy is growing at a 0.3 percent annualized rate in the first quarter, based on data on domestic construction spending in December released on Monday, the Atlanta Federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors announce second person 'cured' of HIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/03/04/second-person-effectively-cured-of-hiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time, doctors appear to have put HIV into “sustained remission” with a stem cell transplant — effectively curing the recipient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT's latest dog-like robot can do backflips on command...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/MIT-s-latest-dog-like-robot-can-do-backflips-on-13661951.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They can already open doors, traverse steep flights of stairs, run at high speed and unload your dishwasher. Now, for the first time ever, a four-legged robot has performed a physical feat that evades all but the most athletic among us: a backflip. The acrobatics arrive courtesy of Massachusetts Institute of Technology, where researchers have unveiled a springy, 20-pound robot that's also capable of walking either right-side up or upside down. The vaguely canine-like machine - dubbed "Mini Cheetah" - is also able to trot over uneven terrain about twice as fast as an average person's walking speed, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Patient Gives Hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-aids-cure/london-hiv-patient-becomes-worlds-second-aids-cure-hope-idUSKCN1QL2C0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An HIV-positive man in Britain has become the second known adult worldwide to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic freeze envelops lower 48...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/04/historic-cold-envelops-most-of-the-lower-48/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When this freakish cold spell is done, several hundred new record low maximum and record low temperatures will have fallen. In the last seven days alone, cold records are outpacing warm by about fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal crossings set to surge; 70,000 detained last month...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/After-cold-busy-month-at-border-illegal-13661974.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas - In a dusty lot along the U.S.-Mexico border fence, a single Border Patrol agent was stuck with few options and falling temperatures. A group of 64 parents and children had waded through a shallow bend in the Rio Grande to turn themselves in to the agent on the U.S. side. He radioed for a van driver, but there were none available. By 2 a.m., the temperature was 44 degrees. The agent handed out plastic space blankets. The group would have to wait. Mothers and fathers swaddled their families in the silvery, crinkling sheets and clustered with them on the ground, shushing the children. They shivered in the cold wind, and the sound of crying carried on, like a broken alarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on Trudeau as second minister resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190305-canada-trudeau-minister-philpott-resigns-snc-lavalin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a serious blow to Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, a second member of his Cabinet resigned on Monday, saying she had lost confidence in how the government had dealt with an escalating political scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Republicans make 'socialism' the bogeyman of 2020, as Democrats bristle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/03/04/trump-gop-make-socialism-bogeyman-2020-democrats-bristle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democrats bristle, but Republicans have successfully framed the 2020 election as a struggle against socialism - an ideology that not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fountain of youth? Scientists switch-off gene to DOUBLE lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/763449/immortality-science-genetics-roundworm-university-east-anglia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone post may violate gag?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6770935/Mueller-tells-judge-Framed-Roger-Stone-Instagram-pic-violate-gag-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new introduction to a re-issue of Stone's 2017 book, he writes: 'Mr. Mueller may frame me for some bogus charge in order to silence me or induce me to testify against the president.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Cameras Spot Shoplifters BEFORE Steal?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/the-ai-cameras-that-can-spot-shoplifters-even-before-they-steal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AI Cameras That Can Spot Shoplifters Even Before They Steal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMPLOYEES UNCOVER ONGOING CENSORED SEARCH WORK...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/03/04/google-ongoing-project-dragonfly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of employees said Google made hundreds of changes to smartphone apps for the controversial project, thought to be defunct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude 'Mona Lisa' may be by Leonardo, say experts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nude-mona-lisa-may-leonardo-experts-183816399.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nude drawing that bears a striking resemblance to the "Mona Lisa" was done in Leonardo da Vinci's studio and may be the work of the master himself, a French museum said Monday. Experts at the Louvre in Paris, where the world's biggest collection of Leonardo's work is held, have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers posing as immigration officials target victims for money and personal info...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/scammers-posing-law-enforcement-immigration-officials-steal-personal/story?id=61457495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scammers posing as immigration officials have targeted and attempted to extort victims for personal information and money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNT ME OUT</title>
      <link>http://westchester.news12.com/story/40067049/im-not-running-hillary-clinton-rules-out-2020-bid-for-first-time-on-camera-in-exclusive-interview-with-news-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;westchester.news12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton ruled out a 2020 presidential run for the first time on camera in an exclusive interview with News 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Teen spiked stepdad's drinks with cattle tranquilizer...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/wisconsin-tranquilizer-teen-872954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 4--A Wisconsin teenager accused of injecting cattle tranquilizer in his stepfather’s energy drinks thought his actions were “funny” and would not harm the victim, according to police who arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axelrod Warns Doc Demand Looks Like 'Witch Hunt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/04/david-axelrod-calls-out-democrats-for-making-investigations-look-like-witch-hunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axelrod criticized House Democrats on Monday for their blanket demand for documents, warning it could play into accusations of a witch hunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastel handles, pink holsters: Women storm into gun sales...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/sports/outdoors/article_e56948ea-3b5c-11e9-b019-d3a05a53fb5f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Women, I think, get a sense of accomplishment and a skill level they didn't used to have. There is a sense of invincibility in a way," said Glenda Craddock. "And</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH GIANT DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/3/4/18250285/google-dragonfly-censored-search-engine-code-dead-employees-doubt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees monitored Google’s code to see if the censored search engine is still being worked on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gargantuan Space Bubbles Spitting Cosmic Rays at Earth?</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64900-space-bubbles-jiggle-through-cosmos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two huge bubbles, thousands of light-years across, have been discovered jiggling near the center of a distant galaxy. They could be spitting all over Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Immortality Elixir' Uncovered in 2,000-Year-Old Tomb...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elixir-of-immortality-uncovered-in-2-000-year-old-chi-1833038438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A yellowish liquid found in a bronze pot dating back some 2,000 years is not wine, as Chinese archaeologists initially thought. It’s actually an “elixir of immortality” concocted during ancient times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-dollar donors fueled Kamala rise, now double-edged sword...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article226975319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defined Cool...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/fien-print/critics-notebook-luke-perry-defined-coolness-a-generation-tv-watchers-1192092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The '90210' star was indelibly hip and heart-throbby as Dylan McKay, but also gained gravitas in the later stages of his career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Top staffer ran $1M slush fund, diverted campaign cash to own companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/politics/ocasio-cortezs-chief-of-staff-ran-1m-slush-fund-by-diverting-campaign-cash-to-his-own-companies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two political action committees founded by Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez’s top aide funneled over $1 million in political donations into two of his own private companies, according to a complaint filed with the Federal Election Commission on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Still Using Uranium-Enrichment Facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/north-korea-still-using-uranium-enrichment-facility-u-n-agency-says-11551728932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea is still using a uranium-enrichment facility at the heart of last week’s summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, the United Nations atomic agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 minute warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/03/04/alabama-tornado-aftermath-workers-search-missing/3053092002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First responders in Alabama huntedÂ for survivors Monday after a devastating tornado killed at least 23 people, smashed homes and toppled power lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest accused of child sex abuse flees country...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Oakland-priest-accused-of-sexual-abusing-child-13661155.php?t=90dc638179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Father Alex Castillo was placed on administrative leave Jan. 31 by the Catholic diocese, which said it received an allegation of inappropriate behavior. Alameda County prosecutors are looking at the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Homicides in NYC spike 50% last month...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-homicides-surge-february-nypd-20190304-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The increase was driven by a 50% spike in the month of February — with 24 homicides last month compared to 16 in February 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez mother flees New York for low-tax Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6748793/Alexandria-Ocasio-Cortezs-mother-tells-hopes-daughter-marries-longtime-boyfriend.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's mother Blanca now lives in Florida and her Trump-supporting neighbors don't know the Democrat star is her daughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/alabama-tornadoes-march-2019/h_9b1dc6af7252f4e2913529d423511137</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN shot this drone footage of the destruction left after tornadoes swept through parts of Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Republicans to vote against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/432463-mcconnell-senate-will-pass-resolution-blocking-trumps-emergency-declaration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) on Monday said that he expects a resolution blocking President Trump's emergency declaration to pass the Senate, but he does not believe lawmakers will be able to override a veto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Investigate Pentagon Ties To AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/reporters-notebook-jason-miller/2019/03/fbi-dod-ig-conducting-preliminary-investigation-into-jedi-procurements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOZENS MISSING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2755bb192bb4aa0b5541ebe853fc7ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEAUREGARD, Ala. (AP) — Rescue crews using dogs and drones searched for victims amid splintered lumber and twisted metal Monday after the deadliest U.S. tornado in nearly six years ripped through...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido returns to Venezuela despite arrest threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190304-venezuela-opposition-leader-guaido-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's opposition leader Juan Guaido defied the threat of arrest to return home on Monday, arriving at Caracas international airport where he was met by cheering supporters, television footage showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Underpaying Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/04/google-found-its-underpaying-some-men-as-it-studies-wage-equity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new internal analysis at Google found that some male software engineers were under-compensated compared to their peers doing similar work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibles found unscathed after church fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/west-virginia-fire-freedom-ministries-church-bibles-cross-untouched/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Though odds were against us, God was not," the volunteer fire department says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students Across US Now Majoring In Marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/03/04/its-a-serious-degree-students-across-us-now-majoring-in-marijuana-at-colleges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expected boom in cannabis-related jobs has colleges responding with a range of offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters gather to protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f60b33eaf80c462382f2077cafe8827f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — A defiant Juan Guaido returned home to Venezuela on Monday despite concerns the opposition leader might be detained and urged supporters at a rally to intensify their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg's recovery prescription: Plenty of opinions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3de2762a73b45848befd231169ee4af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Now we know what Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was doing as she recuperated from lung cancer surgery: churning out opinions for the court at a faster clip than any of her younger...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like bomb went off'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/tornadoes-alabama-kill-23-figure-officials-expect-rise/story?id=61448219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 23 were killed by tornadoes in Lee County, about 60 miles northeast of Montgomery, Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Underpaying Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/04/technology/google-gender-pay-gap.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a recent study, the company gave raises to thousands of men after determining they were earning less than women in similar jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS HOAX</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6770169/Its-political-hoax-Trump-blasts-Democrats-abuse-power-probe-81-document-requests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'You know the beautiful thing?' Trump asked as he joshed with North Dakota State University football players. 'No collusion. It’s all a hoax. ... You’re going to learn about that as you grow older,'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: New Powerful Flu Strain On Rise...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/03/01/a-new-more-powerful-strain-of-flu-has-just-hit-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado is not done yet. Hope that the flu season is winding down is gone now that a new, deadlier strain has struck our state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Suspends Nuclear Missile Treaty With USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russia-withdraws-from-nuclear-missile-treaty-11551713037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin formally ordered a suspension of Russia’s obligations under a Cold War-era nuclear treaty with the U.S., heightening the threat of a new arms race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOLVO imposes speed limit on cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/03/04/volvo-speed-limit/3053169002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volvo plans to impose a speed limit of about 112 miles per hour on all of its vehicles beginning in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Perry Dead at 52...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/03/04/luke-perry-dead-dies-stroke-beverly-hills-90210-riverdale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former "Beverly Hills, 90210" teen heartthrob has passed away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tightens embargo on Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69cf0d1c83d74456be4c5779d49424c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — The Trump administration announced Monday that it is symbolically tightening the six-decade trade embargo on Cuba by allowing lawsuits against Cuban companies using properties...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deploys advanced anti-missile system for first time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e434a488591451aba197feab8c84642</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — The U.S. has deployed a highly advanced missile defense system in Israel for the first time, the American and Israeli militaries announced Monday, reflecting their shared concerns...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE DID IT AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/03/ilhan-omar-blasted-over-latest-anti-semitic-tweet-about-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Ilhan Omar is catching flak on Twitter yet again for suggesting that US politicians were being forced to “pledge allegiance” to Israel. “It’s ‘Antisemitic Weekends with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi Will Never Go Quietly...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-bibi-netanyahu-never-quietly-070020832.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin is also a fan. After meeting Bibi in Moscow, just a day before the Israeli Attorney General Avichai Mandelblit released his legal bombshell, Putin praised the fine bilateral relationship that has flourished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OPENS OBSTRUCTION PROBE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41ea4c23629d4aa3a2a66ccde545c0f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on a House panel's expanding investigations of President Donald Trump (all times local): 11:30 a.m. The House Judiciary Committee is launching a sweeping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81 SUBPOENAS FLY</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190304161931-vbruj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-CONGRESS (PIX):US House panel issues 81 document requests in Trump obstruction probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>-13&amp;#176; in Minneapolis!</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/03/03/record-snowfall-february-record-temps-march/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although a record-setting February is behind us, March is on track to set some records of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Coldest Early March  In 60 Years...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/03/03/denver-weather-near-record-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many places on the northeast plains fell below zero Sunday morning and will be as cold if not colder tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send message: Impeachment is on...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-house-dems-send-message-impeachment-is-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the House Judiciary Committee says there is no doubt President Trump has obstructed justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Under Fire After Making Phone Numbers Searchable...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90314763/now-facebook-is-allowing-anyone-to-look-you-up-using-your-security-phone-number</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media Big Brother continues to do whatever it wants with your data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: WWF Funds Guards Who Torture, Kill People...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/tomwarren/wwf-world-wide-fund-nature-parks-torture-death </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beloved animal charity with the cuddly panda logo funds vicious paramilitary forces to fight poaching. A BuzzFeed News investigation reveals the hidden human cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary's Southern Accent Returns in Selma...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-hillary-affects-southern-accent-selma-when-spirit-breathed-t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former First Lady was speaking at a voting rights event in Selma, Ala.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Sellers' Doctored Photos Challenge Buyers' Bots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/home-sellers-doctored-photos-challenge-buyers-bots-11551708001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A computer-versus-computer showdown is brewing in the residential property market, pitting investors’ house-hunting algorithms against sellers’ virtual listing photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs Expected in Major WARNERMEDIA Overhaul...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-t-shakes-up-warner-media-unit-11551708372 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T started reorganizing its WarnerMedia unit by combining its disparate networks and entertainment businesses, an overhaul that is expected to lead to cost-cutting and layoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis announces opening of Secret Archives on 'Hitler's Pope'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/vatican-to-open-archives-on-wwii-era-pope-accused-of-silence-on-holocaust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secret documents on Pius XII, who served during WWII and its aftermath, could shed light on leader widely criticized by Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STARBUCKS on steroids': America's new weed cafes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/mar/03/america-weed-cafes-smoking-recreational-marijuana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational marijuana is legal in Canada and parts of the US, but for the most part it’s not allowed in public spaces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: President Tried to Block AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER to Punish CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-reportedly-tried-to-have-doj-block-att-time-warner-merger-to-punish-cnn-for-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey murder rampage through village leaves two dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/763306/monkey-murder-india-villages-rampage-primate-killings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,500 turtles found inside luggage...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/over-1500-turtles-found-inside-luggage-in-philippines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — Philippine authorities said Monday that they found more than 1,500 live exotic turtles stuffed inside luggage at Manila's airport. The various types of turtles were found Sunday inside four pieces of left-behind luggage of a Filipino...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia wants to unplug. Is that even possible?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/europe/la-fg-russia-internet-20190304-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia wants to tighten its control over the internet by passing a law to allow the Kremlin to temporarily pull the plug whenever it wants. The bill has so far passed in the Russian parliament's first reading, but critics of the proposed law say Russia lacks the technical abilities to pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Nazi salutes around makeshift swastika, Newport Beach students spark outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-nazi-party-newport-beach-20190303-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images of Newport Beach students forming a Nazi salute around a makeshift swastika sparked outrage and prompted an investigation by school officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of 'hood CNN' pioneer exposes gangland reporting risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/death-of-hood-cnn-pioneer-exposes-gangland-reporting-risks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shawn Cotton no longer drives his $55,000, bright pink Corvette to work because he's afraid it could get him killed like his friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Plans 5% Digital Tax as Govts Chase Internet Giants...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/france-plans-5-digital-tax-as-governments-chase-internet-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France Plans 5% Digital Tax as Governments Chase Internet Giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain 'Smart Chip' To Give Humans Super-Intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/03/04/northwestern-neuroscientist-researching-brain-chips-to-make-people-superintelligent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if you could make money, or type something, just by thinking about it? It sounds like science fiction, but it might be close to reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton has advice -- but few candidates seeking it...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/177df08931aa47a9b462ee771875bf66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 20 years after he left the White House, Bill Clinton is still sought after for advice by some Democrats running for president. But the names on his dance card in recent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: RED EVERYWHERE...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/03/socialism-and-young-socialists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s AOC’s calling card, Trump’s latest rhetorical bludgeon, and a new way to date in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENPEACE Co-Founder Rips...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-03/greenpeace-co-founder-rips-pompous-little-twit-ocasio-cortez-garden-variety</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRODIGY lead singer found dead in home...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8555072/prodigy-keith-flint-dead-suicide-firestarter/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Prodigy star Keith Flint has been found dead in a suspected suicide at his home, aged 49. The iconic singer, from Essex, was discovered at around 8am this morning after police and paramedics we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel successor slammed as intersex toilet joke falls flat...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190304-merkel-successor-slammed-intersex-toilet-joke-falls-flat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel successor slammed as intersex toilet joke falls flat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smaller Countries Becoming Healthiest...</title>
      <link>https://www.fin24.com/Economy/smaller-countries-are-becoming-the-healthiest-in-global-surveys-but-not-sa-20190304</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fin24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thereâ€™s more to life than money, and economists know it. The Global Wellness Index ranked many smaller countries as far healthier - but in a tighter ranking of G20 nations combined with the 20 most populous countries on the planet, SA came dead last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Traitor' Is New 'Infidel' as Nationalism Grips Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/-traitor-is-the-new-infidel-as-nationalism-grips-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabiaâ€™s undergoing an aggressive nationalist rebranding, downplaying an austere religious doctrine associated abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican rebellion?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/432405-trump-on-brink-of-gop-rebellion-over-emergency-declaration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is facing a potential revolt among Senate Republicans over his decision to declare a national emergency to construct the U.S.-Mexico border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Socialism's Millenial fans don't even know what is...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/03/socialisms-millennial-fans-dont-even-know-what-it-is/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who isn’t a socialist at 20 has no heart, but anyone who isn’t a conservative by 40 has no brain: That old epigram is certainly playing out in today’s Democratic Party. Millennials — ignoran…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panhandler accused of killing woman. But family staged attack, police say...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/03/03/jacquelyn-smith-good-samaritan-killing-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keith Smith, Jacquelyn's husband, and Valeria Smith, her stepdaughter, were arrested by Texas state police in Harlingen, near the Mexican border while trying to leave the country, acting Baltimore police commissioner said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
