<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Buck takes shelter inside church on hunting season's 1st day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-lifestyle-michigan-animals-hunting-02bea9f79d1868f2af7b221610d752f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STURGIS, Mich. (AP) — A 10-point buck sought sanctuary inside a southern Michigan church on opening day of the state's firearm deer hunting season. Pastors at Grace Sturgis encountered the buck inside the church's auditorium on Monday before it leapt through a window and back into the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL IT EVER END!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211116201618-9nvu1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FAUCI (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Fauci says boosters for all key to U.S. reaching COVID-19 endemic level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX TV STAR CANNED FOR NOT GETTING JAB...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/rockmond-dunbar-exits-911-covid-vaccine-mandate-medical-religious-exemptions-1234874927/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOILER ALERT: The story includes details about the Nov. 15 episode of Fox’s 9-1-1. EXCLUSIVE: Original 9-1-1 cast member Rockmond Dunbar is leaving the hit Fox drama series after more than f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIPCHAT hacked: Cam site security breach exposes 65 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4078374/stripchat-hacked-security-breach-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ADULT cam site security breach has caused the data of millions of users and models to be exposed. StripChat, which is one of the internet’s top five adult cam sites, suffered the breach ea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates causing global shortage 'crisis', disrupting supply chains...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4075998/pirates-global-shortage-crisis-criminals-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIRATES and drug cartels could cause global shortages – as a “crisis” begins to unfold, experts have warned. The pandemic, coupled with driver shortages, are already causing probl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57% of Detroit public school students chronically absent
...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/education/2021/11/16/detroit-public-schools-students-absent/6390112001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of Detroit Public Schools students are considered chronically absent this school year from district schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. spies look to future:  China...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/16/1051170999/as-u-s-spies-look-to-the-future-one-target-stands-out-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When current and former U.S. intelligence officials gathered at a conference in Sea Island, Ga., there was a clear message — a pivot to China is already underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs, cannon fire, 184-mph winds: Life weird atop CA volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/ufos-cannon-fire-and-184-mph-winds-life-gets-weird-atop-this-california-volcano/ar-AAQLEAt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR labels first Asian-American Boston mayor a 'disappointment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/npr-slammed-disappointment-boston-asian-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR took heat Tuesday after its report that Asian American Michelle Wu’s election win in Boston was considered a "disappointment" to some for being chosen over Black candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gas prices soar to record highs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-gas-prices-soar-record-130054189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soaring gas prices are one more challenge for residents heading into the second holiday season of the pandemic, with supply chain issues and inflation too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch plan to drop 'corona pass' for unvaccinated faces political push back...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211116193846-plu67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Dutch plan to drop 'corona pass' for unvaccinated faces political push back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercers Throw Under Bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mercers-throw-steve-bannon-under-the-bus-in-election-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the FEC started looking into Cambridge Analytica’s campaign work in 2016, a lawyer for billionaire backer Rebekah Mercer blamed Steve Bannon for any potential misdeeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs, cannon fire, 184-mph winds: Life weird atop CA volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2021-11-16/he-lives-alone-atop-a-california-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vincent Valencia lives alone at the summit of Mammoth Mountain — a frozen world that is lashed regularly by California's ugliest weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: NO MATTER AGE, 2 SHOTS DON'T LAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/no-matter-how-old-you-are-two-shots-of-pfizer-vaccine-dont-last-study-685141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People’s ages had no effect on the vaccine’s waning, meaning that the vaccine waned for everyone and not just older people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Giving Millions of Photos To Facial Recognition Researchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgdxqd/south-korea-is-selling-millions-of-photos-to-facial-recognition-researchers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers to the country are having their biometric data given to private companies under a program recently uncovered by civil rights advocates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag queens being swatted while streaming on TWITCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/drag-queens-are-swatted-streaming-twitch-want-stop-rcna5631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, six members of the streaming group Stream Queens, a collective of drag queens who stream mostly horror video games on Twitch, have been swatted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother Says Alec 'Target' Because Of His Political Views...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/alec-baldwins-brother-daniel-has-strong-words-about-rust-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin's brother Daniel Baldwin spoke out about the Rust shooting on Monday, complaining [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIMES SQ BACK OPEN FOR NEW YEAR'S -- WITH JAB PROOF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-arts-and-entertainment-new-york-80d211eaa55312ebfe10dcfd479d5fbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Crowds will once again fill New York's Times Square this New Year's Eve, with proof of COVID-19 vaccination required for revelers who want to watch the ball drop in person, Mayor Bill de Blasio announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Russia admits destroying satellite with space missile strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/russia-admits-destroying-satellite-with-space-missile-strike/ar-AAQLmb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Tuesday admitted to destroying one of its satellites during a missile test but rejected US accusations that it had endangered the International Space Station. Last year, Britain and the US accused Russia of testing a "nesting doll" satellite that opened up and released a smaller craft to stalk an American satellite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gas prices soar to record highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-11-15/california-gas-prices-soar-to-record-highs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of a gallon of gasoline in California has climbed to a record $4.682. Several counties, including L.A., neared record highs as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos hits back at critics for saying Earth before space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/jeff-bezos-hits-back-critics-25471455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Blue Origin founder has said billionaires need to "do both" when it comes to fixing problems on Earth and going to space, and recounted William Shatner's reaction to landing back on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK accused of continuing to surveil teens...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2021/11/16/facebook-accused-of-still-targeting-teens-with-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The adtech giant formerly known as Facebook is still tracking teens for ad targeting on its social media platforms, according to new research by Fairplay, Global Action Plan and Reset Australia — apparently contradicting Facebook’s announcement this summer when the tech giant claimed it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew $2M Loan Repaid by Banker, Triggering Calls for Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/lifestyle/celebs/prince-andrew-s-2m-loan-repaid-by-banker-triggering-calls-for-investigation/ar-AAQLh1P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second HIV patient may have been 'naturally' cured, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/16/health/hiv-patient-cured-intl-scli-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they have found a second patient whose body seemingly had rid itself of the human immunodeficiency virus (HIV) that causes AIDS -- supporting hope that it may be possible someday to find a way to cure more people of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Inflation Spoils Holidays for Struggling Families...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/inflation-set-to-spoil-holidays-for-struggling-u-s-families</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation Set to Spoil Holidays for Struggling U.S. Families</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children sick after receiving wrong dose in CA...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/kids-given-wrong-dose-of-covid-vaccine-sutter-health-for-california-get-adult-pfizer-shot/11242363/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They absolutely failed my children": One mother says she didn't hear from the Northern California clinic for 10 hours, at which point her 11-year-old had already fallen down twice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK TO DEMAND 3 SHOTS FOR COVID PASSES!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/nov/15/no-10-plans-booster-jab-requirement-for-people-to-obtain-covid-pass</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Currently, people only need to have had two shots to qualify as being fully vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANCEL CULTURE:  Wyoming GOP votes to no longer recognize Rep. Cheney as Republican...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/state-and-regional/govt-and-politics/wyoming-gop-votes-to-no-longer-recognize-rep-cheney-as-a-republican/article_66c3a62d-7207-54c7-b277-183817c0563c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wyoming Republican leaders voted this weekend to no longer recognize Rep. Liz Cheney as a member of their party following her repeated criticisms of former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER, BIONTECH, MODERNA MAKING $1,000 PROFIT EVERY SECOND...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-11-pfizer-biontech-moderna-profit-analysis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer, BioNTech and Moderna are making combined profits of $65,000 every minute from their highly successful COVID-19 vaccines while the world's poorest countries remain largely unvaccinated, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury Begins Deliberations at Rittenhouse Murder Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2021-11-16/jury-to-begin-deliberations-at-kyle-rittenhouse-murder-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors will begin deliberating Tuesday at Kyle Rittenhouse's murder trial after two weeks of testimony in which they were given starkly different portrayals of his actions the night he shot three men on the streets of Kenosha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Sierra Nevada red foxes survive massive Dixie fire that burned habitat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/rare-sierra-nevada-red-foxes-survive-massive-dixie-fire-that-burned-habitat/ar-AAQILJE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans broadly support upholding Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/americans-broadly-support-supreme-court-upholding-roe-v-wade-and-oppose-texas-abortion-law-post-abc-poll-finds/ar-AAQLhCg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second HIV patient may have been 'naturally' cured, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/healthcare/581713-second-hiv-patient-may-have-been-naturally-cured-scientists-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman from Argentina is believed to be the second known person whose body naturally eliminated the human immunodeficiency virus (HIV) without treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida woman who sued for ivermectin dies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-lawsuits-florida-2fe950228fab741789f32fa943776e0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH GARDENS, Fla (AP) — A Florida teacher hospitalized with COVID-19 has died after her husband unsuccessfully sued to force doctors to treat her with ivermectin, a drug popular among some skeptics of accepted coronavirus treatments despite a lack of studies proving its effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On ONLYFANS and other sites, adult content creators fear new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2021/11/16/onlyfans-adult-content-creators-mastercard-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the job losses of the pandemic, thousands signed up to produce adult content for sites. Now some adult performers say their income is threatened by new regulations intended to fight child sexual abuse and sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt dramatically underestimated job growth this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-government-dramatically-underestimated-job-growth-this-summer/ar-AAQLyDI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Island in Indonesia Become New Frontier in Space Race?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/16/will-an-island-in-indonesia-become-a-new-frontier-in-the-space-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIAK, Indonesia — For 15 generations, members of the Abrauw clan have lived much like their ancestors. They farm with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sudden $400 Billion Crypto Price Rout Sees Bitcoin Crash; Others Plummet...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2021/11/16/sudden-400-billion-crypto-price-rout-sees-bitcoin-crash-under-60000-as-ethereum-bnb-solana-cardano-and-xrp-plummet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sudden crypto price crash has wiped around $400 billion from the combined crypto market, which last week touched a record high of around $3 trillion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video appears to show Iranian helicopter's 'unsafe' maneuver near U.S. warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iran-helicopter-uss-essex-unsafe-maneuver-pentagon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video published by Iranian media appeared to show the helicopter flying low and coming close to the USS Essex, an amphibious assault ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious neurological illness haunts Canadian Atlantic region...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/nov/16/neurological-illness-haunts-remote-canadian-region</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cases have prompted a row between health officials who deny the sicknesses form a true ‘cluster’ and medical experts looking for a link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Pompeo, Mnuchin Considered Invoking 25th Amendment to Remove Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/just-in-pompeo-and-mnuchin-considered-invoking-25th-amendment-to-remove-trump-after-capitol-riot-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stunning passage from Jon Karl's new book reveals that two of former President Donald Trump's most prominent allies considered removing him from office in the wake of the Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail sales jump 1.7%, but high prices play role...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/coming-up-u-s-retail-sales-11637068497</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales at U.S. retailers such as Wal-Mart and Amazon rose in October at the fastest pace in seven months in another strong show for the economy, but high...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY sanitation workers suspended amid probe into fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/581695-new-york-sanitation-workers-suspended-amid-probe-into-fake-vaccine-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of several dozen sanitation workers in New York City has been suspended without pay as officials investigate whether the employees used counterfeit vaccine cards in order to circumvent the city's vaccine mandate,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Biomarker Predicts Diabetes 19 Years Before Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/diabetes-marker-predicts-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High follistatin levels appear to be predictive of type 2 diabetes onset regardless of the patient's age, diet, and level of physical activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters display swastika, Star of David outside Jewish politician's office to oppose vax rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/protesters-display-swastika-star-of-david-outside-jewish-politician-e2-80-99s-office-to-oppose-vaccine-rules/ar-AAQLeif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland Uses Water Cannons, Tear Gas as Tensions Rise at Belarus Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59302919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland's defence ministry says migrants were throwing stones and trying to destroy a border fence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MN AMID VIRUS 'BLIZZARD'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-minnesota-infectious-diseases-60ae579505b6e99a0a4d35e9d2e2e3bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — Minnesota health officials say the state is currently in the middle of a coronavirus “blizzard” with its rate of new infections worst in the nation over the pasts seven days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUNICH CANCELS CHRISTMAS MARKET...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/munich-cancels-popular-christmas-market-over-covid-surge-mayor-01637065207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German city of Munich on Tuesday cancelled its upcoming Christmas market, which usually draws some three million visitors annually, citing Bavaria's "dramatic" coronavirus resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY PLANS CURBS FOR UNVAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/germany-plans-curbs-for-unvaccinated-as-europe-battles-covid-19-spike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases over the past seven days climbed to a record 312.4 per 100,000 people.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could wormholes be used for future space travel? New study explains...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/could-we-actually-use-wormholes-for-space-travel-new-study-explains-685098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A theory proposed in a new study says that wormholes, if they exist, might be more stable than previously suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Wall St set for biggest bonuses since Great Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/wall-street-is-set-for-biggest-bonuses-since-great-recession-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sharp rebound in business activity this year has translated to unprecedented workloads for Wall Street professionals — and a competitive job market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police swamp streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuban-opposition-protest-despite-ban-121756770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban security forces foiled a planned mass protest on Monday, with police flooding Havana's streets and prominent dissidents arrested or confined to their homes to prevent them from staging the banned rights gathering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAULT:  Alex Jones Found Liable In More Sandy Hook Lawsuits Over 'Hoax' Conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/connecticut-judge-orders-infowars-e2-80-99-alex-jones-to-pay-damages-to-families-of-sandy-hook-shooting-victims-in-defamation-lawsuits/ar-AAQJC15?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women to sue Qatar for invasive airport gynecological searches, highlighting rights concerns ahead of  World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Women-to-sue-Qatar-for-invasive-airport-body-16622547.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven women based in Australia plan to sue the Qatari government and state airline over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse in centuries... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/the-longest-lunar-eclipse-in-centuries-will-happen-this-week-nasa-says-what-to-know/article_b4d0edf6-f4d6-58cb-84f0-d5f36bcb6438.html#:~:text=%E2%80%9CThe%20Moon%20will%20be%20so,centuries%2C%20Space.com%20reported.</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can see the longest partial lunar eclipse in hundreds of years this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Cuban dissidents wary or in jail, call for fresh protests falls flat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211116001237-zkt7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUBA-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-With Cuban dissidents wary or in jail, call for fresh protests falls flat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN POWER IN SPACE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211115201210-gw5zk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/SPACE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Russian anti-satellite weapons test 'dangerous and irresponsible' -U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon talks tough after court appearance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/steve-bannon-donald-trump-mark-meadows-congress-subpoenas-5bd5638acb5d93bd8478f57f2b177ded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Longtime Trump ally Steve Bannon appeared before a judge on Monday to face criminal contempt charges for defying a subpoena from Congress' Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SESAME STREET' debuts Ji-Young, first Asian American muppet...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sesame-street-asian-american-muppet-ji-young-390bd29ba9d986524b242e9fa69695be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's in a name? Well, for Ji-Young, the newest muppet resident of “Sesame Street,” her name is a sign she was meant to live there. “So, in Korean traditionally the two syllables they each mean something different and Ji means, like, smart or wise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorpions sting and hospitalize hundreds in Egypt, roused by freak storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16737111/stung-death-storms-wash-scorpions-snakes-egyptian-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCORPIONS washed into homes by heavy rain stung three people to death and left 500 injured in Egypt. Hail and thunderstorms along the River Nile swept the scorpions, as well as snakes, away from th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO RETURNS WITH RUN FOR GOV...</title>
      <link>https://www.texasmonthly.com/news-politics/beto-running-for-texas-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texasmonthly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democrat from El Paso talked about why he thinks he can beat Greg Abbott, his 2020 presidential campaign, and whether he's too liberal for Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Russia conducts its first anti-satellite weapon test with Earth-based missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-conducts-its-first-anti-satellite-weapons-test-with-earth-based-missile/ar-AAQK4Vr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leader seeks release from D.C. jail, alleging inhumane conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/proud-boys-leader-seeks-release-from-dc-jail-alleging-inhumane-conditions/ar-AAQK53a?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company says it's revolutionized truth-telling technology. Experts highly skeptical...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-utah-company-says-it-e2-80-99s-revolutionized-truth-telling-technology-experts-are-highly-skeptical/ar-AAQJSi4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE FIGHTS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/exclusive-alex-jones-responds-to-default-judgement-in-conn-sandy-hook-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch &amp; share this exclusive statement where Alex Jones breaks down how all of our rights are being sacrificed on the altar of political correctness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAULT:  Alex Jones Found Liable In Sandy Hook Lawsuits Over 'Hoax' Conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/breaking-news/hc-br-sandy-hook-lawsuit-alex-jones-hearing-20211115-ccie6kyugrcenm5pjrje7xswk4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Connecticut judge has ruled conspiracy theorist Alex Jones is responsible for all damages in the defamation lawsuits brought against him by the families of those killed in the 2012 Sandy Hook school shooting after his repeated claims that the Newtown massacre was a hoax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Kamala's frustrating start as vice president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/14/politics/kamala-harris-frustrating-start-vice-president/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worn out by what they see as entrenched dysfunction and lack of focus, key West Wing aides have largely thrown up their hands at Vice President Kamala Harris and her staff -- deciding there simply isn't time to deal with them right now, especially at a moment when President Joe Biden faces quickly multiplying legislative and political concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specter of new restrictions rises in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Specter-of-new-restrictions-rises-in-Europe-with-16623321.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two years into the coronavirus era, much of Europe is once again facing a surge in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas National Guard member charged with arson for synagogue fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/halloween-synagogue-fire-bring-federal-charge-texas-national-guard-mem-rcna5622</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 18-year-old Texas National Guard member arrested for allegedly lighting a fire at an Austin synagogue on Halloween now faces a federal arson charge,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE READY TO DEFEND UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211115-putin-tells-macron-us-leading-provocative-exercises-in-black-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin told French counterpart Emmanuel Macron on Monday that "provocative" US-led exercises in the Black Sea were "increasing tensions" between Moscow and NATO, the Kremlin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India turns to lockdown -- for air pollution...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/15/1055849927/india-air-pollution-new-delhi-city-wide-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Delhi's schools are already closed this week because of air pollution that has been about four times the safe limit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
