<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots fuelling massive rise in sex addiction, expert warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6789055/sex-robot-addiction-warning-clinic-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE access to artificially intelligent sex robots could fuel a rise in sex addiction, warn psychology experts. The controversial pleasure droids are being manufactured by a range of companies in t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Trashes Israel, Calls Them 'Occupiers' of Palestine...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/socialist-darling-ocasio-cortz-trashes-israel-calls-them-occupiers-of-palestine-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY TROLLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/sore-loser-hillary-clinton-trolls-pres-trump-on-eve-of-putin-summit-questions-his-loyalty-to-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump winks at Putin during high stakes Helsinki summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6791406/bizarre-moment-donald-trump-winks-at-putin-during-high-stakes-summit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump appeared to wink at Vladimir Putin as the world leaders met face-to-face in Finland today. Flanked by Russian and US flags, they sat awkwardly just feet apart at the start…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Criticized for 'Stolen Valor' on Hijacked Billboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sacha-baron-cohen-criticized-stolen-valor-hijacked-la-billboard-1127231 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A street artist took over a Los Angeles billboard early Monday morning by using a crew to place a gigantic overlay on top of a legitimate ad for the 'Young Sheldon' show on CBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Trump group run out of LA bar by Democratic socialists calling them 'fascist'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/397177-pro-trump-group-run-out-of-la-bar-by-democratic-socialists-calling </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the pro-Trump group “Proud Boys” were chased out of a Los Angeles bar on Saturday by a group of Democratic Socialist protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Slammed For 'Homophobic' Trump-Putin Gay Romance Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/33097/ny-times-slammed-embarrassing-homophobic-trump-james-barrett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An animated cartoon posted by New York Times Opinion portraying Donald Trump in a gay romance with Vladimir Putin has been met with overwhelming backlash online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The military is building a space plane. Now it looks to have an engine up to the task...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-boeing-phantom-express-20180716-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reusable spaceplane under development by Boeing Co. and DARPA reached a milestone earlier this month when its rocket engine was test fired 10 times in 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong retail sales report suggests robust economic growth in second quarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/16/us-retail-sales-june-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. retail sales rose solidly in June, boosted by increases in purchases of motor vehicles and a range of other goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Anderson Defends Assange and Putin: 'Everything Is So Anti-Russia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pamela-anderson-defends-assange-and-putin-everything-is-so-anti-russia </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cultural icon sat down with Marlow Stern to discuss her Ride Responsibly initiative, the mission to pardon pal Julian Assange, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN plane to launch ROCKET into SPACE at 35,000ft!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716624/Virgin-Atlantic-Orbit-space-plane-flight-Cornwall-Newquay-Airport-UK-rocket-satellite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Israel Strikes Hamas Targets in Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/israel-strikes-hamas-targets-in-gaza-1.6279798</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body language expert analyzes meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/life/989515/donald-trump-putin-news-summit-finland-body-language</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD TRUMP met Vladimir Putin in Finland today, with the eyes of the world on the two men. The US President is attending his first face-to-face meeting with Russia’s leader this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock over ruling that 'brides of Christ' need not be virgins...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/16/shock-over-ruling-that-brides-of-christ-need-not-be-virgins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consecrated virgins say they are disappointed by Vatican’s new guidance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RON PAUL: Biggest bubble in history of mankind going to burst...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/13/this-is-the-biggest-bubble-in-the-history-of-mankind-and-its-going-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This market is in the “biggest bubble in the history of mankind” and, when it bursts, it could cut the stock market in half, says Ron Paul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China watching and learning...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/16/china-watches-as-donald-trump-meets-vladimir-putin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Trump meets Putin, nearby superpower China will be paying the most attention to the relationship dynamic between the two leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schultz ambitions give STARBUCKS jitters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/16/howard-schultz-starbucks-2020-president-run-democrats-722199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A partisan run for the White House could be bad for business, company brass and Wall Street worry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year Arizona turns blue?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/07/16/deciders-arizona-election-democrats-219008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have been expecting Barry Goldwater’s home state to flip for years now. Powered by a Latino electorate fired up by Donald Trump, they just might do it — as long as they can actually get them to the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contentious bill defines Israel as Jewish nation-state...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/contentious-bill-defines-israel-jewish-nation-state-120123184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — An Israeli parliamentary committee is deliberating a contentious bill that would define Israel as the nation-state of the Jewish people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WORLD WANTS US TO GET ALONG'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kicking-off-summit-russias-putin-trump-says-really-111521931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Kicking off summit with Russia's Putin, Trump says 'I really think the world wants to see us get along'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACE TO FACE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5958541/Putin-arrives-Finnish-Presidential-Palace-ahead-talks-President-Trump-later-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The summit at the Finnish Presidential Palace in Helsinki consists of a one-on-one meeting and a larger working lunch, and will conclude with a joint news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE</title>
      <link>http://abc13.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live streaming video on ABC13.com and stay up-to-date with the latest KTRK news broadcasts as well as live breaking news whenever it happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Lounge Wars Heat Up as Airlines Vie for High-End Passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/16/travel/airport-luxury-lounges-airlines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disparity between the haves and have-nots in airline travel extends well beyond the cabin experience and is increasingly playing out inside the terminals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$88 Million and Counting: Trump Amasses Huge Head Start...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/15/us/politics/trump-fundraising-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s re-election haul reflects a brisk fund-raising effort. Most of his predecessors, by contrast, did not kick off their campaigns until after the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitchy West looks on...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180716005957-zptwj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/SUMMIT (TV, PIX):Trump and Putin to hold first summit talks as twitchy West looks on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power to the drones: Utilities place bets on robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-utilities-drones-europe-analysis/power-to-the-drones-utilities-place-bets-on-robots-idUSKBN1K60TS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flying robots that can travel dozens of kilometers without stopping could be the next big thing for power companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president-elect slashes his own salary...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexican-president-elect-slashes-own-salary-223821370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican President-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Sunday he plans to earn less than half of what his predecessor makes when he takes office in December as part of an austerity push in government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU official urges not to destroy global order...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/eu-chief-urges-trump-putin-033201281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A senior European official on Monday urged U.S. President Donald Trump, Russian President Vladimir Putin and China to work with Europe to avoid trade wars and prevent conflict and chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim candidates running in record numbers face backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/62d762b7e25b49bc916d02f8d538a247/Muslim-candidates-running-in-record-numbers-face-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Mass. (AP) — A liberal woman of color with zero name recognition and little funding takes down a powerful, long serving congressman from her own political party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES HELSINKI</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c4f9d4e5ecb54d4cb93d782f0046839a/Amid-investigations-and-tensions,-Trump-Putin-going-1-on-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — President Donald Trump blamed the United States, and not Russian election meddling or the country's annexation of Crimea, for a low-point in U.S.-Russia relations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attacks US 'foolishness' heading into Putin showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/trump-attacks-us-foolishness-heading-putin-showdown-doc-17p79c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British caver considering legal action after Musk 'pedo' tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/205/british-caver-says-considering-legal-action-after-elon-musk-pedo-tweet-doc-17p8y71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reiner Movie Earns Measly $41,000 on Opening Weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/rob-reiner-shock-and-awe-earnings-opening-weekend-flop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes: Indictment tracks House Intel report...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/nunes-mueller-indictment-tracks-house-intel-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a tweet Sunday, Sen. Dianne Feinstein, D-Calif., a member and former chair of the Senate Intelligence Committee, boiled down special counsel Robert Mueller's new Russian election-meddling indictment to one basic lesson: "Key point in Special Counsel Mueller's indictment: A dozen Russian military…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorpion deaths rising in Brazil as arachnid adapts to urban life...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/15/scorpion-deaths-rise-brazil-cities-urban-adaptation-risks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths have more than doubled as specialists warn of increasing danger for city-dwellers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman chases down, stabs man who flashed her at park...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article214927800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cynthia Christine Molina, 51, chased down and stabbed a 28-year-old man who exposed himself to her early Tuesday in Redlands, California, police say. The man initially reported it as a random attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% vacancy: Feds release illegals instead of filling detention centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/15/illegal-immigrant-family-detention-facilities-belo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government pays for thousands of detention beds for illegal immigrant families, but nearly 40 percent of them were sitting unused in late June, even as the Department of Homeland Security was rushing to release parents and children into communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Mayor Laments Human Poop On Streets: 'More Than Ever Seen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/SF-Mayor-Theres-more-feces-on-the-sidewalks-than-Ive-ever-seen-488156431.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco Mayor London Breed believes homeless advocacy groups that receive funding from the city need to better educate the homeless to “clean up after themselves.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry mob butchers hundreds of crocodiles to avenge eaten villager...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/angry-mob-beats-hundreds-crocodiles-12921076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES The furious locals massacred almost 300 of the captive reptiles after breaking into a private property in Indonesia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $247,000,000,000,000 global debt bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/the-247-trillion-global-debt-bomb/2018/07/15/64c5bbaa-86c2-11e8-8f6c-46cb43e3f306_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To service these debts requires rising incomes, while an expanding trade war threatens to squeeze incomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen jokes about women being raped...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/6786774/sacha-baron-cohen-rape-skit-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORAT star Sacha Baron Cohen is facing fresh controversy over his new TV series after it emerged he jokes about women being raped. In one skit Cohen plays an Israeli terrorism expert called Erran M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS MAYHEM AFTER WORLD CUP WIN...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5956427/French-fans-home-abroad-erupt-celebration-sides-second-World-Cup-triumph.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired tear gas as scuffles broke out on the Champs-Élysées as French football fans celebrate their side's spectacular World Cup victory over Croatia in Moscow today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delirious French revel in World Cup victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/delirious-french-revel-world-cup-victory-203440468.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France erupted in joy on Sunday as the country clinched the World Cup, with fans streaming into the streets, honking car horns and flying the tricolour flag at the start of an enormous national celebration. Cheers rang out throughout the country for each of four goals in the final as "Les Bleus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May warns rebels...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/british-pm-may-warns-rebels-back-risk-no-074800526--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Guy Faulconbridge and William James LONDON (Reuters) - British Prime Minister Theresa May warned her divided party on Sunday that there may be "no Brexit at all" if they wrecked her plan to forge a close relationship with the European Union after leaving the world's biggest trading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police clash with unruly fans, clear Champs Elysees...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180715225652-3exti</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCCER-WORLDCUP-FINAL/PARIS-TROUBLE (TV, PIX):French police clash with unruly fans, clear Champs Elysees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago police release video of shooting that sparked violent protests...</title>
      <link>http://abc7chicago.com/chicago-police-release-body-cam-video-of-south-shore-police-shooting/3766539/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities released Sunday the identity of a man who was fatally shot by Chicago police in the South Shore neighborhood on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Brexit referendum 'is only way to end deadlock'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/justine-greening-new-brexit-referendum-is-only-way-to-end-deadlock-55gd5rcpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May’s hopes of winning support for her Brexit compromise have been dealt a huge blow as Justine Greening has become the first senior Conservative to support calls for a second referendum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Trump in White House, candidates who sound like him hit campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/With-Trump-in-the-White-House-candidates-who-13077071.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA - In last week's debate between Georgia's Republican candidates for governor, policy was quickly abandoned as Lt. Gov. Casey Cagle and Secretary of State Brian Kemp lit into one another with a familiar slate of accusations. Kemp called Cagle a liar at least a dozen times. Cagle accused Kemp of conspiring with another Republican to release a recording of an "out of context" private conversationKemp accused Cagle of spreading "fake news" to Georgians, and Cagle repeatedly refused to apologize for saying what he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant children held in shelters: 'They told us to behave, or we'd be here forever'... </title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Immigrant-children-held-in-shelters-They-told-13077041.php?src=hp_totn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON - When the 8-year-old stepped off a plane here earlier this month with freshly cut bangs and a shelter-issued sweatsuit, she was met by crowds and television cameras and finally, in a carpeted airport conference room, by the mother who had been taken from her two months earlier at the border. But now, a day after that joyous reunion, the girl from Guatemala was shoving a toddler who had tried to give her a hug and a kiss at a welcoming party in the suburbs. Now she was screaming and crying and telling the boy to stay away. This is what two months in a Texas shelter had taught Sandy Gonzalez. "They always kept the boys and the girls separate," the second-grader explained last week. "And they punished us if we went near each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games show off modern Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/445a4d2de1ba4b898b6dcc8e3c24140d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Despite a national wave of elation from the World Cup that bathed Russia in a rosy light, President Vladimir Putin will face some challenges in extending the post-so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadians still visiting USA despite trade flap...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cc07ddb7c9f469081c414021d2bd19d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLD ORCHARD BEACH, Maine (AP) — The United States and Canada are engaged in a trade dispute, angering Canadians, but it doesn't seem to be having an impact on tourism. Not yet, an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump resists Mueller interview, leaving decision on subpoena before fall elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-resists-mueller-interview-leaving-decision-on-subpoena-before-fall-elections/ar-AAA7owy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS apologizes after white manager calls police on black customer...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/news/black-woman-says-cvs-manager-called-police-because-she-had-wrong-coupon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the video went viral on Facebook, representatives of the company reached out to Camilla Hudson to apologize "profusely" for the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gowdy rules out Rosenstein impeachment... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/397127-gowdy-rules-out-rosenstein-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Trey Gowdy (R-S.C.) on Sunday ruled out the possibility of impeaching Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein, saying there is not enough support for his ouster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pedo guy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/thai-cave-rescue-elon-musk-british-diver-vern-unsworth-twitter-pedo-a8448366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sorry pedo guy, you really did ask for it'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley eyes Africa as new tech frontier...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-07-silicon-valley-eyes-africa-tech.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna at 60: Pop culture still reeks of her influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/15/barbara-ellen-on-madonna-sexist-slurs-pop-surivor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the singer’s 60th birthday approaches, the Observer columnist celebrates pop’s greatest survivor• Thurston Moore on Madonna: ‘She was really ahead of the game’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUBRICK FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE? Lost screenplay found 60 years on...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jul/15/stanley-kubrick-lost-screenplay-burning-secret-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Script co-written by master director is so close to completion that it could be developed into a full feature film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists peer into heart of hurricanes to improve intensity forecast...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180715100024-aeg6u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a better way to predict a storm's power, people will be more prepared in knowing whether a hurricane headed their way will cause devastating floods and winds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk attacks hero diver and questions if he was even involved in Thai rescue...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5955753/British-caver-helped-save-Thai-boys-says-Elon-Musk-stick-submarine-hurt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has hit back at a British caver who helped rescue 12 Thai school boys and their soccer coach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botswana may put elephants in cross-hairs as it moves to lift hunting ban...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/botswana-may-put-elephants-cross-hairs-moves-lift-133639202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Botswana, home to the world's largest elephant population, may lift a ban on hunting for sport in the face of what the government says is growing conflict between humans and wildlife, a move sure to provoke protest from animal welfare groups. Conservationists estimate the land-locked southern African</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6f78cad4eb024bf2a2d47b2df035f664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — A face-to-face sitdown with a long-feared foe. Endless media hype. Huge ratings.        Although President Donald Trump has met with Russia's Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok arrogance 'product of corrupt FBI'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/peter-strzoks-arrogance-is-the-product-of-a-corrupt-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching FBI agent Peter Strzok battle with Congress, my initial reaction was pure anger. His repeated, arrogant insistence that he had done nothing wrong despite tons of evidence to the contrary c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Jaguar escapes New Orleans zoo, goes on animal killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6782468/jaguar-valerio-escapes-new-orleans-zoo-killing-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A JAGUAR escaped from its zoo enclosure and slaughtered six other animals in a terrifying hour-long killing spree. The big cat, named Valerio, was sedated he after he killed four alpacas, one emu, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHAME IS DEAD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/who-is-america-review-1127051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen's new Showtime comedy is occasionally funny, but it's hard to be outrageous in a world where ideologies that used to be concealed are now proudly public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret plot to EVICT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716573/julian-assange-wikileaks-evicted-ecuadorian-embassy-london-usa-deported</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary begins speech: 'I'm so tired, I can barely stand'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-starts-speech-im-so-tired-i-can-barely-stand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton may have visions of 2020 — if she can just keep her eyes open. The failed presidential candidate started her speech to the American Federation of Teachers union on Friday in a bizarre way: by telling everyone how tired she was. ﻿ “Well, I’ll tell you,” she said, “I’ve been back there listening …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
