<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>One week in, Biden embracing order, routine...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/One-week-in-Biden-embracing-order-routine-15903805.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Almost every day of his young tenure, President Joe Biden has entered the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Proud Boys leader 'prolific' informer for law enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-proudboys-leader-exclusive/exclusive-proud-boys-leader-was-prolific-informer-for-law-enforcement-idUSKBN29W1PE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enrique Tarrio, the leader of the Proud Boys extremist group, has a past as an informer for federal and local law enforcement, repeatedly working undercover for investigators after he was arrested in 2012, according to a former prosecutor and a transcript of a 2014 federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns Beijing over expansionism ...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/multiple-messsages-biden-warns-beijing-013100552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One week into the job, US President Joe Biden has sent a clear warning to Beijing against any expansionist intentions in East and Southeast Asia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS FOR PRIME MINISTER?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/piers-morgan-reveals-intentions-run-23398586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Morning Britain co-anchor Piers Morgan has dropped hints that we may see him standing outside Downing Street as Prime Minister, after grilling MPs during the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HOTEL TURNS GHOST TOWN IN DC...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/JaneMayerNYer/status/1354533185909043200?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New kid on Paris fashion block sparks YSL comparisons...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kid-paris-fashion-block-sparks-211150218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 24-years-old, Charles de Vilmorin pulled no punches as he launched himself into the rarefied world of haute couture on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Rich Get Richer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/reddit-day-trader-army-fattens-fortunes-of-the-super-rich/ar-BB1d97n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horde of traders on Reddit that see themselves as sticking it to the establishment by hunting for heavily shorted stocks is adding billions to the wealth of some of the world’s ultra-rich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab-grown wood to let us grow furniture?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90596673/lab-grown-wood-could-let-us-grow-furniture-in-a-lab-instead-of-in-a-forest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why cut down trees when you can grow wood in the exact shape you need?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles gone mad!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/27/gamestop-rally-is-warning-that-market-bubbles-have-gone-mad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1630s, it was tulips. In the 1990s, it was Netscape and Pets.com. Later, as we all know, it was housing. Today, the warning sign flashing “danger,” signaling that the stock market has lost i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five or six doses? Controversy over PFIZER vials...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/five-six-doses-controversy-over-144318589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US pharmaceutical giant Pfizer, which is manufacturing the Covid-19 vaccine developed by Germany's BioNTech, now considers each vial contains six doses compared to five previously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen 'Monitoring'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-monitoring-gamestop-market-activity-183420988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said it is “actively monitoring” volatility in options and equities markets amid a surge in GameStop Corp. and other companies over the past week that prompted Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren to demand action from regulators.“Consistent with our mission to protect investors and maintain fair, orderly, and efficient markets, we are working with our fellow regulators to assess the situation and review the activities of regulated entities, financial intermediaries, and other market participants,” the SEC said in a statement Wednesday.Retail investors have rapidly driven up GameStop’s shares in recent days, squeezing hedge funds with large short positions in the company, in a twist that has grabbed attention on Wall Street and in Washington.Shares in the video-game retailer more than doubled on Wednesday, triggering at least two volatility halts as it at one point notched its biggest-ever intraday advance. GameStop has surged eightfold in the past week, adding almost $20 billion to its market value.The moves led Warren to pressure financial regulators to crack down on Wall Street, citing the frenzied activity.In a sharply worded statement earlier Wednesday, the Massachusetts Democrat and longtime corporate foe expressed astonishment at the rally while also criticizing hedge funds and others with short positions in company.‘Personal Casino’“For years, the same hedge funds, private equity firms, and wealthy investors dismayed by the GameStop trades have treated the stock market like their own personal casino while everyone else pays the price,” Warren said. “It’s long past time for the SEC and other financial regulators to wake up and do their jobs -- and with a new administration and Democrats running Congress, I intend to make sure they do.”Warren’s comments came after White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki said that Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen and Biden’s economic team were watching stock market activity around GameStop and other heavily shorted companies.“Our team is of course -- our economic team including Secretary Yellen and others -- are monitoring the situation,” Psaki told reporters at the White House on Wednesday. She called the trading in the video-game retailer “a good reminder, though, that the stock market isn’t the only measure of the health of our economy.”A Treasury Department spokesperson declined to comment. Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell also declined to weigh in on the activity around GameStop.“I don’t want to comment on a particular company or day’s market activity or things like that. It’s just not something really that I would typically comment on,” he told reporters at a Wednesday afternoon news conference.Read More: GameStop Rally Hits New Extremes as Short Sellers SurrenderGameStop’s meteoric rise has captivated Wall Street, as an army of small traders spurred on by Reddit posts have pushed the company’s stock price to unheard-of levels. Shares in the company began the year at just $19. Hedge funds that held short positions in GameStop, such as Melvin Capital, have closed out of them as the rally continued, suffering billions of dollars in losses.Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a New York Democrat, said in a tweet that Wall Street and those posting online have taken a similar approach to the economy and markets.“Gotta admit it’s really something to see Wall Streeters with a long history of treating our economy as a casino complain about a message board of posters also treating the market as a casino,” she wrote.While some commentators have cast the frenzy as a populist uprising against Wall Street institutions, others see a dangerous play that could eventually leave investors exposed to major losses. Some wondered if it was the result of purposeful market manipulation.Earlier: Michael Burry Calls GameStop Rally ‘Unnatural, Insane’ Investor Michael Burry, who previously championed GameStop in 2019, called the current phenomenon “unnatural, insane and dangerous.”“What is going on now -- there should be legal and regulatory repercussions,” tweeted Burry, who made his name for his bet against mortgage-backed securities before the 2008 financial crisis.Burry’s tweet tagged the SEC’s Division of Enforcement.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 11 Hours of Pure Mania, 100% Stock Gains Popped Up Everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/11-hours-pure-mania-100-222605181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Cooped up at home, glued to Reddit and Stocktwits chat forums, empowered by Robinhood accounts, funded by massive government money-printing and emboldened by a bull market that has turned reckless risk-taking into a virtue, America’s new band of day traders is frantically bidding up a wide range of fringe, oddball stocks in what has become one of the great financial manias in recent history.To capture how fast and furious the action is and how extreme the price swings — and the trash-talking — are, Bloomberg News tracked Wednesday’s events in real time.The fireworks actually started the night before, when Elon Musk blasted out a tweet that became a rallying cry for redditors to keep piling into shares of GameStop, which had already soared 276% in the past five days, and inflict more pain on the Wall Street pros.Here are some of the day’s highlights.Wednesday, 5:45 a.m. EST:Propelled by Musk’s “Gamestonk!!” tweet, GameStop hits $365.42 in early morning trading. A week ago, it sold for less than $40.The tweet also spurs excited speculation on Reddit about whether Musk had joined in. One redditor, whose username is Apparently, asks, “Papa Elon, are you here? Show us a sign”7:33 a.m., stocktwits.com:It’s not just GameStop. Retail traders band together, scouring the internet for other bygone ’90s-era companies. On Stocktwits, a user named CEO_Andrew_Ryan casually muses:9:15 a.m., r/wallstreetbets:In their frenzy, the cocky hordes on Reddit’s r/wallstreetbets forum manage to turn the tables on short sellers and inflict heavy losses on the likes of Andrew Left and Melvin Capital. According to one early morning post, they’re not done yet.And did we mention cocky?9:30 a.m., Summit, NJ:Mike Zigmont, head of trading and research at Harvest Volatility Management, can only shake his head as the market opens.“I don’t know if this is the future, I don’t know if this is just something quirky, but thank god I’m not involved. It’s not investing, it’s a financial form of a game of uncle. The fundamentals don’t matter, numbers don’t matter. Boy oh boy, it’s wild.”9:40 a.m., minutes after the market open:AMC Networks, ticker AMCX (and not to be confused with Reddit darling AMC Entertainment, ticker AMC), soars 19%, extending a rally to 67% over past five days. And AMC Entertainment?#SaveAMC also starts trending on Twitter, while Barstool Sports founder Dave Portnoy says he’s buying AMC on his “Davey Day Trader” livestream.“I’m rooting for AMC, I’m rooting to put the hedge funds out of business,” Portnoy says.Meanwhile, other heavily-shorted Reddit names like Macy’s and Dillard’s also jump. 9:43 a.m., Tootsie Roll is halted after its shares soar 53%:Max Gokhman, director of asset allocation at Pacific Life Fund Advisors, via IB chat from Costa Mesa, CA:09:48:06 Wow ok, I didn't even know that was a stock09:48:17 Or, rather, a stonk10 a.m., Newton, MA:Matt Maley, chief market strategist at Miller Tabak + Co., sees a direct link between the speculative retail buying of heavily-shorted stocks and the broader market decline, which takes the S&amp;P 500 down roughly 1.5%.“It’s due to concerns about hedge funds. A lot of them are getting burned by their shorts, and I think the market is worried that they’ll have to sell some stocks to meet their margin calls.”10:16 a.m., r/wallstreetbets:The crush of retail trading causes outages at several online brokerages. Charles Schwab, Robinhood, E*Trade and Fidelity are all hit by service disruptions. TD Ameritrade limits some transactions on shares of GameStop, AMC and others. It says high volume may have curtailed access to its mobile app and urges clients to use its other platforms.Some redditors see darker motives:10:44 a.m., the number of “degenerates” on r/wallstreetbets tops 3 million:A user named WildInjury celebrates with this NSFW post, “3 F---ING MILLION OF US. NEVER STOP! TENDIES FOR 2021!”11:32 a.m., r/wallstreetbets:A user claiming to be Elon Musk piles on ...11:33 a.m., Mountain View, CA:The froth is also alive and well in SPAC land.*23ANDME SAID TO BE IN TALKS ON GO-PUBLIC DEAL VIA BRANSON SPAC*23ANDME DEAL COULD BE VALUED AT ROUGHLY $4 BILLION12:08 p.m., AMC trades at $14.19, up 186% from its previous close:The movie theater operator says it sold 63.3 million shares in at-the market transactions since Jan. 25, raising about $305 million in the process.YOLO indeed. Meanwhile on WSB, the hedge fund taunts keep coming ...12:53 p.m., GameStop shares trade at $338.83, up 129% on the day:On Stocktwits, Dude2U has some thoughts ...Less than a half an hour later, White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki says at a briefing that Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen and others are monitoring the situation with GameStop.1:56 p.m., shares of Koss are halted again after surging 296%The circuit-breaker halt is one of at least 84 on the day. As of roughly 2:30 p.m., trading in Koss, a maker of loudspeakers and headphones, has been stopped at least 18 times. 2:39 p.m., Federal Reserve press conference following its policy meeting:Fed Chair Jay Powell starts taking questions from the Eccles Building in Washington D.C. The first one is on Gamestop’s wild ride. He ducks it.“I don’t want to comment on a particular company,” Powell says. He parries away other questions related to monetary policy and market froth.In a chatroom for Reddit users, SmokeHalo responds: “Powell dodging questions like neo dodging bullets.”3:20 p.m., Washington D.C.:Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren releases a sharply worded statement pressuring the Biden administration’s financial regulators to crack down on Wall Street, citing the frenzied volatility in GameStop.“For years, the same hedge funds, private equity firms, and wealthy investors dismayed by the GameStop trades have treated the stock market like their own personal casino while everyone else pays the price,” she said. “It’s long past time for the SEC and other financial regulators to wake up and do their jobs — and with a new administration and Democrats running Congress, I intend to make sure they do.”3:30 p.m., shares of companies with tickers starting “BB” surge to highs:4 p.m., the stock market closes, with the S&amp;P 500 falling 2.6%, the most since October: The slump does nothing to damp the enthusiasm on r/wallstreetbets. In the past 24 hours alone, more than 800,000 users join.4:34 p.m., shortly after the market closes:The SEC releases a statement saying that it’s “actively monitoring the on-going market volatility in the options and equities markets.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNITCH ON THE STREETS?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/riots-florida-dc84086d78b688bc585f874452d2b481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of the Proud Boys, who was arrested in Washington shortly before the Capitol riot, previously worked undercover and cooperated with investigators after he was accused of fraud in 2012,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -633</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-seoul-tokyo-hong-kong-shanghai-cd16870f9e23357f6a39b85b0cdb3ab7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology companies led a broad sell-off in stocks Wednesday, knocking more than 600 points off the Dow Jones Industrial Average and handing the market its worst day in nearly three months....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLORIS LEACHMAN DEAD AT 94...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/academy-awards-mel-brooks-california-cloris-leachman-mary-tyler-moore-7b9eb2aa8de5a62e8502ca94cff89e83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Cloris Leachman, an Oscar-winner for her portrayal of a lonely housewife in “The Last Picture Show” and a comedic delight as the fearsome Frau Blücher in “Young Frankenstein”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SERVER SHUTDOWN!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9193697/GameStops-three-largest-shareholders-gotten-3BILLION-richer-two-weeks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Users of a Reddit group led by a YouTube financial guru known as 'Roaring Kitty' (left) sent shares in GameStop up another 120 percent on Wednesday. Shareholder Ryan Cohen (right) has gained $2B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militiaman Who Plotted to Kidnap MI Gov Pleads Guilty, Turns on Pals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ty-garbin-michigan-militiaman-who-planned-to-kidnap-gretchen-whitmer-pleads-guilty-and-turns-on-his-pals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ty Garbin, 25, has agreed to cooperate with agencies investigating the wild plot to overthrow the Michigan government and execute the governor for treason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL HELL:  SEAHAWKS Player Accused Of Choking Girlfriend Unconscious...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/seahawks-offensive-tackle-ex-giant-chad-wheeler-arrested-on-suspicion-of-felony-domestic-violence-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wheeler is accused of assaulting his girlfriend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Soars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-coronavirus-pandemic-27452d3cfc5797132bf04df3977890f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook capped a tumultuous 2020 with soaring earnings in the final quarter, its user base boosted by people staying home and its revenue buoyed by a shift to digital advertising amid the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLORIS LEACHMAN DEAD AT 94...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/01/27/cloris-leachman-dead-dies-94/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloris Leachman -- the incredibly talented and hilarious actress and comedian, who starred in some of the biggest movies and TV shows ever -- has died ... TMZ has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California faces backlash for lifting stay-home order...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/27/covid-surge-california-lifts-stay-at-home-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move comes as Covid surge has pushed local healthcare systems to brink of collapse and funeral industry faces horrifying backlog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed dismisses worries about inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/27/economy/federal-reserve-jerome-powell/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve left interest rates unchanged Wednesday and assured investors that there are no near-term plans to raise them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE blowout!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/apple-aapl-earnings-q1-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple reported its first-quarter earnings after the bell Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry pledges to work with China on climate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210127-us-will-work-with-china-on-climate-despite-other-differences-kerry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US will work with China on climate despite other differences: Kerry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members defend...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/proud-boys-rush-to-defend-leaders-past-life-as-a-police-informant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the Proud Boys are rushing to the defense of their leader after court documents revealed he previously worked as an undercover informant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans plan to filibuster 'Homeland' nominee...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/27/politics/senate-republicans-mayorkas-nomination-dhs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans plan to object to any efforts to quickly confirm Alejandro Mayorkas as secretary of Homeland Security, further delaying his confirmation as the department grapples with the Covid-19 pandemic, national security concerns and President Joe Biden's ambitious immigration plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIX FLAGS Opening World's Tallest, Longest &amp; Fastest Single-Rail Roller Coaster...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/01/27/jersey-devil-coaster-worlds-tallest-longest-fastest-single-rail-roller-coaster-set-to-open-at-six-flags-great-adventure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Flags put the last piece of track together for the new Jersey Devil Coaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WE OWN YOU NOW'</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/wallstreetbets-reddit-gamestop-stock-blackberry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How one subreddit — and a tech-friendly new way of investing — is shaping the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ PLAN TO THWART</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/nasdaq-ceo-suggests-halt-to-trading-to-allow-big-investors-to-recalibrate-their-positions-to-combat-reddit-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman suggested Wednesday that her exchange could halt trading activity for stocks to enable investors to "recalibrate" in the event they were targeted by internet users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats against lawmakers fuel safety concerns for travel outside DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/27/politics/congress-members-threats-outside-dc/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As threats continue to mount against members of Congress, concern is growing about the safety of some lawmakers when they travel outside Washington and the security bubble it provides, multiple sources told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO DEBATE ERUPTS AFTER STRANGE LIGHTS IN NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article248795870.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people have reported seeing light clusters in Union County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC to stay neutral should Trump run again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-elections-only-on-ap-michael-pence-8c87215b20a50f58a18f8406cf49e75f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The head of the Republican National Committee on Wednesday declined to encourage former President Donald Trump to run for the White House in 2024, saying the GOP would stay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand's borders may stay shut for most of year...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/01/26/asia/new-zealand-covid-borders-shut-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's borders will remain closed for most of this year as the Covid-19 pandemic rages on, but the country will pursue travel arrangements with neighbouring Australia and other Pacific nations, Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WH: Many More to Come...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-pandemics-public-health-coronavirus-pandemic-c5e88cea134097e3b17d512e5711c5df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As many as 90,000 Americans are projected to die from the coronavirus in the next four weeks, the Biden administration warned in its first science briefing on the COVID-19...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma seeking to return $2M worth of hydroxychloroquine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-malaria-coronavirus-pandemic-oklahoma-09e3f4db37dda112ecec70d780bc964d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — The Oklahoma attorney general's office is attempting to return $2 million worth of a malaria drug once touted by former President Donald Trump as an effective treatment for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Influencer' charged with spreading election disinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/27/social-media-influencer-election-disinformation-463170</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrest marks a rare instance of an individual facing criminal charges over a disinformation campaign carried out on prominent social media platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Hits Record Covid Deaths in January...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/us-reports-record-number-of-covid-deaths-in-january.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is working to ramp up the rollout of the Covid-19 vaccines, blaming the initially slow pace on the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire defends investors' right to sway stocks like pros...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/chamath-palihapitiya-closes-gamestop-position-but-defends-individual-investors-right-to.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO of Social Capital and former Facebook executive tweeted Tuesday that he bought $125,000 worth of February $115 GameStop call options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark populations drop 71%...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/animals-pets/2021/01/empty-seas-oceanic-shark-populations-dropped-71-since-1970/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study drawing on 57 global datasets underscores just how dramatically worldwide shark populations have collapsed in the past half century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands of voters drop party affiliation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/536113-tens-of-thousands-of-voters-drop-republican-affiliation-after-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 30,000 voters who had been registered members of the Republican Party have changed their voter registration in the weeks after a mob of pro-Trump supporters attacked the Capitol — an issue that led the House to impeach the former preside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Pence is 'HOMELESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2218266/mike-pence-homeless-couch-surfing-indiana-politician/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIKE Pence is “homeless” and is now allegedly couch-surfing with an Indiana politician after leaving office, reports claim. The former vice president and his wife Karen are residing at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington and Lincoln are out. San Fran school board tosses 44 school names in controversial move...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/education/article/Washington-and-Lincoln-are-out-S-F-school-board-15900963.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco school board approved changing the names of 44 school sites, including Lincoln, Washington and Lowell high schools. School sites have until April to come up with suggestions for new names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai police arrest foreign tourists for breaking rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/89-foreigners-arrested-at-thai-bar-flouting-coronavirus-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police raided a party at a bar on a popular resort island in southern Thailand and arrested 89 foreigners for violating coronavirus regulations, officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT MOB ROILS STOCK MARKET</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/gamestop-jumps-another-50percent-even-as-hedge-funds-cover-short-bets-scrutiny-of-rally-intensifies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest move higher comes as some of the high-profile short sellers announced that they covered most or all of their positions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top MAGA gathering finds new reality complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/27/cpac-2021-462907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPAC was at the top of its powers last year. Then Covid-19 hit, Trump lost, and the postelection chaos ensued. Now, the confab has some challenges ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK LOCKDOWN UNTIL MARCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/uks-johnson-warns-lockdown-will-last-until-at-least-march-8/ar-BB1d8UKN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson put England on notice that the national virus lockdown will continue for at least another six weeks, with schools staying closed and new border quarantine rules coming into force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Holds Off On New Lockdown, Worries About Unrest Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-holds-off-on-new-lockdown-worries-about-unrest-risk/ar-BB1d8Gyf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is delaying an agonizing decision to lock down the country once more, mulling options to slow new variants of Covid-19 as the current curfew is considered insufficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 23ANDME Tool Assesses Risk of Covid Becoming Severe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/new-23andme-tool-assesses-risk-of-covid-19-becoming-severe/ar-BB1d8VpA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA-testing company 23andMe Inc. has launched a new tool that aims to predict an infected person’s risk of developing a severe case of Covid-19, expanding the company’s bid to deliver actionable insight on health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's 2021 COVID-19 Bill Costs More Than Entire 1981 Federal Government!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/bidens-2021-covid-19-bill-costs-more-entire-1981-federal-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $1.9 trillion relief bill that President Joe Biden wants Congress to pass now as his response to the COVID-19 pandemic would cost Americans more than the entire federal government cost in fiscal 1981.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All against all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/russias-putin-warns-of-a-fight-of-all-against-all-at-wef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin warned the World Economic Forum that the coronavirus pandemic has exacerbated preexisting imbalances and tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Donald rehab his reputation? Some lessons from Nixon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-trump-rehab-reputation-130022440.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Khachigian joined the president in exile after Watergate. One suggestion for Trump: Be quiet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trigger Volatility Halts Across Market...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/reddit-fueled-traders-trigger-volatility-160742020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The number of volatility halts across equity markets has soared in recent days amid the rapid ascension of amateur traders armed with Robinhood and their favorite social media platforms.About 30 circuit breaker halts were triggered in the first hour of trading Wednesday due to a rocky session that sent ripples across the stock market. From cult-favorite GameStop Corp. to stereo headphone and loudspeaker retailer Koss Corp., trading volume soared as gains and losses fluctuated by the minute.Day traders have taken to online forums like Reddit, posting bullish touts to encourage others to join an epic retail frenzy that has tested the mettle of short sellers. Reddit is also routinely used to drive up penny stocks that, unlike GameStop, have ceased publishing financial results and don’t trade on regulated exchanges. Volatility halts are relatively common for small stocks that are surging or tumbling and are used by exchanges to help smooth rapid movement in either direction and prevent flash crashes. They are often done to force traders to digest the news and recalibrate their trades over the typical five-minute pause.Online brokerages including Robinhood Markets and Charles Schwab Corp. were hit again Wednesday by service disruptions as traders were transfixed by wild swings in shares of GameStop Corp. and other heavily shorted stocks. TD Ameritrade Holding Corp., Morgan Stanley’s E*Trade and Fidelity were also affected, according to Downdetector.com, which tracks user complaints.GameStop shares, which soared as much as 140% in early trading, were halted at least twice, while movie theater company AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc. triggered four halts as it more than quadrupled on volume that was roughly ten times the three-month average.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI steps up efforts to build conspiracy case in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/536064-fbi-steps-up-efforts-to-build-conspiracy-case-on-capitol-riot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is stepping up its efforts to build a possible conspiracy case after authorities have arrested more than 150 people for their alleged role in the Capitol riot, law enforcement officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST REQUIRED FOR DOMESTIC TRAVEL?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210126222729-wmirw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (PIX):U.S. 'actively looking' at mandating COVID-19 testing for domestic air travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Human Fatter Than Elephant...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/humans-fatter-than-an-elephant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find the average human carries between 6 and 31 percent body fat. The average male elephant carries less than 9 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New war on opposition suggests he sees it as real threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/opinions-putins-new-war-on-the-opposition-suggests-he-sees-it-as-a-real-threat/ar-BB1d8VPA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides seem to think the future of Russia is at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China rolls out new anal swab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/china-rolls-out-new-anal-23393894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid, invasive test inserts a swab 2-3 centimetres into the rectum and rotates it several times. It is currently being used in Beijing to curb the spread of a new Covid outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Lives of NFL Cheerleaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-dangerous-lives-of-nfl-cheerleaders </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five or six doses? Controversy over PFIZER vials...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210127-five-or-six-doses-controversy-over-pfizer-vaccine-vials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five or six doses? Controversy over Pfizer vaccine vials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks slide... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors pored through mixed earnings from major companies and awaited the latest policy decision from the Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People must explain travel reasons under new border measures...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127135918-tptoe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-PATEL (URGENT):People must explain travel reasons under new British border measures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Arrested for Killing Weak to Save Strong...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/did-this-italian-covid-doc-kill-the-weak-to-save-the-strong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A primary care physician from one of the hardest hit regions in Italy has been arrested for lethally injecting weak COVID patients to free up beds during the peak of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots disinfecting hotels. It's tip of hospitality revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/robots-are-disinfecting-hotels-during-the-pandemic-it-e2-80-99s-the-tip-of-a-hospitality-revolution/ar-BB1d8SjZ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under Biden, Dems ready to revive net neutrality rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/under-biden-democrats-are-ready-to-revive-net-neutrality-rules/ar-BB1d8PCW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House, Federal Communications Commission and Congress face early pressure to bring back open-Internet safeguards scrapped under former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope marking Holocaust warns another genocide possible...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pope-francis-europe-the-holocaust-5cad22f0e43abc3d3bc33d2b3526585f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis marked Holocaust Remembrance Day on Wednesday by warning that warped ideologies can pave the way to another genocide. Francis spoke off the cuff at the end of his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leader was 'prolific' informer for law enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127130008-0o116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PROUDBOYS/LEADER (EXCLUSIVE):EXCLUSIVE-Proud Boys leader was ‘prolific’ informer for law enforcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International team disables world's most dangerous malware...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127125007-efnid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International team disables world's most dangerous malware:International team disables world's most dangerous malware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican TV host under fire after going to Florida to get shot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/26/mexican-tv-host-gets-covid-shot-in-florida-amid-vaccine-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Mexican TV host is under fire after traveling to Florida just to get the coveted COVID-19 vaccine, which most Americans have not received. Juan José Origel, who’s famous for hosting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves GOP with identity crisis. First test: Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-leaves-gop-identity-crisis-110041043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Virginia races this year to the 2022 midterm, Republicans will face contests that pit Trump loyalists against those who want to distance the party from him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden signals tougher Russia stance in call with Vladimir...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-signals-tougher-russia-stance-213819197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden signalled a tougher US stance on Russia Tuesday in his first phone call with President Vladimir Putin, raising concerns over human rights and "aggression" against Ukraine, but welcoming cooperation on a new nuclear weapons accord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates Shocked by 'Evil' Microchip Theories...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-gates-conspiracies-idUSKBN29W0Q3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft co-founder turned philanthropist Bill Gates says he has been taken aback by the volume of "crazy" and "evil" conspiracy theories about him spreading on social media during the COVID-19 pandemic, but said on Wednesday he would like to explore what is behind them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly let 'college kids' distribute jabs. Result was 'disaster'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/philadelphia-let-e2-80-98college-kids-e2-80-99-distribute-vaccines-the-result-was-a-e2-80-98disaster-volunteers-say/ar-BB1d8ns7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One volunteer alleged that the 22-year-old CEO had pocketed vaccine doses. Another described a “free-for-all” where unsupervised 18- and 19-year-olds vaccinated one another and posed for photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART to build more robot-filled warehouses at stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/plano-texas-0237967389d2cc911f1ee729a9aacf19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Walmart is enlisting the help of robots to keep up with a surge in online orders. The company said Wednesday that it plans to build warehouses at its stores where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>131 arrested on 'calmer' night during Dutch curfew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mark-rutte-general-elections-netherlands-media-social-media-06f771a568eebdac2cdfbb99f6cc0740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — Dutch police said Wednesday that the fourth night of the Netherlands' coronavirus curfew passed more peacefully than the previous three nights marred by rioting. Even...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swearing sign of intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9189539/Science-reveals-swearing-sign-intelligence-creativity-helps-endure-pain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science shows using foul language may be beneficial. People who curse are seen as more honest, found to have a more fluent vocabulary and withstand more pain when using such words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanted: New media bosses, everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wanted-new-media-bosses-everywhere-658eb3b4-062a-4551-97d4-ef8ca4a40fb3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Post is the latest looking for a new boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wear THREE masks?</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2021/01/27/experts-now-say-americans-should-wear-three-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why not just a full Hazmat suit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With All Eyes on Covid, Drug-Resistant Infections Crept In...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/27/with-all-eyes-on-covid-19-drug-resistant-infections-crept-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Covid-19 took hold over the last year, hospitals and nursing homes used and reused scarce protective equipment — masks,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVY 'UFO Patent' Details 'Spacetime Modification Weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/38937/navy-ufo-patent-documents-talk-of-spacetime-modification-weapon-detail-experimental-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy spent three years and considerable sums of money testing the "Pais Effect" and may have transferred the program to another agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT Traders Take on Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/gamestop-stock-market-0689e407-d1a3-4947-b4b5-5aef23c72acf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short-selling is a crucial but dangerous element of efficient markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator presiding over trial taken to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senator-presiding-over-trump-impeachment-000826689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 80-year-old senator presiding over the impeachment trial of Donald Trump was briefly hospitalized Tuesday after sounding hoarse and unwell while being swore in.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
