<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New PRINCE Album To Be Released 5 Years After Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/prince-60-minutes-welcome-2-america-2021-04-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songs from Prince's "Welcome 2 America," an album written and recorded before a 2010 tour, but never made public, will be heard for the first time Sunday night on 60 Minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Music As Addictive As Alcohol, Money, Fast Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/music-addictive-fast-food-alcohol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the reason for this lies in the reward center of the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NFL player kills 5, then self... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rock-hill-shootings-south-carolina-aaf71f2618f139ab3781592634c8e37c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — The gunman who killed five people including a prominent doctor in South Carolina was former NFL pro Phillip Adams, who killed himself early Thursday, according to a source...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro doubling down despite Brazil's soaring death toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20210408-why-is-bolsonaro-doubling-down-despite-brazil-s-soaring-death-toll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases steady at 65,000 per day...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-coronavirus-cases-fourth-wave-4b6f697d-f560-4ec8-9470-c26a9982c939.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A significant fourth wave is still on the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insane Bezos-ENQUIRER Drama Takes Bizarre New Turn...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/insane-jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-005815611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyThe bizarre years-long drama behind the story of Jeff Bezos’ secret extramarital relationship is about to get even weirder. A shady figure affiliated with the National Enquirer claims in court that one of Hollywood’s most powerful players provided the supermarket tabloid with the sordid details of the affair.After Bezos announced in 2018 he was separating from Mackenzie Bezos, his wife of 25 years, the National Enquirer revealed the world’s richest man was having an affair with Lauren Sanchez, a southern California-based television host and pilot. The sleazy supermarket tabloid’s series on the affair—which included racy text messages and suggestive photos between Bezos and Sanchez—set off a bizarre and sprawling public hunt for the source or sources of the information, roping in Sanchez’s now-estranged brother Michael Sanchez, top executives at Enquirer parent company American Media Inc., and even the Saudi government. 1155581071 "LONDON, ENGLAND - JULY 14: Jeff Bezos and his partner, Lauren Sanchez, look on from the Royal Box on Centre Court on Day 13 of The Championships - Wimbledon 2019 at the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club on July 14, 2019 in London, England. (Photo by Simon Stacpoole/Offside/Getty Images)" Simon Stacpoole/Offside/Getty Now, Nikolaos Tzima Hatziefstathiou, a journalist with a strange and disturbing criminal history who reported the story with the National Enquirer and AMI (since rebranded as “A360 Media”), is claiming one major source of the information was Lauren Sanchez’s then-husband, William Morris Endeavor executive Patrick Whitesell.Hatziefstathiou’s allegations are part of a defamation lawsuit Michael Sanchez brought this year against AMI, claiming that the tabloid media company lied when it outed him as the sole source of information about the Bezos affair.In an affidavit filed by Michael Sanchez’s legal team, Hatziefstathiou claimed then-AMI-senior vice president Dylan Howard assigned him to look into Bezos’ affair after he was told about the relationship by Whitesell, the executive chairman of Endeavor, one of the most prominent talent agencies in the world.Hatziefstathiou asserted that the affair was a convenient excuse for the Endeavor executive to break off his marriage, but AMI was intent on protecting him as a source.“Mr. Whitesell discovered the Affair and, by serving as AMI’s secret, undisclosed source, literally turned the Affair into a ‘get out of divorce free card,’ allowing him to leave his wife… through a pre-planned divorce in which he appeared blameless and scandal-free, just months prior to WME’s planned initial public offering,” Hatziefstathiou wrote in the filing.Representatives for Howard and AMI/A360 did not immediately return requests for comment. “This is categorically untrue, and unfortunately not the first time we have seen this desperate attempt from Michael Sanchez to perpetuate this odd and tiresome circus,” Patrick Whitesell’s spokesman told The Daily Beast. “The fact that Patrick has been implicated in this bizarre series of lawsuits and incriminations is a direct result of the character of those involved and is completely disconnected from reality. Any suggestion to the contrary is malicious and libelous.”In Hatziefstathiou’s 2020 resignation letter from AMI, which is included in this week’s filing, he wrote that the company included “blatant lies” in its court filings related to the Bezos affair, saying AMI was misleading the courts about the source of information.But the former AMI journalist himself has a dubious history of legal troubles which could color the court’s view of his reliability and veracity. In 2019, he was charged with 20 criminal counts for a bizarre scam in which he posed as journalists from the New York Times and Good Morning America and created a fake racist email that purported to be from a Delaware County Adult Probation and Parole officer.As the Philly Voice noted, he previously pleaded guilty to calling law enforcement to report a disturbance at his neighbor’s home after sending dozens of prostitutes there, and was told by a judge to stop watching cop movies after trying to set up a drug dealer for the police.Much of Hatziefstathiou’s testimony this week is a somewhat rambling of his defense of his own personal conduct and details of his reporting on the Bezos affair. Additionally, while Hatziefstathiou claims Whitesell was involved, the filing did not include any exhibits beyond his own testimony clearly linking the WME executive to AMI.Still, Hatziefstathiou said in the filing he additionally has “ten terabytes” of data consisting of a million documents about AMI and his coverage of the Bezos affair to support his claims.The question of who leaked information on the Bezos affair to AMI and the Enquirer has sparked a sprawling years-long hunt involving some of the shadiest players in the world of tabloid journalism, entertainment, and corporate espionage. In 2019, The Daily Beast first reported that Michael Sanchez was AMI’s source for the steamy text messages between his sister and Bezos, a revelation the Enquirer later confirmed.In a court filing last July—AMI’s motion to dismiss Michael Sanchez’s lawsuit and sanction him for allegedly abusing the judicial system—the Enquirer’s parent company included a cache of emails, text messages and sworn statements from AMI employees that tended to finger Sanchez as the source of the salacious stories. The court documents painted a picture of Sanchez as a disloyal brother eager to sell out his married sister and her secret billionaire-lover. 1200028606 "MUMBAI, INDIA - JANUARY 16: Lauren Sanchez and Jeff Bezos attend the Amazon Prime Video celebration on January 16, 2020 in Mumbai, India. (Photo by Prodip Guha/Getty Images)" Prodip Guha/Getty AMI ultimately agreed to pay Sanchez $200,000, according to the July 2020 court filing, for “information, photographs, and text messages documenting an affair between Bezos and L. Sanchez.” It was, as it turned out, a losing proposition. Last month, after Los Angeles County Superior Court judge dismissed Michael Sanchez’s separate defamation lawsuit against Bezos and his security consultant Gavin de Becker, Sanchez was ordered to pay the billionaire $218,385 for Bezos’ legal costs.AMI’s court filing, meanwhile, contained chronological inconsistencies, raising questions about the Enquirer’s initial source, that are outlined in detail in Hatziefstathiou’s affidavit alleging that it was Hollywood powerbroker Whitesell who first alerted the tabloid to the Bezos-Sanchez relationship.The text messages, supplied by Michael Sanchez, weren’t the only salacious evidence of the affair in the Enquirer’s possession. And Sanchez maintained he was not the only AMI source, a theory Bezos’ camp seemed to share.In a lengthy 2019 column for The Daily Beast, Bezos’ top security consultant Gavin de Becker wrote that his investigation concluded with “high confidence” that the “Saudis had access to Bezos’ phone, and gained private information. As of today, it is unclear to what degree, if any, AMI was aware of the details.” United Nations experts later lent credence to those claims.While he suggested that the Saudis had access to Bezos’ phone, de Becker publicly wondered why AMI itself almost seemed intent on outing Michael Sanchez as the Enquirer’s source. “What was unusual, very unusual, was how hard AMI people worked to publicly reveal their source’s identity,” he wrote. “First through strong hints they gave to me, and later through direct statements, AMI practically pinned a kick me’ sign on Michael Sanchez.”Bezos wrote in a 2019 Medium post that AMI was trying to “blackmail” him, saying the media company was threatening to publish a “below the belt selfie — otherwise colloquially known as a ‘d*ck pick [sic]’” unless the Washington Post stopped investigating the leak.“Any personal embarrassment AMI could cause me takes a back seat because there’s a much more important matter involved here,” wrote Bezos. “If in my position I can’t stand up to this kind of extortion, how many people can?”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack on Iran ship off Yemen escalates shadow war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-israel-iran-iran-nuclear-united-arab-emirates-9835ba4644959e9cb4584ca999f49002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An attack this week on an Iranian cargo ship that is said to serve as a floating base for Iran's paramilitary Revolutionary Guard forces off the coast of Yemen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Home Inspector Pleasured Self With ELMO Doll In Nursery...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/elmo/elmo-assaulted-798513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While unaware that he was being recorded by a nursery camera, a Michigan home inspector pleasured himself with an Elmo doll, according to police. Kevin Wayne VanLuven, 59, was arraigned yesterday on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businessman plans to go 35,000 feet underwater on historic dive to ocean's deepest point...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/04/08/ohio-larry-connor-dive-mariana-trench-date-set-april-2021/7122098002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A businessman and entrepreneur is scheduled to make two dives to the deepest part of the ocean – each one to depths of more than 35,000 feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol riot defendant flips to help prosecutors against Proud Boys...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/07/politics/capitol-riot-flip-proud-boys/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one of the Capitol riot defendants has flipped against the Proud Boys, agreeing to provide information that could allow the Justice Department to bring a more severe charge against the group's leadership, according to an attorney involved in the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Population Growth Slowest Since 1918...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/america-s-population-growth-looks-to-be-the-slowest-since-1918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s Population Growth Looks to Be the Slowest Since 1918</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Costs Keep Climbing in Threat to Consumer Wallets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/global-food-costs-keep-climbing-080444402.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The global food-price rally that’s stoking inflation worries and hitting consumers around the world shows little sign of slowing.Even with grain prices taking a breather on good crop prospects, a United Nations gauge of global food costs rose for a 10th month in March to the highest since 2014. Last month’s advance was driven by a surge in vegetable oils amid stronger demand and tight inventories, according to Abdolreza Abbassian, a senior economist at the UN’s Food and Agriculture Organization.Food prices are in the longest rally in more than a decade amid China’s crop-buying spree and tightening supplies of many staple products, threatening faster inflation. That’s particularly pronounced in some of the poorest countries dependent on imports, which have limited social safety nets and purchasing power and are struggling with the Covid-19 pandemic.Breakdown of last month’s food costs:The FAO’s food price index rose 2.1% from February.Vegetable oil prices jumped 8% to the highest since June 2011.Meat and dairy costs rose, boosted by Asian demand.Grains and sugar prices fell.Grains prices recently climbed to multiyear highs as China imports massive amounts to feed its hog herds that are recovering from a deadly virus. Still, there are signs that tight supplies may get some relief from upcoming wheat harvests in the Northern Hemisphere.“Generally speaking, supplies for now are adequate,” Abbassian said. “We might have reached a level whereby from now on even if we see price increases, they may be a bit more subtle” than advances seen in previous months, he said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Fauci says surge on way?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/08/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new Covid-19 cases has plateaued at a "disturbingly high level," and the US is at risk from a new surge, Dr. Anthony Fauci warned on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ARCHEGOS MELTDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-04-08/how-bill-hwang-of-archegos-capital-lost-20-billion-in-two-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast rise and even faster fall of a trader who bet big with borrowed money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Have New Offer: Vax Cards...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/08/online-scammers-have-a-new-offer-for-you-vaccine-cards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — On Etsy, eBay, Facebook and Twitter, little rectangular slips of paper started showing up for sale in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin used body weight to pin Floyd's neck and never moved, expert says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/derek-chauvin-used-his-body-weight-to-pin-george-floyd-s-neck-and-never-moved-use-of-force-expert-says/ar-BB1fpqeX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pressure of Chauvin’s body weight — estimated by another witness to be about 140 pounds along with 40 pounds of police equipment including body armor — would have put Floyd at risk of “positional asphyxia,” a known danger that is mentioned in most police training, expert Jody Stiger said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property Taxes Jump Most in Four Years With Sun Belt Catching Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/us-property-taxes-jump-most-in-four-years-with-sun-belt-catching-up/ar-BB1fp1u1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber-Producer Rudin Ex-Staffers Speak Out on Abusive Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/everyone-just-knows-hes-an-absolute-monster-scott-rudins-ex-staffers-speak-out-on-abusive-behavior</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as other Hollywood bullies are being sidelined, the uber-producer behind 'The Social Network' and Broadway’s 'To  Kill a Mockingbird' has been given a pass for his volcanic temper. Now, former employees open up about a boss who left many traumatized: "It was a new level of unhinged."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before becoming terrorist leader, ISIS chief was prison informer for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Before-becoming-a-terrorist-leader-ISIS-chief-16084735.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In confidential interrogation reports, Iraqi detainee M060108-01 is depicted as a model...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'KARDASHIANS' is ending. The Kardashians will never go away...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-Kardashians-is-ending-The-Kardashians-will-16085545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian is one of the most recognizable celebrities on the planet, someone who can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadband use surges 30% during pandemic!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/broadband-use-surged-more-than-30-during-pandemic-industry-group-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it's time to buy a mesh router or pay for better upload speeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline apologizes to cancer survivor who was told to remove hoodie with vulgar word...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article250491574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘American Airlines did a very disrespectful and embarrassing thing to me,’ woman says on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas's conservative gov quietly bucking GOP's dive into culture wars...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/547019-arkansass-conservative-governor-is-quietly-bucking-the-gops-dive-into</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arkansas Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singles ready for casual sex...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/nyc-singles-ready-for-2021s-slutty-summer-of-casual-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few weeks ago, Ashwin Deshmukh saw something he hadn’t in over a year:  “Uhhhh it’s happening. Host is escorting a couple out of a soho restaurant for bathroom shenanigans. They met outside …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan mayor marks homes of patients with red symbol...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210407174659-g0bx8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VENEZUELA-POLITICS:Venezuelan mayor marks homes of COVID patients with red symbol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel Calls Bitcoin 'Chinese Financial Weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/peter-thiel-china-using-bitcoin-093000576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thiel made these comments after he expressing worry the Chinese are using bitcoin to corrode the U.S. financial system. Bitcoin boogeyman Thiel gave his more-than-skeptical sounding comments at a virtual roundtable for members of the Richard Nixon Foundation on April 7. “Even though I’m a pro-crypto, pro-bitcoin maximalist person, I do wonder whether at this … Continued</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military cites rising risk of Chinese move against Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-beijing-taiwan-china-788c254952dc47de78745b8e2a5c3000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The American military is warning that China is probably accelerating its timetable for capturing control of Taiwan, the island democracy that has been the chief source of tension...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Israeli forces' strike Iranian ship in Red Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iranian-ship-attacked-in-the-red-sea-unconfirmed-report-664311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While officially listed as a merchant ship, the Saviz was likely a covert IRGC forward base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz trip to Bahamas part of federal probe into sex trafficking, sources say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/matt-gaetz-trip-to-bahamas-is-part-of-federal-probe-into-sex-trafficking-sources-say/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe rights court: Obligatory jabs 'necessary in democratic society'...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/obligatory-jabs-necessary-in-democratic-society-europe-rights-court-01617875705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) on Thursday ruled that obligatory vaccinations can be seen as necessary in democratic societies, in a landmark judgement after a complaint brought by Czech families over compulsory jabs for children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army vax begins trials...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/04/07/armys-own-vaccine-that-could-fight-covid-variants-begins-clinical-trials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX SITE SHUTS AFTER ADVERSE REACTIONS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/07/covid-vaccine-site-closes-early-after-adverse-reactions-to-jj-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen people at a COVID-19 vaccination site in Colorado had adverse reactions to the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine on Wednesday — shutting down operations for the day, a report said. Peopl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to unveil actions on guns, including new ATF boss... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-violence-merrick-garland-gun-politics-gun-violence-7ddb30681ca3abbf1a0faa286e3df7b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is preparing to unveil a series of executive actions aimed at addressing gun violence, delivering his first major action on gun control since taking office....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discarded masks litter beaches worldwide, threaten sea life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-jersey-oceans-coronavirus-pandemic-environment-california-3d9e892ea922a6bf954159525c0b8d93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANDY HOOK, N.J. (AP) — To the usual list of foul trash left behind or washed up on beaches around the world, add these: masks and gloves used by people to avoid the coronavirus and then discarded...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Autism Linked To Gut Health?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gut-microbiome-autism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado researchers reveal bacterial changes in the stomach predicted behavioral fluctuations among patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm sounded over 'significant' increase in Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210407-alarm-sounded-over-significant-increase-in-covid-cases-in-michigan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alarm sounded over 'significant' increase in Covid cases in Michigan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  McConnell backs away from warning biz to stay out of politics...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/547023-mcconnell-backs-away-from-warning-businesses-to-stay-out-of-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) on Wednesday backed off his stern warning that major companies such as Major League Baseball, Delta and Coca-Cola should stay out of high-profile political fights after they criticized Geor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Departing CNN anchor airs grievances...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/departing-cnn-baldwin-grievances-women-liberal-network</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On her way out the door, departing CNN anchor Brooke Baldwin is airing grievances about the lack of opportunities for women at the liberal network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE suspends sponsorship of Deshaun Watson amid allegations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-rusty-hardin-football-sexual-assault-deshaun-watson-469c00241f79cdaf8f5c7c42456c1d13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike has suspended its endorsement contract with Deshaun Watson amid allegations of sexual assault and harassment against the Houston Texans quarterback. “We are deeply concerned by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Some kind of cult?': Doc depicts tech CEOs downfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/streaming/article/hulu-wework-documentary-47-billion-unicorn-16081429.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among other revelations, former CEO Adam Neumann doesn't know what a latte is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Husband who propped dead wife on couch for kids on Christmas convicted of murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2021/04/07/anaheim-man-who-propped-dead-wife-on-couch-for-kids-on-christmas-convicted-of-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jury finds William Wallace guilty of second degree murder for the death of 26-year-old Za’Zell Preston in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz using sex-trafficking allegations to raise money...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/matt-gaetz-is-using-sex-trafficking-allegations-to-raise-money-asking-for-donations-to-fight-back-against-the-fake-news/ar-BB1fo40i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was reported last week that the DOJ was investigating whether Gaetz had a sexual relationship with a 17-year-old girl and paid for her travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Hill LOSES suit against DAILYMAIL over article exposing 'throuple'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9446539/Katie-Hill-loses-throuple-story-lawsuit-against-Daily-Mail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgraced former congresswoman Katie Hill has lost a lawsuit against DailyMail.com over revealing details of her three-way affair with a campaign staffer in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strong' evidence found for new force of nature..</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/56643677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physicists may have just made a major breakthrough in our understanding of the Universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Church Fenced Off by Authorities for Breaking Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avggb/canadian-church-fenced-off-by-authorities-for-breaking-covid-19-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The church was run by controversial pastor James Coates, who has already been jailed during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doesn't even get a ticket...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/07/why-tiger-woods-wasnt-charged-over-terrifying-high-speed-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods wasn’t slapped with so much as a ticket despite recklessly driving 87 mph in a 45-mph zone for a variety of reasons — including that there were no witnesses, California authoritie…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasty notes came from celebs, not Obama aides, Chappelle says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/07/notes-left-for-trump-staffers-came-from-celebs-dave-chappelle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When former President Donald Trump first moved into the White House in January 2017, his staffers said they found nasty notes stuffed into the drawers and cabinets — a claim President Barack Obama&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYPERSONIC MISSILE FAILS TEST LAUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/business/2021/04/hypersonic-missile-fails-test-launch-b-52-bomber/173186/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force called the ARRW failure “a setback.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-Year-Old Who Stole Minivan, Led Police On Chase -- Just Wanted CHEERIOS...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/06/boy-10-who-took-minivan-and-led-police-on-chase-says-he-just-wanted-to-buy-cheerios/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The boy fled when the officer activated his emergency lights, leading police on a chase that reached speeds of 50 mph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious leader arrested on suspicion of sex assault during exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/religious-leader-arrested-on-suspicion-of-sexual-assault-during-exorcism-664430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Paying Homeless To Clean Up After Themselves -- And It's Working!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/elk-grove-homeless-pay-keeping-clean/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Elk Grove has developed a unique way to get the homeless to clean up after themselves. It's an unusual idea: a city paying homeless people to keep their camps clean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman describes Cuomo's alleged groping at mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/cuomo-alleged-groping-victim-mansion-incident-16078748.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman who has accused Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of groping her at the governor’s mansion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's priciest painting not a full da Vinci, claims doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210407-world-s-priciest-painting-not-a-full-da-vinci-claims-doc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World's priciest painting not a full da Vinci, claims doc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applause for 104-year-old who beat coronavirus -- twice...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/world-latin-america-56667027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carmen Hernandez was given a standing ovation as she left hospital in Colombia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg partners with Charles Koch to push federal marijuana legalization...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/lobbying/546742-Koch-group-joins-marijuana-Snoop-dogg-coalition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group backed by GOP mega-donor Charles Koch, on Tuesday, launched</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers Union Chief: 'Jews now part of ownership class'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/randi-weingarten-has-strong-words-for-jews-who-say-unions-are-an-obstacle-663912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Federation of Teachers President Weingarten speaks on coronavirus and school closures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario to issue 4-week stay-at-home order...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/newsalert-ontario-to-issue-four-week-stay-at-home-order-starting-thursday-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to unveil long-awaited executive action on guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/07/biden-executive-actions-guns-479704</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement, expected for Thursday, comes amid a spate of high-profile shootings and as some advocates have grown frustrated in the White House's delay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: UK variant now dominant strain in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/07/us/uk-variant-dominant-coronavirus-strain/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus variant first identified in the United Kingdom is now the most common strain of coronavirus in the United States, US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE social media's big winner during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/07/youtube-is-social-medias-big-winner-during-the-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube saw the most significant growth of any social media app among American users during the pandemic, according to the Pew Research Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals seeing more young adults with severe symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/07/hospitals-are-seeing-more-young-adults-with-severe-covid-symptoms-cdc-says-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are seeing more and more younger adults in 30s and 40s admitted with severe disease from the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breyer says packing Supreme Court could diminish public trust...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/supreme-court-pack-biden-breyer-trust-785f008a-cd6e-4b41-b6be-6f7ebf99cbaf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breyer warned against justices being seen as "politicians in robes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner explores run for CA gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/caitlyn-jenner-california-governor-newsom-recall-a2815644-5855-4162-9ed9-50c93a01ae0d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jenner is a high-profile Republican and previous Trump supporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis elects 1st Black female mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/chance-rise-st-louis-elects-1st-black-female-mayor-n1263292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are done ignoring the racism that has held our city and our region back,” Jones said in her victory speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland volcano unleashes third lava stream...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210407-iceland-volcano-unleashes-third-lava-stream</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iceland volcano unleashes third lava stream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Lines Up Allies, Nodding at Possible 2024 Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/amp/opinion/politics/pence-forms-advocacy-group-to-highlight-agenda-defend-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under-30s offered alternative to ASTRAZENECA jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-56665517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move comes as review finds link to rare clots getting firmer, but jab still beneficial for most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight to the end...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210407110151-ogoug</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-DEFENCE/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-China sends more jets; Taiwan says it will fight to the end if there's war</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
