<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WEDNESDAY: VOTE TO TRANSMIT IMPEACHMENT ARTICLES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/14/house-vote-wednesday-to-transmit-trump-impeachment-articles-to-senate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Representatives is preparing a likely Wednesday vote to transmit articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump to the Senate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN: I'll Bypass Congress to Cancel Federal Student Debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/14/elizabeth-warren-says-she-can-forgive-student-loan-debt-without-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan, which comes weeks before voting begins in the first primary and caucus states, adds urgency to legislation she introduced over the summer to cancel the bulk of the nation's outstanding student debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to headline Davos summit as Iran drops out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-headline-davos-summit-iran-drops-143858980.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump will be the star attraction at this year's Davos forum, which will also focus on the fallout of climate change and a more inclusive model of capitalism, organisers said Tuesday. The annual gathering of global movers and shakers in the village of Davos in the Swiss Alps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline employee took woman's number from her bag tag, then followed her on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Airline-employee-took-woman-s-number-from-her-bag-14972771.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashley Barno was in a boarding area at San Diego International Airport, awaiting a Chicago-bound flight, when a message from an unfamiliar number flashed across her phone, saying hello and asking how she was doing.  The person then added, "Btw I must tell you that you are gorgeous!"  Barno thanked the sender for the flattery and asked again for his name. How had he gotten her number, she asked, and why was he texting her?  "You guess!!" he told her, adding that he worked for American Airlines, which was operating the flight Barno was waiting to board.  "I just saw you at the airport again!" he wrote, telling her in a later message: "you are looking very gorgeous in grey top today!!"  Barno, clad in a gray shirt, looked around the gate area, glancing over her shoulder. She was scared.  The disturbing encounter, which occurred in April and unfolded over more than 100 text messages that were later shared with The Washington Post, spurred a lawsuit against the airline and its employee over allegations of negligent hiring, sexual harassment and stalking. The interaction has left Barno reeling more than eight months later, nervous when she travels and sometimes fearful she's being watched, her attorney, Joseph Samo, said in an interview.  American Airlines did not answer specific questions about the allegations or the case, but company spokesman Joshua Freed said in a statement that, "The employee involved in the complaint is no longer employed at American Airlines."  "American Airlines takes the privacy and safety of our customers seriously. We investigated the allegations and took appropriate action," Freed said.  The person was not on duty at the time, he said.  The messages continued even after Barno got on the plane.  "This is weird," she wrote to him.  Then she learned he was on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret UFO files could 'gravely damage' national security, Navy says...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/top-secret-ufo-files-gravely-damage-us-national-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense has top-secret classified briefings and a classified video about a UFO incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO POPES: Dispute over former pontiff's role in controversial book...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dispute-over-former-popes-role-controversial-book-112936166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican was gripped Tuesday by a dispute over whether elderly ex-pope Benedict XVI was being used by the Catholic Church's ultra-conservative wing to undermine his successor Pope Francis. At least three Vatican correspondents cited a source close to Benedict saying the former pontiff had not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL DEBATE BEFORE VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-clash-final-debate-iowa-votes-020822527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Democrats braced for Tuesday's final presidential debate before Iowa kicks off the nomination process February 3, and with no candidate yet gaining the upper hand, they were ready to rumble. Former vice president Joe Biden is leading nationally, but no clear frontrunner has emerged in Iowa,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Philippine volcano trembles more, spews lava half-mile high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b3f5c5efe6cba83e0790745a8d5f2ed7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAGAYTAY, Philippines (AP) — A volcano near the Philippine capital spewed lava into the sky and trembled constantly Tuesday, possibly portending a bigger and more dangerous eruption, as tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia executes record number of prisoners...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/saudi-arabia-executed-record-number-prisoners-2019-report/story?id=68250502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia executed record number of prisoners in 2019, a year which saw the kingdom come under scrutiny for its human rights record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER REMOVES VIDEO OF PRINCE HARRY PITCHING MEGHAN MARKLE TO DISNEY CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/twitter-removes-cringey-video-of-prince-harry-pitching-meghan-markle-to-disney-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Showcases worst of cronyism: a brazen display of influence-peddling, among elites of government, big business, and Hollywood...'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vince Vaughn faces backlash after shaking Trump's hand at football game...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/vince-vaughn-trump-handshake-lsu-clemson-tigers-republican-melania-a9282706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen agrees 'period of transition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7882589/Prince-Harry-Prince-William-Prince-Charles-leave-Sandringham-separate-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unprecedented statement came after a summit at Sandringham between the Queen and Princes Charles, William and Harry, with Meghan believed to have dialled in from Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to live longer? Art museums may be key...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/lifestyles/health/want-live-longer-art-museums-may-the-key-study-suggests/p7MFFirkuR2t9y1jeqMAUP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Living longer may be a matter of attending more art museums, theaters and galleries, according to a study published in the BMJ journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speakeasies back in vogue -- in echo of Prohibition era...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-speakeasies-back-vogue-echo-prohibition-era-021241525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A century after the United States clamped down on alcohol and ushered in the Prohibition era, speakeasies are once again popping up behind hidden doors and luring in revelers seeking fancy cocktails with an illicit 1920s vibe. Just a few blocks from the White House in downtown Washington, a steady stream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee to be first black head of Cannes film festival jury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spike-lee-first-black-head-cannes-film-festival-105950497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American director Spike Lee was named president of this year's Cannes film festival jury on Tuesday, becoming the first black head of the panel. The maker of "Malcolm X" and "Do the Right Thing" is the first person of black African descent to preside at the world's biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed up Venezuelans find solace on beach...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fed-venezuelans-solace-beach-013646156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido called for street protests at the weekend in a bid to rekindle popular outrage against President Nicolas Maduro, only a few hundred people turned up. It's a far cry from the tens of thousands he mobilized a year ago after declaring himself interim president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EILISH TO RECORD BOND THEME?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/hans-zimmer-confirmed-james-bond-pic-no-time-to-die-billie-eilish-record-theme-1202829945/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar-winning composer Hans Zimmer has officially taken over the reins on the next James Bond pic, No Time To Die, replacing Dan Romer. The James Bond twitter account tweeted the following message …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO says new China virus could spread, warns hospitals worldwide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200114111930-u8ea4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/PNEUMONIA-WHO (UPDATE 1, TV):UPDATE 1-WHO says new China coronavirus could spread, warns hospitals worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran makes arrests over plane disaster as protests rage on...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200114111028-rpkhe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-CRASH/ (WRAPUP 2, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 2-Iran makes arrests over plane disaster as protests rage on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LIVING ROBOT' DEVELOPED BY SCIENTISTS USING FROG EMBRYOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/jan/13/scientists-use-stem-cells-from-frogs-to-build-first-living-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers foresee myriad benefits for humanity, but also acknowledge ethical issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BURNOUT' LINKED WITH IRREGULAR HEARTBEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-01-14/burnout-linked-with-irregular-heartbeat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do the Machines Driving Markets Remember 2000?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2020-01-14/u-s-stocks-rally-starts-to-resemble-2000-tech-euphoria-k5derskz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian gas company at center of impeachment 'hacked by Russian agents'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51103556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian energy company Burisma is at the centre of President Donald Trump's impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up to 10 Republican senators consider bucking Trump on war powers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478093-up-to-10-gop-senators-consider-bucking-trump-on-war-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 10 Republican senators are considering bucking President Trump on a resolution that would limit his ability to take military action against Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHEP SMITH TO MSNBC?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jitters-at-msnbc-as-brass-eyes-moving-chuck-todd-and-talks-to-shep-smith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chuck Todd’s daily show could move to mornings, causing angst among the show’s staff. Other potential changes could alter weekends and, eventually, the network’s primetime roster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP leadership: There aren't 51 votes to dismiss articles of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478080-gop-leadership-there-arent-51-votes-to-dismiss-trump-articles-of-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  66% Want To See Bolton Testify In Senate Impeachment Trial...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters Divided On Killing Of A Top Iranian General, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; 66% Want To See Bolton Testify In Senate Impeachment Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 73: Suzanne Somers Boasts About Libido,  '8 Orgasms In Couple Hours'... </title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/suzanne-somers-new-way-to-age-threes-company-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor and author discusses her life at 73 and reminisces about her days on Three's Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 teen hunters charged with animal cruelty after attack on wounded deer...</title>
      <link>https://fox43.com/2020/01/10/teens-accused-of-torturing-deer-on-video-charged-with-animal-cruelty-related-offenses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox43.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON COUNTY -- One of the two teens allegedly seen torturing a whitetail deer in a video that went viral last month has been charged with aggravated animal cruelty and related offenses, court documents show. Alexander Brock Smith, 18, of Brookville, Jefferson County, is charged with four felony counts of aggravated cruelty to animals, one misdemeanor count of corruption of minors, a misdemeanor count of cruelty to animals, a misdemeanor count of altering or destroying physical evidence, and summary offenses of disturbance of animal or wildlife, unlawful taking of game or wildlife, unlawful hunting devices or methods, and a hunting violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems unveil billboard showing Trump tossing paper towels as Pence plans to visit Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/politics/os-ne-trump-billboard-kissimmee-20200113-kxgbg6wqgbd4vf3ks7q7tafs7a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billboard shows a photo of Trump throwing rolls of paper towels to victims of the hurricane in Puerto Rico and includes the phrase “Prohibido Olvidar,” which in English translates to “Never Forget.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN MOVES TO TOP IN IOWA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-leads-democratic-field-in-poll-of-iowa-caucus-goers/ar-BBYUN1M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's father of 4 and worked as a chemist. Now he's accused of murder and cannibalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/2020/01/13/accused-grindr-killer-cannibal-father-4-worked-chemist/4439756002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Latunski had a high paying job as a chemist and has 4 kids. Now he is accused of killing and eating parts of Kevin Bacon, a man he met on Grindr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Hollywood less trustworthy than govt or Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90451213/sorry-tom-hanks-and-oprah-americans-think-amazon-and-google-are-much-more-trustworthy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USPS, Amazon, Google, PayPal, The Weather Channel, and Chick-fil-A, are among the most trusted brands in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX launches 'FOX SOUL' channel targeting black audience...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2020/01/13/fox-launches-fox-soul-streaming-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Soul includes original content featuring Los Angeles radio host Tammi Mac; Mike Hill and Donny Harrell; and Keyshia Cole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Of-A-Kind Storm-Chasing Vehicle; Withstands 175 MPH Winds...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/tornado-intercept-vehicle-ryan-shepard-colorado-storm-chasing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A storm chaser who has spent more than a decade following severe weather has brought a unique tool to Colorado so he can travel toward tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo says Iraqi leaders privately want American troops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pompeo-says-iraqi-leaders-privately-want-us-troops-210738727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo alleged Monday that Iraqi leaders have told him privately they support the US troop presence, despite public appeals for them to leave. The Iraqi parliament last week voted to rescind the invitation to foreign troops after a US strike at the Baghdad airport killed a top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California weighs unique intersex surgery ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa38740d8906996ce1e137c30d814823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California lawmakers are considering a first-of-its-kind ban on medically unnecessary surgeries for children born with ambiguous or conflicting genitalia until they are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department security officials weren't notified of 'imminent' threats to US embassies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/politics/state-embassy-threat-iran-blindsideded/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department officials involved in US embassy security were not made aware of imminent threats to four specific US embassies, two State Department officials tell CNN, further undermining President Donald Trump's claims that the top Iranian general he ordered killed earlier this month posed an imminent threat to the diplomatic outposts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard prof sues NYTIMES over Epstein donations story...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/478025-harvard-professor-sues-nyt-over-epstein-donations-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harvard law professor is suing The New York Times, accusing the paper of publishing "false and defamatory" information and employing "clickbait" in an article about him. Lawrence Lessig, the legal scholar and politic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at Pensacola Navy base was 'act of terrorism,' AG says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/13/naval-air-station-pensacola-shooting-act-terrorism-attorney-general-says/4454574002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi pilot Mohammed Alshamrani opened fire on Dec. 6 on service members at Naval Air Station Pensacola, killing three and injuring eight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's campaign rallies Wall Street donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/13/joe-biden-campaign-chairman-rallies-wall-street-donors-for-fundraising-push.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's campaign chairman privately met with some of Wall Street's top donors last week in an attempt to rally them around the former vice president's push for the Democratic nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Manager to Get Crushed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/13/red-soxs-alex-cora-is-going-to-get-crushed-after-astros-cheating-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you thought the punishments levied at the Astros following MLB’s investigation into sign-stealing were harsh, just wait. Current Red Sox skipper and former Houston coach Alex Cora likely still f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US budget deficit running 11.8% higher this year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/179b7a049feebdc199d1699408bb5310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. budget deficit through the first three months of this budget year is up 11.8% from the same period a year ago, putting the country on track to record its first $1 trillion deficit in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain secretly funded REUTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-media/britain-secretly-funded-reuters-in-1960s-and-1970s-documents-idUSKBN1ZC20H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British government secretly funded Reuters in the 1960s and 1970s at the beh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb in Van of NJ Shooting Attack Suspects Could've Killed People 5 Football Fields Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/bomb-in-van-of-nj-shooting-attack-suspects-couldve-killed-people-5-football-fields-away-officials/2259079/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. attorney in New Jersey and the head of the local FBI said Monday that the bomb found in the van of alleged domestic terrorists Francine Graham and David Anderson could have killed or maimed people up to five football fields away. They also said there was enough material in the van to make a second bomb. Four innocent…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTROS GM, Manager Suspended 1 Year for 'Cheating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28476780/sources-houston-astros-jeff-luhnow-aj-hinch-suspended-1-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astros GM Jeff Luhnow and manager AJ Hinch have been suspended for one year after an MLB investigation found the team used technology to cheat during its World Series-winning 2017 season, it was announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How High Schooler Uses Online Trick To Scoop CNN...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/01/11/dublin-teens-url-sleuthing-trick-scoops-cnns-iowa-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN unveiled a much-anticipated Iowa Democratic primary poll, but Dublin High School senior Arjav Rawal had already done it for them, tweeting out the numbers 20 minutes earlier. How?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Entertainment, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SAYS A WOMAN CAN'T WIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/politics/bernie-sanders-elizabeth-warren-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stakes were high when Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren met at Warren's apartment in Washington, DC, one evening in December 2018. The longtime friends knew that they could soon be running against each other for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Yoga instructor punched, kicked man for using phone during 'ONCE UPON TIME IN HOLLYWOOD' screening...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/once-upon-an-assault-287569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 13--An Iowa yoga instructor allegedly pummeled a fellow moviegoer whose use of a phone during a showing of “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood” was purportedly responsible for “ruining the film” f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S CHEAPEST MAN:  Bezos gives Oz fire victims just $690,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/249608/jeff-bezos-slammed-for-giving-australia-fire-victims-just-690000-the-same-as-you-giving-0-0006-of-your-salary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON billionaire Jeff Bezos has been slammed for donating a tiny fraction of his mega-wealth to the Australian bush fire fund. The uber-rich tech tycoon has pledged $690,000 ($1m Aus) to the reli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight polls, impeachment, billionaire wild cards: Uncertainty reigns in  2020 Dem race...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/tight-polls-impeachment-billionaire-wild-cards-uncertainty-reigns-in-the-2020-democratic-race/ar-BBYUr9K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein spy says he's not sorry for secretly trailing 91 Hollywood figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7881959/Harvey-Weinstein-SPY-says-hes-not-sorry-trailing-91-Hollywood-figures-including-Rose-McGowan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seth Freedman, left, worked for private intelligence agency Black Cube. They were hired by Weinstein, right with accuser McGowan, in July 2017 to look into 'a plot against him'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stadium Ran Out Of Fireworks During Scoring Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/chiefs-run-out-of-fireworks-at-arrowhead-stadium-during-51-point-scoring-blitz-in-playoff-win-over-texans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was so much Kansas City offense that Arrowhead couldn't keep up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/stories-51061969/hired-by-weinstein-to-spy-on-celebrities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spy posed as a journalist to extract information from Hollywood stars for Weinstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals present united front...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queen-gathers-royals-crisis-meeting-prince-harry-055916398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry and his brother Prince William put on a united front as they were summoned to showdown talks Monday on Harry's future after he and his wife Meghan unilaterally announced they were quitting as front-line British royalty. William, 37, and 35-year-old Harry formed a close bond following</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies Gun Confiscation Request For First Time Under Red Flag Law In Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/12/colorado-judge-red-flag-confiscation-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, a judge has denied a request to take away a man's guns under Colorado's new red flag law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113140914-x3iun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TOPLESS (PIX):U.S. Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumbling volcano shuts down Philippine capital...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113050635-e0zn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands evacuated as seismologists warn that a hazardous eruption could happen any time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Panic: It's Not Clear That Colorado's Mystery Drones Even Exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/pkeb9k/mass-panic-its-not-clear-that-colorados-mystery-drones-even-exist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone hobbyists say the media and the FAA regularly uses drone panic to enact strict regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women Scored Record 31% of All Contenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/oscars-2020-women-record-31-percent-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;65 of the 209 nominees this year were women despite leaving out "Little Women" filmmaker Greta Gerwig</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: William Barr, President's Sword and Shield...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/01/20/william-barr-trumps-sword-and-shield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Attorney General’s mission to maximize executive power and protect the Presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Nets Blast Trump with 93% Neg News...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2020/01/13/tvs-trump-news-three-fourths-impeachment-and-93-negative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first 100 days since House Democrats began their impeachment push, ABC, CBS and NBC have aggressively aided the effort. An MRC analysis finds the Big Three evening newscasts battered the President with 93% negative coverage and promoted impeachment at the expense of nearly all other Trump news. At the same time, the broadcast networks donated at least 124 hours of wall-to-wall live coverage as they pre-empted regular programming in favor of House Democrat-led impeachment activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX LEADS ALL STUDIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/oscars-netflix-leads-all-hollywood-studios-24-nominations-1268945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Disney empire picked up 23 nods, while Sony makes a huge comeback with 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will alleged CIA misbehavior set Assange free?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/477939-will-cia-misbehavior-set-julian-assange-free</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior of UC Global and the CIA seems indistinguishable from the government’s behavior in the Ellsberg case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: ESPN Planning 'Historic' Offer for Tony Romo; Between $10-14M?</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/report-espn-to-make-cbs-tony-romo-a-historic-offer-to-join-its-nfl-coverage-033157777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Romo was an instant star at CBS, and ESPN reportedly wants him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker suspends... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/sen-cory-booker-suspends-presidential-campaign/story?id=67472609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Cory Booker ends presidential campaign</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
