<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ROME IN RUINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/24/travel/rome-pollution-trash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some worry that the city is in danger of becoming a dump. Not a “rubbish heap of history,” or a precious junkyard of antiquities, but an actual garbage dump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fishermen rescued by cruise ship after stranded at sea for 3 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-stranded-fisherman-rescued-cruise-ship-20181224-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean Chief Meteorologist James Van Fleet wrote on Twitter that the men went adrift on Dec. 1, 2018, after falling sleeping as they let their nets soak. When they awoke, they realized heavy wind had blown them away from their gear had been.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Opal Tower: Thousands evacuated after 'crack'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-46671811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents reported a loud "cracking noise" in the new building at Sydney Olympic Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE Tom Brady Health Questions After ANOTHER Poor Performance...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/24/patriots-tom-brady-health-mcl-nfl-week-17-playoffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a whole lot of chatter about the health of one Tom Brady. But the Patriots quarterback remains adamant that he is indeed healthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Song prompts 200 teens to explode into massive fight at skating rink...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article223514530.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two hundred youths erupted into a sprawling fight early Sunday at Virginia skating rink and police in Roanoke say they don’t know what started it. Some witnesses say the fight began over a song.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia probes mysterious hole in International Space Station capsule...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/international-space-station-soyuz-capsule-mysterious-hole-drilled-from-inside-russian-law-enforcement-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian cosmonaut who recently returned to Earth is revealing more details about the mysterious hole in a Soyuz capsule docked to the International Space Station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOCTOR: 'Selfie Wrist' Growing...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/22/selfie-wrist-injuries-doctor-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Levi Harrison explained that the condition is caused by hyper-flexing your wrist inwards to capture the perfect selfie angle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY JEER: Santa Egged Riding Fire Truck Through Community...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/12/24/santa-claus-egged-fire-truck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Essex Volunteer Fire Company said their truck was egged as they transported Santa Claus through the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of global conflict over nuclear pact collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russia-warns-global-conflict-over-nuclear-pact-collapse-095918391--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia said on Saturday that the scrapping of a Cold War era nuclear pact may lead to an arms race and direct confrontation between several global regions, after a proposal by Moscow was rejected in a United Nations vote. Moscow had put forward a resolution in support of the 1987 Intermediate-range</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  Fed 'Only Problem Our Economy Has'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/treasury-secretary-works-to-calm-investor-jitters-11545665311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump criticized the Federal Reserve, calling the central bank the “only problem our economy has” and likening its policies to a golfer who can’t putt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Extend Fall Despite Mnuchin Bid to Reassure Investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-slip-amid-treasury-department-comments-11545642300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bruising stock selloff continued, erasing more than 650 points from the Dow Jones Industrial Average as Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin tried to instill calm into a jittery market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET WEAPON:  IVANKA AND JARED BREAK DC GRIDLOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/ivanka-scores-her-own-big-win-joins-jared-as-trumps-secret-to-bipartisan-deals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Kushner isn’t the only member of his family with a winning touch on bipartisan deals in acrimonious Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-generation inspiration...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/why-are-democrats-trying-to-annihilate-an-beto-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The howls from the Chapo wing of the Internet say as much about Bernie Sanders’s diminished stature as they do about the golden boy from Texas. Is Beto the real deal, or just a Davos Democrat on a skateboard?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman disguised as Rudolph robs store...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/12/24/suspected-burglar-dressed-rudolph-colorado-police/2405348002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect who burglarized a Colorado business last week was caught on video dressed as 'Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer.' Police want to notify Santa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron James Apologizes for 'Jewish Money' Slam...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/lebron-james-apologizes-for-jewish-money-instagram-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It definitely was not the intent, obviously, to hurt anybody," the basketball star tells ESPN in an interview after a Laker's game Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al-Qaeda terror group returns to target airliners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/al-qaeda-terror-group-returns-to-target-airliners-mlj3lgf87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Al-Qaeda is resurgent and seeking to carry out new terrorist atrocities against airliners and airports, the security minister Ben Wallace warned last night. The terrorist group behind the 9/11...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo cries in court...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8049581/el-chapo-cries-court-twin-daughters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOTORIOUS drug lord Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman burst into tears in the courtroom after his twin daughters made a surprise appearance during his trial. The 61-year-old sobbed in front of the jury whe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Zayn defying expectations, remaining in ascent...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/23/zayn-malik-icarus-falls-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RCA)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezulean exodus has Brazil at breaking point...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/dec/24/venezuelan-exodus-brazil-at-breaking-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Brazil threatens to quit the new UN migration pact, its border-town shelters are bursting at the seams, with hundreds more arriving each day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students launch Satanic club at NC State...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/students-launch-satanic-club-at-nc-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mission includes to 'reject tyrannical authority' ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toubling insider knowledge?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/whats-behind-steve-mnuchins-press-release/578968/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury secretary put out an alarming—and confusing—press release on Sunday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Joy From Giving Lasts Much Longer Than Joy From Getting...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/joy-from-giving-lasts-longer-joy-from-getting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this season of giving and getting, the findings are in. It is more blessed to give than to receive. According to two new studies conducted by researchers with the University of Chicago and Northwestern University, giving to others rather than to ourselves makes us happier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake priest unmasked after 18 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/americas/fake-colombian-priest-unmasked-after-18-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AFP) - A Colombian man who pretended to be a Roman Catholic priest for 18 years hearing confessions and celebrating weddings, was exposed just before Christmas, the diocese in Spain where he was preaching said Monday (Dec 24).. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid shutdown, bigger worries are brewing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Amid-shutdown-bigger-worries-are-brewing-13486674.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Bernardine and Russell Yamamoto arrived in Washington from their home in Hawaii - their first-ever trip to the nation's capital - to find the federal government shutting down. But as the couple waited to tour the U.S. Capitol on Saturday, the shutdown was the least of their worries. "Washington just seems to be in chaos," said Russell Yamamoto, 62. Bernadine, 60, agreed. "What is going on? What is happening? A lot of people resigning from office," she said. "It doesn't give you a sense of comfort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE: 'MARY POPPINS' HITS SOUR NOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/23/mary-poppins-returns-is-disneys-third-big-live-action-disaster-for-2018-with-just-31-mil-opening-weekend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a good thing Disney bought all those other companies like LucasFilm, Marvel,  and Pixar. Back in the actual Mouse House, it hasn’t been such a happy year for the studio’s liv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock jock ordered to co-host show with feminists after sexism accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.sbs.com.au/news/argentinian-shock-jock-ordered-to-co-host-show-with-feminists-after-sexism-accusations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sbs.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angel Etchecopar is well-known for his verbal attacks on feminists and is now on probation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Plunge Protection Team'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-treasury/top-trump-official-calls-bankers-will-convene-plunge-protection-team-idUSKCN1OM0LJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's Treasury secretary called top U.S. bankers on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where's the Beef? Burgers Must Be Meat, Ranchers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2018/12/21/wheres-the-beef-burgers-must-be-meat-ranchers-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beef industry wants to limit what food producers can describe as “meat.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Cold, Dark,  Lacks Parking. But Is This Finnish Town World's Happiest?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/24/world/europe/finland-happiness-social-services.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polling suggests that Kauniainen, a small suburb of the Finnish capital, is the most satisfied town in the world’s happiest country. The secret may be the wealth of state-funded services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie-world's war on Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/inside-bernie-world-s-war-beto-o-rourke-n951016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Texas congressman's star rises, Sanders supporters turn up the heat: "Reading Karl Marx is cool. Doing a livestream while you’re doing your laundry is a gimmick."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -653</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dow-sp-logs-largest-decline-ever-on-christmas-eve-2018-12-24?mod=newsviewer_click</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU COALITION COLLAPSES; ISRAEL HEADING TO EARLY ELECTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Israel-headed-to-early-elections-in-April-575277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"With God's help, we will win," said Netanyahu, who vowed to form the same coalition after the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONELINESS, ISOLATION AS BAD FOR HEALTH AS CHRONIC DISEASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2018-12-24/loneliness-and-isolation-as-bad-for-health-as-chronic-diseases-doctor-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Nicaraguan journalist detained for 'terrorism' in press crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181224-second-nicaraguan-journalist-accused-terrorism-latest-crackdown-dissent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second journalist critical of Nicaraguan President Daniel Ortega was accused Sunday of inciting terrorism after authorities raided the TV station's offices in their latest salvo against independent media and nongovernmental organisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIEGEL to file criminal complaint against cheating reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181223-spiegel-file-criminal-complaint-against-cheating-reporter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spiegel to file criminal complaint against cheating reporter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers fear wider spread of paralysis linked to mystery virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/science-medicine/2018/12/21/medical-researchers-fear-wider-spread-paralysis-linked-mysterious-polio-like-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medical researchers fear that more children will develop paralysis from a mysterious polio-like illness that has struck every two years since...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much does $5 billion buy? 215 miles...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/12/21/much-border-wall-5b-buy-215-miles-half-already-fenced-trump-aides-say-shutdown-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Homeland Security officials laid out the stakes in the budget brinkmanship that threatens a partial government shutdown late Friday:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Human beings to live FOREVER in 30 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/749484/immortality-human-biology-science-negligible-senescence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY: Trump to visit Erdogan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6527441/Official-Trump-agrees-visit-Turkey-2019-no-date-set.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman for Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan said Monday that President Donald Trump has accepted an invitation to visit the country that straddles Asia and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive explosion rocks Mount Etna; Erupts with huge ash cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6526923/Mount-Etna-releases-gigantic-ash-cloud-Sicily.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents and tourists near the volcano took to social media to share stunning visuals of Italy's Mount Etna, the largest active volcano in Europe, which has been erupting throughout December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Run, a wave is coming!'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6526385/Officials-warn-tsunami-strike-Indonesia-death-toll-huge-wave-climbs-281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials have warned people living near Anak Krakatau to stay away from beaches amid fears constant eruptions at the Indonesian volcano could trigger further tsunamis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO SANTA IN SIGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/24/us-stock-futures-fall-slightly-as-the-dow-attempts-to-rebound-from-its-worst-week-in-a-decade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks plunged on Monday in their worst Christmas Eve trading ever, as the S&amp;P 500 entered a bear market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Raise Possibility There Was No Drone at Gatwick Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/24/uk-police-drone-at-gatwick-airport-suspects-released.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They led to three days of travel chaos and 1,000 flights being canceled or diverted, but drone sightings at Gatwick Airport last week are still managing to cause confusion and uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startles Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-steven-mnuchin-bank-ceos-20181223-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury secretary called the heads of the biggest U.S. banks to confirm that they are financially sound and not experiencing excessive financial stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 300 robots reorganize autonomously...</title>
      <link>https://www.c4isrnet.com/unmanned/robotics/2018/12/23/watch-a-swarm-of-300-robots-reorganize-autonomously/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c4isrnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research into self-organizing robots could lead to better autonomous military swarms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Enters Third Day With No Urgency to Reopen Government...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/shutdown-enters-third-day-with-no-urgency-to-reopen-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No signs of urgency to resolve President Trumpâ€™s fight over border wall money as lawmakers leave Washington for Christmas.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risks Making Bad Situation Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/mnuchin-bid-to-calm-markets-risks-making-bad-situation-worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mnuchin Bid to Calm Markets Risks Making Bad Situation Worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators Say Nothing Out of Ordinary in Markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-regulators-tell-mnuchin-nothing-out-of-ordinary-in-markets-jq2ijbtp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The regulators briefed Mnuchin on their plans for monitoring markets during the government shutdown, and the state of markets.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Tech's Deceptively Good Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/closing-the-books-on-tech-s-deceptively-good-year#gs.WIue4H4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Closing the Books on Techâ€™s Deceptively Good Year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-Month Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/asian-stocks-set-to-slip-yen-up-as-caution-reigns-markets-wrap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian Stocks Set to Slip, Yen Up as Caution Reigns: Markets Wrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg blasts Trump as 'recklessly emotional and senselessly chaotic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2018-12-23/shutdown-stock-slump-and-mattis-exit-cap-grim-year-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash, emeralds found in faith healer's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/aa283672f8d04091abe6747ecc29451b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil's state police say they have found a suitcase full of cash and emeralds hidden in the home of a faith healer accused of sexual abuse by hundreds of women. The suitcase was discovered at the home of Joao Teixeira de Faria on Friday in a basement accessed by a trap door in a closet. Police in the central state of Goias said they also found about $300,000 worth of Brazilian reals. They had yet to appraise the emeralds. De Faria worked for several decades in rural Brazil as a healer who claimed he could cure diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like a cancer:' Militias grow, control swaths of Rio de Janeiro...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3114823293824992ae13365d540d040e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — The latest scheme works like this: Brazilian paramilitary groups buy boxes of cigarettes in neighboring Paraguay for 14 cents a pack and then smuggle them back home, where prices and taxes are much higher, and sell them for up to $2.15. The cigarettes offer the militias the lion's share of an estimated $330 million in profits and add to a portfolio of illicit operations the groups have honed over two decades, including imposing surcharges on cable service, electricity and transportation. The groups are also known to conduct extortion and summary executions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: President would accept less money for border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2cb11c3652bb4f18a760216bf53b58ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump was meeting with his Homeland Security secretary and other officials on Monday to discuss border security issues as a partial government shutdown over his U.S.-Mexico border wall entered Christmas without a clear resolution in sight. Though both sides have traded offers over the dollars, they remain far apart on the wall. The White House insists Trump will reject any deal that does not include money for a wall or fence; Democrats were holding firm in their opposition to a wall or other physical barrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessed horse unearthed in ancient stable near Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2bf879bbdabc4d038fed74cc1b0f4926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Archaeologists have unearthed the petrified remains of a harnessed horse and saddle in the stable of an ancient villa in a Pompeii suburb. Pompeii archaeological park head Massimo Osanna told Italian news agency ANSA that the villa belonged to a high-ranking military officer, perhaps a general, during ancient Roman times. Osanna was quoted on Sunday as saying the remains of two or three other horses were also discovered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One year in, tax law faces test with filing season...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/422539-one-year-in-trumps-tax-law-faces-next-test-with-filing-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump signed his much-anticipated tax overhaul bill into law on Dec. 22, 2017. One year later, it has fallen short of GOP expectations on several fronts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona on high alert after US issues terror warning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/422718-barcelona-on-high-alert-after-us-issues-terror-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security in Barcelona is reportedly on high alert following a warning from the U.S. of the risk of a terror attack over the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No warning meant no escape...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/no-warning-meant-no-escape-indonesia-tsunami-064204651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unpredictable chain of events and an inadequate early warning system combined to deadly effect with the tsunami that slammed into coastal areas of Indonesia killing nearly 300 people, disaster officials and experts said Monday. The killer wave struck tourist beaches and low-lying settlements on both</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami triggered by volcano kills nearly 400 in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/world/indonesia-tsunami-live-updates-java-sumatra-dead-injured-5505771/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesia volcano tsunami live updates: According to a statement from the Meteorology, Climatology and Geophysics Agency (BMKG), "the tsunami hit several areas of the Sunda Strait, including beaches in Pandeglang regency, Serang, and South Lampung."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court intervenes in apparent Mueller mystery case...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/23/robert-mueller-john-roberts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the first time a Mueller case has reached the Supreme Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air marshals moved to back of plane...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/exclusive-tsa-planning-major-shift-air-marshal-operations/story?id=59974300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some fear it could make passengers less safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea ordered to pay $501 million to Otto Warmbier parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/north-korea-must-pay-501-million-to-otto-warmbiers-parents-judge-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American judge has ruled that Kim Jong Un’s North Korean regime must pay $501 million to the parents of Otto Warmbier after their son died following his time spent in captivity there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside lab protecting US infrastructure from cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/80749f2dd5a84bb49b7aceb1a4c43b8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IDAHO FALLS, Idaho (AP) — It's called the "Dark Side" because the 50 workers there prefer to keep the lights low so they can dim the brightness on their computer screens. Or maybe it's because of what they do in cyber research and development. Questions about exactly what goes on at the heart of one of the United States' primary cybersecurity facilities at the Idaho National Laboratory aren't always answered, and photos by outsiders aren't allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so deadly?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-46667970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
