<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Singapore preps for Trump-Kim summit with fresh paint and arrests...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-fg-singapore-summit-prep-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Singapore gears up to host the historic summit between an unpredictable U.S. President and a little-seen North Korean dictator, the lead-up featured a cat-and-mouse game between an aggressive international press corps and a notoriously controlled city-state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron handshake leaves mark on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/firm-friends-macron-handshake-leaves-mark-trump-140529338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They once shook hands for an eye-watering 29 seconds, with neither man willing to show a hint of weakness. Now Emmanuel Macron has left a firm impression on Donald Trump in their latest squeezing contest. Photos that have gone viral show how Macron turned part of Trump's hand pale with a blood-squeezing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some See End Of World Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/in-donald-trump-some-see-the-end-of-the-world-order-1864774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime partners worry about the lasting effect of confrontations with the U.S. president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man found dead at Bonnaroo...</title>
      <link>https://consequenceofsound.net/2018/06/man-found-dead-at-bonnaroo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;consequenceofsound.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;13 people have died at Bonnaroo over the course of the festival’s 17-year history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man commits suicide at Mecca's Grand Mosque...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-5824437/Man-commits-suicide-Meccas-Grand-Mosque.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has committed suicide by throwing himself off the roof of the Grand Mosque in Islam's holiest city of Mecca, Saudi police said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sculpture of king's head dating back 3,000 years sets off modern-day mystery caper...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd3713cc12f24a4090d1a34b650bdd5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — An enigmatic sculpture of a king's head dating back nearly 3,000 years has set off a modern-day mystery caper as scholars try to figure out whose face it depicts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In charging Senate staffer and seizing reporter's records, DOJ ignites debate over leak crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-charging-Senate-staffer-and-seizing-reporter-s-12979970.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Justice Department took a significant step this week toward advancing its long-promised crackdown on leaks, charging a former Senate Intelligence Committee staffer with lying to the FBI about his contacts with reporters, and seizing the phone and email records of a journalist to help make its case. As the man charged in the brewing controversy made his first court appearance, free-press advocates warned that federal prosecutors' heavy-handed tactics might send a further chill through the government, where officials already are reluctant to share information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat traces 'found in vegan and vegetarian ready meals'...</title>
      <link>http://www.itv.com/news/2018-06-09/meat-traces-found-in-vegan-and-vegetarian-ready-meals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China hosts Russia, Iran for summit as US tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-hosts-russia-iran-summit-us-tensions-rise-211038252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping will open late Saturday a two-day regional security summit attended by Russia, Iran and other allies confronting rising tensions with the US over trade and Washington's withdrawal from the Iranian nuclear deal. Armoured vans lined the streets of the coastal city of Qingdao</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'50s Motels Go From Bleak to Chic...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/50s-motels-go-from-bleak-to-chic-1528480694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motor lodges and motels from California to Long Island are getting dolled up, giving road trippers reasons to linger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robo-calls targeting Mexico presidential frontrunner put voters on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-calls/robo-calls-targeting-mexico-presidential-frontrunner-put-voters-on-edge-idUSKCN1J503X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spate of calls in recent days attacking Mexico's leftist presidential frontrunner has put his supporters on edge and underscored the last-ditch attempts to dent the candidate's commanding lead three weeks before the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Robot Encounter: Dinner, Drinks and a Massage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/your-next-robot-encounter-dinner-drinks-and-a-massage-1528542000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collaborative robots that work alongside humans—“cobots”—are getting cheaper and easier to program. That is encouraging businesses to put them to work at new tasks in bars, restaurants and clinics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their Grandparents Toppled a Dictator. Now They Are the Revolutionaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/their-grandparents-toppled-a-dictator-now-they-are-the-revolutionaries-1528545600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicaraguan students whose families fought with Daniel Ortega to oust the Somozas now lead a rebellion against Ortega’s own family dynasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justify bidding for rare Triple Crown sweep in Belmont...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/369a2723adca4f40aa047ad709464bb0/Justify-bidding-for-rare-Triple-Crown-sweep-in-Belmont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Three races at various distances on three different tracks over a span of five weeks.        Just 12 horses have swept the Triple Crown, one of the rarest f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns oil executives: 'Climate change' may 'destroy civilization'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/391470-pope-warns-oil-executives-climate-change-may-destroy-civilization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Saturday issued a dire warning to top oil executives, saying that climate change could “destroy civilization.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers stole sensitive Navy undersea warfare plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/china-hacked-a-navy-contractor-and-secured-a-trove-of-highly-sensitive-data-on-submarine-warfare/2018/06/08/6cc396fa-68e6-11e8-bea7-c8eb28bc52b1_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stolen material included secret plans to develop a supersonic anti-ship missile for use on U.S. submarines by 2020, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIRD TIME: MANAFORT HIT WITH FRESH INDICTMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/08/special-counsel-robert-mueller-files-new-indictment-against-paul-manafort-nbc-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller earlier this week asked a federal judge to revoke Manafort's bond and jail him because of alleged witness tampering in advance of his upcoming federal criminal trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian official admits for first time to aiding 9/11 terrorists...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/08/iran-facilitated-passage-of-9-11-attackers-politician/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Our government agreed not to stamp the passports'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGONY OF DEFEAT</title>
      <link>http://abc7news.com/sports/warriors-win-2018-nba-title-blow-out-cavs-in-game-4-108-85/3577657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Golden State Warriors did not hold back against the Cavaliers, putting together an incredible team performance in Cleveland. The Dubs beat the Cavs 108-85, securing their third NBA title in four years in a blowout game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton Defends Al Franken...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/laurettabrown/2018/06/08/bill-clinton-defends-franken-it-was-a-difficult-case-and-the-snl-women-defended-him-n2488880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian official admits for first time to aiding 9/11 terrorists...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-admits-facilitating-9-11-terror-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian officials have admitted to facilitating the 9/11 terrorist attacks in the U.S. by secretly aiding the free travel of al Qaeda operatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone surveillance state becomes real...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1299947/this-is-the-week-that-the-drone-surveillance-state-became-real/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hardware and the AI are here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jodie Foster 'Much More Comfortable Having Robots' Own Guns Than Humans...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/06/08/jodie-foster-much-more-comfortable-having-robots-own-gun-than-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Jodie Foster said she would be "much more comfortable having robots" own a gun than a human do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7? G8? G6+1?</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/world/is-it-the-group-of-seven-eight-six-plus-one-1.3965573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREETINGS FROM QUEBEC...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5821265/Trump-says-PUTIN-G7-summit-Canada.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump arrived at the G-7 summit in Canada after throwing another bomb on his way there – saying Russia should be allowed back into the group of industrial nations for the talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arm found inside massive alligator suspected to have killed lady walking dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/florida/broward/davie-alligator-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An arm was found inside an alligator that was caught in a Davie lake, sources told Local 10 News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy breaks with EU, backs Russian return...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/conte-trump-russia-g8-breaks-with-eu-backs-call-for-to-return/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK gave companies access to user records well after they claimed to cut them off...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-gave-some-companies-access-to-additional-data-about-users-friends-1528490406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook struck customized data-sharing deals with a select group of companies, some of which had special access to user records well after the social-media giant cut off developers from that information, according to court documents, company officials and people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE warns suppliers of 20% drop in iPhone parts orders...</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Companies/Apple-warns-suppliers-of-20-drop-in-new-iPhone-parts-orders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;asia.nikkei.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say US company prepares two OLED models earlier to avoid repeat of last year's delays</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian officials travel to CA, FL to stem wave of immigrants heading their way...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/06/08/canada-warns-immigrants-u-s-heading-north-border/683297002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadians are increasing the number of immigrants and refugees it accepts to help deal with the global migrant crisis. But Canadian officials are worried about increases in illegal immigration and are warning people they will be deported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK gave companies access to user records well after they claimed to cut them off...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-gave-some-companies-access-to-additional-data-about-users-friends-1528490406?mod=breakingnews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook struck customized data-sharing deals with a select group of companies, some of which had special access to user records well after the social-media giant cut off developers from that information, according to court documents, company officials and people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: NYT reporter-source romance muddies seizure...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2018/06/08/how-a-reporters-romance-with-her-source-muddies-the-fbis-seizure-of-her-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media's footing on the high ground is not so stable here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indicted former Senate staffer in court as Russia leak probe sets off fireworks...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-leak-indictment-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Senate staff member, indicted for lying to federal investigators, makes his initial court appearance Friday as the charges against him, involving the leak of information from the Senate Intelligence Committee, set off partisan fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodman headed to Singapore: Will support 'my friends'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/former-nba-star-rodman-head-singapore-u-north-162554330--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former National Basketball Association star Dennis Rodman said on Friday he will be heading to Singapore for the planned June 12 summit between U.S. President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un. "I will be flying to Singapore for the historical Summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta high-rise evacuated as crews investigate fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/downtown-high-rise-evacuated-as-crews-investigate-possible-fire/765674870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Peachtree Summit Federal Building was evacuated Friday afternoon as fire crews investigated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protest thwarted by rogue balloon cam...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/canadian-anti-g7-protest-thwarted-rogue-balloon-cam-190514364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian anti-G7 activists were on Friday reduced to appealing to authorities or bystanders to return their camera after they lost contact with a ballon deployed to hoist it aloft. "The drifting camera poses no danger to the public, unlike the G7 itself," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazen couple caught romping on gravestone in broad daylight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/2753349/shocking-moment-brazen-couple-were-caught-romping-on-a-gravestone-in-broad-daylight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a brazen couple were caught romping on a GRAVESTONE in broad daylight. The shameless pair were filmed having sex by an appalled dog walker in the middle of a Greater Man…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAWORLD bans straws, plastic bags...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/tourism/sd-fi-seaworld-straws-ban-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SeaWorld decides to ban plastic straws and shopping bags at all of its 12 parks, joining a growing movement to phase out straws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Monroe statue near church draws ire...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/local/article/Marilyn-Monroe-s-icon-pose-in-front-of-Stamford-12978964.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STAMFORD - It's a jarring sight for members of the First Congregational Church: The underwear-clad buttocks of Marilyn Monroe mooning the downtown parish.  A 26-foot Seward Johnson statue illustrating the star in her iconic pose from "The Seven Year Itch" was installed this week in Latham Park as part of the Stamford Downtown Special Services District's "Art in Public Places" series that lasts through the summer. But much like the subway grate stirred up her skirt, Monroe has created a whirlwind in just a few days in Stamford. Lorri Tamburro, a lifelong Stamford resident, was disturbed when she visited the statue with her husband and watched children climbing up Monroe's leg and looking up her skirt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA pulls 2 more from Cuba; New potential health cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-pulls-2-more-cuba-amid-potential-health-183150328--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States is testing two more workers from its embassy in Cuba for possible brain injury amid concerns they may have been affected by mysterious health incidents harming U.S. diplomats in Cuba and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAUTHAMMER:  WEEKS TO LIVE...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/08/fox-news-star-charles-krauthammer-reveals-has-weeks-to-live-in-heartbreaking-letter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles Krauthammer, the beloved and brilliant Fox News Channel personality who gave up a pioneering career in psychiatry to become a Pulitzer Prize-winning political analyst, on Friday revealed the heartbreaking news that he is in the final stages of a losing battle with cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS CHARGED WITH DOMESTIC VIOLENCE...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/08/james-wolfe-domestic-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US unveils world's most powerful supercomputer...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/the-download/611385/americas-new-supercomputer-beats-chinas-fastest-machine-to-take-the-worlds-most/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summit is a stepping stone towards a world of exascale computing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo goes to church: Southern Baptist reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/sexual-misconduct/metoo-goes-church-southern-baptists-face-reckoning-over-treatment-women-n880216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Many women have experienced horrific abuses within the power structures of our Christian world," Beth Moore, an evangelical teacher, wrote in a letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient teeth unlock bubonic plague secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/06/08/bubonic-plague-bacteria-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teeth found in two people buried together 3,800 years ago in modern-day Russia revealed an ancestor of the bacteria responsible for the Black Death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen hospitalized for surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/708331/Queen-royal-news-hospital-surgery-update-wedding-meghan-markle-prince-harry-philip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  Likely to support ending federal pot ban...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-marijuana-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said he likely will support a congressional effort to end the federal ban on marijuana, a major step that would reshape the pot industry and end the threat of a Justice Department crackdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force grounds B-1 bomber fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/8/air-force-grounds-b-1-bombers-due-safety-concerns-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force has grounded its entire fleet of B-1B Lancer bombers due to safety concerns, military officials said Friday, putting out of service a key part of U.S. long-range bombing capabilities that had recently taken part in air strikes in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum discovers secret order to destroy Gulag data...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/08/russian-museum-discovers-secret-order-to-destroy-gulag-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papers reveal that ministers ordered erasure of prisoner files in 2014, say archivists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA prepares to thwart Chinese spying at summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/china/u-s-officials-prepare-thwart-chinese-spying-singapore-summit-n880896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese have used everything from bugged hotel keys to “friendship” pins to spy on Americans — and they’re getting better at it all the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's tariffs on newsprint are killing newspapers?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trumps-tariff-on-canadian-newsprint-is-killing-us-newspapers-republicans-warn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen House lawmakers have introduced legislation to remove President Trump's tariffs on Canadian newsprint so a study can be done on how much those tariffs are crushing local newspapers around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'Punk Kid' to 21st Century Tyrant: Kim Jong Un Seizes His Moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/from-punk-kid-to-21st-century-tyrant-kim-jong-un-seizes-his-moment-1528467258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once seen as a sadistic recluse who lacked the confidence to meet a single foreign leader during his first six years in power, the North Korean dictator is now on a diplomacy blitz, having won a coveted nuclear summit with President Donald Trump. Diplomats say it would be a big mistake to underestimate Mr. Kim—as many initially did.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
