<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY $1 BILLION BET: FIRST LOOK AT NEW 'STAR WARS' RIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/10479085/disney-star-wars-rise-of-the-resistance-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS our droid-piloted space vehicle spins into a huge hangar occupied by two full-size AT-AT walkers, the whoops from the passengers almost drown out the sound of imperial laser blasters being fired…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misconduct 'worse than any president'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/03/trump-impeachment-inquiry-judiciary-committee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President’s allies expected to launch procedural objections during a second round of public impeachment hearings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited baby experiment 'may have created unintended mutations'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/dec/04/china-gene-edited-baby-experiment-may-have-created-unintended-mutations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He Jiankui’s original research, published for the first time, could have failed, scientists say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Deer Hunters Tell Tale of Kidnapping After Deadly Mexican Cartel Shootout...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/texans-donald-chapman-and-colby-williams-tell-tale-of-kidnapping-after-deadly-mexican-cartel-shootout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colby Williams and Donald Chapman said their captors told them, “You’ll be OK. We don’t hurt Americans.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Lost Temple City Where Monkeys Rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hampi-inside-indias-lost-temple-city-where-monkeys-rule</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When this former center of the jewel trade was plundered in the 16th century, it was left abandoned, and today it’s one of the most magical (and unknown) visited ruins in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not going to take any sh*t'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/03/nadler-judiciary-impeachment-074985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Judiciary Committee chairman is ready for the scrutiny that's coming as he takes the reins of the impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEADERS TRASH TALK TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-calls-trudeau-two-faced-after-hot-mic-catches-nato-n1095351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian premier and others were heard apparently speaking about the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly couple arrested for sex outside of theater...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/florida-elderly-couple-arrested-for-sex-outside-of-theater-in/article_22e793b7-5e61-57a9-afb3-a4d0bcca0790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man and woman were arrested Thursday after they were caught having sex in public in front of a 12-year-old child outside a Clearwater, Fla., theater on Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet who served on USS Nimitz recalls seeing '2-mile-wide UFO' over base...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/navy-vet-who-served-uss-21023711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former US Navy officer said the “government knows” about the bizarre object, which was seen above a base in Virginia Beach</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican witness won't come to rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7754109/Serious-misconduct-Trump-takes-center-stage-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Turley, the only Republican witness allowed by Democrats in the impeachment hearing Wednesday, is unlikely to defend Donald Trump, according to his opening statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466833-1/judiciary-hearing-constitutional-framework-impeachment&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee holds a hearing with legal experts to discuss the constitutional framework for potentially drawing up articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VIDEO, THE DRAMA</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/04/trump-calls-trudeau-two-faced-after-video-shows-prime-minister-mocking-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump called Justin Trudeau “two-faced” after a video surfaced showing the Canadian prime minister mocking Trump for taking time to speak to reporters at the NATO meetings in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private payrolls growth tumbles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/04/private-payrolls-up-67000-in-november-vs-125000-expected-adpmoodys.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big miss could call into question the relatively rosy estimates for Friday's closely watched nonfarm payrolls report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 Los Zetas Cartel Gunmen Cross into Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/12/03/150-los-zetas-cartel-gunmen-crossed-into-texas-before-deadly-attack-that-killed-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor of Coahuila is now walking back his statement, claiming the gunmen did not cross the international boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Pours Whipped Cream into Volunteer's Mouth...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2020-election/2019/12/04/video-andrew-yang-pours-whipped-cream-in-campaign-volunteers-mouths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang poured whipped cream into volunteers' mouths at the opening of his newly-minted field office in New Hampshire on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging from obscurity: 2019's unforeseen history-makers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/emerging-obscurity-2019s-unforeseen-history-makers-035335296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the many people who made history in 2019, some surprised themselves and the world by emerging from obscurity to make their mark, though one remains anonymous for the time being -- "The Whistleblower" behind the impeachment probe into US President Donald Trump. Following are brief profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOND 25: FULL TRAILER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/james-bond-trailer-no-time-to-die-rami-malek-daniel-craig-1202800232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bond is Back. Here’s the anticipated first trailer for Bond 25 No Time To Die, featuring a moody Daniel Craig, some stunning visuals (the Italian city of Matera in particular), a first look a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=44lWO3qhQMk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to Posthumous Forgiveness: https://TameImpala.lnk.to/Posthumous_ForgivenessYD Pre-order The Slow Rush (out February 14, 2020): https://TameImpala.lnk....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accuse Trump of abusing power, obstructing impeachment probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment/democrats-accuse-trump-of-abusing-power-obstructing-congress-impeachment-probe-idUSKBN1Y71LP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump solicited foreign interference to boost his re-elect...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 51% of Florida voters disapprove of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/472864-poll-51-percent-of-florida-voters-disapprove-of-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About half of voters in Florida disapprove of President Trump, posing a 2020 challenge for the president as he seeks to notch back-to-back electoral victories in the battleground state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAME IMPALA: 'Unafraid to go all the way this time'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tame-impala-unveils-song-posthumous-forgiveness-115124613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Posthumous Forgiveness" will appear on the Australian band's forthcoming album, "The Slow Rush," which is set to arrive on February 14, 2020.This poignant number finds Tame Impala frontman Kevin Parker paying homage to his late father, who passed away from cancer while the band</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers to consider drawing up impeachment articles...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrat-report-makes-forceful-impeachment-case-against-trump-221825535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US lawmakers will start debating whether to draw up articles of impeachment against Donald Trump on Wednesday, based on a report detailing "overwhelming evidence" the US president committed misconduct in office and obstruction. The House Intelligence Committee report published Tuesday accused</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Star Wars: Jedi Temple Challenge': Jar Jar Binks Actor Will Host Disney+ Game Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/star-wars-jedi-temple-challenge-jar-jar-binks-actor-will-host-disney-game-show-1202799403/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Wars: Jedi Temple Challenge, a new game show aimed at kids and hosted by Jar Jar Binks actor Ahmed Best, will premiere on the Disney+ subscription streaming service in 2020. The live-action sk…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Division pervades NATO as 'brain dead' meet 'delinquent'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191204093403-0kelv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO-SUMMIT/ (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Division pervades NATO as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Nelson quits pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/music/2019/12/04/willie-nelson-has-quit-marijuana-smoking-after-breathing-issues/2604719001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country music outlaw and marijuana lover Willie Nelson has quit smoking the drug for health reasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian couple first to carry baby in both their wombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/12/03/british-lesbian-couple-first-carry-baby-wombs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British lesbian couple have become the first parents to have a baby carried in both of their wombs in a landmark &amp;ldquo;shared motherhood&amp;rdquo; procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abused power of presidency, Dems conclude in impeachment report...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/03/trump-abused-power-of-presidency-dems-conclude-in-impeachment-report-074924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee's report on Trump's Ukraine dealings is a roadmap for lawmakers drafting articles of impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 DOWN: KAMALA OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/03/kamala-harris-drops-out-out-of-presidential-race-074902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California senator took a deep look at the campaign’s resources over the holiday and decided she did not have a path to the nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un back on his white horse, as NKorea flags big decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-un-is-back-on-his-white-horse-as-north-korea-flags-a-big-decision/ar-BBXJ723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRISHMAN' Named Best Film By National Board of Review...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/irishman-tops-national-board-review-2019-honorees-full-list-1259206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other multiple honorees include 'Richard Jewell,' 'Once Upon a Time in Hollywood' and 'Uncut Gems.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO LEADERS MOCK TRUMP?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7753821/Justin-Trudeau-Emmanuel-Macron-Boris-Johnson-caught-appearing-gossip-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a clip shared online the three world leaders seem to be discussing Trump. None of the men mention Trump by name but Trudeau seems to refer to POTUS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pooch starts house fire by switching on microwave...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/03/world/dog-fire-microwave-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every now and again incredible stories emerge of heroic dogs saving their owners from house fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spray-painted polar bear baffles experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50643315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of a bear inscribed with "T-34" - the name of an iconic Soviet tank - is shared in Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang campaign contacts FBI over death threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/472928-yang-campaign-receives-death-threats-in-new-hampshire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businessman Andrew Yang's presidential campaign says it has contacted the FBI after receiving several death threats during its latest swing through New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to Create Super Pig...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-u-racing-create-super-210028643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Inside a fortress-like megafarm on the outskirts of Beijing, dozens of pink-and-black pigs forage and snooze, unfazed by the chilly spring air. These experimentally bred hogs are fortified with a gene for regulating heat, buffering them against northern China’s hypothermia-inducing winters.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Serious misconduct' by Trump takes center stage at hearing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe334cf50d267b749874ddf1089ca6bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Judiciary Committee is moving swiftly to weigh findings by fellow lawmakers that President Donald Trump misused the power of his office for personal political gain and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE co-founders step aside as antitrust scrutiny heats up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36493aa8b04d4121914b38c2bc5f8ad7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Google’s co-founders are relinquishing their executive positions just as state and federal regulators, not to mention the Department of Justice and Congress, are taking a keen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Husband, wife die day apart after being married 68 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/03/minnesota-husband-wife-married-68-years-die-day-apart/2594742001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert and Corinne Johnson were married for 68 years. They lived in the same farmhouse for 67 years, raising their children and farm animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Require citizens be photographed at airports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96804155575044d5908e0697c53d6a70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Federal officials are considering requiring that all travelers — including American citizens — be photographed as they enter or leave the country as part of an identification system...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORMER SLAVE GIRL CONFRONTS CAPTURED ISIS TERRORIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.memri.org/tv/former-yazidi-slave-girl-confronts-isis-terrorist-who-violently-raped-her-ashwaq-hamid-abu-humam-faint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.memri.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On November 26, 2019, Al-Iraqiya Network (Iraq) aired a report about Ashwaq Haji Hamid, a Yazidi girl who had been held ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Page steps down as CEO of ALPHABET...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/larry-page-steps-down-as-ceo-of-alphabet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Page said in a blog post that "it's the natural time to simplify our management structure." Co-founder Sergey Brin will also step down as president of the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi felons push court to restore voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b34a318e6e594ea586756d82ce7c718d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — The man at the center of a Mississippi case aimed at restoring the voting rights of felons said Tuesday that he is fighting on behalf of everyone like him who "made a mistake in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair STILL hold more than 50% voting shares...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/955f9c26bcc346e28fffcb6afb364dd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The co-founders of Google are stepping down as executives of its parent company, Alphabet, ending a remarkable two decades during which Larry Page and Sergey Brin shaped a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes slaps CNN with $435 million defamation lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/3/devin-nunes-slaps-cnn-435-million-defamation-lawsu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Devin Nunes on Tuesday filed a defamation suit against CNN for its Nov. 22 “demonstrably false hit piece” that said the California Republican traveled to Vienna in 2018 to dig up dirt on former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani calls, texts at center...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/giuliani-mystery-phone-calls-texts-uncovered-democrats-impeachment-report-n1095086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's personal lawyer is at the center of questions about Trump's handling of aid to Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Warn Of Deadly Drug-Resistant Fungus; 806 Cases Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/12/03/over-140-confirmed-cases-candida-auris-deadly-drug-resistant-fungus-new-jersey-health-department-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC calls C. auris a "serious global health threat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pundits Furious At Whiteness Of Dem Field...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/03/democrats-2020-candidates-white-males/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skin color of Democratic 2020 frontrunners moved to the forefront of discussion among left-of-center pundits after Kamala Harris dropped out of the race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: CA man now highest-ranked American in terror group...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-man-now-highest-ranking-American-14878582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are re-upping a $5 million reward related to the capture of a 37-year-old man on the FBI's Most Wanted Terrorists List whom it called "the highest-ranking U.S. citizen fighting overseas with a terrorist organization."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested 'for making 24,000 complaint calls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50651355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 71-year-old pensioner from Tokyo allegedly called his phone operator for two-and-a-half years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Loses 'Top Destinations' Status As Tourists Pick Asia Over USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90438500/fewer-tourists-are-visiting-america-nyc-pushed-out-of-top-10-world-destinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here comes another sign of doom and gloom for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL AND HILLARY 'FREQUENT GUESTS' AT RANCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7748467/Bill-Hillary-Clinton-frequent-guests-Jeffrey-Epsteins-New-Mexico-ranch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill and Hillary Clinton would stay at Jeffrey Epstein's New Mexico ranch almost every year, former estate workers told DailyMail.com. They didn't stay at the main house but a Western-themed village.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron crushes hand again in power shake...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10475279/macron-crushes-trumps-hand-isis-fighters-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH their eyes locked on their presidential counterpart, Donald Trump and Emmanuel Macron crushed each other’s hands in yet another power shake. Their tense grip came as Trump bizarrely thre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Average Person Will Watch 78,000 Hours Of TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-the-average-adult-will-watch-more-than-78000-hours-of-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey finds that the average TV viewer will watch an astounding 78,705 hours of programming (movies, sports, news, etc) in their lifetime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang of teens brutally beats officer defending woman at mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article237996109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley giants accused of avoiding over $100 billion in taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/02/silicon-valley-giants-accused-of-avoiding-100-billion-in-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six of Silicon Valley's biggest companies had a combined "tax gap" of more than $100 billion this decade, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump deploys 'surge' of park rangers to patrol Mexican border...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/03/trump-deploys-park-rangers-patrol-mexican-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diverting rangers is a way to direct federal resources to the border without the need for congressional approval</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN BOOK SPILLS SECRETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/the-shocking-spy-story-behind-the-jeffrey-epstein-scandal-revealed-in-epstein-dead-men-tell-no-tales-300967846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prnewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/PRNewswire/ -- A new investigation led by best-selling true crime author Dylan Howard breaks stunning new ground in the case of disgraced billionaire sex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURPEME BATTLE FOR TRUMP FINANCIALS?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-loses-appeal-block-banks-handing-over-his-financial-records-n1094831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump sued the banks to stop them from complying with subpoenas seeking the information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans becoming less charitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fewer-americans-are-giving-money-to-charity-and-it-could-be-because-theyre-spending-less-time-at-church-2019-10-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 20 million fewer households donate to charity than they did two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Queen Economy 'Booming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hollywood-is-finally-catching-booming-drag-queen-economy-1258829?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive success of 'RuPaul's Drag Race' has launched dozens of stars and ignited red-carpet appearance deals for films like 'Frozen 2.' Still, for a queen, "your money is on the road."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court sides with Congress over bank records...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-financial-records-subpoena-deutsche-bank-8ad4507e-aa16-4641-ae5f-5dbc022cb030.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank and Capitol One were ordered to comply with a congressional subpoena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinance Forbids Throwing Snowballs In City...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/12/02/ordinance-forbids-throwing-snowballs-in-wausau-wisconsin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snowballs are lumped in with missiles, rocks, arrows, none of which are you allowed to throw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER DIGITAL TAX INTENSIFIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-trade-france-macron/frances-macron-hopeful-of-settling-digital-tax-dispute-with-u-s-idUSKBN1Y71UC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron said on Tuesday he was hopeful that trade and e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Tiger Woods catch Nicklaus? He's got a shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.golf.com/news/2019/12/02/tiger-woods-reaching-18-majors-who-knows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods said at the Hero World Challenge on Monday that Jack Nicklaus' 18 major titles is still in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Would you like some nice ISIS fighters?'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7750351/Donald-Trump-kicks-NATO-meetings-London-unloading-Emanuel-Macron.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump blasted French President Emanuel Macron for his own comments that the alliance was suffering 'brain death' at the start of two days of NATO meetings in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Florida mansion sells for record $111 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/billionaire-steven-schonfeld-buys-florida-mansion-for-111-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founder of New York-based hedge fund Schonfeld Strategic Advisors closed on the six acre-estate known as La Reverie Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden woos Iowa voters, Pete seems increasingly to be in his way...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-12-03/joe-biden-woos-iowa-voters-pete-buttigieg-increasingly-in-his-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among centrist voters inclined to like Biden, the 37-year-old Buttigieg is becoming plausible as an alternative, and he highlights what Biden is not: energetic, articulate and young.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW drops 400 points... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/03/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-south-america-trade-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In some ways, I like the idea of waiting until after the election for the China deal, but they want to make a deal now," Trump said from London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four ousted GOOGLE workers to file charges with federal labor board...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/472750-four-ousted-google-workers-file-charges-with-federal-labor-board</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's decision last month to fire four longtime employees involved in worker activism has kicked off a firestorm of internal protest and public demonstrations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami's buzziest buildings open ahead of Art Basel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/03/miamis-buzziest-buildings-open-ahead-of-art-basel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of planning and construction, many of Miami’s most anticipated new developments are finally open. Perhaps the most significant is Paramount Miami Worldcenter, the biggest building proje…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches NATO summit with attack on 'nasty' France...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/squabbles-overshadow-nato-70th-anniversary-summit-013415153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump launched a two-day NATO meeting Tuesday with a blistering attack on France's criticism of the alliance and on "delinquent" members that do not pay their way. At a news conference held to celebrate NATO's success in cajoling European allies to boost their defence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's First 'Fly And Drive' Car To Be Unveiled In Miami...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/03/worlds-first-fly-drive-car-miami-debut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's first 'fly and drive' car will be unveiled Tuesday night in Miami.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decapitated body found in Los Angeles' Griffith Park...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/News/decapitated-body-found-los-angeles-griffith-park/story?id=67456952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have opened a homicide investigation after dismembered human remains were discovered in Los Angeles’ Griffith Park.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
