<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>For Elizabeth II, '21 brought sorrow and scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/for-queen-elizabeth-ii-2021-brought-sorrow-and-scandal-to-the-royal-family/ar-AAS71B7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruises once again facing disruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cruise-ships-covid-19-disruption/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four ocean cruise ships were turned away from ports of call or were prohibited from letting passengers disembark in the Americas this week because of Covid-19 cases aboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4334624/holiday-travel-airline-cancellations-omicron-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DELTA, United, and other US airlines have canceled more than 1,800 flights over Christmas weekend after the surge in the Omicron variant of Covid led to staff shortages. Globally, more than 5,800 f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France rocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211225-daily-covid-19-infections-in-france-cross-100-000-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid infections in France hit six figures Saturday, health officials recording 104,611 cases over the previous 24 hours, the third consecutive day the numbers have been record highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Slams Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344369/NYT-editorial-board-responds-judge-orders-return-documents-Project-Veritas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times has blasted a judge who ordered the paper to return documents they obtained from the conservative activist group Project Veritas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising art world star 'faked' works by pal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/rising-art-world-star-christian-rosa-faked-works-by-pal-raymond-pettibon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scandal of a rising Brazilian art star who allegedly counterfeited the work of his famous friend and mentor Raymond Pettibon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY warns of rise in child hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/new-york-dept-of-health-warns-of-rising-child-covid-hospitalizations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jump in hospitalizations of children is “concentrated in New York City and the surrounding greater metropolitan area.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice releases longest video yet of Capitol riot violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/justice-department-releases-three-hour-video-of-violent-capitol-riot-clashes-in-tunnel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department released the longest video yet from the government showing clashes between rioters and police at a U.S. Capitol tunnel on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candace Owens asks conservatives to go easy on Trump over vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344193/Candace-Owens-asks-conservatives-easy-Trump-Hes-old-research-vaccines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Candace Owens says that former president Donald Trump only praised vaccines because he is 'too old' and not savvy enough to do better online research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Thousands of Russian troops withdrawing from Ukraine border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thousands-russian-troops-withdrawing-ukraine-131138933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Russian troops are reportedly withdrawing from the Ukrainian border after conducting drills for roughly a month.Reuters reported on Saturday that more than 10,000 Russian troops were leaving a number of regions near Ukraine - including Crimea, Rostov and Kuban - and returning to permanent bases.The news service pointed to reporting from the Interfax news agency, which cited the Russian military."A stage of combat coordination of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Turns to Antitrust Enforcers to Combat Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-turns-to-antitrust-enforcers-to-combat-inflation/ar-AAS8D3w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Divides Fans By Equating Covid to Flu, Cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/lebron-james-divides-nba-fans-with-meme-comparing-covid-to-the-flu-and-the-common-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James ignited a Twitter firestorm when he compared Covid-19 to both the flu and the common cold in a post on his Instagram account page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Dems who could run in '24 if Biden doesn't...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/586948-ten-democrats-who-could-run-in-2024-if-biden-doesnt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2022 midterm elections are less than a year away, but questions are already being raised about what the Democratic ticket will look like in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More shows go dark on Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/24/thoughts-of-a-colored-man-and-waitress-go-dark-on-broadway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Great White Way was darker on Christmas Eve as two Broadway productions permanently closed due to surging COVID-19 cases in the Big Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER booster's ability to prevent wanes within WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/uk-agency-pfizer-boosters-ability-to-prevent-symptomatic-covid-wanes-within-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data shows 3rd shot 70% effective in preventing illness after 2 weeks but only 45% after 10 weeks; Moderna seems to offer more durable protection, staying at 70% after 10 weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's well-oiled military machine launches 3 warships in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3161052/chinas-well-oiled-military-machine-launches-three-warships-one</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two vessels destined for Thailand and Pakistan while a third built to bolster PLA fleet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After years of doubts, hopes grow nuclear fusion finally real...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/12/22/science/after-years-doubts-hopes-grow-that-nuclear-fusion-is-finally-real-could-help-address-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After breakthroughs this year at MIT and elsewhere, scientists — and a growing number of deep-pocketed investors — insist that fusion is for real and could start sending power to electricity grids in about a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Webb telescope launches, starting nail-biting mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/12/25/nasa-james-webb-telescope-launches-south-america/9016763002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's flagship science instrument took flight from South America early Saturday, a high-stakes mission that will peer deep into the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warship sidelined with outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/24/navy-warship-milwaukee-covid-526138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USS Milwaukee is staying in port.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Suspect charged with shooting man over loud music...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/story/news/crime/2021/12/25/boca-raton-christmas-eve-shooting-over-loud-music/9016891002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim's family was able to wrestle Zachary Moncada to the ground after he fired at them, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood banks experiencing biggest shortage in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/12/25/world/omicron-covid-vaccine-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blood banks across the country are struggling to maintain their usual three-day supply as virus cases make donors and medical staff scarce. Britain is administering booster shots throughout the Christmas holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds, arguments across NYC as demand for tests rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/angry-crowds-arguments-across-nyc-as-demand-for-covid-tests-rises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some parts of the city, larger-than-expected turnouts for free at-home COVID testing kits led to angry scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB cracks down on disruptive FL parties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-florida-orlando-holidays-new-years-eve-dcb7746159cbfd916b99b5a7d558efd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — If you're planning to rent a home in central Florida over New Year's Eve, you may be out of luck. Airbnb says potential guests without a history of positive reviews will be unable to make one-night reservations in Orlando and Kissimmee over New Year's Eve, in an effort to crack down on disruptive parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Nuns Who Grow Weed...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/california-weed-cannabis-nun-sisters-valley-1272595/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a New Age order of feminist nuns is reimagining spiritual devotion and trying to heal the world — one joint at a time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 10 Londoners infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/one-in-10-londoners-are-likely-infected-with-covid-new-figures-show/ar-AAS7uGV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over masks mandates, other rules, spurs states to curb power of public health officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anger-over-masks-mandates-other-covid-rules-spurs-states-to-curb-power-of-public-health-officials/ar-AAS8BLX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New record for daily infections in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dpa-international.com/topic/new-record-daily-infections-australia-marks-second-covid-urn%3Anewsml%3Adpa.com%3A20090101%3A211225-99-500849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Stories from around the globe brought to you by dpa International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/23/united-delta-cancel-dozens-of-christmas-eve-flights-as-covid-hits-crews.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. airlines have recently ramped up pressure on the CDC to loosen quarantine rules for breakthrough Covid cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador frees women convicted of abortions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-caribbean-nayib-bukele-el-salvador-san-salvador-894e8808713a4174d127d1ba513a8847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — President Nayib Bukele's government has freed three Salvadoran women who were sentenced to 30 years in prison under the nation's strict anti-abortion laws after suffering obstetric emergencies, according to abortion rights groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA HIT WITH RECORD CASES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-miami-florida-b10650dbe748751d2c2c830813d64df8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — With Florida hitting a record number of cases, getting a COVID test Saturday on Christmas Day was almost as popular as eating a ham or drinking egg-nog-like coquito, for some. Hours before a testing site opening at Tropical Park in Miami, dozens of cars lined up along a road leading to its entrance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GONSALVES:  Biden failing on pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/12/22/president-biden-is-failing-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is playing catch-up and doing damage control as omicron rages across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344125/Christmas-Day-airport-misery-thousands-flight-cancelations-climb-quarter-24-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domestic travelers are facing a nightmare this holiday season as airlines on Christmas day cancelled over 850 flights and delayed 520.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest armed man breaking into Windsor grounds...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/armed-intruder-arrested-in-grounds-of-windsor-castle-as-queen-celebrates-christmas-12503764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen is celebrating this Christmas at Windsor Castle with Prince Charles and Camilla, the Duchess of Cornwall, after cancelling her traditional plans of going to Sandringham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Christmas speech particularly personal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-queen-elizabeth-ii-lifestyle-health-europe-b2e2e0abe96f5a8bf94e9f9d166903e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II in her Christmas Day message shared the pain she felt after the death of her husband as she encouraged people everywhere to celebrate with friends and family, despite the grief caused by a pandemic now stretching into its second year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER COVID CHRISTMAS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-religion-new-zealand-9ec85a6390d13e3144bdaa236b988666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Christians around the world celebrated their second COVID-19 Christmas on Saturday with surging infections in many countries overwhelming hospitals, canceling flights and curbing religious observances, even as coronavirus vaccines were more available than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic decimates tourism at Jesus' birthplace...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211225133739-sqk9w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 10,000 troops returning to bases after drills...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211225082435-ynljw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders NYT to return PROJECT VERITAS internal memos...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211224220928-h7dpr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PROJECT VERITAS (PIX):Judge orders New York Times to return Project Veritas internal memos</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
