<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Robot companions improve mental health and loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1436520/robots-loneliness-mental-health-older-people/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Calls Cops on 12-Year-Old Holding Toy Gun During ZOOM Class...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/09/07/zoom-nerf-gun-school-cops-kid-isaiah-elliott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isaiah Elliott also received a five-day suspension, but plans to transfer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mighty Mice' Stay Musclebound in Space, Boon for Astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/news/articles/2020-09-07/mighty-mice-stay-musclebound-in-space-boon-for-astronauts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Final Stretch, Biden Defends Lead Against Onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-final-stretch-biden-defends-lead-against-trumps-onslaught/ar-BB18KPHj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece to boost military amid tensions with neighbor Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2451f1547136c0a75ebcd417e7b7fb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece will bolster its military with new arms, more personnel and by developing the country’s defense industry, the government said Monday, as a tense standoff with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hints at Vaccine 'Surprise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-hints-at-vaccine-surprise-as-biden-demands-transparency/ar-BB18NqWu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA reviews BOEING Dreamliner quality-control lapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/07/faa-reviews-boeing-dreamliner-quality-control-lapses-wsj-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The review could require enhanced or accelerated inspections for as many as about 900 Dreamliners delivered since 2011, the report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 2M acres burned so far this year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a168491f2cb25810c9e2a40316fe43a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAVER LAKE, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires have burned more than 2 million acres in California this year, setting a state record even as crews battled dozens of growing blazes in sweltering temperatures...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters light fire near Portland police precinct...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Portland-Oregon-has-quiet-night-after-100-days-15547353.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) - A fire started outside a police precinct on Portland's north side resulted in about 15 arrests during protests Sunday night into Monday morning, police said.  Demonstrators protesting police brutality began marching at about 9 p.m. Sunday and stopped at the North Precinct Community Policing Center, the site of several volatile protests in recent months.  Officials warned demonstrators against entering the precinct property, saying they would be trespassing and subject to arrest.  Shortly after arriving, the crowd began chanting, among other things, "burn it down," police said in a statement. Some in the group lit a mattress on fire just after 10 p.m.  "Because it was not an immediate threat to life safety or structures, officers remained far back and did not engage," police said. "Another mattress was added to the fire, as was some yard debris. The larger fire began to send lit embers into the air."  Since Multnomah County has a burn ban in effect due to extremely dry conditions, firefighters came in to extinguish the blaze.  Demonstrators moved to another side of the building and blocked some streets until dispersed by police. Most protesters were gone by about 1 a.m. Monday.  "Officers discovered one arrestee was in possession of a glass jar filled with flammable liquid," police said. "Another had a bottle containing an accelerant and a slugging weapon known as a slung shot. Still another had an electronic control weapon ("stun gun") and a baton. Two arrestees had ballistic vests, including one, marked with the word "press," with rifle plates."  Most of those arrested were from Portland. Others were from San Francisco; Sacramento, California; Mesa, Arizona; and two from Vancouver, Washington.  Charges included interfering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer's not over yet: Remote workers extend their vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/travel/summer-s-not-over-yet-remote-workers-extend-their-vacation-n1239474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotels in summer hotspots usually go into hibernation once Labor Day rolls around. But this is 2020, and rules no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says Pentagon brass doesn't 'love' him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-troops-love-him-even-if-pentagon-brass-doesn-t/ar-BB18NjeF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President goes on the attack in Labor Day speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-is-a-stupid-person-trump-goes-on-the-attack-in-labor-day-speech/ar-BB18NvOe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Respect for troops, military sacrifice becomes election friction point...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2020/09/05/respect-for-troops-military-sacrifice-becomes-an-election-friction-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accusations that Trump insulted troops and wounded veterans will be a frequent talking point for election rivals this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postmaster General Accused of Pressuring Employees to Make Political Donations, Then Reimbursing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/06/politics/dejoy-gop-fundraiser-contributions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former employees of the company that US Postmaster General Louis DeJoy previously ran told The Washington Post they were pressured to donate to GOP candidates and then reimbursed through bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA moves on vaccines spark political worries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/515210-fda-moves-on-vaccines-spark-political-worries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health officials are taking aim at the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), warning it should not bow to political pressure and clear a COVID-19 vaccine before one is ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divers pull human remains from Central Park pond...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/07/divers-pull-human-remains-from-central-park-pond/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divers pulled a body out of a pond in Central Park on Labor Day afternoon, FDNY officials said. The human remains were taken out of The Pond around 12:30 p.m. near the park entrance at 59th Street …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Turns Into Furnace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-wildfires-extreme-heat-turns-state-into-a-furnace/ar-BB18NlFZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi killers have death sentences overturned in Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706159/Saudi-Arabia-convicts-eight-people-killing-Jamal-Khashoggi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has convicted eight people of killing Jamal Khashoggi and has jailed them for up to 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy opens competition probe into APPLEGOOGLE cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/07/italy-opens-competition-probe-into-apple-google-and-dropbox.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Competition and Market Authority said it launched six total investigations into the Google Drive service, Apple's iCloud and DropBox.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Journalist Jailed for Christian Persecution Coverage: 'They're Going to Have to Kill Me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/09/07/cuban-journalist-jailed-christian-persecution-coverage-theyre-going-have-kill-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo welcomed the release of Cuban journalist Roberto de Jesús Quiñones Haces from a year in prison on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Soviet Triple Agent Recruited New Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/leaked-kgb-manual-reveals-how-soviet-spies-recruited-in-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A KGB manual, published in English for the first time, reveals how Soviet spies infiltrated Western governments in an elaborate game of cat-and-mouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran shatters 1904 heat record by 8 degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Some-spots-in-San-Francisco-could-break-100-15546642.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a light ocean breeze fails to develop along the Northern California coast on Sunday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black families put trust in Black doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/During-pandemic-Black-families-put-trust-in-15547723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Dr. Janice Bacon was exactly the person Kay McField hoped to talk...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange faces 18 new charges as he appears in court to fight US extradition...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/julian-assange-wikileaks-founder-arrested-over-18-new-allegations-as-he-appears-in-court-to-fight-us-extradition-12065979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new US indictment, filed in June, contains 18 charges and was handed to Assange moments before he appeared at the Old Bailey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bold hopes for antibody tests still unfulfilled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd6b3e37ed51fe770b60c2ec5f8bc293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — At the height of the coronavirus lockdown, President Donald Trump and his top health advisers trumpeted a new test that would help Americans reclaim their lives — one that would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line judge bombarded with death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/tennis/article-8706299/US-Open-line-judge-struck-ball-hit-Novak-Djokovic-bombarded-death-threats-trolls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Open line judge hit in the throat with a ball by Novak Djokovic has been subjected to vile online abuse after fans of the world No 1 discovered her Instagram account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN SURPRISE CASH CRUNCH</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-election-campaign-fundraising-cash-eb9915fc-bbab-410f-8e99-fcca14a68024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of states Trump has to worry about has actually grown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President looms large over campaigns for control of Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ede31313f4988e76dc220bc5302afca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The battle for control of Congress is solidifying into a race about President Donald Trump, as Republicans hitch their fortunes to their party’s leader and Democrats position...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin critic Navalny out of coma, Berlin hospital says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-navalny-hospital/putin-critic-navalny-has-come-out-of-coma-berlin-hospital-says-idUSKBN25Y1E0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny has been removed from a medically induced coma and is responding to speech, Berlin's Charite hospital said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How NETFLIX Reed Hastings Rewrote The Hollywood Script...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dawnchmielewski/2020/09/07/how-netflixs-reed-hastings-rewrote-the-hollywood-script/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant had upended show business long before the pandemic hit. But with a highly unusual management style, its billionaire founder has now positioned his entertainment juggernaut to prosper like few companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'kidnaps' five Indian citizens in disputed border territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706069/China-KIDNAPS-five-Indian-citizens-disputed-border-territory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five missing men are from the Indian state of Arunachal Pradesh, which China claims as South Tibet, and the Indian Army said it had made representations to the People's Liberation Army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest trend in RV'ing: Getting way off the grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/07/success/boondocking-rvs-dry-camping/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational vehicle makers often boast how their RVs and trailers can feel just like home. Besides their cleverly packaged bathrooms and kitchenettes, when you park your rig at a campground you can find something else that will make you feel you never left home: neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organized labor staging political resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/515345-organized-labor-staging-political-resurgence-for-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unions, with only a few exceptions, are going all out for Joe Biden this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCHESTER: Naked protesters demand action after Daniel Prude's killing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e04d590aa95eb033a7e5a50dad3df4e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCHESTER, N.Y. (AP) — Naked except for “spit hoods” in a reference to the killing of Daniel Prude, several protesters sat outside Rochester's police headquarters Monday morning to push for police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Claim DISNEY Covering Up Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/workers-reveal-disney-is-covering-up-its-covid-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers and their worried spouses reveal to The Daily Beast that Disney is not only underreporting its COVID cases but clearing COVID-positive employees to return to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Pardons U.S. Marine Who Killed Trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200907-philippines-president-pardons-us-marine-in-transgender-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines president pardons US marine in transgender killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party voters imperil Trump margins in battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/third-party-voters-were-major-factor-trumps-2016-victory-how-could-they</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a warning sign" for the Trump campaign, said pollster Scott Rasmussen. "Maybe it's a yellow flag as opposed to a red flag. And it is one of many things that could change in the three states that shocked everybody: Pennsylvania Michigan and Wisconsin."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tale of 2 recessions': Rich Americans get richer, bottom half struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/07/income-inequality-wealth-gap-409234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend is on track to exacerbate dramatic wealth and income gaps in the U.S., where divides are already wider than any other nation in the G-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISS cameras capture fast-moving object 'with antennae' hurtling past astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/iss-cameras-capture-fast-moving-22641859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorist Mr MBB333 said the so-called UFO had "legs" or an "antennae-like" attachment coming off the bottom of the craft as it sped past the International Space Station (ISS)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor dies in front of virtual class amid symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/07/professor-dies-in-front-of-virtual-class-amid-covid-19-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A college professor in Argentina who had been suffering from persistent coronavirus symptoms collapsed and died at her home during a lecture in front of her virtual class, according to reports. Pao…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stock 'biggest house of cards'; 'Ready to fold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/06/tesla-could-be-the-most-dangerous-stock-on-wall-street-investment-researcher-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla shares may be up 400% this year, but one investment researcher is sounding the alarm on the stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients May Have Prolonged Gut Infection, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-09-07/covid-19-patients-may-have-prolonged-gut-infection-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and loathing in Hollywood at streamers' stranglehold...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fear-loathing-hollywood-streamers-stranglehold-101859368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood stars and top directors are getting increasingly anxious about the hold streaming giants Netflix and Amazon are exerting over cinema.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crazy 2020 makes for presidential race like no other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crazy-2020-makes-presidential-race-113058743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the campaign heats up post-Labor Day, President Trump emphasizes law and order while Joe Biden seeks to keep focus on the incumbent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters gather for Assange court extradition showdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33036b21539ccfa9d926306ecd41ac4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange appeared in a London court on Monday to fight a U.S. extradition request, at a high-stakes hearing that was delayed by the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming rise of technosexuals...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/alarming-rise-technosexuals-132943318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the pandemic wasn’t a surreal enough experience, a recent study suggests that lockdown has amplified a disturbing trend. Research by sex toy company WeVibe revealed that 14 per cent of men admit to being aroused by their smart-speaker Alexa, which confirms my view that we have been sleepwalking into a different kind of epidemic – one of loneliness and fear of intimacy. I’ve been a practising psychotherapist for 20 years, and never have I worked with so many men and women who are unhappy and scared because their deepest attachments and primary source of arousal are through interacting with their tech. I call these people ‘technosexuals’. Technosexuals are joined – as though surgically – to their favourite gadgets. Whether it’s the ‘ping’ of a message, swiping right, or the seductive, authoritative tones of a cloud-based voice service, their tech fulfils them by mobilising the reward system in the brain and releasing dopamine – the ‘happiness hormone’. The instant activity of using their tech – likes and comments – is like a sexual turn on. This ‘dopamine hit’ happens in all of us but, in technosexuals, something else is at play. For them, the modern digital world influences all their libidinous activity. It dictates who they fancy, and how they present and value themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaze triggered by 'gender reveal firework'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8704833/El-Dorado-wildfire-burned-7-050-acres-California-started-gender-reveal-party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildfire which broke out on Saturday 40 miles from Palm Springs was sparked by a pyrotechnic device at a gender reveal party. The El Dorado fire has burned for 36 hours and is only 5% under control.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
