<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'The Giuliani problem'... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/giuliani-problem-takeaways-diplomats-impeachment-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. diplomats told House lawmakers they largely treated Rudolph Giuliani like something of a pariah. That approach helped prompt the impeachment inquriy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying for a better life: Fake funerals teach lessons to the living...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-livingfunerals/dying-for-a-better-life-south-koreans-fake-their-funerals-for-life-lessons-idUSKBN1XG038?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Korean service is offering free funerals - but only to the living.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS:  KY GOV...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2019-general-elections/kentucky-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial would be test for chief justice already attacked by President... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-chief-justice-john-roberts-would-lead-the-senate-impeachment-trial/ar-AAJBuo8?li=AA4Zoy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THISCLOSE:  DEM LEADS KY GOV RACE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7653979/Kentucky-governors-election-flip-Democrat-Trumps-coattails-hang-balance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president rallied Kentuckians one day before polls opened, meaning he would have been credited if the GOP governor kept his job. But now Trump's coattails seem to have shortened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS GOV...</title>
      <link>http://nbcnews.com/politics/2019-general-elections/mississippi-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK reveals new privacy mishap involving apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/11/5/20950541/facebook-groups-api-developer-improper-user-data-access-disclosure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 11 accessed data in the last two months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Any Sane Adult 2020'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Independents-are-pulling-away-from-Trump-14812116.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. - The latest Washington Post-ABC News poll has some seriously troubling news for President Donald Trump: A year out from the 2020 election, he is hemorrhaging the support he once enjoyed from independents.  If it hadn't been for voters who claim no party affiliation, Trump most likely would not be in the White House today.  In 2016, he carried independents by four percentage points across the country, according to the National Election Pool exit poll. But in the states that mattered most, independents pulled him across the finish line. For instance, in Michigan, which had the nation's closest contest, Trump won independents by 16 percentage points over Hillary Clinton.  So which Democrat is best positioned to benefit from the disenchantment that many of these less partisan voters are feeling about the Trump presidency?  Three months ago, the answer was clear. Former vice president Joe Biden was the only Democratic contender who beat Trump - by a narrow seven percentage points - among independents in a theoretical head-to-head matchup in the Post poll.  But in the latest survey, five of the most talked-about Democratic candidates are besting Trump with independents. Biden has expanded his lead over the president to 17 points, while Sens. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., do nearly as well, each leading the president by 16 points among independents. They favor Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., over Trump by 11 points, and South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg by 10 points.  In other words, the poll suggests that independents are increasingly willing to vote for a Democrat, no matter which of the most likely possibilities the party nominates. It also erodes to an erosion in Biden's chief selling point, which is that he is the most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too dangerous to go to court? Feds say Aryan gang members eyeing jail security, locks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article236998639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems probing Trump hotel, emoluments...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/impeachment-transcripts-show-democrats-probing-trump-hotel-emoluments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment transcripts released Tuesday show Democratic investigators have also probed on issues surrounding Rudy Giuliani, the Trump hotel and emoluments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year out, four scenarios for the big elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/a-year-out-heres-four-ways-2020-elections-could-go</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How voters feel about the economy and impeachment, and how Democrats’ nominee plays with general electorate, will decide which party rules in 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President could get whacked by legal losses in coming months...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/04/trump-legal-landmines-guide-065080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Nightclub Boom Ends With $28 Million PALMS Bar Writeoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/money/vegas-nightclub-boom-ends-with-2428-million-palms-bar-writeoff/ar-AAJUnOm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Vowed to Shrink the Trade Gap. It Keeps Growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trump-vowed-to-shrink-the-trade-gap-it-keeps-growing/ar-AAJTqg9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALIO:  No other option but to raise taxes in coming years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/05/ray-dalio-says-the-us-will-have-no-other-option-but-to-raise-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dalio says that the U.S. will have little choice but to raise taxes in the coming years to offset its mounting liabilities and debts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman facing felony for cancer fundraiser scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pennsylvania-woman-felony-charges-allegedly-faking-cancer-racking-up-10000-in-donations-gofundme-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"She took advantage of other people's generosity by lying about having cancer. She also lied about her own father's death to get another day off from work"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden accuses Warren of having elitist view...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b491ca4f60f04b55903cf7f3c1df6371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Without naming her, Joe Biden attacked fellow Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren on Tuesday for employing a "condescending" approach to politics that smacks of "elitism." The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to test laser weapon that incinerates drones, planes and missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10282673/us-army-laser-weapon-drone-plane-missiles/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEAVILY-ARMOURED vehicles loaded with laser cannons will be deployed by the US Army within the next three years. The upcoming weapon systems each chew through enough energy to power several homes a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says Senate would acquit if trial held today...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/05/mcconell-senate-acquit-trump-066103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple sell everything they own to live debt-free on bus with daughter and dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/couple-sell-everything-live-debt-20818536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Watson and wife Kristin, from Jacksonville, Florida, have been keen adventurers since they were children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharon Stone Sues Rapper Over 'SHARON STONED' Track...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/sharon-stone-sues-rapper-chanel-west-coast-sharon-stoned-track-1252604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artist released the song in 2018, and the actress alleges it "gratuitously repeats the name 'Sharon Stone' thirty-three times and the name 'Sharon' ninety-nine times."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPING:  ELECTIONS TEST 2020</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/state-elections-barometer-trump-popularity-ahead-2020-172704578.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Washington swept up in an impeachment saga, results in Kentucky, Mississippi and Virginia will be closely watched for how the crisis is influencing their voters, how strong the support is for Trump in Republican bastions, and whether Democrats are wielding increasing influence in the suburbs. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment reversal: Diplomat now acknowledges quid pro quo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2398dd73d3a444eb2257ba245d83af1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — "I now do recall." With that stunning reversal, diplomat Gordon Sondland handed House impeachment investigators another key piece of corroborating testimony Tuesday. He...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambush...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e55d2bec8ccb4dd694f4c0b34aa4b147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Drug cartel gunmen ambushed three SUVs along a dirt road, slaughtering six children and three women — all U.S. citizens living in northern Mexico — in a grisly attack that left...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials link childhood trauma to adult illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf647b36c0a64e4b935b96426d5baf86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. health officials estimate that millions of cases of heart disease and other illnesses are linked to abuse and other physical and psychological harm suffered early in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims From Mormon offshoot community...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/90d478d46e1d45bda0d969e9b517828c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — The nine women and children killed by drug cartel gunmen in northern Mexico lived in a remote farming community where residents with dual U.S.-Mexican citizenship consider...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House lawyers expected to take lead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ba4935edb764ef88c597176ad651e21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As House Democrats prepare for public impeachment hearings, President Donald Trump and his legal team are working to organize a defense that will rely heavily on White House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump OKs wider Syria oil mission, raising legal questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/251062e322ab4bba99251fe59c90540a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has approved an expanded military mission to secure an expanse of oil fields across eastern Syria, raising a number of difficult legal questions about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Lawn Mowers To Concerts, 'Deafening World' Hurting Our Ears...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/11/05/776242285/from-lawn-mowers-to-rock-concerts-our-deafening-world-is-hurting-our-ears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volume Control author David Owen says our ears largely evolved in a far quieter time than the one we currently live in. He warns that the ambient noises that surround us pose a threat to our hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Echo Buds' have mysterious hidden fitness tracking option...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/05/amazon-echo-buds-fitness-tracking-appears-in-alexa-software.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Alexa software to manage Echo Buds shows that they may soon be able to track your workouts, but it's not currently active.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow flags, red flags, black eyes for NFL's 100th season...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2019/11/05/yellow-flags-red-flags-black-eyes-for-nfls-100th-season/40552029/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL's centennial celebration has included a slew of yellow flags, red flags and black eyes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia voters cast ballots in wrong races...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/local/government-politics/unknown-number-of-stafford-voters-cast-ballots-in-wrong-races/article_5cd7747c-2ae2-565f-92c1-c77caf811a44.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unknown number of voters in six Stafford County precincts cast ballots in the wrong races Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women killed had alleged ties to sex cult...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/05/women-killed-in-mexican-cartel-murders-had-alleged-ties-to-sex-cult-nxivm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outpost Mormon community in Mexico is where underlings of Nxivm leader Keith Raniere recruited young women to work as nannies in an upstate New York compound run by the accused cult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy preps allies to 'protect navigation' in Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-navy-prepares-allies-protect-navigation-gulf-201625103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is training Gulf allies to "protect navigation" in the region's troubled waterways, as Washington seeks to build an alliance of friendly nations to contain Iran. The US' three-week-long International Maritime Exercise (IMX) that began on October 21 comes after a number</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 911 Supervisor Watched NETFLIX During Shooting Call...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/04/coral-springs-police-911-supervisor-watching-netflix-during-shooting-call/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Coral Springs Police Department Internal Affairs report provides a shocking snapshot inside the Coral Springs Police 911 call center on June 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-year-old charged in double murder escapes courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article237028179.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly Issues: New Touchscreen Voting Machines List Wrong Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/11/05/chaotic-start-to-election-day-in-philadelphia-as-some-new-touchscreen-voting-machines-not-taking-paper-ballots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a chaotic start to Election Day in Philadelphia, where new touchscreen voting machines were rolled out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rep. Omar Officially Divorced After 'Irretrievable Breakdown'...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/11/05/rep-ilhan-omar-officially-divorces-husband-ahmed-hirsi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Ilhan Omar has officially divorced from her husband in Minnesota, just a month after she filed a petition saying there was an "irretrievable breakdown" in their marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Introducing 'Skip Politics' Button To Bypass Trump Jokes In Seth Meyers' Special...</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/tv-shows/2019/11/05/netflix-skip-politics-button-trump-jokes-seth-meyers-special/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seth Meyers is known for his political comedy, something he displays on a daily basis as part of [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T to pay $60M for slowing cellphone data on unlimited plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-at-t-settlement/att-to-pay-60-million-in-settlement-for-slowing-cellphone-data-on-unlimited-plans-idUSKBN1XF26Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T will pay $60 million to resolve U.S. allegations it misled millions of smar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News orgs reject calls to expose...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/05/rand-paul-whistleblower-identity-media-outlets-066033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS BOSSES SCRAMBLE...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/05/abc-bosses-scramble-after-amy-robachs-comments-about-jeffrey-epstein-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC bosses are battling to deal with the fallout from comments made by “Good Morning America” reporter Amy Robach, who was caught on a hot mic claiming network brass scrapped her interv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Tells Followers to Set Forest Fires in USA, Europe...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/isis-tells-followers-to-set-forest-fires-in-u-s-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A media outlet affiliated with ISIS has been instructing the group's radical adherents to set forest fires in the U.S. to cause ecological disasters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone leaves court early on trial's 1st day, complaining of food poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/05/roger-stone-trial-opens-065991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence aide likely to testify in inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/05/politics/jennifer-williams-impeachment-inquiry/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior adviser to Vice President Mike Pence is likely to comply with a request to testify on Thursday in front of the committees leading the impeachment inquiry, multiple sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney next?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/05/mick-mulvaney-asked-to-testify-before-committees-conducting-impeachment-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the three House panels said the investigation “has revealed that you may have been directly involved in an effort orchestrated” by the president and his personal lawyer …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming Start as Man Has Seizure in Court...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/roger-stones-trial-gets-off-to-alarming-start-as-man-has-a-seizure-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sleep Divorce' on Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2019/11/05/sleep-divorce-on-the-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For couples who don't sleep well together, the stigma of separate beds may be changing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant dies of 'exhaustion' from carrying tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/travel/elephant-dies-tourists-sri-lanka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Breaks my heart."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels Winning Propaganda War...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/11/05/mexican-cartels-are-winning-the-propaganda-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cartels repeatedly demonstrate their capabilities as propagandists against the public, rivals, and even international governing bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worms found in woman's eye as scientists warn of emerging disease...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/parasitic-worms-found-woman-eye-163709192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parasitic worm typically found in cattle has been discovered in a woman’s eye in what scientists have warned may be an “emerging zoonotic disease” in the US.The 68-year-old woman is the second human to have become infected by the parasite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Historic division worse than Nixon...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/historic-division-87-democrats-want-trump-impeached-92-republicans-dont-worse-than-nixon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The partisan divide over impeaching and removing President Trump is at a record level, far worse than the similar fight over former President Richard Nixon, who resigned before he could be impeached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLISHER PUBLISHING...</title>
      <link>https://www.publishersweekly.com/pw/by-topic/industry-news/publisher-news/article/81646-hachette-warned-by-doj-moving-ahead-with-a-warning.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.publishersweekly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice has warned Hachette Book Group that its planned publication of 'A Warning' by an anonymous Trump administration official may violate a non-disclosure agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We had Clinton, We had Everything'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/11/05/okeefe-bombshell-abc-host-says-net-spiked-epstein-story-2016-had</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years ago, during the 2016 presidential election, ABC spiked an expose into convicted pedophile Jeffrey Epstein and his network of connections to powerful men, including Bill Clinton. That’s the bombshell scoop by investigative journalist James O’Keefe. In a hot mic video leaked to O’Keefe, 20/20 co-anchor Amy Robach can be heard angrily lamenting the fact that ABC killed the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaming addict dies from stroke caused by all-night sessions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/teenager-dies-suddenly-stroke-caused-20813891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of Piyawat Harikun, 17, want the tragedy to warn others that computer gaming can be deadly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Epstein's social contacts with Stephanopoulos, other celebs scrutinized...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/07/09/jeffrey-epsteins-social-contacts-with-katie-couric-george-stephanopoulos-other-celebs-scrutinized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Stephanopoulos denies being friends with Jeffrey Epstein, while Bill Clinton downplayed their travels together, and Prince Andrew and Sarah Ferguson long ago expressed regret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS CALL FOR POPULATION CONTROL</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/population-control-critical-part-climate-150004993.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Forty years ago, scientists from 50 nations converged on Geneva to discuss what was then called the “CO2-climate problem.” At the time, with reliance on fossil fuels having helped trigger the 1979 oil crisis, they predicted global warming would eventually become a major environmental challenge.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California hits Philly-area AMAZON seller with $1.6 million sales-tax bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/business/california-sales-tax-amazon-seller-philadelphia-business-20191105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Freifelder, who sells clothing, shoes, and groceries out of a small warehouse in Bensalem, has been caught in what his lawyer called “an interstate commerce speed trap.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein combative and in denial ahead of rape trial, inner circle says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/04/entertainment/harvey-weinstein-upcoming-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weinstein's impending criminal trial, which is set to begin January 6, has depleted him, members of the former film executive's small inner circle told CNN. The 67-year-old is physically weaker, but they don't describe an otherwise changed man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS CALL FOR POPULATION CONTROL</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/scientists-call-for-population-control-in-mass-climate-alarm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Population Control Is a Critical Part of Climate Fight, Scientists Warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well-oiled campaign has everything planned -- except him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article236866838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls for war...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-calls-for-war-against-mexican-drug-cartel-monsters-after-americans-murdered-in-shootout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday offered U.S. assistance as he called on Mexico to “wage war” against the country's murderous drug cartel “monsters” in response to the brutal killing of multiple Americans a day earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey savagely kills baby by dropping rock on his head...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/monkey-savagely-kills-baby-dropping-20816364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tot, aged four months, died in hospital after the primate dropped a huge stone on him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-month-old miraculously survives...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/05/7-month-old-baby-miraculously-survives-mexico-cartel-massacre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7-month-old baby survived a volley of gunfire unleashed by drug cartels in Mexico — thanks to one final, selfless act from her mother before the woman was killed. Baby Faith was one of several su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Recording From ABCNEWS Reveals Network Killed Story Implicating Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3lfwkTsJGYA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€¢ â€œIâ€™ve Had This Story for Three Yearsâ€¦ (ABC) Would Not Put It on The Airâ€� says Good Morning America Breaking News Anchor, and 20/20 Co-Anchor Amy Robach. â€œI...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodies left to burn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10280224/sonora-cartel-attack-mexico-us-families-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN AMERICAN mum died saving her baby as at least nine members of a Mormon family were murdered in a bloody shooting attack by a suspected drug cartel. Christina Langford Johnson, 31, was among thre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDEPENDENTS SHIFT LEFT</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-trails-Democratic-rivals-in-national-survey-14810165.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year from the 2020 election, President Donald Trump trails some potential Democratic rivals in head-to-head matchups, with his national support level fixed at about 40 percent, according to a Washington Post-ABC News poll.  The new poll highlights the degree to which most of the country already has made a judgment about the president's performance and its voting preferences next year. Among the 39 percent of registered voters who approve of Trump's job performance, Trump is winning at least 95 percent support against each of five possible Democratic opponents. But among the 58 percent of voters who disapprove of Trump, he receives no more than 7 percent of support.  Former vice president Joe Biden, Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., run strongest against the president nationally, with Biden leading by 17 points (56 percent to 39 percent), Warren by 15 points (55 percent to 40 percent) and Sanders by 14 points (55 percent to 41 percent).  South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg and Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., the other two Democrats tested against Trump, also lead the president among registered voters, with Buttigieg up by 52 percent to 41 percent, and Harris ahead by 51 percent to 42 percent.  The poll reflects national findings; other surveys in the states expected to play an outsize role in the 2020 contest have shown tighter races, particularly in parts of the Upper Midwest that Trump flipped from Democrats in 2016.  Nonetheless, the national results represent a shift away from Trump since the summer, when only Biden had a clear advantage over the incumbent. With Republicans and Democrats mostly locked into their voting intentions, the biggest difference between the results from July and those in the new poll is that independents have moved in the direction of the Democratic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts and fire knocked out thousands of cellphones. What happens in big quake?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-05/mass-cellphone-outages-during-blackouts-and-fires-are-a-grim-preview-of-life-after-a-major-earthquake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California saw significant interruptions of cellphone service due to the planned power shut-offs at precisely the time customers needed to be alerted about evacuation warnings — raising questions about how prepared California is for future electric shut-offs and other public safety emergencies,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fatally stabbed over POPEYE'S sandwich...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/man-stabbed-to-death-in-maryland-popeyes-after-altercation-over-chicken-sandwich-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fight over someone cutting in line lead to a fatal stabbing Monday night at a Maryland Popeyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue black cat steals show during 'Monday Night Football'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/rogue-black-cat-at-metlife-stadium-steals-show-during-monday-night-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An accidental star is born</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistaken identity?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/05/death-toll-climbs-in-mexican-cartel-shootout-as-more-us-citizens-identified/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI has opened an investigation into the massacre of US citizens gunned down by drug cartels in northern Mexico — as the death toll has climbed to nine, including three women, 8-month-old…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucson to decide whether to be Arizona's only sanctuary city...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f4b359eeb2747cabd825fd1b9576a8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUCSON, Ariz. (AP) — Voters in Tucson will decide Tuesday whether to make the liberal enclave Arizona's only sanctuary city in an effort to confront President Donald Trump's immigration policies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-police violence surges in the tough suburbs of Paris...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21ceaa641a6c48e0baffdcb9169e7512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A resurgence of anti-police violence has emerged in the long-troubled towns around Paris, signs that lawlessness still simmers in French urban hotspots that exploded in three weeks of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO under pressure over 'hugs not bullets' policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/05/mexicos-security-failure-grisly-cartel-shootout-shows-who-holds-the-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amlo strategy of alleviating poverty and a ban on corruption questioned amid recent cartel violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts fear voters will be deceived by 'deepfake' videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-05/deep-fakes-2020-election-silicon-valley-cure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technologists unveil the first significant effort to arm reporters and campaigns with software tools to combat the growing problem of "deep fake" videos. The effort faces formidable hurdles — both technical and political — and developers say there's no time to waste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Protesters Want to Soak the Rich, But That's Not All...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-protesters-want-soak-rich-050000214.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.Sharp divisions between the rich and poor are fueling a global wave of unrest -- but that’s just one of the grievances driving people onto the streets, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running just once a week could significantly lower risk of death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-running-just-once-week-could-significantly-lower-105213397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research has found that any amount of running, and even at a slow pace, could be beneficial for health and could help lower an individual's risk of death. The researchers analyzed the data to investigate the association between running/jogging and the risk of death from all causes, cardiovascular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orwell exhibit bares 'doublespeak' legacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d00f819347c04c08833fd3b419935b31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — War is Peace. Freedom is Slavery. Ignorance is Strength. Those were the slogans of the Party in George Orwell's 1949 novel "1984" that allowed the superstate of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elections in 4 states offer tests of 2020 voter enthusiasm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a713901560a8432ba36d24e65e68f4d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gubernatorial and legislative elections in four states Tuesday will test voter enthusiasm and party organization amid impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump and a fevered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aviation industry to counter 'flight shaming' movement...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191105110922-soqa0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIRLINES-ENVIRONMENT/IATA (PIX):Aviation industry to counter flight shaming movement: IATA chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORSESE: I Said MARVEL Movies Aren't Cinema. Let Me Explain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ie/entertainment/indepth/martin-scorsese-i-said-marvel-movies-arent-cinema-let-me-explain/ar-AAJSMU9?li=BBr5KbJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORMON MASSACRE: American mothers, children executed by cartel gunmen in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7650129/Relatives-say-5-US-citizens-killed-northern-Mexico.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventeen family members from the LeBaron and Langford families were 'ambushed' eight miles apart while heading to celebrate a wedding anniversary in three cars from La Mora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone trial promises political drama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf3e43dc56f244bda7dd6c4308d38e1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a longtime Republican provocateur and former confidant of President Donald Trump, is going on trial over charges related to his alleged efforts to exploit the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOBBS:  BETTER THAN GEORGE WASHINGTON</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dear-leader-goes-full-circle-trump-praises-great-lou-dobbs-for-praising-trump-as-greatest-president-in-us-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dear Leader goes full circle at Kentucky Rally: Donald Trump praises 'Great' Lou Dobbs for praising Trump as 'greatest president' in US history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST:  Pure, brazen contempt for Congress on full display...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Trump-s-pure-brazen-contempt-for-Congress-is-on-14809452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This editorial appears in The Washington Post.  - - -  "He must be brought forward to testify," President Donald Trump fumed on Twitter on Monday, regarding the whistleblower who revealed the president's corrupt attempts to extort political favors from Ukraine. "Written answers not acceptable!"  The president considered written answers more than adequate when special counsel Robert Mueller sought information from Trump during the Justice Department's Russia investigation. More to the point, if Trump were interested in fact-finding and truth-telling, rather than distracting from the substance of the charges against him, he would provide documents and encourage all relevant witnesses to testify. Instead, administration officials are refusing to testify before the House Intelligence Committee - officials who likely have firsthand knowledge crucial to the House's impeachment inquiry.  Robert Blair, an aide to acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney, was on the call during which Trump pressed Ukraine's president to investigate former vice president Joe Biden. John Eisenberg, a National Security Council lawyer, reportedly suggested limiting access to the transcript of that call and told others not to discuss it. Russell Vought, the acting director of the Office of Management and Budget, might shed light on Trump's peremptory suspension of military aid to Ukraine, an act that appears to have been an element in the president's corrupt pressure campaign.  These no-shows are just the latest examples of the contemptuous war Trump and his allies have waged on Congress and its legitimate, constitutional oversight role, starting well before the impeachment inquiry. Even when Republicans controlled both chambers, former White House adviser Steve Bannon absurdly claimed executive privilege to refuse to answer congressional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 most vulnerable senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/10-vulnerable-senators-2020-republicans-play-defense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;List includes two GOP senators running in states that Democrat Hillary Clinton won in 2016, but the most vulnerable senator of all is a Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China presses for more tariff roll-backs in 'phase one' trade deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-7649805/China-pushing-Trump-remove-tariffs-ahead-trade-deal--media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By David Lawder and Andrea ShalalWASHINGTON, Nov 4 (Reuters) - China is pushing U.S. President Donald Trump to remove more tariffs imposed in September as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING ABOUT 'WARNING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7648605/Donald-Trumps-Justice-Department-tries-BLOCK-Anonymous-tell-all.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Department has warned the anonymous author of a forth-coming tell-all about Donald Trump's White House  he or she may be violating nondisclosure agreements by writing the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN:  AMAZONFACEBOOKGOOGLE engage in abuse of personal privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/edward-snowden-says-facebook-amazon-and-google-engage-in-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking remotely at Web Summit, Snowden slams big tech companies, saying they make people vulnerable to surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubles, what troubles? Trump basks in populist love...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/troubles-troubles-trump-basks-populist-love-020104750.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking the stage in a packed Kentucky arena to the strains of America's unofficial patriotic anthem, "God Bless the USA," Donald Trump didn't look like a man in trouble. The ear splitting cheers from the crowd of around 20,000 in Lexington's Rupp Arena explained why. Dressed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARAMUCCI: President is Like Jim Jones cult leader...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/president-trump-will-be-out-of-office-by-march-2020-says-anthony-scaramucci-210434593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump insider Anthony Scaramucci predicts Republican leadership will force President Trump to leave office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman goes blind tattooing eyeballs...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/beauty/face-body/dragon-girl-24-who-has-spent-over-37k-modifying-her-body-goes-blind-for-three-weeks-after-tattooing-eyeballs-blue/news-story/43d40d9c7ca3af99cbc2c8fa8a07f360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who has spent over $37,000 modifying her body reveals she went blind for three weeks after getting her eyeballs tattooed with blue ink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER BURNS THROUGH ANOTHER BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/uber-shares-tumble-6-on-116-billion-quarterly-loss-2019-11-04?mod=newsviewer_click</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber has lost more than $7 billion so far this fiscal year, prompting a flurry of questions from some analysts about its long-term prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARAMUCCI: President is Like Jim Jones; GOP Drinking Kool-Aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/11/04/scaramucci-trump-is-like-jim-jones-unfortunately-gop-is-drinking-kool-aid-punch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During an interview on Monday's with Yahoo! Finance, former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci said he was disappointed Republican lawmakers have not turned on President Donald Trump yet because he believed Trump is like cult leader Jim Jones. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris and Corbyn Trade Brexit Barbs as UK Election Heats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnson-corbyn-trade-brexit-barbs-230030434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Prime Minister Boris Johnson and his main rival, Labour Leader Jeremy Corbyn, traded blows over Brexit as the U.K. prepares to vote next month on which of the two men should lead it out of the European Union.Johnson wrote an open letter to Corbyn asking him to clarify his strategy for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky governor looks for last-minute boost from Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dde5664a631345dea7fe1ce1e5c3597f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEXINGTON, Ky. (AP) — Pushing to help a Republican governor hold onto his office, President Donald Trump barnstormed for Gov. Matt Bevin of Kentucky on Monday, delivering a raucous election eve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a18021c61d964b0a94555b208ae7ebe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Dow Jones Industrial Average returned to a record on Monday, joining other market gauges at all-time highs, as the stock market's rally carried into a fifth week. Oil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat lays out White House campaign to oust her...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/19a3091850b546e9af821a5a4d9c1701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It started with a warning to watch her back, that people were "looking to hurt" her. From there, former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch told House investigators, it...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
