<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Will Trump pardon?</title>
      <link>https://www.predictit.org/markets/detail/5211/Will-Trump-pardon-Stone-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.predictit.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Heart Attack Injects New Life Into Campaign?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/13/bernie-sanders-heart-attack-070538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Down Drones With Standard Laser Pointers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/11/how-chilean-protesters-took-down-drone-standard-laser-pointers/161288/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The low-powered presentation tool/dangerous children’s toy is becoming a weapon of choice for protesters around the world trying to take down or disable surveillance tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt 'Asian gunman in dark clothes'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/los-angeles-county-deputies-respond-report-santa-clarita-school-shooting-n1082231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is an active shooter situation," said the Santa Clarita Valley sheriff's office. "If you live in neighborhoods anywhere near Saugus High, PLEASE LOCK DOORS and stay inside."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPSOS:  PRESIDENT'S JOB APPROVAL 39%...</title>
      <link>https://www.ipsos.com/sites/default/files/ct/news/documents/2019-11/2019_reuters_tracking_-_core_political_impeachment_tracker_11_13_2019.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ipsos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple faces jail for living in RV on own property...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/couple-may-be-jailed-for-living-in-rv-after-fire-burns-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mississippi couple whose home was partially gutted in a fire is now facing fines and jail time for temporarily living in an RV while they dealt with insurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California high school on lockdown after at least seven people shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7686163/California-high-school-lockdown-six-people-shot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting was reported st 7.45am Pacific Time at Saugus High School on Centurion Way in Santa Clarita, leaving at least six people wounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Morgue Overwhelmed with Dead Migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/11/13/exclusive-border-countys-facilities-overwhelmed-with-dead-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A border county medical examiner's office is now packed beyond capacity with the remains of migrants who died after crossing from Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling narratives on Trump's actions collide for shared audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/11/14/dueling-narratives-on-trumps-actions-collide-for-shared-audience/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A witness had a moment of speechlessness when pressed on conspiracy theories apparently driving the president’s actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg's path to convention  -- and beyond...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/470231-bloombergs-path-to-the-convention-and-beyond</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Bloomberg runs, he'll open those deep pockets in the presidential primary contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems confront prospect of long primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/470378-the-memo-democrats-confront-prospect-of-long-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no true front-runner in the Democratic presidential race — and that opens up the specter of a long and divisive nomination fight within a party desperate to beat President Trump in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/shooting-at-saugus-high-in-santa-clarita/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle lines harden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d7dff9c076d44b0b55ed4d822cf383b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With historic impeachment hearings underway, Democrats and Republicans are hardening their arguments over the actions of President Donald Trump as they set out to win over a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Kellyanne Blows Up at Blitzer for Saying 'There Are Issues' With Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kellyanne-conway-blows-up-at-cnns-wolf-blitzer-for-saying-there-are-issues-with-her-marriage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Did you just say there are issues there?” she exclaimed. “You don’t want to talk about—why would you say that?!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SAYS, SHE SAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/kellyanne-conway-rips-msnbc-featuring-george-conways-anti-trump-commentary-where-is-the-shame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Senior Advisor Kellyanne Conway appeared on CNN Thursday morning for special coverage of the ongoing impeachment inquiry, and things got strange and heated when host Wolf Blitzer asked her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They turn '49 MERCURYS and COBRAS into EVs, one TESLA carcass at a time...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-11-14/tesla-electric-vehicles-classic-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing army of hot rodders is cannibalizing crashed electric cars and turning them into custom vehicles with electric power trains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye 'Sunday Service' with Joel Osteen to attract record crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/kanye-west-joel-osteen-sunday-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The focus of the all-day affair will be Kanye’s journey to finding God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID...</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.idrudgereport.iDrudgeReportUniversal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;play.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, Android will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allows results in alerts being sent to your phone whenever there is a siren, new banner or a highlighted headline (e.g. colored red.) Review these urgent headlines anytime by tapping on the urgent headlines button (bell with lines under it.) Then to modify which alerts you receive by tapping on the settings (gear) icon. *** SCROLL TO TOP *** Tap on the reload button.  *** COLUMN SWITCHING (phones) *** Tap on the columns icon once to be taken to the top of the first column. Tap again for the top of the second column. Tap for the third column. Tap one more time and you'll be brought to the top. Repeat as desired. A personal response for those who tap on the Notifications Button &gt; Settings Button &gt; Tap "App Support" for comments, bug reports or suggestions for improvement. Posting bugs in the comments may not get the attention they deserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I wish I'd never been born: Rise of the anti-natalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/14/anti-natalists-childfree-population-climate-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adherents view life not as a gift and a miracle, but a harm and an imposition. And their notion that having children may be a bad idea seems to be gaining mainstream popularity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass brawl breaks out at gym as men swing punches, dumbbells, pull-up bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/mass-brawl-breaks-out-gym-20879199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group of gym-goers grabbed exercise equipment to use as weapons during the terrifying scrap at the Ab Salute training facility in Brentwood, Essex</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>468%: Stocks 10-year run becomes best bull market ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/the-markets-10-year-run-became-the-best-bull-market-ever-this-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current bull market, which started March 9, 2009, has enjoyed a whopping 468% gain for the S&amp;P 500 through the first day of November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Kellyanne goes off after CNN plays clip of husband criticizing president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/470433-kellyanne-conway-after-cnn-plays-george-conway-remarks-im-embarrassed-for-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House counselor Kellyanne Conway confronted CNN's Wolf Blitzer on live television Thursday after he played footage of her husband criticizing President Trump and Republicans as part of MSNBC's coverage of the impeachment hearing the day befo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN MERCH: WAR ON WEALTHY!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elizabeth-warren-billionaire-tears-mugs-145359512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren isn’t backing down from her fight against billionaires — in fact, the Democratic senator from Massachusetts is now selling $25 “billionaire tears” mugs on her campaign website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of city hangs in balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10345964/venice-flooding-mayor-barrier-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mayor of Venice says the “future of the city” hangs in the balance after “apocalyptic” floods devastated the iconic lagoon metropolis. More questions have been asked about a multi-b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Falling Asleep, Staying Asleep Increasingly Rare...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-falling-asleep-staying-asleep-growing-more-difficult-for-americans-each-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may not think twice about the occasional sleepless night, but a new study finds that falling asleep and staying asleep is an increasingly rare skill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea threatens military escalation as clock ticks on year-end deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/North-Korea-threatens-military-escalation-as-14834092.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea - North Korea has a message for President Donald Trump and the United States: The clock is ticking, and a bomb is about to explode.  There are seven weeks until North Korea's leader Kim Jong Un is scheduled to deliver a keynote New Year's Day speech. That will come a day after his self-imposed year-end deadline expires for the United States to come up with new proposals to restart nuclear talks.  On Wednesday - with Washington transfixed on the House impeachment inquiry - North Korea significantly raised the stakes, making an implicit threat to resume long-range missile or nuclear tests. In an official statement, the North said it felt "betrayed" by a U.S. decision to continue with joint air drills with South Korea, calling it an "undisguised breach" of an agreement made between Kim and President Trump in Singapore last year.  As a result, North Korea said it no longer felt bound by previous commitments. That could signal plans to resume nuclear or long-range missile tests.  "The U.S. is not accepting with due consideration the year-end time limit that we set out of great patience and magnanimity," the statement from the country's State Affairs Commission said.  "We, without being given anything, gave things the U.S. president can brag about but the U.S. side has not yet taken any corresponding step," it added. "Now, betrayal is only what we feel from the U.S. side."  Trump has repeatedly boasted that North Korea has stopped conducting nuclear or long-range missile tests under his watch, although it has conducted about a dozen shorter-range ballistic missile tests since April. But Pyongyang says Trump has reneged on a promise to end joint military exercises with Seoul.  Relations between the two sides deteriorated sharply after a failed summit in Hanoi in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Paramedic Cut $8K Ring Off Dead Woman's Finger, Sold It For $45...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/11/13/paramedic-accused-of-cutting-diamond-ring-off-dead-patients-finger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arkansas paramedic was arrested Monday for allegedly cutting a 1.7-carat diamond ring from a deceased woman's finger at a hospital and selling it at a pawnshop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans struggle to ID true facts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c762f01370ee4bbe8bbd20f5ddf2adbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a sharply divided country, here's something many Americans agree on: It's hard to know what's a true and honest fact. A new poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old dogs, new tricks: 10,000 pets needed for science...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bee7e617c2b44b397e79f4a16523877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Can old dogs teach us new tricks? Scientists are looking for 10,000 pets for the largest-ever study of aging in canines. They hope to shed light on human longevity too. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite police force spreads terror in the barrios of Venezuela...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114123112-q82ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-VIOLENCE/POLICE (SPECIAL REPORT, PIX, TV):SPECIAL REPORT-Elite police force spreads terror in the barrios of Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are human and want to have sex too, disabled women say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114121711-tjt2p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women with disabilities are often ignored, shunned or mocked when seeking help from medical practitioners or even friends or family, victims said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire threat darkens California dream, residents say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114093153-rsecy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more powerful wildfires threaten more people, the Golden State may be losing its shine, some residents say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America, Friendship, Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/13/ford-v-ferrari-starring-matt-damon-and-christian-bale-races-to-the-screen-with-big-ideas-about-america-friendship-and-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ford v Ferrari,” much buzzed for Oscar nominations, is coming this Friday. Among racing movies, it’s a winner, with a compelling central story about Henry Ford’s team vs. F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Humans Step In After Robots Fumble 777 Jet Assembly...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/boeing-abandons-its-failed-fuselage-robots-on-the-777x-handing-the-job-back-to-machinists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing said Wednesday it is reverting to an older approach that "has proven more reliable, requiring less work by hand and less rework, than what the robots were capable of."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Manly Appeal of 'FORD V FERRARI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/11/movie-review-ford-v-ferrari-manly-appeal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a delightful throwback, an old-school story of hard men solving tough problems, in superbly entertaining fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses can expect abuse, death threats, say survivors of past scandals...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114103057-qj0y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-SPOTLIGHT (PIX):Impeachment witnesses can expect abuse, death threats, say survivors of past political scandals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love him or hate him, voters say hearings will not change views...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114010359-6qkkm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-DECIDERS (PIX):Love him or hate him, voters say impeachment hearings will not change their views on Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENGALS? STEELERS? Bookmaker posts odds on Kaepernick team...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/entertainment/2019/11/gambling-site-posts-odds-on-colin-kaepernicks-next-team.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick will work out for NFL teams on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATE ENTRY:  Deval Patrick running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/deval-patrick-2020-former-massachusetts-governor-expected-to-announce-he-is-running-for-president-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He starts far behind in a record-sized field that polling shows is now divided into two tiers — with the top tier consisting of Joe Biden​, Elizabeth Warren​, Bernie Sanders​ and Pete Buttigieg​</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From sci-fi to science lab: Holograms you can 'feel'...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-11-sci-fi-science-lab-holograms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walking, talking holograms have been a staple of sci-fi films since Princess Leia was magically brought to life in "Star Wars".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT FLOOD OF VENICE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venice-braces-more-high-water-alarms-sound-090208346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice braced itself for more rising waters on Thursday as Italy's government prepared to take emergency measures for the canal city struck by an exceptional tide this week. As authorities on Thursday prepared to assess the extent of the damage to Venice's cultural treasures, such as St Mark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gaza rockets disrupt Israel, Islamic Jihad cease-fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3609c737a22e4c3a95cda6c2eb411a59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Gaza militants fired a barrage of rockets into Israel on Thursday, hours after a cease-fire was declared to end two days of intense fighting between Israel and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Mueller prosecutor advises Dems to evoke Watergate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/top-mueller-prosecutor-andrew-weissmann-offers-impeachment-advice-to-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of special counsel Robert Mueller's top prosecutors is offering advice to House Democrats for their impeachment proceedings against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother speaks about autistic son who died after being restrained at school...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/education/article237229909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATE ENTRY:  Deval Patrick running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/former-mass-gov-deval-patrick-announce-presidential-bid-n1081881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A late-entry into the Democratic primary would face fundraising and organization challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC features George Conway...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-conway-on-msnbc-republicans-were-fundamentally-illogical-and-incoherent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway continued his surprising appearance on MSNBC panels covering the impeachment hearings and not disappoint loyal viewers eager for harsh criticism of Congressional Republicans in defense o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  'Superbugs' on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/superbugs-rise-new-cdc-report-finds-threat-has-increased-previous-report-2013-2865723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report found that 35,000 people die every year from these drug-resistant "superbugs" compared to 23,000 in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA expects record number of fliers over Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/470366-tsa-expects-record-number-of-fliers-over-thanksgiving-holiday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) is anticipating a record number of fliers over the Thanksgiving holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal deficit hits $134 billion in one month!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/economy/470314-federal-deficit-hits-134-billion-in-one-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal deficit reached $134 billion in October, the first month of fiscal 2020, according to data the Treasury Department released Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Hong Kong chaos raises fears about what's next...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-descends-chaos-china-015123212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sharp escalation of violence in Hong Kong is once again raising the question of how China's central government will respond: Will it intervene, or allow the chaos to persist? The Liaison Office, which represents mainland authorities in Hong Kong, said Wednesday that actions in the semi-autonomous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS to be on hand for Kaepernick workout...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/cowboys/2019/11/13/colin-kaepernick-nfl-workout-dallas-cowboys/4179869002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite owner Jerry Jones' stance of mandating players stand for the anthem, the Cowboys will be in attendance for Colin Kaepernick's workout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a lot of mistakes? Try meditating, research says...</title>
      <link>https://preview.ajc.com/lifestyles/health/making-lot-mistakes-try-mediating-research-says/2Qfi3vRiTbSRNAW283cYMJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;preview.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found that meditating even just once can help people make fewer mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop who investigated sex abuse accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bef8c2e19d1247268fd8c47141623719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Roman Catholic bishop named by Pope Francis to investigate the church’s response to clergy sexual abuse in Buffalo, New York, has himself been accused of sexual abuse of a child,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors to decide on Roger Stone's fate...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/11/13/roger-stone-trump-allys-trial-over-russia-wikileaks-concludes/2581039001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors hear closing arguments Wednesday in the trial of Roger Stone, a longtime GOP operative and Trump ally accused of lying to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Turkeys So Bold -- They Knock on Door for Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/where-wild-turkeys-are-so-bold-they-knock-on-the-door-for-food/ar-BBWHDw8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren buys CNBC commercial time to blast billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/elizabeth-warren-blasts-billionaires-in-campaign-ad-calling-for-wealth-tax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is time for a wealth tax," Elizabeth Warren says in a fiery new campaign ad blasting billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insect apocalypse coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/13/europe/insect-apocalypse-report-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's being called the unnoticed apocalypse. The number of insects is declining rapidly and 41% face extinction. However, scientists say we can be the first responders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow closes at record high as DISNEY pops more than 7%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/dow-futures-fed-chair-jerome-powell-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow hit an all-time high on Wednesday as Disney shares popped and investors digested testimony from the top-ranking Fed official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE To No Longer Sell Shoes On AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nike-shoes-no-longer-on-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike's direct sales to consumers are growing, and some analysts say its split with Amazon could curb counterfeiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL: WE WILL HAVE A TRIAL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/13/mcconnell-trump-impeachment-articles-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell on Wednesday said the Senate cannot dismiss the articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbug infections rising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a646fe6429ab46e0aab3f09a60d77b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Drug-resistant “superbug” infections have been called a developing nightmare that could set medicine back a century, making conquered germs once again untreatable. So there’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop who investigated sex abuse in Buffalo accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/national/bishop-who-investigated-sex-abuse-accused-of-sex-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney informed Catholic officials in New Jersey that he is preparing a lawsuit on behalf of a client who says he was molested by Brooklyn Bishop Nicholas DiMarzio in the mid-1970s, when DiMa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/11/13/jobs-why-retirement-disappearing-boomers-gen-xers/2579098001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Americans are opting to work well into retirement, a growing trend that threatens to upend the old workforce model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deval Patrick tells allies he's running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/13/politics/deval-patrick-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick is telling friends and allies in phone calls on Wednesday that he has made a decision to run for president, two people familiar with the matter say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Wallace: Testimony 'Very Damaging'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/13/fox-news-chris-wallace-taylor-testimony-very-damaging-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Chris Wallace said that Ambassador William Taylor's House testimony Wednesday was &amp;quot;very damaging&amp;quot; to President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY Anthrax A Powerful Weapon -- In Fight Against Cancer?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-anthrax-a-powerful-weapon-in-fight-against-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of researchers say they have formulated a new method of bladder cancer treatment, and it involves an unconventional ingredient: anthrax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House projects disinterest: 'Boring'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/13/donald-trump-impeachment-hearings-070575</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA readies new nuke missile test?</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/space/2019/11/13/is-the-us-about-to-test-a-new-ballistic-missile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A test of an intermediate-range ballistic missile could be coming soon. Here's what to watch for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY+ surpasses 10 million sign-ups in 1 day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/disney-surpasses-10-million-sign-ups-since-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's new streaming service launched Tuesday with some technical difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Prozac pollution' making fish less aggressive...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/prozac-pollution-making-fish-less-aggressive-says-study-11860507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the behaviour of solitary fish is not altered, it does appear to have an effect on fish in a group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UF student president faces impeachment threat over Trump Jr. visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/education/2019/11/12/uf-student-president-faces-impeachment-threat-over-trump-jr-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A push to oust Student Body President Michael Murphy comes after an email surfaces, suggesting he worked with the Trump campaign to bring a political speech to campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURLEY:  Are Dems building a collapsible impeachment?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/470217-are-democrats-building-a-collapsible-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The constitutional basis to remove a president from office must rest on a solid foundation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
