<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Crocodiles and monkeys left in garbage-filled cages at world's filthiest zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9280305/disgusting-zoo-depressed-monkeys-crocodiles-rotting-rubbish-cages-indonesia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zoo in Indonesia has sparked outrage after images emerged showing monkeys and crocodiles rotting in rubbish-strewn cages. The photos were taken at a compound for the Strategic Army Command, a bra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top AI researchers race to detect deepfake videos: 'Outgunned'......</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Top-AI-researchers-race-to-detect-deepfake-13975018.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top artificial-intelligence researchers across the country are racing to defuse an extraordinary political weapon: computer-generated fake videos that could undermine candidates and mislead voters during the 2020 presidential campaign.  And they have a message: We're not ready.  The researchers have designed automatic systems that can analyze videos for the telltale indicators of a fake, assessing light, shadows, blinking patterns - and, in one potentially groundbreaking method, even how a candidate's real-world facial movements relate to each other, like the angle they tilt their head when they smile.  But for all that progress, the researchers say they remain vastly overwhelmed by a technology they fear could herald a damaging new wave of disinformation campaigns, much in the same way fake news stories and deceptive Facebook groups were deployed to influence public opinion during the 2016 race.  Powerful new AI software has effectively democratized the creation of convincing "deepfake" videos, making it easier than ever to fabricate someone appearing to say or do something they didn't really do, from harmless satires and film tweaks to targeted harassment and deepfake porn.  And researchers fear it's only a matter of time before the videos are deployed for maximum damage - to sow confusion, fuel doubt or undermine an opponent, potentially on the eve of a White House vote.  "We are outgunned," said Hany Farid, a computer-science professor and digital-forensics expert at the University of California, Berkeley. "The number of people working on the video-synthesis side, as opposed to the detector side, is 100 to 1."  These AI-generated videos have yet to drive their own political scandal in the U.S. But even simple tweaks to existing videos can create turmoil, as happened...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell Is Going On In Dominican Republic?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/dominican-republic-grand-bahia-hard-rock-american-tourist-death-846888/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though it’s unclear if they’re connected, at least six American tourists have died under mysterious circumstances in the last year alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MSNBC Shakeup as Andy Lack Fumes Over Ratings Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/exclusive-msnbc-shakeup-puts-jonathan-wald-and-dan-arnall-in-charge-of-dayside-programming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC implemented a big shakeup in programming this week, Mediaite has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino R-rated 'STAR TREK' will be f*cking foulmouthed...</title>
      <link>https://www.empireonline.com/movies/news/tarantino-star-trek-project-sweary-r-rated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.empireonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE HICKS TO TESTIFY ON HILL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7135071/Hope-Hicks-testify-Democrat-run-House-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Hope Hicks has agreed to appear before the House Judiciary Committee next week - the first former White House aide to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela: Overcrowded Morgue Asks Families to Take Bodies Home..</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/06/12/venezuela-overcrowded-morgue-asks-families-to-take-bodies-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overcrowded morgue in San Cristóbal, western Venezuela, has asked families of the deceased to take their bodies home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/reality-tv/2019/06/12/barbara-corcoran-brother-john-mysteriously-found-dead-dominican-republic-hotel-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shark Tank star Barbara Corcoran is speaking out about her brother's death amid an FBI [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chopper crash renews 9/11 worry about rogue aircraft in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dfbd1d85669a4431af3fcd8f9be81331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor charged with reusing rectal sensors inserted in patients...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/doctor/medical-device-reused-105892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are encouraging patients of a Michigan doctor to consider HIV and hepatitis testing after state investigators charged that the physician reused rectal devices at his Kalamazoo-area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  MARK LEVIN 'UNFREEDOM' #1 NYT FOR 3 WEEKS AFTER SELLING 250,000; TOPS WOLFF, HOWARD STERN, GEORGE WILL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/D85Z8iiXUAAprBB.jpg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world's largest pot farms...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-santa-barbara-pot-grows-20190612-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Santa Barbara County opened the doors to large-scale cannabis cultivation, a largely unregulated rush led by moneyed interests ensued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considering new military base in Poland that could be named after him...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-poland-us-military-duda-base-fort-trump-rose-garden-a8956301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New video shows adult cows being abused at Indiana farm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27937278db654a56978ae301fb536451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine becomes 8th state to legalize assisted suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwlp.com/news/health/maine-becomes-8th-state-to-legalize-assisted-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwlp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUSTA, Maine (AP) — Maine legalized medically assisted suicide on Wednesday, becoming the eighth state to allow terminally ill people to end their lives with prescribed medication. Democratic Gov…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removed organs a 'mystery' after Army vet died in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/everett-palmer-prison-death-organs-removed-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of Army veteran Everett Palmer Jr. still doesn't how or why he died in a Pennsylvania prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oversight Committee votes to hold Barr, Ross in contempt...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/448226-oversight-panel-holds-barr-ross-in-contempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Oversight and Reform Committee voted largely along party lines on Wednesday to hold Attorney General William Barr and Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross in contempt for failing to comply with congressional subpoenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS:  Average illegal has lived in US for 15 years, longest on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/census-average-illegal-immigrant-has-lived-in-us-for-15-years-longest-on-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the latest example of how ineffective immigration law has been for decades, a new report on Census Bureau numbers shows that the typical illegal immigrant has lived inside the United States for 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of Adults Still Sleep With Childhood 'Comfort Object'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/third-adults-sleep-comfort-object-childhood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting a good night's sleep is a just as much as challenge as it is a priority for many of us, which is why people often turn to various nighttime "rituals" before and after hitting the sack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Schultz pausing presidential run; Recovering from surgeries...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/846867/howard-schultz-says-hes-taking-detour-from-exploring-2020-candidacy-recovering-from-back-surgeries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz won't be doing any more 2020 campaign exploring until September. Schultz announced in January that he was "seriously considering" running for president in 2020. But after an early media blitz and a series of appearances across the country, he mostly dropped off the radar in recent weeks, sparking questions about what exactly the status of his potential campaign was and whether he was still exploring a candidacy. In a letter on Wednesday, Schultz addressed his absence, saying that he had to "cut my travels short" after experiencing back pain while in Arizona and that he underwent three back surgeries over the course of two months. "Today, I am feeling much better, and my doctors foresee a full recovery so long as I rest and rehabilitate. I have decided to take the summer to do just that." A previous report form Fox Business had suggested that Schultz delayed his campaign decision to see whether former Vice President Joe Biden would emerge as the likely nominee, with the report saying that "this would be a significant impediment to Schultz running for president since his campaign would focus on similar issues to Biden." Schultz in his Wednesday letter said he's taking "this detour from the road reluctantly" but that he will be "back in touch after Labor Day." Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Cops Sue Claiming Bias Against Whites...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/06/11/san-francisco-police-officers-sue-city-claiming-bias-against-whites-in-promotions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen present and former San Francisco police officers sued the city in federal court Tuesday, claiming that they have been discriminated against in promotions because they are white.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police who shot rapper 55 times in 3.5 seconds acted reasonably, report found...</title>
      <link>http://www.ktvu.com/news/police-who-shot-vallejo-rapper-55-times-in-35-seconds-acted-reasonably-report-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;A retired peace officer with experience in training police&amp;nbsp;officers in the use of force said the Vallejo police officers' fatal shooting&amp;nbsp;of rap artist Willie McCoy, 20, in a Taco Bell drive-thru in February was reasonable and in line with modern training and police practices,&amp;nbsp; the city attorney said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly man robs bank to go back to prison...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/elderly-robbery-suspect-wanted-to-return-to-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 81-year-old man who has spent most of his adult life behind bars for stealing from banks said he robbed a credit union in Tucson months after his release from prison because his monthly $800 Social Security payment wasn't enough to live on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois establishes abortion as 'fundamental right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190612-illinois-establishes-abortion-fundamental-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illinois establishes abortion as 'fundamental right'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL SPENDING TOPS $3 TRILLION IN '19</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-spending-tops-3-trillion-through-may-first-time-deficit-hits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden leads by 'landslide proportions' in new national poll...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/447972-biden-leads-trump-by-landslide-proportions-in-new-national-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden leads President Trump by 13 points nationally, according to the latest Quinnipiac University survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of ritual pot smoking found in ancient graves...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/58838bed92544a40a5ff9e20f3768498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Navy fighter loses stealth coating at high speeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2019/06/12/supersonic-speeds-could-cause-big-problems-for-the-f-35s-stealth-coating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supersonic flight at the edge of the F-35 jet's flight envelope could cause structural damage or degrade its stealth coating, warn documents exclusively obtained by Defense News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts about to show his cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/12/politics/chief-justice-john-roberts-supreme-court-june/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a deadline for nearly 30 cases looming and weighty issues of religion, gerrymandering and the 2020 census pending, Chief Justice John Roberts took his black leather chair at the bench this week and said three decisions were ready to be announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cereals contain ROUNDUP ingredient, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/glyphosate-breakfast-cereal-still-contains-roundup-ingredient-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An environmental group says the results show many glyphosate levels above what it considers safe for children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'jumping genes' could transform gene editing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jump-around-jumping-genes-could-transform-gene-editing-170209347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, scientists have used a tool something like a pair of scissors for the complex task of gene-editing, but a newly discovered technique using "jumping genes" could offer a seamless, safer alternative. A key tool for editing is the CRISPR-Cas9 process, which uses CRISPRs -- a part of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATOR: Drug Trafficking Business from Mexico 'Larger than WALMART'...</title>
      <link>ttps://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/06/11/sen-perdue-drug-trafficking-business-from-mexico-to-u-s-larger-than-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Confidence Drops to Lowest Level of Trump Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-ceo-confidence-drops-to-lowest-level-of-trump-presidency-1.1272219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advertisers Reconsider Targeting Millennials -- Because They're Broke...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/brand-marketing/why-targeting-millennial-consumers-might-not-be-such-a-hot-idea-after-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing body of evidence shows why Gen Y consumers aren’t ideal: because many of them are broke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 200 dogs rescued from nightmare house; Dozens Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Dog-Hoarding-New-Jersey-Hundreds-Dogs-511185661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of dogs were rescued from a nightmare hoarding situation in New Jersey on Tuesday -- some pregnant, many sick and most having had only limited human contact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7131207/Thousands-rally-Hong-Kong-China-extradition-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clashes broke out shortly after 3pm local time - the deadline protesters had given for the government to abandon a bill that would allow criminal suspects in Hong Kong to be sent for trial in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT BEING SCREENED, QUARANTINED...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/550-african-migrants-just-caught-texas-dhs-head-says-arent-screened-ebola/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threat of bringing in dangerous diseases is higher than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH:  1,000 POUR IN...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/BrianKolfage/status/1138474868616441856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Last week @harkjay350 of the IBWC left this gate open and 1000 migrants flooded it!!! RESIGN NOW! https://t.co/03mKvxjX3V”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked Intruder On Immigration Hold After Threatening Dallas Couple...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/06/11/naked-intruder-ill-kill-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A loud noise awoke a Dallas couple to the sight of a naked man rummaging through a bookshelf in their room</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters vow to keep fighting extradition law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b18a69c0d9684c6a86792031bcb23bb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ASSERTS PRIVILEGE OVER CENSUS DOCS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/292e6a9a05f345ae83bff304efebf76b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ranked 128th most peaceful nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/12/annual-global-index-rates-us-128th-most-peaceful-n/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world has gotten a little more peaceful, according to the 13th annual Global Peace Index, a complex study that ranks 163 nations around the world based on factors ranging from rates of homicide and incarceration to the presence of small arms, military expenditures, ongoing conflicts, terrorism, the overall economic impact of violence and even climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>By 2040, Most 'Meat' -- Won't Be Meat?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jun/12/most-meat-in-2040-will-not-come-from-slaughtered-animals-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consultants say 60% will be grown in vats or plant-based products that taste like meat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD swarm Manhattan streets after mysterious cages appear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Police-Swarm-Midtown-Corner-After-Cage-Appears-Chained-to-Street-Sign-511176041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police swarmed the corner of 6th Avenue and West 48th Street in the heart of Midtown, where a cage appeared on the street corner Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious snake-like UFO seen glowing above desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/men-film-glowing-snake-like-16506345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cody Kennedy and his friends captured a bright moving tail in the sky over a desert in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 Penises in One Episode: HBO 'EUPHORIA' Courts Controversy with Graphic Teen Sex, Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hbos-explicit-euphoria-courts-controversy-how-teen-sex-is-1217606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty penises in one episode? Zendaya’s new series, filled with graphic nudity, violence and drug use among young people, is so extreme that one star quit mid-shoot, but the network hopes that authenticity will help the show break through: "It's not sensational to be sensational."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA readies mission to $10,000 QUADRILLION asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1139428/nasa-10000-dollar-quadrillion-psyche-asteroid-mission-space-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is preparing to explore a mysterious asteroid made of metal, the US space agency has announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLAPSE: CNN Loses Third of Primetime Audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/06/12/death-spiral-continues-cnn-loses-one-third-primetime-audience/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-left CNN's ratings death spiral marched into last week as the fake news network lost one-third of its primetime audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Lee Daniels Blames Smollett for 'EMPIRE' Cancellation...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/06/12/nolte-empire-creator-lee-daniels-blames-jussie-smollett-for-cancellation/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Empire" creator Lee Daniels blames Jussie Smollett for the cancellation of the hit TV show and has cut him out of his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HER CHOICE?</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2218095?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Two of the best-known women in Democratic politics had just recorded a video to upbraid Treasury Secretary Steven T. Mnuchin, when Sen. Elizabeth Warren and Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez started bantering about the final episode of "Game of Thrones." Their ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ASSERTS PRIVILEGE OVER CENSUS DOCS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/448113-trump-asserts-executive-privilege-over-subpoenaed-census-docs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has asserted executive privilege over congressionally subpoenaed documents on the addition of a citizenship question to the 2020 census, the Department of Justice announced Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM influencer painted rosy picture despite being groped, nearly kidnapped...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/12/instagram-influencer-i-was-groped-nearly-kidnapped-in-dominican-republic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram influencer known for traveling around the world with her husband said she was nearly abducted and sexually assaulted during their trip to the Dominican Republic. Cora Smith — who, with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  Mexico doing great job at border, really helping us...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-inadvertently-reveals-more-us-mexico-migrant-deal-221224930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump revealed Tuesday that Mexico agreed to take stronger legal action to halt Central American migrants if its initial efforts to stem the flow don't show results in 45 days. In bright sunshine outside the White House, Trump waved what he said was the text of an agreement Mexican</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'Blacklists' Uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/06/11/revealed-two-google-blacklists-fringe-domains-special-search-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two other blacklists are applied to Google's web answers feature, documents obtained by The Daily Caller indicate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR OF BLUE TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/fear-of-a-blue-texas-new-gop-group-to-spend-millions-registering-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy Republican donors are preparing a multimillion-dollar effort to register more than 1 million new GOP voters in Texas for 2020 amid anxiety that President Trump could be in more trouble in this reliably red state than some in the party realize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX named worst airport in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/06/12/fodors-travel-awards-best-worst-airports-airlines-cruises/1421927001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fodor'sÂ Travel Awards has named the best airports, airlines andÂ cruises across the U.S. and the world in a variety of categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit the mute button: Why everyone trying to silence outside world...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jun/12/hit-mute-button-why-everyone-trying-to-silence-outside-world-uber</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber is trialling a feature that allows customers to stop their drivers from talking. But there’s growing evidence that cutting ourselves off like this isn’t healthy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Makes Another Homophobic Joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stephen-colbert-makes-another-homophobic-trump-putin-joke</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spoiler alert: It has to do with Putin having his hand up Trump’s butt, puppeteering him. These sort of gay ‘jokes’ need to stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deaths of despair' soaring in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/u-s-death-rates-suicides-alcohol-drug-overdoses-reach-all-n1016216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Virginia and Ohio far outpace other states in drug overdose death rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Le Pen to go on trial for tweeting gruesome ISIS images...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190612-frances-le-pen-go-trial-tweeting-gruesome-images</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's Le Pen to go on trial for tweeting gruesome IS images</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crawling Out of Manholes in El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/invasion-illegals-crawl-out-of-manhole-in-us-border-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Located less than half mile from US-Mexico border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Gayle King Steady CBSNEWS?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/gayle-king-cbs-news-woes-charlie-rose-r-kelly-staying-at-cbs-1217434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a year of scandal and upheaval, King takes the lead (and a new three-year deal) at 'CBS This Morning' as she opens up on Charlie Rose, that R. Kelly interview, advice from Oprah and becoming the face of the news division: "I am now a part of that history. Let's see what we do."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US women's soccer team slammed for 'disgusting' celebrations during World Cup thrashing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7130947/US-team-slammed-disgusting-obnoxious-celebrations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Cup favorites thrashed the minnows in Riems, France on Tuesday night and reacted to each goal as if it were their first. Even the substitutes joined arms and jumped up and down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy pigs found beaten to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/11/us/therapy-pigs-beaten-killed-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO: Glass Skydeck At Chicago Tower Cracks Under Visitors' Feet...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/06/11/protective-layer-of-willis-tower-skydeck-ledge-cracks-under-visitors-feet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was another sky-high scare at the Willis Tower, when the skydeck cracked under visitors' feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Robots and End of Civilization...</title>
      <link>https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/darwins-subterranean-world/201906/sex-robots-and-the-end-civilization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.psychologytoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90363132/videos-show-hong-kong-protest-against-china-extradition-bill </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Straight, country boy' turns pickup rainbow for pride month...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b25886604c824b8da08a0a79bf5e05b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Lovelorn fish turn gloomy when separated...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lovelorn-fish-turn-gloomy-separated-study-112019890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny Central American convict cichlid may only be a few centimetres long but it's a fish with a big heart. Researchers in France found that the tropical fish -- known to be a loyal and monogamous partner -- suffers from heartache when separated from its lover. Scientists believe that over the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Flamingos Find Love At Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/06/11/same-sex-pair-flamingos-denver-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Chilean flamingo Lance Bass and American flamingo Freddie Mercury have paired up for several years," zoo officials tweeted Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media has big problem: Who will pay for news?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-media/the-media-has-a-big-problem-reuters-institute-says-who-will-pay-for-the-news-idUSKCN1TC2WV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News organizations are being challenged by technology giants and unsettled by a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. CITIES OVERWHELMED WITH ILLEGALS FROM EBOLA COUNTRIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/u-s-cities-overwhelmed-with-numbers-of-illegal-migrants-arriving-from-ebola-stricken-countries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Africans fleeing pandemic being transported throughout America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Sequel Factory Churns Out Worrisome Duds This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hollywood-s-sequel-factory-churns-out-worrisome-duds-this-summer-1.1271994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug to Replace Chemotherapy May Reshape Cancer Care...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/drug-to-replace-chemotherapy-may-reshape-cancer-care-1.1271773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yemeni Missile Attack on Saudi Airport Wounds 26 in Escalation...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yemen-rebels-attack-saudi-airport-090807975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The projectile hit the arrival section at Abha International airport in the southwest of the country, according to the state-run Saudi Press Agency. Yemen’s Houthis said earlier in the day that they had used a cruise missile to target the airport, a claim that couldn’t be independently verified. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy dies of Ebola in Uganda in first cross-border case...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190612093916-ddcfe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four of the boy's relatives are being monitored in isolation wards with two exhibiting symptoms of the disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'One of worst things I've seen in sports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/sports/nba-finals-kevin-durant-injury-game-5-fans-cheering-toronto-raptors-reactions-024600888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After several Raptors fans started cheering when Kevin Durant went down in Game 5, players and social media both quickly supported the Warriors star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPP pledges to sue users over off-platform misbehavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/461558-whatsapp-sue-off-platform-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WhatsApp is threatening users who violate its rules with lawsuits, even if the only evidence of “rule-breaking” exists outside of the Facebook-owned messaging app and the only judge is an AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL CRAZY:  BIDEN OVER TRUMP IN LANDSLIDE?</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=2627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Dems Lead Trump In Head-To-Head Matchups, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; Democratic Primary Race Narrows As Biden Goes Flat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: 'NOT EVEN CLOSE' TO STARTING IT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f21ffd0d5d244cbb6789307a91f9f05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
