<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Mulvaney on shaky ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/28/politics/mick-mulvaney-impeachment-inquiry-donald-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney is on shaky ground in the wake of a bad week for President Trump, according to multiple sources with knowledge of discussions surrounding the whistleblower fallout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intense Hong Kong clashes ahead of China's 70th anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-leads-global-anti-china-rallies-ahead-090342060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fierce clashes broke out between protesters and riot police in Hong Kong on Sunday as thousands marched through the strife-torn city, during a day of global protests aimed at casting a shadow over communist China's upcoming 70th birthday. Beijing is preparing for huge, tightly-choreographed festivities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept. ramps up probe into Clinton email server...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/463525-state-dept-ramps-up-probe-into-clinton-email-server</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department reportedly intensified a probe into former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's private email server, contacting dozens of former aides involved in email exchanges that passed through Clinton's server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lights Go Out on Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/videos/politics/2019/09/29/pete-buttigieg-power-outage-campaign-event-vpx.cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg was left in the dark when a power outage at his campaign event in Sparks, Nevada, caused the lights to go out mid-speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese parade a glimpse into military ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca6f789c8b95493ba0a3327a042da596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A parade Tuesday by China's secretive military will offer a rare look at its rapidly developing arsenal, including possibly a nuclear-armed missile that could reach the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi 'heartbroken, prayerful' as impeachment moves forward...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pelosi-heartbroken-prayerful-dems-move-forward-impeachment-inquiry/story?id=65931464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi said that she is heartbroken and prayerful as House Democrats move forward with their impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Could Soon Say 'I Do' to Married Priests...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vatican-may-approve-married-priests-but-conservative-catholics-arent-celebrating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of hand-picked clerics meeting in Rome next week about the ecumenical needs of the Amazon could change the entire Catholic Church forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Premiere Week Sinks to Record Low Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/premiere-week-ratings-lows-tvs-new-normal-1244033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Same-day Nielsen ratings for network series have fallen precipitously in the past five years, and delayed and multi-platform viewing isn't likely to get all of those losses back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRISHMAN' reviews 100% positive...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/09/28/martin-scorsese-irishman-reviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what critics are saying about Martin Scorsese’s 'phenomenal' mob drama coming to Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR HANGS TOUGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d134da3dadd497e9af37c60278d68dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As Washington plunges into impeachment, Attorney General William Barr finds himself engulfed in the political firestorm, facing questions about his role in President Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH: IGER FOR PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7515479/Oprah-Winfrey-says-wants-Disney-CEO-Bob-Iger-president-United-States.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winfrey made the remarks in an interview with Iger set to air on Sunday on her OWN Network , as Iger promotes his his new memoir, The Ride of a Lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish Gay Pride marchers push past violent counter-protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/polish-gay-pride-marchers-push-past-violent-counter-161935152.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish Gay Pride marchers under heavy police guard defied far-right groups and conservative campaigners on Saturday who hurled bottles and eggs in an attempt to block them, an AFP journalist saw. Some 400 supporters of LGBT+ rights marched through the eastern Polish city of Lublin some 170 kilometres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer calls out fashion's richest man on Greta attack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/designer-calls-fashions-richest-man-thunberg-attack-170958853.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vivienne Westwood designer Andreas Kronthaler hit out Saturday at fashion's most powerful man Bernard Arnault for attacking Greta Thunberg. The French billionaire and head of the LVMH conglomerate that owns labels like Louis Vuitton, Dior, Givenchy, and pop idol Rihanna's new brand Fenty, said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia goes silent on mysterious drill hole in Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/space/nasty-surprise-russia-goes-silent-on-mysterious-drill-hole-in-international-space-station/news-story/1e47f49df0f0e21b99d82e5582cb96db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspicious hole in a Soyuz spacecraft vented air from the International Space Station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These retirees 'couldn't afford' America -- now live on $2,000 a month in Ecuador...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/these-arizona-retirees-couldnt-afford-america-now-they-live-their-dream-life-on-2000-a-month-in-ecuador-2019-06-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They haven’t been back to the U.S. in years, and say they don’t miss it much (except for Home Depot and some friends).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Trump, high-velocity threat like none he's ever faced...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6f4f4a684812489ab29bd43fb5862111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — From the moment Donald Trump became a national political figure, he has been shadowed by investigations and controversy. They have been layered, lengthy and often...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Embracing President Pence might be party's best play...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/463502-embracing-president-mike-pence-might-be-gops-best-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been quite a decade for the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of discomfort in defense of president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/463463-republicans-shows-signs-of-discomfort-in-defense-of-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans, even as they generally show support for President Trump, are showing signs of discomfort amid an impeachment fight that has engulfed the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT 2019:  POMPEO SUBPOENAED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec576ac2faa942d18450f7bdfac0ef24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats took their first concrete steps in the impeachment investigation of President Donald Trump on Friday, issuing subpoenas demanding documents from Secretary of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After turbulent year, rabbis wrestle with politics of faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-27/los-angeles-rabbis-politics-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of Rosh Hashana and Yom Kippur, rabbis debate whether to get political at Los Angeles synagogues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brave puppy dies protecting owner's kids from deadly snake that bit it 4 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/brave-puppy-dies-protecting-owners-20321366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*WARNING, DISTRESSING CONTENT* Coral snakes have a powerful venom that can kill an adult human within hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cracking issue' discovered on some of BOEING 737 planes...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/09/27/business/boeing-737-ng-cracks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration has ordered inspections of a Boeing 737 model after the company notified the agency of structural cracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New blood test detects 20 types of cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/09/28/new-blood-test-could-detect-20-types-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new blood test could detect more than 20 types of cancer, allowing cases to be identified and treated far earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to Unveil Mars Spaceship...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/elon-musk-starship-design-update-2019-preview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's time for the annual architecture update!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still time...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/with-biden-damaged-and-warren-surging-could-hillary-clinton-still-enter-the-presidential-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just a few weeks ago, it seemed exceedingly unlikely that Hillary Clinton would enter the race for the White House in 2020.  But now the Biden campaign is deeply struggling, and the constant focus that the impeachment inquiry is putting on his son's dealings in Ukraine has already significantly dama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Gearing Up For Late-Stage Do-Over?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/hillary-gearing-late-stage-do-over-against-corrupt-human-tornado-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREVIEWS GOSPEL MOVIE...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/entertainment/music/brian-mccollum/2019/09/27/kanye-west-plays-jesus-king-detroit-fans-previews-new-imax-movie/3794975002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper's Detroit adventure with Kim Kardashian continued Friday as fans at the Fox got the first listen to his upcoming album "Jesus Is King."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Premiere Disinvites Interview Press From Red Carpet...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/joker-premiere-red-carpet-journalists-1203352046/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. Entertainment has restricted access for print and broadcast journalists from the red carpet at the upcoming U.S. premiere of “Joker.” The event, which will take place on Sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METALLICA postpone tour after frontman enters rehab...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/metallica-postpone-australia-nz-tour-frontman-enters-rehab-111535502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington (AFP) - Metallica are postponing their upcoming tour of Australia and New Zealand after lead vocalist James Hetfield re-entered rehab, the American band announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
