<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ammon Bundy builds militia network on Covid backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/pacific-northwest-news/2021/02/ammon-bundy-veteran-of-armed-standoffs-builds-militia-network-on-covid-19-backlash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the tap of a thumb on a smartphone, members of the People’s Rights can call a militia like they’d call an Uber and stage a protest within minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Billions in Stimulus Was Swindled By Con Artists, Crime Syndicates...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/how-billions-pandemic-aid-was-swindled-con-artists-crime-syndicates-n1257766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior federal law enforcement source said the fraud is so complex and multilayered that it will take months to develop a full accounting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Informant Panic Ruining Friendships All Over Far Right...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-informant-panic-ruining-friendships-042446613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyAs federal authorities crack down on the far right after the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, the movement’s leaders have found new sources of suspicion: each other.In the Trumpist “America First” movement and the far-right paramilitary group the Proud Boys, alliances are fracturing as extremists brand each other as potential informants. Now racist live-streamers are accusing their former comrades of attempting to turn over followers to law enforcement, while Proud Boys chapters are splintering from the national organization over similar fears.Proud Boys Dealt Another Blow as Feds Crack DownUntil the FBI started closing in, white nationalists Nick Fuentes and Patrick Casey were the two most prominent figures in the racist “America First” movement.The pair built up shared audiences on live-streaming platforms, and cheered as their fans, nicknamed “groypers” after an obese version of the cartoon Pepe the Frog, heckled more moderate Trump allies at conservative events.But the federal heat is on after Fuentes received roughly $250,000 in a much-scrutinized bitcoin transfer, then appeared outside the U.S. Capitol during the Jan. 6 riot. The FBI is reportedly investigating the bitcoin transfer, though Fuentes has not faced charges over the money or the riot. Nick Fuentes, the leader of a Christian based extremist white nationalist group speaks to his followers, 'the Groypers.' in Washington D.C. on November 14, 2020 Zach D Roberts/NurPhoto via Getty On Thursday, Casey distanced himself from Fuentes and America First in a live-streamed video, slamming Fuentes’ decision to gather his followers in Orlando later this month for a conference right as other America First supporters face charges over the riot.“Some people who were at the Capitol are going to flip,” Casey said in his video.Declaring the aftermath of the Capitol riot “a million times worse” for the far right than the crackdown that followed the fatal white supremacist rally in Charlottesville in 2017, Casey claimed, without offering evidence, that Fuentes’ bank accounts have been frozen by federal authorities. He also accused Fuentes of planning to drive cross-country, rather than fly, to the Florida conference because he suspected he was on the federal no-fly list, then concealing that possibility from his followers.Worst of all, Casey argued, Fuentes planned to gather all of his supporters in Orlando, where they could be easily recorded by federal investigators or informants. He went on to suggest America First’s members would see the conference for what he thinks it could be: an FBI trap.“He wants you to give him your real name, to show up to his event where your face will be visible, where your cellphone data will be in close proximity to his,” Casey said.Fuentes didn’t respond to a request for comment.Accusations that one-time allies have become federal informants aren’t uncommon in the extreme right, which has built up an entire lexicon of terms to describe the varieties of real or suspected federal infiltrators. But that paranoia has been ratcheted up in the aftermath of the riot, with the Proud Boys—a group that has seen a slew of members indicted—splintering under accusations that leaders have become informants or otherwise been compromised by the FBI.Proud Boys leader Enrique Tarrio was arrested in Washington, D.C., two days before the riot, and now faces felony charges over the possession of illicit firearm magazines. But a Reuters report on Tarrio’s history as a federal informant cast members’ suspicions on their own leader, even as Proud Boys who allegedly participated in the riot face federal conspiracy charges.Proud Boys chapters in three U.S. states—including four local chapters in Indiana—now claim to have broken with the national organization over Tarrio’s work as a federal informant. (Tarrio did not return a request for comment.)“We reject and disavow the proven federal informant, Enrique Tarrio, and any and all chapters that choose to associate with him,” read a statement shared by the Indiana group’s state-level Telegram channel and on the Alabama group’s website, previously reported by USA Today. “We do not recognize the assumed authority of any national Proud Boy leadership including the Chairman, the Elders, or any subsequent governing body that is formed to replace them until such a time we may choose to consent to join those bodies of government.”Proud Boys in Oklahoma also broke from Tarrio’s leadership, issuing a statement on messaging app Telegram in which they accused him and other national “elders” of “failure to take disciplinary measures [which] have jeopardized our brothers safety and the integrity of our brotherhood.”Tarrio responded to the Oklahoma chapter’s departure with a series of memes accusing Oklahomans of being rednecks, or having sex with relatives. Anti-Tarrio Proud Boys responded with their own memes accusing their former leader of ratting out members of the group, photoshopping his face on rapper and government witness Tekashi69. Another meme played on the menacing Proud Boys motto “Fuck Around and Find Out,” claiming that Tarrio would instead “Snitch Around and Rat Out.”But don’t expect Proud Boy splinter groups to morph into peaceful book clubs. The Indiana Proud Boys, for example, are led by Brien James, a longtime member of white supremacist groups with a history of violent brawls. Other white supremacists have previously slammed James as a law enforcement risk (someone “you want to keep away from you because you know he’s going to do something to bring the cops over,” one previously noted). Nevertheless, James took to Telegram this week to blame Tarrio and Ethan “Rufio Panman” Nordean, a prominent Proud Boy who was arrested on Feb. 3 over his own alleged role in the riot, of being untrustworthy. “Now we have another ‘war boy’ and elder who is trying to snitch on the president? For something he knows damn well the president didn’t do? You made your own choices Rufio,” James wrote, adding that “if you are a Proud Boy I would recommend having your chapter declare full autonomy from the national structure at the very least.” (A public defender listed as representing Nordean did not respond to a request for comment.)The Capitol riots have been followed by still more rifts internationally.Anti-fascist activists in Manitoba, Canada, also claim their province’s Proud Boys chapter has dissolved. The CBC reported that, while the chapter had been largely inactive for the past year, the group was confirmed dead this month, when the Canadian government designated Proud Boys as a terrorist organization.Inside the Alt-Right Meltdown After Failed Capitol PutschMeanwhile, Jason Lee Van Dyke, who registered the group’s trademark and briefly led the Proud Boys in 2018, filed this week to surrender the trademark to the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office, legal documents show. Van Dyke previously told The Daily Beast he revoked Tarrio’s license to use the name after a Black church in Washington, D.C., sued the Proud Boys for allegedly burning their flag in a rally weeks before the Capitol attack.“I don’t want any recourse or anyone thinking I have any control over this group, that I have anything to do with this group, or that I am going to have anything to do with this group in the future,” Van Dyke said in a separate interview this week. He claimed he’d tried to transfer the trademark to another Proud Boy, who got spooked after Canada slapped the group with a terrorist label.“There was one individual… who contacted me about having the trademark transferred to him,” Van Dyke told The Daily Beast. “After the Canadian government made a determination of the Proud Boys as a terrorist group for whatever reason they did that, that individual told me he was out and he would not be taking over the trademark. My response to that individual and those who had been working with him on acquiring the trademark was that they had seven days to get back to me regarding who was going to take it over, or I was going to surrender it.“I did not hear back from anybody and the trademark is surrendered.”As for the America First movement, Casey’s criticism of Fuentes has riled the “groypers,” who have been forced to choose between their two leaders. Fuentes appeared to respond to Casey on Thursday night by tweeting a video of Donald Trump talking about disloyalty. Nick Fuentes, Alex Jones, Ali Alexander during a 'Stop the Steal,' Far-Right Rallies leaders, broadcaster rally at the Governor's Mansion in Georgia November 19th, 2020 as the state finishes the recount in the Presidential election - calling on Governor Kemp to help President Trump. Zach Roberts/NurPhoto via Getty But Fuentes’ supporters and allies have good reason to believe federal law enforcement is focusing on their group. Anthime Gionet, a Fuentes ally who goes by the alias “Baked Alaska,” was arrested in January after filming himself entering the Capitol. Riot suspect Riley June Williams, who wore an “I’m With Groyper” shirt to the Capitol, allegedly stole a laptop computer from Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-CA).Casey urged his followers to consider how they would react to Fuentes’ conference if any other far-right leader had been behind it.“You would be like, ‘Wow, federal honeypot, federal honeypot event,’” Casey said. “You would probably accuse the guy of being a fed.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage &amp; divorce on decline amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-steve-harris-minnesota-coronavirus-pandemic-couples-c004c459d5007ec9f57297906c270787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many U.S. couples yearning to be married, the pandemic has wreaked havoc on their wedding plans while bolstering their teamwork and resilience. For couples already married, it has posed a host...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO Wuhan mission finds possible signs of wider original outbreak in '19...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/14/health/who-mission-china-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators from the World Health Organization (WHO) looking into the origins of coronavirus in China have discovered signs the outbreak was much wider in Wuhan in December 2019 than previously thought, and are urgently seeking access to hundreds of thousands of blood samples from the city that China has not so far let them examine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown opponents call for arrest, assault, murder of health officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.stcatharinesstandard.ca/news/niagara-region/2021/02/13/lockdown-opponents-call-for-arrest-assault-and-murder-of-medical-officer-of-health.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stcatharinesstandard.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-maskers, some hospitality industry owners, attack Dr. Mustafa Hirji on social media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ravi Zacharias' ministry concealed and enabled his abuse...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/you-are-one-step-away-from-complete</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inside story of how Ravi Zacharias’s ministry concealed and enabled his abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN's Chris Cuomo Skips Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/cnns-chris-cuomo-skips-andrew-cuomo-controversy-still-finds-time-to-tweet-moral-lectures-at-republicans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opinion: CNN's Chris Cuomo has engaged in situational ethics regarding his coverage of his brother, Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D-NY), and New York nursing home deaths from Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wary Washington seeks to move forward...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210214095847-bus03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (PIX):With Trump impeachment trial over, wary Washington seeks to move forward</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moves to extinguish pro-Navalny 'flashlight' protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-russia-cb331fa15a10be0f368b153e09e1e0f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — When the team of imprisoned Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny urged people to come out to their residential courtyards and shine their cellphone flashlights in a display of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City-wide blackouts shut down Dallas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/from-the-archives/2021/02/14/freezing-temperatures-and-city-wide-blackouts-shut-down-dallas-as-residents-struggled-to-keep-warm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editor’s note: Take a look back into The Dallas Morning News Archives. North Texas became a casualty of a 250-mile winter storm that left the city— and its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How evidence tested TV's standards...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-riots-television-broadcast-television-impeachments-7f2d7b1147666213fecc809bd46c84b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — All the words abounded — the ones that you're not supposed to hear on broadcast television or, for that matter, in a lot of other places. Former President Donald Trump's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake officer with gun, badge detained South Carolinians during 'traffic stops'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article249210685.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is facing charges, according to authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disgraceful dereliction of duty'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/after-acquitting-trump-mcconnell-slams-him-disgraceful-dereliction-duty-n1257900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi called the Senate Republican leader's remarks "pathetic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Blasts Cowards...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/cowardly-pelosi-crashes-dem-presser-to-blast-mcconnell-for-speech-justifying-vote-to-acquit-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi was not supposed to speak at the press conference held by the House impeachment managers after former President Donald Trump was acquitted by the Senate. But the speech delivered by Mitch McConnell — which condemned Trump but argued against impeaching a former president — prompted her to make a furious statement blasting the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: New Yorkers fleeing to Palm Beach -- and businesses following...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/13/new-yorkers-are-fleeing-to-palm-beachand-businesses-are-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed-up New Yorkers have escaped to Palm Beach where they’re finding new freedom, old friends — and their favorite gathering spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  White House aide resigns after threatening reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/02/13/tj-ducklo-resigns-white-house-press-aide-after-threatening-reporter/4478936001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House deputy press secretary T.J. Ducklo resigned the day after he was suspended for issuing a sexist and profane threat to a journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence against elderly in Bay Area skyrocketing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/violence-anti-asian-racism-bay-area-rising-15943348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany tightens border checks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/austria-coronavirus-pandemic-czech-republic-horst-seehofer-germany-29a32c8aab1256d89afd4b1b8da22141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany on Sunday implemented tighter border controls on its frontiers with the Czech Republic and Austria’s Tyrol province in an effort to stem the spread of more contagious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don escapes conviction but even allies say he's damaged...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/13/trump-impeachment-witch-hunt-469001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president may be out for revenge after his acquittal. But beyond that, his future is uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell launches all-out attack -- AFTER voting to clear him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9257859/Mitch-McConnell-claims-Trump-solely-responsible-MAGA-riot-voting-clear-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell tore into Donald Trump after voting to acquit him of 'incitement of insurrection' - but then immediately argued the former president is solely to blame for Capitol storming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEVEN REPUBLICANS VOTE 'GUILTY'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9257497/Donald-Trump-ACQUITTED-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was acquitted in his Senate impeachment trial Saturday as the vast majority of Republicans held together against a charge that he incited the Capitol riot of January 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE ACQUITS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/13/senate-acquits-former-president-donald-trump-on-charge-of-inciting-insurrection-at-us-capitol-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Saturday acquitted former President Donald Trump in a 57-43 vote on the charge of inciting insurrection for his role in the Jan. 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Ripped: 'Unbelievable Cave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/senate-democrats-get-absolutely-destroyed-for-nixing-plan-to-call-witnesses-at-trump-trial-what-an-unbelievable-cave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats are under fire from all sides after striking a deal to avoid witnesses in former President Donald Trump's impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak at nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-japan-earthquake-sparks-leak-23496187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan was on Saturday rocked by an earthquake. It has been reported that this has led to a nuclear fuel spill at Fukushima Daini Nuclear Power plant, although no one has been harmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protege of Halperin, Lauer...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/biden-ducklo-dignity-restored/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T.J. Ducklo, the White House deputy press secretary who threatened to "destroy" a female journalist seeking comment for a story about his ethically problematic relationship with an Axios reporter, will keep his job despite President Joe Biden's warning that staff members who treat others with "disrespect" would be fired "on the spot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Georgia, New District Attorney Starts Circling Trump and Allies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/13/in-georgia-a-new-district-attorney-starts-circling-trump-and-his-allies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After six weeks as a district attorney, Fani T. Willis is taking on a former president. And not just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves toward finishing impeachment trial WITHOUT witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/13/senate-votes-in-favor-of-calling-witnesses-in-trump-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chamber voted to allow witnesses in a 55-45 vote, as five Republicans joined all Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYT boss Abramson responds to unrest at paper...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/13/ex-new-york-times-boss-jill-abramson-responds-to-unrest-at-the-paper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have been called by many reporters about the controversial departure of reporter Donald McNeil from The New York Times. “Do I think the Times treated McNeil unfairly?” “Is there a management melt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon admits it has been testing wreckage from UFO crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2321251/pentagon-admits-testing-wreckage-ufo-crashes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Pentagon has admitted to holding and testing wreckage from UFO crashes in a bombshell Freedom of Information letter, shared with The Sun. Researcher Anthony Bragalia wrote to the Defense Intell…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trumpworld 'Total Panic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/total-panic-abc-news-reports-trumpworld-freaking-out-over-impeachment-witness-twist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources close to ex-President Donald Trump are in a panic over the last-minute addition of witnesses to the Senate impeachment trial, according to ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's female dervish takes transcendence online...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210213-france-s-female-dervish-takes-transcendence-online</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's female dervish takes transcendence online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210213142042-9fl09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Strong quake hits off Japan coast, triggering blackouts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House prosecutors to call Republican lawmaker to testify at Trump trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9257009/Mitch-McConnell-wil-vote-ACQUIT-Donald-Trump-sign-ex-president-escape-conviction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell has told colleagues he will vote to acquit Donald Trump on the charge of incitement of insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECHNO MUSIC LEAST EFFECTIVE AT REDUCING ANXIETY?</title>
      <link>https://mixmag.net/read/techno-anxiety-music-genre-euphoria-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mixmag.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has found that techno is the least relaxing form of music – anyone who's spent the weekend at Movement or Berghain might disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will money laundering laws end art world's culture of secrecy?</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/money-laundering-laws-end-art-020347054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a Botticelli painting went under the hammer last month at Sotheby's in New York for $92 million, it was assumed the buyer was a Russian oligarch since the bidding was done by an adviser to wealthy Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE TO HAVE WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2021/02/13/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment charge against Trump alleges that he “willfully made statements that encouraged — and foreseeably resulted in — imminent lawless action at the Capitol.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details about Trump conduct revealed in McCarthy call...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/13/trump-impeachment-trial-day-5-468985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If no witnesses are called, the trial on Saturday will move to closing arguments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign nationals getting vaccines in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-foreign-nationals-are-getting-coronavirus-vaccines-in-the-united-states/ar-BB1dEqPa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Difficult issues of immigration and health policy are playing out in border states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence 'could let humans to talk to animals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/artificial-intelligence-could-humans-talk-23454476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much effort has gone into teaching systems such as Siri and Alexa to understand us that using AI to decode animal communication could be a logical next step.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of Proud Boys: What does future hold?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/decline-proud-boys-does-future-100010463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the Trump era, the group enjoyed presidential support and recruited thousands – but their role in the Capitol attack has led to new charges A member of the Proud Boys in Sacramento, California, on 7 November 2020. Photograph: David Odisho/EPA During the the Trump era, the far-right Proud Boys rode high, enjoying presidential support, recruiting thousands of men, and, as the self-nominated nemesis of leftist Antifa activists, participating in a string of violent street altercations around the country. But now since Trump’s election loss and the aftermath of the 6 January attack on the Capitol in Washington DC, a series of blows dealt by law enforcement, elected officials and their own leaders have shaken the extremist fraternity that the Southern Poverty Law Center describes as a hate group. The cumulative impact has experts wondering about the Proud Boys’ long-term future. Since their foundation in 2016 by the far-right Canadian media personality and entrepreneur Gavin McInnes, the all-male group – who wear uniform clothing, enforce bizarre initiation rituals, eschew masturbation, and reward violence with higher degrees of membership – have been an outsized presence on the landscape of pro-Trump extremism, and successful in promoting themselves as the most militant part of his coalition. But their role in the Capitol insurrection especially has brought far less welcome attention. Law enforcement agencies have connected at least 10 Capitol arrestees with the Proud Boys in criminal complaints and affadavits. Those charged include leaders like the Florida combat veteran and conspiracy theorist Joe Biggs and Washington state’s Ethan Nordean, whose prominence rose in the group after he was caught on film attacking an antifascist during a 2018 riot in downtown Portland, Oregon. Proud Boys members Enrique Tarrio, left, and Joe Biggs, in Washington DC on 12 December 2020. Photograph: Jim Urquhart/Reuters Biggs – a former employee of Alex Jones’s conspiracy-minded Infowars network – was central in organizing incursions into the city of Portland in 2019 and 2020, each of which drew Fred Perry-clad militants from around the country to confront antifascists and city authorities. He is now charged with impeding Congress, unauthorized entry to the Capitol, and disorderly conduct. However, the affidavit supporting the charges also alleges Biggs was involved in extensive radio communications with other Proud Boys on the day. The allegations of coordination between members of the group may hint at more charges to come. Alex Newhouse, a researcher at the Center on Terrorism, Extremism, and Counterterrorism at the Middlebury Institute, said in a telephone conversation that it was likely that “more conspiracy charges being levied on some of these people in the future”. Shannon Reid, an assistant professor in criminology at the University of North Carolina, said the strategy in these cases resembles the one prosecutors often use in pursuit of criminal enterprises, where the aim is to “pick up as many people as humanly possible and to hope that they just plead out”. The cases against Biggs and Nordean turn what had been the Proud Boys’ greatest weapon – social media – against them as authorities have detailed their alleged misdeeds using material that they and others posted online. For example, a grand jury indictment of a Texan, Nicholas Decarlo, and the founder of the group’s Hawaiian chapter, Nicholas Ochs, alleges that they together inscribed “Murder the media” on the front door of the Capitol before stealing a Capitol police officer’s handcuffs. In an affidavit, an FBI special agent says that they determined that Ochs had been in the building from his own Twitter account. Meanwhile, Dominic Pezzola and William Pepe allegedly conspired with each other in a sequence of events which included Pezzola assaulting a Capitol police officer, stealing his riot shield, and then using it to smash in one of the Capitol’s windows. The evidence cited in affidavits includes Pezzola’s account on the shuttered conservative-friendly social media service, Parler, and videos posted online by other rioters. The FBI says that another arrestee, Bryan Betancur, was wearing a Proud Boys cap at the rally. They also say that Betancur is a “self-professed white supremacist” who discussed carrying out school shootings and expressed support for Charlottesville killer, James Fields. He was placed inside the Capitol building by signals from his court-ordered ankle monitoring device, a parole condition related to an earlier offense. Newhouse said that voluminous social media evidence suggests that “this was carefully planned and extensively communicated in the moment”. The connection between Proud Boys and other extremist organizations – previously noted on several occasions by US law enforcement – has now led to the first instance of the group being outlawed. Last Wednesday, the Canadian parliament formally declared the Proud Boys a terrorist group, citing their “misogynistic, Islamophobic, antisemitic, anti-immigrant and/or white supremacist” ideology and their association with “white supremacist groups”. The designation opens the way for any crimes committed by Proud Boys to be prosecuted as terrorist acts. It also means that any fundraising, travel, recruitment and training for the group can be prosecuted, and members can be added to no-fly lists or denied entry to Canada. Meanwhile, parliamentarians in Australia are pushing their government to follow suit, after McInnes was denied entry to the country on character grounds in 2018. Gavin McInnes speaks on stage with Proud Boys in New York City on 20 January 2018. Photograph: Andrew Kelly/Reuters In the US, while criminal acts can be prosecuted as domestic terrorism, it has not been possible to designate domestic groups as terrorist, and, at least in theory, the first amendment prevents authorities from surveilling domestic groups on the basis of their political beliefs, even if those beliefs encompass an advocacy of violence. Increasingly over the life of the Trump administration, however, Democratic politicians advocated for just such an approach to rightwing extremists. Now, the first bill aimed at addressing rightwing extremism as domestic terrorism has been introduced to Congress by the Illinois Democrat Brad Schneider and has attracted bipartisan sponsorship. If passed it would set up dedicated domestic terrorism units within the Department of Justice, the Department of Homeland Security and the FBI. It would also require those departments to report to Congress twice a year on domestic terrorism incidents and hate crimes, and their progress in dealing with such cases. In a telephone conversation, Schneider said that while he had first proposed a version of the bill in 2017, before he had become aware of the group, the Proud Boys were “certainly a troubling group, in their rhetoric and their actions”. “We have seen what they’ve done in various places, whether it was in Washington last year or it with the insurrection in the capital last month,”Schneider added, calling the latter event an attack “not just members of Congress, but the foundation of our government, our constitution, and our republic”. Other events have compounded the effects of the additional scrutiny. During the Trump presidency, police in cities from California to Kalamazoo were regularly accused of having a soft touch when it came to the Proud Boys and their far-right allies, and these claims have been borne out in nationwide studies. But since the election, local agencies around the country have appeared more ready to respond with force when the group’s street protests become violent. Police have used batons, gas and other “non-lethal” weapons on Proud Boys in Salem, Oregon, and Washington DC during December and January. Some Proud Boys have remarked on the apparent sea change: in a podcast released on 4 January, Nordean, the Washington state arrestee, said that “the police are starting to become a problem,” even though “we’ve had their back for years”. On 2 February, those comments were quoted in the criminal complaint detailing Nordean’s alleged participation in the riot. Just before the riot, Enrique Tarrio, the chair of the Proud Boys, was arrested on charges related to the vandalism of a black church and illegal weapons. Then, last week, it was revealed that he had been a “prolific” police informant. Since the revelation that he had been a police informant, Proud Boyschapters in Nevada, Missouri and Alabama have publicly announced theirdeparture from the main organization on the messaging platform,Telegram. On the same platform, the also-departed Oklahoma Proud Boyshave exchanged barbs with Tarrio and other leaders. Proud Boys during a Trump rally in Washington DC on 12 December 2020. Photograph: The Washington Post/Getty Images Tarrio took over leadership of the group after McInnes ostentatiously resigned as a member following Guardian reporting that revealed that federal authorities considered them an extremist group. Notwithstanding his earlier public disavowals, in 2020 McInnes attended and spoke at the group’s annual WestFest event in Las Vegas in 2020, and has persisted in advocating for the group in the online outlets available to him, including his Telegram and Parler accounts. Though the Proud Boys may be reeling now, Newhouse warns that opposing a Democratic president gives them a similar opportunity to previous waves of rightwing militancy, like the militia movement in the Clinton years, and its revival as the so-called Patriot Movement during Obama’a time in office. “I don’t think they’re going anywhere,” he said. “The more extreme fringe actors are going to gain influence,” with some Proud Boys drifting into adjacent extremist groups in the Boogaloo movement or neo-Nazism. “De-radicalization is one of the hardest problems,”Newhouse said, “harder even than preventing acts of terrorism.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Nightmare -- Even for Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-is-a-covid-nightmare-even-for-vaccinated-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a state defined by pandemic recklessness, getting a shot is no silver bullet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rogue Paparazzo Who Made Life Living Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/adnan-ghalib-the-rogue-paparazzo-who-made-britney-spears-life-a-living-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-paparazzo who dated Britney Spears at the height of the tabloid frenzy (and was allegedly shopping a sex tape) won’t take responsibility for his own role in the chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fall of John Weaver, LINCOLN PROJECT co-founder whose career shrouded in mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/The-fall-of-John-Weaver-a-Lincoln-Project-15948531.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The puzzle that is John Weaver comes in fragmented pieces: He's described as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen 'could win French presidential election'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210213122938-mcy50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-LEMAIRE/LEPEN: Far-right leader Le Pen could win French 2022 presidential election-Le Maire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender identity bill divides Spain feminists, left-wing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-spain-gender-identity-1d53f28df5988032e538c37f80928633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Victòria Martínez continues to sign official documents with the name that she, her partner and their two daughters ditched four years ago. Barring any surprises, she expects the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
