<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SOROS:  EVERYTHING HAS GONE WRONG!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5825399/Billionaire-investor-liberal-donor-George-Soros-blasts-Trumps-presidency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire and liberal donor, 87-year-old George Soros, blamed the Trump administration for the current woes in society, adding that 'everything that could go wrong, has gone wrong.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge brawl erupts in crowd at heavy weight boxing match -- and fighters stop to watch...	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/6491936/tyson-fury-sefer-seferi-crowd-15-man-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE 15 man brawl broke out in the crowd at the Tyson Fury fight. The brutal rumble exploded during Fury’s victory over Sefer Seferi as blokes leaped from their chairs to throw punches. Fur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump refuses to back declaration calling for tariff reductions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/09/us-signs-g-7-declaration-calling-for-reduction-of-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a press conference earlier in the day, Trump threatened to stop trading with countries that do not reduce barriers to American exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine Corps weighs wooing older members for new cyber force...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/marine-corps-weighs-wooing-older-members-cyber-force-161354832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine Corps is considering offering bonuses and other perks to entice older, more experienced Marines to re-enlist as it builds up its cyber operations to defend the nation, especially against cyberattacks from Russia and China. About 62 percent of Marines are 25 years old or younger with many</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rough talks sour G7 mood; Confrontations...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180609194409-l5tmi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/MOOD (PIX, TV):One 'rant,' rough talks sour G7 mood in confrontations with Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump holds solo news conference, defends bashing press...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-holds-solo-news-conference-defends-bashing-press-190705939--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA MALBAIE, Quebec (AP) — President Donald Trump stepped to the microphone alone Saturday to take reporters' questions, just the second time he'd done so since taking office more than a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel plane fires warning to deter Gaza balloon, kite attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-plane-fires-warning-deter-gaza-balloon-kite-172628393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli aircraft fired a warning shot Saturday to deter a group of Gazans preparing to fly a balloon fitted with explosives over the border, in the first such case, the army said. "The Israeli army spotted a group of Palestinians preparing balloons equipped with explosive devices to cause fires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young reporter in leak investigation enjoyed meteoric rise in DC journalism... </title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-leak-investigation-new-york-times-reporter-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first known leak investigation of the Trump administration has put under scrutiny a 20-something New York Times reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Bill's Belated #MeToo Moment... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/09/opinion/sunday/bills-belated-metoo-moment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 20 years of the same old song and dance, the former president is forced to face the music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decades Later and Far Away, Chernobyl Disaster Still Contaminates Milk...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/milk-radioactive-cow-ukraine-healthy-dairy-safe-chernobyl-a8388576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn dangerous contamination will continue until at least 2040 without action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son of Farrah Fawcett and Ryan O'Neal Charged with Attempted Murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/redmond-oneal-son-farrah-fawcett-ryan-oneal-charged-attempted-murder-1118704</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 33-year-old was also charged with two counts of assault with a deadly weapon, one count of criminal threats, one count of brandishing a knife and one count of battery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Newark, Police Cameras, and the Internet, Watch You...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/in-this-city-police-cameras-and-the-internet-watch-you/17616168/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWARK, N.J. — The camera perched above the bus stop sends back a continuous feed from the corner of 16th Avenue and South 18th Street in Newark’s West Ward. Regular customers come and go from Max’s, a convenience store, and a man without a shirt paces aimlessly on the same slice of pavement. Anyone with a fast internet connection and a desire to watch could also see Fernando Demarzino stepping out of his cousin’s barbershop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Finals Ratings Fall Hard...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/06/kevin-durant-warriors-win-nba-finals-ratings-down-nba-abc-1202406923/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many ways, the end of the 2018 NBA Finals was very much like the end of the 2017 NBA Finals, except in the ratings for the league and ABC. The similarities saw the Golden State Warriors defeat t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of LA's oldest community gardens thrived for decades. Then water wars began...</title>
      <link>http://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/one-of-la-s-oldest-community-gardens-thrived-for-decades/article_2207cd43-9b6e-52fc-884d-bdf1a4e977a1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The old Italian men pass their mornings near the top of the hill, tending thick grape vines and rows of fava beans, smoking crumbling Toscano cigars, staying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Auto theft suspect had small monkey clinging to chest when arrested...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/animals/man-and-his-monkey-029734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 8--A man arrested this morning for auto theft had a small diaper-clad monkey clinging to his chest when Florida cops apprehended him after he drove the hot wheels into a ditch. Investigators all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Justify' bidding for rare Triple Crown sweep in Belmont... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER  Punishes Farrakhan...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/08/louis-farrakhan-twiiter-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Thoroughly and completely unmasked'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP APPROVAL TOPS OBAMA AND REAGAN AT SAME TIME IN PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/trump-approval-rating-better-than-obama-and-reagan-at-same-point-in-their-presidencies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOROS:  EVERYTHING HAS GONE WRONG</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/09/george-soros-go-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He also admits to being in a 'bubble'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 4.4 earthquake shakes part of northern Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/magnitude-4-4-earthquake-shakes-part-northern-oklahoma-174658426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEROKEE, Okla. (AP) — The U.S. Geological Survey says a 4.4 magnitude earthquake shook parts of northern Oklahoma and neighboring Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel stare down photo sums up meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/06/09/angela-merkel-posts-photo-stare-off-trump-g-7/687597002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conversations at the G7 summit were expected to be intense after President Trump imposed tariffs on steel and aluminum. Angela Merkel's photo was posted Saturday after the president described his relationship with the allies as "a 10."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii volcano disaster will affect marine and wildlife for DECADES...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5824465/Scientists-say-Hawaii-volcano-eruptions-affect-marine-wildlife-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hawaii volcano eruption is expected to impact Hawaii's marine and animal life for decades as the environment changes in the wake of the lava flow, according to scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE inches closer to $1 TRILLION mark as Wall St tech panic dissipates...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jun/09/apple-first-company-valued-at-1-trillion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech’s stock market dominance is no longer a Wall Street fear as Apple is close to becoming first company valued at $1tn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of TSA agents searching 96-year-old woman in wheelchair sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tsa-agents-search-96-year-old-woman-wheelchair-dulles-airport-outside-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman's daughter complained that the 6-minute search was quote "prolonged and repetitive"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Crowds Gather to Hear Geert Wilders Demand Tommy Robinson Release...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/london/2018/06/09/london-massive-crowds-gather-to-hear-geert-wilders-demand-tommy-robinsons-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive crowds turned out in London to rally for free speech and hear Dutch firebrand Geert Wilders demand the release of Tommy Robinson from prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: KIM</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/one-time-shot-peace-north-korea-trump-152935254.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump said his summit with North Korea represented "a one-time" chance to forge peace and that he would know within a minute if his counterpart Kim Jong Un was a serious partner. Speaking shortly before beginning his long journey to Singapore, Trump told reporters that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump delivers warning on trade as he leaves G-7 summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-floats-end-to-all-tariffs-threatens-major-12981080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUEBEC CITY - President Donald Trump told foreign leaders at the Group of Seven summit that they must dramatically reduce trade barriers with the United States or they would risk losing access to the world's largest economy, delivering his most defiant trade threat yet to his counterparts from around the globe. Trump, in a news conference before leaving for Singapore, described private conversations he held over two days with the leaders of Britain, France, Germany, Italy, Japan and Canada. He said he pushed them to consider removing every single tariff or trade barrier on American goods, and in return he would do the same. But if steps aren't taken, he said, the penalties would be severe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore preps for Trump-Kim summit with fresh paint and arrests...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-fg-singapore-summit-prep-20180608-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Singapore gears up to host the historic summit between an unpredictable U.S. President and a little-seen North Korean dictator, the lead-up featured a cat-and-mouse game between an aggressive international press corps and a notoriously controlled city-state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron handshake leaves mark on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/firm-friends-macron-handshake-leaves-mark-trump-140529338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They once shook hands for an eye-watering 29 seconds, with neither man willing to show a hint of weakness. Now Emmanuel Macron has left a firm impression on Donald Trump in their latest squeezing contest. Photos that have gone viral show how Macron turned part of Trump's hand pale with a blood-squeezing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some See End Of World Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/in-donald-trump-some-see-the-end-of-the-world-order-1864774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime partners worry about the lasting effect of confrontations with the U.S. president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man found dead at Bonnaroo...</title>
      <link>https://consequenceofsound.net/2018/06/man-found-dead-at-bonnaroo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;consequenceofsound.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;13 people have died at Bonnaroo over the course of the festival’s 17-year history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man commits suicide at Mecca's Grand Mosque...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-5824437/Man-commits-suicide-Meccas-Grand-Mosque.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has committed suicide by throwing himself off the roof of the Grand Mosque in Islam's holiest city of Mecca, Saudi police said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sculpture of king's head dating back 3,000 years sets off modern-day mystery caper...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd3713cc12f24a4090d1a34b650bdd5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — An enigmatic sculpture of a king's head dating back nearly 3,000 years has set off a modern-day mystery caper as scholars try to figure out whose face it depicts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In charging Senate staffer and seizing reporter's records, DOJ ignites debate over leak crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-charging-Senate-staffer-and-seizing-reporter-s-12979970.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Justice Department took a significant step this week toward advancing its long-promised crackdown on leaks, charging a former Senate Intelligence Committee staffer with lying to the FBI about his contacts with reporters, and seizing the phone and email records of a journalist to help make its case. As the man charged in the brewing controversy made his first court appearance, free-press advocates warned that federal prosecutors' heavy-handed tactics might send a further chill through the government, where officials already are reluctant to share information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat traces 'found in vegan and vegetarian ready meals'...</title>
      <link>http://www.itv.com/news/2018-06-09/meat-traces-found-in-vegan-and-vegetarian-ready-meals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China hosts Russia, Iran for summit as US tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-hosts-russia-iran-summit-us-tensions-rise-211038252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping will open late Saturday a two-day regional security summit attended by Russia, Iran and other allies confronting rising tensions with the US over trade and Washington's withdrawal from the Iranian nuclear deal. Armoured vans lined the streets of the coastal city of Qingdao</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'50s Motels Go From Bleak to Chic...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/50s-motels-go-from-bleak-to-chic-1528480694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motor lodges and motels from California to Long Island are getting dolled up, giving road trippers reasons to linger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robo-calls targeting Mexico presidential frontrunner put voters on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-calls/robo-calls-targeting-mexico-presidential-frontrunner-put-voters-on-edge-idUSKCN1J503X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spate of calls in recent days attacking Mexico's leftist presidential frontrunner has put his supporters on edge and underscored the last-ditch attempts to dent the candidate's commanding lead three weeks before the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Robot Encounter: Dinner, Drinks and a Massage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/your-next-robot-encounter-dinner-drinks-and-a-massage-1528542000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collaborative robots that work alongside humans—“cobots”—are getting cheaper and easier to program. That is encouraging businesses to put them to work at new tasks in bars, restaurants and clinics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their Grandparents Toppled a Dictator. Now They Are the Revolutionaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/their-grandparents-toppled-a-dictator-now-they-are-the-revolutionaries-1528545600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicaraguan students whose families fought with Daniel Ortega to oust the Somozas now lead a rebellion against Ortega’s own family dynasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justify bidding for rare Triple Crown sweep in Belmont...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/369a2723adca4f40aa047ad709464bb0/Justify-bidding-for-rare-Triple-Crown-sweep-in-Belmont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Three races at various distances on three different tracks over a span of five weeks.        Just 12 horses have swept the Triple Crown, one of the rarest f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns oil executives: 'Climate change' may 'destroy civilization'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/391470-pope-warns-oil-executives-climate-change-may-destroy-civilization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Saturday issued a dire warning to top oil executives, saying that climate change could “destroy civilization.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers stole sensitive Navy undersea warfare plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/china-hacked-a-navy-contractor-and-secured-a-trove-of-highly-sensitive-data-on-submarine-warfare/2018/06/08/6cc396fa-68e6-11e8-bea7-c8eb28bc52b1_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stolen material included secret plans to develop a supersonic anti-ship missile for use on U.S. submarines by 2020, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIRD TIME: MANAFORT HIT WITH FRESH INDICTMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/08/special-counsel-robert-mueller-files-new-indictment-against-paul-manafort-nbc-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller earlier this week asked a federal judge to revoke Manafort's bond and jail him because of alleged witness tampering in advance of his upcoming federal criminal trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian official admits for first time to aiding 9/11 terrorists...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/08/iran-facilitated-passage-of-9-11-attackers-politician/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Our government agreed not to stamp the passports'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGONY OF DEFEAT</title>
      <link>http://abc7news.com/sports/warriors-win-2018-nba-title-blow-out-cavs-in-game-4-108-85/3577657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Golden State Warriors did not hold back against the Cavaliers, putting together an incredible team performance in Cleveland. The Dubs beat the Cavs 108-85, securing their third NBA title in four years in a blowout game.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
