<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AI Can Predict Heart Attack  --  From An Eye Scan...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ai-heart-disease-eye-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests show the computer program can predict patients at risk of a heart attack in the next 12 months with up to 80 percent accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows punishment over alleged insult by journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/erdogan-vows-punishment-over-alleged-insult-by-journalist-01643231107?refsec=afp-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdogan Wednesday promised that a well-known television journalist would not go "unpunished" after she was arrested for allegedly insulting him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Charlie Brown' commits suicide...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/entertainment/charlie-brown-voice-actor-dies-at-65/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlsbad native Peter Robbins, the voice actor who brought Charlie Brown to life in the Peanuts cartoons from the 1960s, has died, his family told FOX 5. He was 65.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/a-shortlist-of-potential-nominees-to-replace-breyer-on-the-supreme-court/article_ee56a738-e6dc-5828-8091-16fa22aed3fa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In what will be one of the most monumental endeavors of Joe Biden's presidency, the retirement of Stephen Breyer sets the stage for an immensely important decision by the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pledge to Nominate Black Woman in Spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/bidens-pledge-nominate-black-woman-scotus-spotlight-breyer-plans-retirement-1673264</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Black woman's nomination would be a historic first, as only two African American men, Thurgood Marshall and Clarence Thomas, have held seats on the court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX rocket will soon crash into the moon after 'chaotic orbit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-spacex-rocket-will-soon-crash-into-the-moon-after-chaotic-orbit-for-7-years-experts-say/ar-AATaYhA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Front-Runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-early-front-runner-for-breyer-s-seat/ar-AATaQp6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade deficit tops $1 trillion FIRST TIME EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-trade-deficit-in-goods-top-1-trillion-in-2021-for-first-time-ever-11643205222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. trade deficit in goods hit an all-time high in 2021 and topped $1 trillion for the first time, as an economic recovery enabled Americans to snap up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit: CEO wore 'Bikini lives matter' mask, discriminated against women...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/business/article257687018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO frequently addressed an all-female marketing team as “sexy bitches” at work, the lawsuit claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic chill set for Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxweather.com/weather-news/arctic-chill-to-bring-30s-for-first-time-in-11-years-to-miami</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floridians living Miami will be grabbing the blankets this weekend, as the coldest temperatures in over 11 years arrive Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt Up $2 Trillion in 1 Year of Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/debt-2-trillion-1-year-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During Biden's first 12 months in office, the federal debt grew by more than $2 trillion — or $2,115,125,273,159.15 to be exact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME:  How Republicans Can Block...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6142711/joe-biden-supreme-court-nominee-mitch-mcconnell-stephen-breyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to managing a power shift in America’s judicial system, no one has proven more adept than Mitch McConnell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA?!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/26/speculation-ramps-up-about-kamala-harris-as-joe-bidens-supreme-court-pick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As news broke about Supreme Court Justice Stephen Breyer retiring, speculation ramped up that President Biden could tap embattled Vice President Kamala Harris to replace him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas man tries to smuggle migrants to US in flag-draped coffin...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-man-tries-smuggle-migrants-230017348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas man admitted to trying to smuggle two people into the United States in a coffin draped with an American flag -- like those that carry soldiers killed in combat -- the Justice Department said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Charlie Brown' commits suicide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/peter-robbins-original-voice-peanuts-192149551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Robbins, who voiced Charlie Brown in 'A Charlie Brown Christmas' and 'It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown,' died by suicide, his agent says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach County clerk seeks to punish newspaper for pursuing Jeffrey Epstein records...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/palm-beach-county-clerk-seeks-215128301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach County Clerk of Courts Joe Abruzzo is asking Judge Donald Hafele to make The Post pay the Tampa law firm he hired to fight the newspaper's request for the records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Ring Alarms Over Musk Brain Implants...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/experts-ringing-alarms-elon-musk-165830231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyThe dystopian television show Black Mirror has begun to feel less like fantasy as Elon Musk’s brain-implant startup, Neuralink, gears up for human trials. Soon the coin-shaped devices could allow patients to operate computers using only their thoughts.But in spite of the never-ending momentum for the world’s richest man, scientists are worried about the company’s oversight, the potential impact on trial participants, and whether society</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  66 percent of Omicron cases are reinfections...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/26/over-66-percent-of-omicron-cases-are-reinfections-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two-thirds of cases of the Omicron variant of COVID-19 are among people who have been reinfected with the virus, a new study said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army's highest ranking Muslim soldier also TIKTOK star...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-religion-media-social-media-3695ea452a07d8692053acb00d2e2d62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — Roughly half of the content creators on social media platform TikTok are under the age of 28. It’s just one reason why the popularity of Army Colonel Khallid Shabazz, who has some 43,000 followers on the social media platform, is so surprising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>140 Warships Drilling Across Europe, Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/01/26/140-russian-navy-warships-drilling-across-europe-middle-east-as-ukraine-tensions-simmer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian Navy is kicking off several simultaneous exercises, with ships from the Baltic and Black seas and its Northern Fleet sortieing from their homeports across Europe, the Kremlin has announced. More than 140 warships and support vessels, along with 60 aircraft and a total of 10,000 personnel, will participate in the drills, according to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 police officers shot in Ferguson... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/jan/26/2-police-officers-shot-in-ferguson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two St. Louis police officers were hospitalized Wednesday - one in very critical condition - after being shot in neighboring Ferguson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We All Are Cops Now...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/25/we-all-are-covid-cops-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politicians evade responsibility when they make civilians enforce mask and vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy discharges 1st active-duty sailors for vax refusal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-c406295348810a22c0f407d63279579c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Navy said Tuesday that it has discharged 23 active-duty sailors for refusing the coronavirus vaccine, marking the first time it has thrown currently serving sailors out of the military over the mandatory shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Outsourcing Human Interaction With Homeless to Robot Dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7dz7b/police-outsourcing-human-interaction-with-homeless-people-to-boston-dynamics-robot-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honolulu PD’s $150,000 Boston Dynamics robot dog is doing the hard work of taking temperatures at one of Hawaii’s several outdoor homeless shelters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL state senator extorted over nude photos says some blame her looks...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/florida-senator-extorted-nude-photos-looks-sex-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida state Sen. Lauren Book details why she's combatting digital sex crimes in the state legislature following extortion over her own private images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew comes out fighting: Demands jury trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10445007/Prince-Andrew-files-legal-papers-DENYING-Virginia-Robertss-sex-abuse-allegations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREAKING: Prince Andrew's legal team has filed legal papers in which the Royal denied all of Virginia Roberts' sex abuse allegations as he prepares for a bitter court battle in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favorite foods about to get more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/26/business/oscar-mayer-hot-dogs-velveeta-cheese-kraft-heinz/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The makers of top food and consumer goods brands plan to raise prices in the spring, dashing shoppers' hopes for a quick drop in their grocery bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of retail: More self-service...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-future-of-retail-more-self-service-2b375762-089f-4209-8f77-2cf12f1c6bc5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart clothing tags let you check out without a cashier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ending asset purchases in March...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fed-expects-it-will-soon-be-appropriate-to-raise-interest-rates-11643223873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve on Wednesday said it expects it will soon be appropriate to raise its policy interest-rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible witness in sex probe involving Gaetz takes plea...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/witness-sex-trafficking-probe-involving-matt-gaetz-takes/story?id=82484669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Possible witness in sex trafficking probe involving Matt Gaetz takes plea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Every indication' Putin plans force by mid-February...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220126-every-indication-putin-plans-force-by-mid-february-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of unnatural selection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220125-how-humans-are-changing-evolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humanity's influence on living organisms – both intentional and unintentional – is causing them to evolve in new and unusual ways. But how far could human-driven adaptation go?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist thrown out of Venice for posing topless on war memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/tourist-nude-venice-war-memorial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Venice tourist from the Czech Republic who was sunbathing topless on a war memorial was fined $513 and banned from the city for 48 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERIOUS OBJECT FOUND IN DEEP SPACE 'SENDING POWERFUL SIGNALS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4545551/astronomers-mysterious-object-anything-seen-before/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS object unlike anything that astronomers have seen before has been discovered in our “galactic backyard”. In research published Wednesday, scientists described the strange, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz stumbles out of the gate in Senate race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/25/dr-oz-senate-race-stumbles-00002056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Identify Factors Linked to Long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/will-get-long-covid-study-may-offer-clues-rcna13436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who is it at risk for long Covid? A study in Nature Communication finds that people who have lower antibody levels to the virus may be at higher risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website lists spies, priests and more deemed threats to Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/dark-website-lists-russian-spies-26051893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As tensions reach a boiling point amid the potential invasion from Russia, names continue to be added to an Orwellian database called 'Myrotvorets' accused of being threats to Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S combines Big Mac, McChicken, Filet-O-Fish  -- into single sandwich...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mcdonalds-menu-hacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's is adding some menu hacks to its official menu items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto, NFTs Rife With Fraud, IRS Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cryptocurrency-and-taxes-irs-has-watchful-eye-as-trading-increases-what-to-know</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For this who traded cryptocurrency for the first time last year: take your tax prep seriously, professionals warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents who retrieved soldier son's sperm after he was killed fight to create grandkids...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/parents-who-retrieved-soldier-sons-26052714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli soldier St.-Sgt. Amit Ben Yigal was killed during an arrest raid in the Palestinian West Bank village of Yabad two years ago and his parents retrieved his semen shortly afterwards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists use computer to predict exactly when society will collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/scientists-used-computer-predict-exactly-26049902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of scientists used a computer and their knowledge of trends to make a prediction about when society would begin to collapse - and their answer isn't so far away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths months after infection point to grim aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2624175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19’s deadly effects manifest long after some patients leave the hospital, according to a new study that points to the pandemic’s grave aftermath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia has lost its virus war...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/australias-lockdown-nightmare-was-inevitable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its pandemic incompetence was inevitable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis demands treatments deemed ineffective by FDA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-governor-de-santis-demands-covid-treatments-deemed-ineffective-by-fda-215854914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is charging that the White House is withholding a COVID-19 treatment that could save lives in a state that has already lost 64,000 to the pandemic, even though medical experts have deemed the therapy ineffective against the variant currently dominant in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Video, FAA Interview Reveal Bizarre Encounter With Unidentified Aircraft Over Atlantic City...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43986/pilot-video-and-faa-interview-reveal-bizarre-encounter-with-unidentified-aircraft-over-atlantic-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Air Force pilot flying a private plane seemed baffled after a strange-looking aircraft mirrored his maneuvers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Case Against Masks at School...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/01/kids-masks-schools-weak-science/621133/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Districts should rethink imposing on millions of children an intervention that provides little discernible benefit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists throughout Mexico say enough to killings and crimes against press...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/journalists-throughout-mexico-say-enough-to-killings-and-crimes-against-press/ar-AAT9q43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopsy finds Palestinian American died of heart attack after bound and gagged by Israeli soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/autopsy-finds-palestinian-american-man-died-of-heart-attack-after-being-bound-and-gagged-by-israeli-soldiers/ar-AATamZn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks worst start to year ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/stock-market-2022-worst-start-year-ever-73c15533-b443-4290-8693-c215df7a44ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech shares tend to get disproportionately dinged up when interest rates rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Super Bowl nears, hundreds of LAPD employees sick...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/2500-lapd-and-sheriffs-department-employees-out-with-covid-related-issues-as-super-bowl-nears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Super Bowl events just a few weeks away, COVID-19 continues to wreak havoc with the Los Angeles Police Department and the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department, with about 2,500 personnel ei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside SUNDANCE Top-Secret Documentary on Putin Target Navalny...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-sundances-top-secret-documentary-on-putin-target-alexei-navalny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A last-minute add to the Sundance Film Festival, Daniel Roher’s ‘Navalny’ trails the Russian opposition leader as he takes on the evil Putin and investigates how he poisoned him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ZOOM'd out:' Kamala mulls escape from DC bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/26/harris-at-a-crossroads-shape-or-escape-the-d-c-bubble-00002173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallon hyped his NFTs on 'TONIGHT SHOW.' Conflict of interest?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/jimmy-fallon-hyped-his-bored-ape-nfts-on-the-tonight-show-conflict-of-interest/ar-AATabdj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime, Homelessness, Taxes: Hollywood Big Shots Fleeing LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hollywood-big-shot-fleeing-la-ryan-kavanaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles at a Crossroads: "A growing chorus of Hollywood executives are talking about leaving the city," one entertainment industry insider tells TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anxiety tech' companies say glowing orbs, audio-playing rocks will improve mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Anxiety-tech-companies-say-their-glowing-orbs-16805366.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usually "mental health tech" means an app with some screen-based features such as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapaport films shoplifter boldly robbing NYC RITE AID...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/25/michael-rapaport-films-alleged-shoplifting-at-nyc-rite-aid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Rapaport posted a video of an alleged shoplifter walking out of a Manhattan Rite Aid, though the NYPD said there was no report of the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ reviewing role of fake Trump electors, top official says...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/justice-department-is-reviewing-role-of-fake-trump-electors-top-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Justice Department is investigating the fake slates of electors that falsely declared Donald Trump the victor of the 2020 election in seven swing states that Joe Biden had, in fact, won, a top agency official said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban peso in free fall against dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/cuba-economy-peso/cuban-peso-in-free-fall-against-the-dollar-idUSL1N2U50UV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cuban peso was trading at nearly 100 to the dollar on the informal market Tuesday, according to a trader and online trackers, a depreciation of more than 30% in less than a month and four times the fixed official rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NETFLIX first Arabic production ignites moral outrage in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20220126-netflix-s-first-arabic-production-ignites-moral-outrage-in-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix's first Arabic film production was always set to be a big event, but within days of its release, public opinion in Egypt was so inflamed that critics called for a ban on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto, NFTs Rife With Fraud, IRS Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/irs-seeing-mountains-and-mountains-of-fraud-with-crypto-nfts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto, NFTs Are Rife With ‘Mountains’ of Fraud, IRS Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're Probably in Simulation. How Much Should That Worry Us?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/26/were-probably-in-a-simulation-how-much-should-that-worry-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine that when your great-grandparents were teenagers, they got their hands on a groundbreaking new gadget, the world’s first fully</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's biggest sperm donor' has fathered 129 children...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4542139/worlds-biggest-sperm-donor-health-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN who says he’s the “world’s most prolific sperm donor” has claimed he has fathered 129 children – but now medical experts have warned against his actions. Clive Jones, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy wants to get crashed stealth fighter back -- before China can...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/asia/us-f-35-crash-recovery-south-china-sea-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Navy is trying to retrieve its most advanced fighter jet from the depths of the South China Sea, an extremely complex operation that analysts say will be closely monitored by Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Cell Phone Usage Can Damage Sperm Quality...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cell-phone-usage-damage-sperm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found that cell phone usage increases exposure to radiofrequency electromagnetic waves that could damage sperm quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Identify Factors That Appear Linked to Long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/scientists-identify-factors-that-appear-linked-to-long-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists Identify Factors That Appear Linked to Long Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most PORNHUB-obsessed cities revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4539646/most-pornhub-obsessed-cities-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GLOBAL sex report has revealed the most Pornhub-obsessed cities in the world and you may be surprised at which location is on top. The research was conducted by LookFantastic with the aim of find…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Exhaustion After Walk May Signal Death Within 3 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/older-adults-fatigue-early-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older adults who feel particularly tired after activities such as light housework or a 30-minute walk may be at an increased risk of dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi stock trades attract growing following online...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-speaker-pelosis-stock-trades-attract-growing-following-online-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year since a Reddit-driven retail trading frenzy rocked the markets and created the 'meme stock' phenomenon, leading U.S. lawmaker Nancy Pelosi's investments have become a meme in their own right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support your children if they are gay, pope tells parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/support-your-children-if-they-are-gay-pope-tells-parents-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis said on Wednesday that parents of gay children should not condemn them but offer them support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EYES ON FED</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/inflation-fighting-fed-likely-flag-march-interest-rate-hike-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is expected on Wednesday to signal plans to raise interest rates in March as it focuses on fighting inflation and sets aside, at least for now, economic risks posed by the ongoing coronavirus pandemic, a bout of market volatility, and Western fears of a Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran 567% increase in anti-Asian hate crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/san-francisco-police-mark-567-increase-in-anti-asian-hate-crime-reports-in-2021/ar-AAT9JpH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Selloff Ultimate Test of What's Real and What's Not...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-26/is-the-stock-market-crashing-2022-stress-test-has-companies-crypto-scrambling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican defends Benedict after report faults abuse record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-crime-germany-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-a7926c80e9af1a6c7688e3529231de82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican on Wednesday strongly defended Pope Benedict XVI’s record in fighting clergy sexual abuse and cautioned against looking for “easy scapegoats and summary judgments," after an independent report faulted his handling of four cases of abuse when he was archbishop of Munich, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATE HIKE MARCH?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-stock-markets-economy-1dd9283e46162b3c0d29a2c55a2934d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Wild volatility in the stock market this week has put heightened scrutiny on the Federal Reserve's meeting Wednesday and whether the Fed will clarify just how fast it plans to tighten credit and potentially slow the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest gorilla Ozzie dead at 61...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4541224/ozzie-zoo-atlanta-oldest-gorilla-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OZZIE, the world’s oldest male gorilla was found dead at Zoo Atlanta on Tuesday. He was 61-years-old. The primate had tested positive for Covid-19 last year along with a group of other gorill…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-variant of omicron on rise, WHO warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nny360.com/news/sub-variant-of-omicron-on-the-rise-who-warns/article_55f16a36-7f18-54af-b711-b9841536e904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nny360.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization warned this week that a sub-variant of omicron was on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moves troops and USA sends weapons as fear of war mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-moves-troops-and-us-sends-weapons-as-fear-of-war-mounts-in-ukraine/ar-AAT6Wri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He trades bitcoin naked. El Salvador paying price...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-trades-bitcoin-naked-el-salvador-is-paying-the-price/ar-AAT9azC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns stolen from rail cars spark LAPD concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/guns-stolen-from-rail-cars-spark-lapd-concern/article_d8a2c8f5-ae59-5caa-b21b-96d3dae43368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Guns are among the items that have been stolen from cargo containers on railroad tracks in Lincoln Heights, Los Angeles Police Chief Michel Moore said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths months after COVID point to pandemic's grim aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/deaths-months-after-covid-point-to-pandemic-s-grim-aftermath</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths Months After Covid Point to Pandemic’s Grim Aftermath</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picasso heirs launch digital art piece to ride 'crypto' wave...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-01-picasso-heirs-digital-art-piece.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pablo, meet Crypto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones says he took Fifth  '100 times' before Jan. 6 panel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/25/alex-jones-pleaded-the-fifth-nearly-100-times-when-questioned-by-jan-6-panel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infowars founder Alex Jones met with the House select committee investigating last year’s Capitol riot and exercised his right against self-incrimination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsized boat found near Florida; 39 people missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-bahamas-us-coast-guard-fort-pierce-67fff9ed65f0432d2cfb09ce309eaff1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The U.S. Coast Guard searched on Tuesday for 39 people missing for several days after a boat believed to be used for human smuggling capsized off Florida’s coast en route from the Bahamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook wins restraining order against stalker...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/25/1075619867/tim-cook-stalker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge granted a restraining order against a woman who allegedly showed up twice to Cook's home in Palo Alto. The filing states she also threatened Cook with photos of a handgun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto plunge wipes out profits for everyday investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-collapse-erases-more-than-1-trillion-in-wealth-forcing-a-reckoning-for-everyday-investors/ar-AAT8lXj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose approves gun owners liability insurance...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/san-jose-approves-controversial-gun-owners-liability-insurance-residents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California city has approved liability insurance for gun owners, the first such measure in the US, as it seeks to lower gun violence through stricter rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WITHDRAWS VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/politics/vaccine-mandate-osha-withdrawn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is withdrawing its Covid-19 vaccination and testing regulation aimed at large businesses, following the Supreme Court's decision to block the rule earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Germany, activists rise up to counter vax skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-berlin-religion-5dc72a0b8fa6956be7227b4100f23f4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Stefanie Hoener was at home one night in Berlin when she heard police sirens wailing through her Prenzlauer Berg neighborhood and anti-vaccine protesters shouting angry slurs as they marched down to the Gethsemane Church — a symbol of the peaceful 1989 revolution in East Germany that ended the communist dictatorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK holds breath as it awaits 'partygate' report...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-boris-johnson-health-business-london-75fb04edd2fb45483f5276bd1fe05079</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prime Minister Boris Johnson is bracing for the conclusions of an investigation into allegations of lockdown-breaching parties, a document that could help him end weeks of scandal and discontent, or bring his time in office to an abrupt close.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
