<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scope of undetected U.S. spread unknown...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/27/a-single-coronavirus-case-exposes-a-bigger-problem-the-scope-of-undetected-u-s-spread-is-unknown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s clear that the virus is spreading undetected in the United States. But how broadly that is occurring is an utter mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman took 550x usual dose of LSD, with surprisingly positive consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/27/health/lsd-overdoses-case-studies-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accidental drug overdoses can be life threatening but for two women who took massive hits of LSD the experience was life changing -- in a good way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov Says State Only Has 200 Testing Kits...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/gov-newsom-coronavirus-testing-kits-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom said Thursday the state is monitoring about 8,400 people for the coronavirus, a day after a Solano County patient was identified as the first coronavirus case in the U.S. from unknown origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New witnesses implicate CIA operative, DEA official in murder plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/2020/02/27/enrique-camarena-dea-agent-murder-narcos-mexico/2566023001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities assess new witness claims that a DEA official and CIA operative were tied to DEA agent Enrique Camarena's 1985 murder in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panicked passengers get family kicked off flight over coughing daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/463636/family-kicked-off-flight-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FAMILY of five say they were kicked off a plane just before takeoff over fears their coughing toddler could be infected with coronavirus. Canadian Emmanuel Faug, his wife Clémentine Ferraton and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to stop providing security for Harry, Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-canada-idUSKCN20L2KH?taid=5e581b2809d31b0001388971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada will no longer provide security for Prince Harry and Meghan Markle, the C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' Star Loses $400K In Email Scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/barbara-corcoran-loses-388700-dollars-phishing-scam-shark-tank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Lesson learned: Be careful when you wire money!" she tweeted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Daily Life Could Change in USA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/coronavirus-us-spread-daily-life-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How could the possible spread of coronavirus change our daily lives? Schools, businesses, hospitals and first responders could all be impacted, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of 100,000 Chinese Ducks on Standby to Combat Locust Swarms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/army-of-100000-chinese-ducks-on-standby-to-combat-locust-swarms/ar-BB10s7K0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY cuts kissing scene from MULAN to appease Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8050961/Disney-cut-kissing-scene-Mulan-China-said-doesnt-feel-right-Chinese-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An early cut of the film featured Mulan sharing a kiss with her love interest, Chen. Disney has decided to remove the scene after their Chinese executives deemed it inappropriate, the director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg releases new heart info; Calls on Sanders to do same...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/27/politics/michael-bloomberg-heart-health/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg's campaign disclosed new information on Thursday about the health of the presidential candidate's heart, and called on Bernie Sanders, who suffered a heart attack last year, to release the same data -- a clear attempt to bring the issue of the Democratic frontrunner's health to the forefront in the 2020 race for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA MONITORING 8,400</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/california-is-monitoring-8400-people-for-the-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski snubs French Oscars fearing 'lynching'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/polanski-snubs-french-oscars-fearing-lynching-161052163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial film director Roman Polanski told AFP on Thursday he would not attend the French Oscars because he fears a "public lynching" by feminist activists. The veteran is at the centre of a storm of protest after his new film about the Dreyfus affair, "An Officer and a Spy"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange extradition hearing paused until May...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/assanges-uk-extradition-hearing-paused-until-may-165709477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British judge on Thursday paused Julian Assange's extradition hearing following four days of intense legal wrangling over Washington's request for the WikiLeaks founder to stand trial there on espionage charges. Judge Vanessa Baraitser, who will ultimately rule on the controversial case, ordered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infects Iranian Vice President, Kills Ambassador To Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/iranian-vice-president-infected-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could hit 80% of Brits in 'worst case scenario'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11041657/coronavirus-could-kill-500000-brits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR in five Brits could become infected by deadly coronavirus — with up to 500,000 killed, according to a doomsday scenario set out in official papers seen by The Sun. Ministers are now considerin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALPERIN: Murderers Treated More Fairly Than Canceled People...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/media/2020/02/mark-halperin-metoo-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disgraced pundit is now portraying himself as a victim. Of cancel culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>700 ASKED TO ISOLATE IN NY</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/02/26/coronavirus-update-de-blasio-cuomo-outline-preparations-in-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Department says 700 people in the state have been asked to voluntarily self-isolate for two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie's New Coalition Put to Test in SCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-coalition-put-test-164038803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders is investing heavily in South Carolina, visiting often and building a solid organization. But the question remains whether his newfound front-runner status and momentum will be enough to attract the coalition of minority voters he needs to do well there.Saturday’s Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Stolen Hearse With Body In Back Crashes After LAPD Chase On Freeway...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/lapd-pursuit-ends-in-wreck-on-110-freeway-in-south-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday evening, a Lincoln Navigator was stolen from in front of a Pasadena church. It contained a casket with a woman's body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Picks Top AIDS Official for Response...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pence-picks-top-u-aids-163417283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Vice President Mike Pence has selected the State Department’s top AIDS official, Deborah Birx, to join his coronavirus response team, his office announced on Thursday.Birx is a career government official who was nominated by former President Barack Obama in 2014 as the U.S. global AIDS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson's Wealth Falls to Earth as VIRGIN GALACTIC Sputters...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/branson-wealth-falls-earth-virgin-150006098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wearing a black suit and harness, Richard Branson once leaped from the roof of a Las Vegas casino to launch one of his ventures.His fortune headed in the same direction this week.The value of the British billionaire’s stake in Virgin Galactic Holdings Inc. has fallen about $1.1 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'UNCONVENTIONAL' ARMY EXERCISE SET FOR UNDISCLOSED SITES IN NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article240651992.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vexed by how to contain virus, countries take tough steps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1631a414cfba8ae39dee4b82748b129b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Saudi Arabia cut travel to Islam’s holiest sites, South Korea toughened penalties for those breaking quarantines and airports across Latin America looked for signs of sick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty shelves hit USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/local-news/worries-over-panic-buying-arise-as-some-supply-shelves-at-stores-empty-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supplies were flying off the shelves Wednesday, with some shoppers taking pictures of empty shelves at stores across Oahu. This comes after a message from the Health Department to stock up on neces…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of gay killer: Why pop culture suddenly thirsty for queer blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/gay-serial-killers-murderers-tv-film-gianni-versace-dont-fuck-with-cats-9362656</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical staff exposed?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8051701/CDC-took-four-days-test-person-unknown-origin-coronavirus-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC reportedly took four days to test a person with the first confirmed case of coronavirus where the origin of the disease is unknown because they 'didn't fit the criteria'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus threatening to end world air-travel boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/coronavirus-raises-worries-about-a-broad-slowdown-in-air-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus will be a test for US airlines that have posted 10 consecutive years of profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appeals court rules tech platforms can censor content...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/484916-federal-appeals-court-rules-tech-platforms-are-free-to-censor-content</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court on Wednesday ruled that internet giants like Google and Facebook can censor content on their platforms, rebuking arguments from conservatives who claim the tech companies violate users' First Amendment rights&amp;nbsp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearse with body in back stolen from church...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/hearse-carrying-body-stolen-from-california-church/5970854/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mortuary's Lincoln Navigator with a body in the back was stolen from a church in California, sheriff's deputies say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Arrested For Vile Cow Manure Battery...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/cow-manure-attack-672985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 27--A Florida Man was arrested yesterday on a felony battery charge after allegedly dumping a bucket of cow manure over the head of a victim, police report. According to a complaint affidavi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg already airs more ads than Hillary in all of '16...</title>
      <link>http://mediaproject.wesleyan.edu/releases-022620/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mediaproject.wesleyan.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say should be prepared to see overnight boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/coronavirus-could-explode-in-the-us-overnight-like-it-did-in-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for a serious test of broken American health infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO official slams Trump's 'ignorant and incoherent' response...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/461542/world-health-organization-official-lashes-out-donald-trumps-incoherent-ignorant-coronavirus-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP WHO adviser has claimed Trump made “ignorant” and “incoherent” remarks during a news conference detailing the administration’s response to the coronavirus outbre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS: 14% of patients who recovered test positive again...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/coronavirus-bombshell-14-patients-who-21588972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recovered coronavirus patients discharged from hospitals in China's Guangdong province have later tested positive for the virus again - and nobody knows why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Joe holds wide lead ahead of primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/484901-poll-biden-holds-wide-lead-in-south-carolina-ahead-of-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden holds a wide 20-point lead over his closest rivals in South Carolina just days before the state’s Democratic presidential primary,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools shut, travel curbed as world races to fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200227142704-o5sk0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 9-Schools shut, travel curbed as world races to fight coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS NOT TESTED FOR DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/coronavirus-CDC-UC-Davis-Solano-County-patient-15088045.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details emerged Wednesday evening about the latest Covid-19 case in Northern California, that's being called the first in the U.S. that has no known connection to travel abroad or another known case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY High School Evacuated After Students Fall Sick; Hazmat Team Responding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/ny-high-school-evacuated-after-students-fall-sick-hazmat-team-responding/2304509/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hazmat team and two fire departments are responding to a Rockland County high school after getting reports multiple students fell ill, some of them vomiting, in the facility Thursday, authorities say. A call about the issue at Ramapo High School in Spring Valley came in shortly before 9 a.m. The building was evacuated as a precaution. It wasn’t immediately…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelly Slater plans to build world's largest artificial wave in California desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/pro-surfer-kelly-slater-build-world-s-largest-artificial-wave-n1143846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is a radically different vision," said real estate developer Noah Hahn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman sees zero earnings growth for US companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/goldman-sees-zero-earnings-growth-for-us-companies-this-year-because-of-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs revised its earnings estimate for the year to $165 per share, representing 0% growth in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady odds of returning to PATRIOTS 'not looking good'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2020/02/27/tom-bradys-odds-of-returning-to-patriots-not-looking-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots have yet to contract Brady’s camp, according to a person with knowledge of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin reveals plan to use body double...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-reveals-plan-body-double-102834805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin on Thursday revealed there was a secret plan to use a double to make public appearances for him, while insisting he vetoed it -- and that he is the real Putin. Putin's comments showed that a conspiracy theory widespread on the internet that the Russian strongman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek islanders stage new protests over migrant camps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greek-islanders-stage-protests-over-migrant-camps-134037383.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 people rallied on the Greek island of Lesbos on Thursday to protest against new migrant camps, a day after violent clashes left more than 60 injured, mostly police officers. On the neighbouring island of Chios, hundreds of protesters took part in a similar rally. The demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running out of time: East Africa faces new locust threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200227122340-3t5r8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The locusts are swiftly breeding and their numbers could increase 400-fold by June if the infestation is left unchecked, the UN has warned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug shortages loom?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/coronavirus-lead-drug-shortages-us/story?id=69243037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent coronavirus outbreak has revealed vulnerabilities in supply chains that deliver drugs to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Two climb over border wall with makeshift ladder...  </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-two-climb-over-border-wall-with-makeshift-ladder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of illegal aliens used a makeshift ladder to climb over the border wall near Tijuana on Thursday. Video captured by Washington Blade reporter Michael Lavers shows a man affixing a rickety contraption to the top of the wall as two others wait nearby. ﻿ Lavers just happened to capture the moment as he …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope cancels mass over illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11054234/pope-ill-vatican-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE Francis cancelled a church service today after he was struck down with illness. The 83-year-year-old pontiff was not well enough to attend the mass, although there is no suggestion at this sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV-like mutation...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3052495/coronavirus-far-more-likely-sars-bond-human-cells-scientists-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research by team from Nankai University shows new virus has mutated gene similar to those found in HIV and Ebola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman kills 5 at Milwaukee brewery before taking own life...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/local/2020/02/26/active-shooter-reported-molsoncoors-campus-unknown-injuries/4884282002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five Molson Coors employees were shot to death by another employee in Milwaukee, who then killed himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: COSTCO Sells Out of Emergency Food Kits...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/costco-sells-out-of-emergency-food-kits-online-amidst-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PAINTED BIRD' trailer: 'Savage' WWII drama that prompted mass festival walkouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-painted-bird-trailer-world-war-2-stellan-skarsgard-harvey-keitel-release-date-a9363021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Wellness Secrets From Canyon Ranch Spa: Sex, Food, Botox...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/bizarre-wellness-secrets-from-canyon-ranch-spa-sex-food-botox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bizarre Rich-People Secrets I Learned Undercover at Canyon Ranch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA cuts global growth forecast to lowest since financial crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200227110828-wlf0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/GROWTH-BOFA (URGENT):BofA cuts global growth forecast to lowest since financial crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 40% adults obese...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2154b643d53afae2a3654f722a9b60a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — About 4 in 10 American adults are obese, and nearly 1 in 10 is severely so, government researchers said Thursday. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention findings come...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman reinfected weeks after recovery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japan-woman-tests-positive-virus-recovery-062631746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in Japan who contracted the new coronavirus and was released from hospital after recovering has tested positive again, officials said Thursday. The case is the first time a patient apparently cleared of the virus has subsequently tested positive for it, a local official in Osaka said. The woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of 8CHAN Faces Arrest on 'Cyberlibel' Charge...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/27/founder-of-8chan-faces-arrest-on-cyberlibel-charge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fredrick Brennan, who founded but later distanced himself from the 8chan message board that has given encouragement and visibility to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Leaders Willing to Risk Party Damage to Stop Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/27/democratic-leaders-willing-to-risk-party-damage-to-stop-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senator Chuck Schumer, the minority leader, hear constant warnings from allies about congressional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan to close schools nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c92ca9ae1c59079557e98275ff814c06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan will close schools nationwide to help control the spread of the new virus, the government announced Thursday. Prime Minister Shinzo Abe asked all elementary, middle and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> ICE has run facial-recognition searches on millions of Maryland drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/ICE-has-run-facial-recognition-searches-on-15087173.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials have been permitted to run facial-recognition searches on millions of Maryland driver's license photos without first seeking state or court approval, state officials said - access that goes far beyond what other states allow and that alarms immigration activists in a state that grants special driver's licenses to undocumented immigrants.  More than 275,000 such licenses have been issued statewide since 2013, when the state became the first on the East Coast to defy federal guidelines and allow undocumented immigrants to obtain a license without having to provide proof of legal status. The technology now under scrutiny could let an ICE official run a photograph of an unknown person through the system and see whether potentially undocumented immigrants are flagged as a match.  "It's a betrayal of immigrants' trust for the [state] to turn around and let ICE run warrantless searches on their faces," said Harrison Rudolph, a senior associate at the Georgetown University law school's Center on Privacy and Technology. "It's a bait-and-switch. . . . ICE is using biometric information in the shadows, without government notice or public approval, to hunt down the most vulnerable people."  A top Maryland law enforcement official told state lawmakers in November that ICE officials had logged nearly 100 sessions in the state's driver's license database since 2018, according to a previously unpublicized letter obtained by The Washington Post. Each session could have included multiple searches of the Maryland Image Repository System database, which includes the photos, names, addresses and other personal information of roughly 7 million drivers statewide.  The battle to grant driver's licenses to undocumented immigrants spanned more than a decade in Maryland and is viewed by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Unleash Herpes Disinfectant for Virus-Tainted Planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theage.com.au/business/companies/airlines-unleash-herpes-disinfectant-to-clean-virus-tainted-planes-20200227-p544sz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theage.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qantas, Singapore Airlines and other carriers are turning to some of the world's hardest-hitting disinfectants, capable of stopping everything from sexually transmitted diseases to the MRSA superbug, in the fight against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Asks TV Stations to Take Down Anti-Biden Ads in His Voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/barack-obama-demands-south-carolina-stations-pull-misleading-ad-attacking-joe-biden/ar-BB10rfxh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Has World's Best-Performing Stock Market Since 1900...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/australia-has-world-e2-80-99s-best-performing-stock-market-since-1900/ar-BB10qXkP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer Fears Would Be Arrested If Released...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/weinstein-lawyer-fears-producer-would-be-arrested-if-released</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weinstein Lawyer Fears Producer Would Be Arrested If Released</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Suspends All Religious Pilgrimages...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabnews.com/node/1633826/saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIYADH: Saudi Arabia has placed a temporary ban on Umrah pilgrims in an attempt to ensure public safety by preventing the spread of the coronavirus. Most foreign pilgrims often visit the Prophet’s Mosque in Madinah before or after the completion of their religious duties in Makkah, this has also been halted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:   Could throw economy into recession...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-says-coronavirus-could-throw-234647173.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former Federal Reserve Chair Janet Yellen said depending on how widely the coronavirus spreads, the economic impact could have a significant impact on Europe and veer the U.S. toward a recession.“We could see a significant impact on Europe, which has been weak to start with, and it’s just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First case of UNKNOWN ORIGIN confirmed in Northern California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/health-and-medicine/article240674471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>83 ISOLATE IN NEW YORK</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/news/over-80-under-quarantine-for-possible-coronavirus-in-nassau</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nassau County health officials are warning residents to remain vigilant as over 80 people remain under voluntary quarantine for possible coronavirus exposure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR IN ITALY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3fdb7f213cbb6bb44c342dd6ae6f2fd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy sought to rally international support for its virus containment efforts Wednesday even as its caseload reached 447, people linked to Italy fell ill across Europe and as far away...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNINGS BERLIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/230fa2d2e2891ab2ccb6d9c8a5f479bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's health minister said Wednesday that the country was “at the beginning of an epidemic” as authorities in the west tested dozens of people who had contact with a couple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Harvey in custody: 'I didn't sexually assault anyone and I didn't rape anyone'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/defiant-harvey-weinstein-custody-didnt-sexually-assault-didnt/story?id=69234657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unrepentant Harvey Weinstein remained in custody at New York's Bellevue Hospital Wednesday, urging his team to keep fighting for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE TO LEAD GOVT RESPONSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-says-coronavirus-risk-americans-very-low-administration-effectively-handling-n1143756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president addressed the health issue at the White House, surrounded by the administration's public health experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS FIGHT VIRUS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/26/dow-futures-fall-after-microsoft-issues-coronavirus-warning.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures traded lower on Wednesday night even as President Donald Trump tried to assuage concerns over the coronavirus in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15+ MILLION VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/cbs-news-debate-ratings-1202868925/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: The latest figures from Nielsen show an even greater audience for CBS News’ coverage of the Democratic debate than the early numbers released on Wednesday morning. An average of 15.3 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump facing growing crisis amid market jitters, administration chaos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67a9a72531ca2e332bea9225cec2fda5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump faces a critical challenge in grappling with the new coronavirus outbreak: Asking Americans to believe him after he and top advisers have contradicted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel first country to warn citizens not to travel...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/898497/israel-first-country-warn-citizens-not-travel-abroad-over-coronavirus-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel on Wednesday became the first country to officially warn its citizens to avoid any international travel amid fears over the coronavirus outbreak. Several airlines have canceled flights to China, where the respiratory virus originated, and governments have issued warnings about travel to certain countries, but no country has actively urged their citizens avoid traveling abroad at large until now. 'If you don't genuinely have to fly â€” don't do so,' Israel's health ministry said in a statement. Although the majority of cases remain in China, the virus has spread to several other countries. In response to criticism that the country was stoking panic and could cause both economic and diplomatic damage, the health ministry said they'd rather deal with the inconveniences now than be sorry later, The Times of Israel reports. The only confirmed Israeli cases so far involve people who were on a cruise ship that was quarantined in Japan, although South Korea â€” which is experiencing one of the larger outbreaks beyond China â€” reportedly informed Israel over the weekend that a members from a group of pilgrims returned to South Korea from Israel and tested positive for the disease. Read more at The Times of Israel. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Issues Beard Guide...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/02/26/coronavirus-san-francisco-cdc-issues-coronavirus-beard-guide-soul-patch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an odd twist in coronavirus prevention recommendations, the Centers of Disease Control and Prevention Wednesday issued a graphic display of facial growth styles that will not interfere with a respirator or face mask.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
