<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Chris ratings soared when he interviewed his brother last spring on CNN -- now that's off-limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Chris-Cuomo-s-ratings-soared-when-he-interviewed-15994172.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, CNN had a sensible policy about whether Chris Cuomo could interview his older...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When U.S. blamed Saudi crown prince for role in Khashoggi killing, fake TWITTER accounts went to war...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/When-U-S-blamed-Saudi-crown-prince-for-role-in-15994516.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi-based Twitter accounts using fake profile pictures, repetitive wording and spammy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo under pressure to quit as third woman alleges harassment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuomo-faces-growing-pressure-quit-182533693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo was fighting for his political life on Tuesday after a third woman accused him of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OPEN 100%'</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article249627903.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is now time to open Texas 100%,” Gov. Abbott said in Lubbock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS OFF TEXAS!</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/texas-biggest-us-state-lift-covid-19-mask-76208428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is lifting a COVID-19 mask mandate that was imposed last summer but has only been lightly enforced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donors gave House candidate $8+ million. Consultants took half of it...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/After-donors-gave-a-House-candidate-more-than-8-15994730.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. House candidate Kim Klacik walked onto Mike Huckabee's cable talk show last August...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men turn to makeup after one-too-many ZOOM calls...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/02/why-zoom-is-boosting-sales-in-mens-cosmetics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When realtor Ben Dixon caught sight of his face during an early morning Zoom call with a client in January, he was distracted by what he perceived were bags and discoloration under his eyes. “I tho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Jumpstart Gun-Control Efforts...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/guns/dems-jumpstart-gun-control-efforts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new Democratic proposals could force gun buyers to wait up to three times longer to receive their weapon and could ban the private sale of used guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith Mulls Entering Politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/02/us/will-smith-politics-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Will Smith teased the idea of running for political office one day during an interview on Pod Save America released on Monday, a politics podcast hosted by a group of aides to former President Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus Checks Should Continue Until Covid Is History, Senators Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/stimulus-check-recurring-covid-19-senate-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans say $1,400 payments included in rescue package will last them less than three months, lawmakers argue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  ENOUGH SHOTS FOR ALL ADULTS BY MAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-covid-19-pandemic-statement-watch-live-stream-today-2021-03-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president said in an address that he's directing states to prioritize vaccinating K-12 educators and staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was quick to tell others to resign over sex harass claims...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/02/andrew-cuomo-was-quick-to-tell-others-to-resign-over-sex-harassment-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY — Gov. Andrew Cuomo has been quick to call for the resignations of powerful Albany lawmakers accused of sexually harassing aides — including known harassers Vito Lopez, Micah Kel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant races through Italy, especially among children...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-mario-draghi-italy-coronavirus-pandemic-d763a3e484cc74be866067a6adf16ced</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The variant of the coronavirus discovered in Britain is prevalent among Italy's infected schoolchildren and is helping to fuel a “robust” uptick in the curve of COVID-19 contagion in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Lawmakers Plan to Curtail Powers...</title>
      <link>https://nystateofpolitics.com/state-of-politics/new-york/ny-state-of-politics/2021/03/02/state-lawmakers-plan-to-curtail-cuomo-s-pandemic-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nystateofpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers have a two-way deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada suffers biggest contraction since Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/news/economy/canadian-press-newsalert-canadian-economy-contracted-5-4-per-cent-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 96% of schoolchildren still unsafe for full-time in-person learning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/enrichment/education/541258-according-to-cdc-96-percent-of-schoolchildren-still</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many are antsy to get kids back in school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Months Later, One Of NJ's First Patients STILL Battling Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/01/covid-1-year-long-haulers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study published by the Journal of the American Medical Association found about 30% of COVID-19 patients reported persistent symptoms as long as nine months after illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Political Flash Point: Passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccine-passports-covids-next-political-flash-point/ar-BB1ea13K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next major flash point over coronavirus response has already provoked cries of tyranny and discrimination in Britain, protests in Denmark, digital disinformation in the United States and geopolitical skirmishing within the European Union. The subject of debate: vaccine passports — government-issued cards or smartphone badges stating that the bearer has been inoculated against the coronavirus. The idea is to allow families to reunite,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY GOV GOES INTO HIDING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-avoids-public-amid-harassment-allegations-74d0eabed103e173b50f1a0ad7853671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo has avoided public appearances for days as some members of his own party call for him to resign over sexual harassment allegations. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC nominee mulls corporate political spending disclosures...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/02/gensler-sec-corporate-political-spending-472607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate disclosure was a dominant theme and key tension at Gensler's confirmation hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS OPENS 100%; ENDS MASK MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/03/02/abbott-hints-at-exciting-news-tuesday-that-could-include-rollback-of-texas-covid-19-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story and will be continously updated. AUSTIN — Texans will no longer be required to wear a face mask in public and all businesses can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat on par with ISIS!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2435097/christopher-wray-senate-hearing-capitol-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Director Chris Wray has blasted the deadly Capitol riot as “domestic terrorism” and said the homegrown threat is on par with ISIS. The director was speaking during a Senate hearing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL JAZEERA Staffers Concerned After Launch of Conservative Platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/a-betrayal-of-the-values-that-we-work-toward-al-jazeera-insiders-troubled-by-launch-of-conservative-platform-rightly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees at Al Jazeera’s English language platforms are deeply concerned that the launch of Rightly, a new digital platform aimed at conservative American audiences, may lead to a shift in editorial direction for Al Jazeera's English-language properties, including AJ+ and Al Jazeera English.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can physics prove if God exists?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210301-how-physics-could-prove-god-exists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there is a God, would they be bound by the laws of physics?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Synthetic Street Drug 'Benzo Dope' on the Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3anmy5/a-deadly-synthetic-street-drug-called-benzo-dope-is-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emerging drug contains two highly-potent highs, fentanyl and etizolam, and has been linked to a string of drug deaths in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boom looking more like baby bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/birth-rate-declining-baby-bust-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data provided to CBS News by 27 states shows births dropped by about 7.2% in December 2020, nine months after COVD-19 was declared a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service accidentally triggers tornado warning in multiple states...</title>
      <link>https://wgem.com/2021/03/02/tornado-warning-test-sparks-confusion-for-cell-phone-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgem.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tornado Warning alert was inadvertently sent to some cell phones by the National Weather Service on Tuesday without any indication it was part of a monthly test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular flea collar linked to 1,700 pet deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2021/03/02/seresto-dog-cat-collars-found-harm-pets-humans-epa-records-show/4574753001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Seresto pet collars were introduced, the EPA has received more than 75,000 reports related to the collars, including 907 involving human harm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent archdiocese urges Catholics to avoid shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article249627163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Johnson &amp; Johnson shot is the third coronavirus vaccine to be authorized by the FDA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Over Declining Birth Rates Among Younger Generations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/declining-birth-rate-younger-generations-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the global population is still growing, a major study from 2020 predicts it will peak in 2064 and then fall by nearly a billion people by the end of the century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 15 killed, dozen hospitalized in California crash... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-us-news-el-centro-33f54179647c0a7160c527b35163887d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El CENTRO, Calif. (AP) — An SUV believed to be carrying 27 people crashed Tuesday into a semitruck in Southern California, killing 15 people and leaving others injured, hospital officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military May Make Jab MANDATORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/03/01/military-may-revisit-making-covid-19-vaccines-mandatory-after-fda-grants-approval.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military leaders are unable to force service members to get the COVID vaccinations at this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of personnel refusing to take...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316827/A-military-personnel-refusing-receive-COVID-19-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some units just 30% of enlistees are willing to have a shot - despite the fact that the coronavirus pandemic continues to rage across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS and WALGREENS to use customer data for 'keeping in touch' and promoting services...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316739/Prepare-onslaught-texts-coupons-COVID-shot-CVS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans can get their vaccines from pharmacies like CVS and Walgreens, but as customers book their appointments they'll also be sharing their data so the retailers can promote their services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says domestic terrorism cases have soared in recent months...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/FBI-director-says-domestic-terrorism-cases-have-15993309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- FBI Director Christopher Wray said Tuesday that his agents are pursuing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vernon Jordan dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Vernon-Jordan-lawyer-and-D-C-political-power-15993038.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vernon Jordan never held elective office, was never a member of the Cabinet and never...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay men detained after kissing on Mexican beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/crowd-rallies-around-gay-men-detained-on-mexico-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of people on a beach in Mexico rallied around three men who were being detained by police after someone reportedly complained about “obscene acts of exhibitionism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Threatens Retribution...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-03-02/biden-sanctions-putins-inner-circle-for-navalny-imprisonment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move, though largely symbolic, represents an abrupt departure from the way President Donald Trump approached Russia, White House officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHMIDT GROUP:  USA not prepared to defend or compete in the A.I. era...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/02/us-not-prepared-to-defend-or-compete-in-ai-era-says-eric-schmidt-group.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is drastically underprepared for the age of AI, according to the National Security Commission on AI, which is chaired by Eric Schmidt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminals stole billions in COVID-19 unemployment benefits. New relief won't stop repeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/criminals-stole-billions-covid-19-120041457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least $40 billion in pandemic-related unemployment has been stolen, but Congress is about to approve more money with few new safeguards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should foreign companies own Missouri farmland? Lawmakers could put stop to it...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/govt-and-politics/should-foreign-companies-own-missouri-farmland-lawmakers-could-put-a-stop-to-it/article_a0e698e4-ca7e-534d-a532-892a9e04a3a3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smithfield Foods, which is owned by a Chinese company, opposes the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets sanctions over poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-russia-sanctions-navalny-poisoning-0e3a655e6a60b2f95be0f241b21ff4fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration announced sanctions of Russian officials and businesses Tuesday for a nearly fatal nerve-agent attack upon opposition leader Alexei Navalny and his subsequent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOY SCOUTS release plan to settle with sex-abuse survivors, exit bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2021/03/01/boy-scouts-bankruptcy-reorganization-plan-woefully-inadequate/6872981002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 95,000 former Boy Scouts have filed claims, saying they were sexually assaulted. The proposal offers an average of just $6,000 apiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia DA's Investigation of Election Fraud Heads to Grand Jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/just-in-georgia-das-investigation-into-trumps-alleged-solicitation-of-election-fraud-heads-to-grand-jury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUST IN: Fulton Country (GA) DA Fani Willis' investigation into former President Donald Trump for soliciting election fraud heads to a grand jury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUNDCLOUD first music app with 'fan-powered' artist payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210302-soundcloud-to-be-first-music-app-with-fan-powered-artist-payments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoundCloud to be first music app with 'fan-powered' artist payments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS BEST DAY SINCE JUNE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/01/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 rallied more than 2% in the previous session for its best day since June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Could 'Stop One-Third Of All Cancers From Developing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gli1-gene-end-one-third-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Along with making cells multiply, GLI1 genes can also increase tumor cell migration and makes the disease more resistant to chemotherapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden announces 'historic partnership': MERCK will help make J&amp;J jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-announce-merck-will-help-manufacture-johnson-johnson-s-coronavirus-n1259262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agreement between the two major pharmaceutical companies could help speed up vaccinations across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: EATING MEAT LINKED TO WIDE RANGE OF ILLNESSES...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/eating-meat-linked-wide-range-135856805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular meat eating could carry a higher risk of a wide range of diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will We Ever Shake Hands Again?</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/03/02/pat-kessler-will-we-ever-shake-hands-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we approach a year of life in quarantine, special correspondent and former WCCO senior political reporter Pat Kessler reflects on his last handshake before the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does marijuana help sick recover?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/does-marijuana-help-sick-recover-from-coronavirus-660685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hospital is now recruiting patients to participate in a more extensive study to explore CBD’s effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vernon Jordan dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/02/politics/vernon-jordan-dies/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vernon Jordan, a civil rights leader and close adviser to former President Bill Clinton, died Monday evening, multiple sources close to the family tell CNN. He was 85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horny toads disappearing. Can they be saved?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/whoa-whats-happening-horny-toads-130004498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas horned lizards, beloved creatures celebrated in local lore, were once so common that few people noticed when their numbers started declining. Now science is trying to save them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioter posed as 'Antifa,' then boasted he beat police who 'got exactly what they deserved'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-Capitol-rioter-said-he-posed-as-Antifa-feds-15992531.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The day before a pro-Trump mob stormed the U.S. Capitol, William Robert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home-security cameras fruitful resource for law enforcement -- and fatal risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Home-security-cameras-have-become-a-fruitful-15992558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police forces across the U.S. made more than 20,000 requests last year for footage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns mankind faces second 'great flood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316549/Pope-Francis-warns-mankind-faces-second-great-flood-caused-global-warming.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis warned that rising temperatures and melting ice caps could combine to produce a second great flood unless world leaders act to stop corruption and injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tina Turner bids farewell to fans with emotional new doc..</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tina-turner-bids-farewell-fans-123455610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music legend Tina Turner is the subject of one of the most successful biopics ever made but she tells the makers of a new documentary there's much more to her story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarkozy's conviction carries echoes for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Sarkozy-s-conviction-carries-echoes-for-Trump-15992485.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president was a polarizing figure, a firebrand who relished in ruffling the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painstaking study of 'Little Foot' fossil sheds light on human origins...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210302065749-2c4g8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-AUSTRALOPITHECUS/ (TV, PIX):Painstaking study of 'Little Foot' fossil sheds light on human origins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fuels attacks on health workers globally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-california-covid-19-pandemic-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-92b2df8f56118ffce9d3507a62ae941e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Nigerian nurses were attacked by the family of a deceased COVID-19 patient. One nurse had her hair ripped out and suffered a fracture. The second was beaten into a coma. Following the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Space hurricane' observed above North Pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencefocus.com/news/space-hurricane-observed-above-the-north-pole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencefocus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space hurricane was detected in the Earth's upper atmosphere and 'rained electrons' over the North Pole for nearly eight hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks that glow in dark? Scientists discover luminous deep-sea predators...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/sharks-glow-dark-scientists-discover-luminous-deep-sea-predators-new-n1259252</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the three glowing sharks, the kitefin shark is now the largest-known luminous underwater creature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland Declares State of Emergency as Pandemic Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/finland-declares-state-emergency-covid-113151118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Finnish government declared a state of emergency on Monday due to rising COVID-19 infections, a step that would allow the Nordic country to shutter restaurants and to impose other measures to blunt the pandemic. The decision comes as new variants contribute to a sharp rise in infections in the country, which has already closed its borders. "The government sees it necessary that we all have fewer contacts," Prime Minster Sanna Marin told a news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Be Compelled to Testify...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/02/cuomo-could-be-compelled-to-testify-in-sexual-harassment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a team of outside investigators begins to examine sex harassment allegations lodged against Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo, its scope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3:  Cuomo Accused of Unwanted Advance at Wedding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/gov-cuomo-accused-of-making-unwanted-advances-at-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third woman came forward on Monday to accuse New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo of inappropriate sexual behavior, saying he grabbed and kissed her at a 2019 wedding. Anna Ruch, 33, told The New York Time…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Chris FINALLY addresses bro's scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2432101/chris-cuomo-addresses-sexual-assault-scandal-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN’s Chris Cuomo finally addressed the sexual harassment scandal involving his governor brother, but insisted, “I can’t cover it.” The CNN anchor acknowledged the sexual ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA Director Brennan says he's 'increasingly embarrassed to be white male'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cia-brennan-embarrassed-white-man</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CIA Director John Brennan lamented his own Whiteness on Monday, suggesting that other men of his race were acting in embarrassing ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil outbreak worse than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/much-of-the-world-is-seeing-coronavirus-cases-fall-but-brazil-e2-80-99s-outbreak-is-worse-than-ever/ar-BB1e7Oj1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are at capacity, a virus variant is rampaging and vaccines are slow to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Manufacturers hobbled by shortage of tiny silicon chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-U-S-manufacturers-were-hobbled-by-a-shortage-15988468.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Semiconductor executive Tom Caulfield knew a crisis was brewing when he started getting...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
