<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Burnt out from tech, media overload...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/millennials-stressed-from-tech-and-social-media-overload/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milennials are suffering from burnout at work -- and tech is a major factor in their stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right party could emerge as kingmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-5590526,00.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ynetnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An end to the Netanyahu era would be unlikely to lead to a big change in policy on hotly disputed issues such as the peace process with the Palestinians that collapsed five years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses lawsuit over SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER's  'hate' group labels...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/16/judge-amy-berman-jackson-tosses-lawsuit-over-south/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has thrown out a lawsuit that accused leaders of the Southern Poverty Law Center of trying to financially destroy one of the organizations that it has labeled as a hate group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/election-liveblog-september-17-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As polls close, 3 main surveys point to fall in Likud support; turnout as of 8 p.m. higher than April vote; Yisrael Beytenu supporters cheer as Liberman becomes apparent kingmaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weirdest animals spotted on flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/9943454/weird-animals-emotional-support-plane-kangaroo/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE weirdest animals that have been spotted on a flight include ducks, turkeys and even horses. Passengers can bring them on the flight if they are “emotional support” pets. Emotional s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS leader calls for more terror attacks on West... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9939894/isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-audio-message/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“BADLY injured” ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has released a new message calling for more deadly attacks on the West – four months after he emerged from the shadows. The latest speec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why knowing Roman history key to preserving America's future...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/opinion/article/Why-knowing-Roman-history-is-key-to-preserving-14445569.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States didn't simply poof into existence, fully formed, from the brains of the Founders. History guided them as they crafted the American system of governance. This included the European traditions they were partially rejecting, but also elements from an older generation of republics that they wished to copy, especially the Roman Republic.  And while our problems today feel distinctly modern, Rome still has lessons that can guide our republic. Polybius, a Greek who saw Rome's republic conquer the world, believed those statesmen and citizens who knew Roman history could shape the future with wisdom and justice. This is what the Founders did, adapting the lessons of Rome to new problems - and it's what we must do again today.  In 509 B.C., leading citizens in Rome overthrew a monarchy and created a republic that slowly took over the Mediterranean. For 500 years, this republic dazzled the world with its hard-working farmers, good laws, shrewd diplomacy and indomitable citizen armies.  The Founders knew this history well. They had read Roman historians like Sallust and Livy, reveled in the biographies of Roman statesman by Plutarch and were steeped in the orations of Cicero. Thomas Jefferson even tweaked the poems of Horace celebrating Roman farms to describe Virginia agricultural life.  Not surprisingly, then, Rome inspired many features of our own constitution, including its checks and balances, bicameral legislature, term limits and age requirements. In some cases, the Founders copied terms straight out of the Roman constitution: words like senate, capitol and committee. They named places in honor of Rome like Tiber Creek and Cincinnati. American coinage and civic architecture are also strikingly Roman.  The Founders also preferred Rome's approach to warfare over Britain's. This preference explains why they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Catastrophic effects of working as FACEBOOK moderator...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/sep/17/revealed-catastrophic-effects-working-facebook-moderator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Job has left some ‘addicted’ to extreme material and pushed others to far right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark crystals: Brutal reality behind booming wellness craze...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/sep/17/healing-crystals-wellness-mining-madagascar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: Demand for ‘healing’ crystals is soaring – but many are mined in deadly conditions in one of the world’s poorest countries. And there is little evidence that this billion-dollar industry is cleaning up its act</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIRATES All-Star Closer Charged With Soliciting Child...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pittsburgh-pirates-all-star-closer-felipe-vazquez-arrested-charged-with-soliciting-a-child</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lefty pitcher allegedly sent a 15-year-old girl video of himself performing a sex act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden bid to attract Rust Belt workers faces troubles in own backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden-analysis/bidens-bid-to-attract-rust-belt-workers-faces-troubles-in-his-own-backyard-idUSKBN1W2110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Joe Biden kicked off his 2020 presidential campaign in April at a Teams...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu fights for MORE after decade in power... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election/israels-netanyahu-fights-for-new-term-after-decade-in-power-idUSKBN1W12UY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's battle for political survival looked se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House intervenes in GM strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/17/white-house-general-motors-strike-1735740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort would effectively put the White House on the side of the United Auto Workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders campaign wracked by dissension...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/17/bernie-sanders-campaign-dissension-1500287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staff shakeup and loss of an endorsement to Elizabeth Warren has allies warning of deeper problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Developing Long-Range Face-Scanning Capability...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/09/intelligence-community-exploring-long-range-biometric-identification/159907/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new IARPA program aims to build biometric technology that can identify people using cameras stationed on far off rooftops and unmanned aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police test 'Spider-Man' device as alternative to Taser...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-test-spider-man-device-as-alternative-to-taser/ar-AAHqBWn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Scientist Keeps Receiving Packages of Serial Killers' Hair...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/us/why-this-scientist-keeps-receiving-packages-of-serial-killers-e2-80-99-hair/ar-AAHovNB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious '60ft water monster' spotting swimming next to hydroelectric dam...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/mysterious-60ft-water-monster-spotting-20079435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge black creature was seen emerging from the water surface just feet away from the Three Gorges Dam in east China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon canceling 3 border wall projects...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2019/09/17/the-pentagon-is-canceling-three-border-wall-projects-because-the-costs-went-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three sections of wall in Arizona are out for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Trump's Cabinet has had more ex-lobbyists than Bush or Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/president-trumps-cabinet-has-had-more-ex-lobbyists-than-bush-or-obama-2019-09-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cabinet choices are a sign that Trump’s pledge to ‘drain the swamp’ may not be happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK suspends chatbot...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Netanyahu-slams-Facebook-says-media-giant-folds-to-Left-pressure-601992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister says media giant folds to Left pressure, and repeated his previous statements that the media is falsely reporting that large numbers of right-wing voters are casting their votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL DEADLOCKED?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Netanyahu-Gantz-stalemate-No-clear-winner-in-super-tight-Israeli-election-601964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Channel 12 and Channel 13 exit polls foresee yet another stalemate, granting Blue and White the highest amount of seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENETICALLY-MODIFIED MOSQUITO PLAN BACKFIRES SPECTACULARLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/genetically-modified-mosquito-apocalypse-plan-backfires-spectacularly-in-brazil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British biotech company Oxitec conducted a 27-month long experiment in 2013 Jacobina, Brazil, aimed at reducing the local mosquito population by 90 percent while preserving the genetic integrity of the local insect population</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERT: SUMMONING ROBOT 'ENTITIES' WHO WILL TREAT US LIKE ANTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/ai-expert-says-we-are-summoning-robot-entities-who-will-treat-us-like-ants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Arab turnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-election-polls-netanyahu-gantz-likud-lieberman-a9107996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of 'JOKER' and Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/defense-joker-1239858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips' bravura work dares to confront the things we're most afraid to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutally Honest EMMYS Ballot: 'POSE' Is 'Pretentious', 'Too Much Trump' on 'SNL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/brutally-honest-emmy-ballot-trump-snl-1240091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One producer abandons past votes ('Game of Thrones' "lost their way when they didn't have a book," while 'Veep' should be subjected to a "mercy rule") and outs a 'Voice' beef: "I've heard Blake Shelton and Adam Levine hate each other."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren, before huge  crowd, touts self as heir to female pioneers... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-before-huge-NYC-crowd-touts-herself-as-14444940.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Sen. Elizabeth Warren hailed the political power of female-led organizing in a speech Monday night that invoked the deadly 1911 Triangle Shirtwaist Factory fire to argue that outrage can spark positive change - and to make the case for her own presidential ambitions.  Warren, D-Mass., has long faced doubts from some Democratic leaders and voters who wonder if she would be able to defeat President Donald Trump, because of her outspoken liberal message and voters' possible reluctance to embrace a woman as president. Monday's speech, and the big crowd it attracted, was in part an attempt to rebut such doubts by arguing that liberal women have won big change before.  "I wanted to give this speech here - but not because of the arch behind me or the president this square is named for," Warren said, reading from a teleprompter in Washington Square Park, blocks from where the Triangle fire killed more than 140 workers, including many young immigrant women.  "We're not here today because of famous arches or famous men," she said. "In fact, we're not here because of men at all - we're here because of some hard-working women."  The comments were a more direct nod to gender than most of her public remarks to date, which typically focus on the ways in which powerful interests have tilted the country's government toward elites.  The event, which the campaign said attracted more than 20,000 people and was easily among her largest crowds, had been heavily promoted by the Warren campaign in the preceding days. It came as the campaign enters a new phase in which voters will be paying closer attention and the field is narrowing, and as Warren is looking for new ways to show off her momentum.  She has started holding large rally-style events in an effort to demonstrate that she enjoys enthusiastic grass-roots support from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says voting more important than sex!</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Netanyahu-has-unusual-pre-election-pitch-14443365.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - In battling to extend his run as Israel's longest-serving prime minister, Benjamin Netanyahu has warned voters of many a hazard, from unrest in the occupied territories to nuclear weapons in Iran. In the hours before the polls were to open Tuesday, he warned of another one: election day sex.  Voting day is a national holiday here and Netanyahu's ruling Likud party posted a last-minute video beseeching supporters not to waste it by going to the beach, lounging on the couch or - as suggested by a shot of four feet intertwining beneath the sheets - engaging in a bit of weekday whoopee. While you're enjoying yourself, the ad ends, "the left is getting ready to take over the government."  It was part of closing pitch that could seem strange to American political consultants who seek to convey an air of building momentum at the end of a campaign. By contrast, Netanyahu's final message has been: I'm losing.  The final public polls showed the race between Netanyahu and former army chief of staff Benny Gantz too close call or even slightly favoring Likud. (It is illegal to release new survey results in the final three days of the campaign.) But in hopes of motivating his base to go vote for the second time in five months, Netanyahu has been waging an all-out, all-is-lost campaign.  Showing his legendary ability to dominate the narrative, the prime minister was ever-present on national television and radio over the campaign's final weekend, sparring with the "hostile media," warning of widespread voter fraud in Arab neighborhoods and claiming that the country's recent run of security and growth was in fact slipping away. Israelis, who have heard the apocalyptic tone before, call it Netanyahu's "oy gevalt" campaign.  "Netanyahu is extremely competent at increasing the turnout of his political base," Yohanan Plesner,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sues Snowden over new memoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/doj-files-civil-suit-against-edward-snowden-over-new-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department filed a civil lawsuit Tuesday against former National Security Agency contractor Edward Snowden for violating his non-disclosure agreements with the CIA and the NSA by writing a new book about his leaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competing versions of populism could define campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/17/from-warren-and-trump-two-versions-of-corruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - Senator Elizabeth Warren stood beneath a marble arch in New York City, telling a crowd of thousands that she would lead a movement to purge the government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>