<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein accuser releases video of groping...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/world-exclusive-video-shows-harvey-weinstein-behaving-inappropriately-with-businesswoman-11496038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The producer is heard telling Melissa Thompson he wants to "have a little part" of her in a meeting to discuss her tech firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite risk to loved ones, Uygurs break silence on China crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2163939/speaking-out-uygurs-united-states-break-silence-chinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emboldened by international scrutiny, the American Uygur diaspora is increasingly willing to publicly condemn China’s re-education programmes, despite the risk to loved ones in Xinjiang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats and Deception: Why Board Turned On Moonves...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/12/business/cbs-les-moonves-board.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After initial harassment allegations against the CBS chief, some board members reflexively defended Mr. Moonves. It took weeks for his support to fade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINS' Chief Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/60-minutes-chief-jeff-fager-steps-down-1132722</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exec had been at CBS News for 36 years and has been a leading figure at the news division for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN: Air Force Intercepts Russian Bombers Near Alaska...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/09/12/russian-bombers-flew-near-alaska-intercepted-by-air-force-jets-us-military-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military said Wednesday that two Russian nuclear-capable bombers escorted by two fighter jets flew near Alaska on Sept. 11 before being intercepted by a pair of Air Force F-22 stealth fighter jets, according to a statement by the North American Aerospace Defense Command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O stadium-sized book tour...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/redeye/culture/ct-redeye-michelle-obama-first-lady-speaking-book-tour-becoming-20180912-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama announced a stadium-sized speaking tour Wednesday for her upcoming memoir, “Becoming,” and the first stop is in Chicago — at the United Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD cops arrested over alleged role in prostitution, gambling ring...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-cops-prostitution-ring-20180912-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of cops were being questioned for their involvement in a prostitution ring, the Daily News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New deep-sea fish species melts when brought to surface...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1387690/a-new-fish-found-26000-feet-deep-melts-at-the-surface-of-the-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blue, pink, and purple Atacama snailfish are perfectly adapted to handle the depths of the ocean, but perish without its tremendous pressure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Admits Met With Iran 3 or 4 Times, Outlines Rogue Diplomacy...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/kerry-meeting-iran-salvage-nuke-deal-rogue-diplomacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State John Kerry disclosed that he has been conducting rogue diplomacy with top Iranian officials to salvage the landmark nuclear deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Retiree army fuels Beto in rural TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/national-politics/article218184070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of awakening a sleeping base of Latino voters, the 45-year-old El Paso congressman has built an army of retirees who are helping him barnstorm the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Airs Disturbing Fager Text: 'Be Careful, People Have Lost Jobs Trying to Harm Me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cbs-news-airs-disturbing-jeff-fager-text-be-careful-people-have-lost-their-jobs-trying-to-harm-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS Boss Declines On-Cam Comment When Asked -- By CBSNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fired-60-minutes-boss-jeff-fager-warned-cbs-news-reporter-there-are-people-whove-lost-their-jobs-trying-to-harm-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If you repeat these false accusations without any of your own reporting to back them up you will be held responsible for harming me"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of venomous snakes swimming in streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/news/local/article218278260.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.myrtlebeachonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horry County snakes will still be out after Hurricane Florence. If bitten, getting to the hospital is important to staying alive. Conway Medical Center and emergency services will remain open during the storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Book Boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/woodwards-fear-posts-strong-sales-as-interest-in-trump-books-continues-1536788320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Woodward’s new book “Fear: Trump in the White House” sold more than 750,000 copies through Tuesday, its first day on sale, according to publisher Simon &amp; Schuster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans hit Dem candidate over rap career, N-word lyric...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/406281-nrcc-hits-democratic-congressional-candidate-over-rap-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Republican Congressional Committee released an ad Wednesday attacking Antonio Delgado, the Democratic candidate for New York’s 19th Congressional District, for his pa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juncker calls for more centralized powers so EU can 'flex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/09/12/jean-claude-juncker-demands-powers-brussels-turn-eu-global-player/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jean-Claude Juncker has demanded that European Union governments sacrifice their vetoes on EU foreign policy decisions in a flagship speech that called for more national powers to be centralised in Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French authorities ban parents from calling boy 'Amber'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/12/french-authorities-ban-parents-calling-baby-boy-amber/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French authorities have refused to let a couple name their newborn boy Amber because the child might suffer from unclear sexual identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gender X' set for NYC birth certificates...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-gender-options-birth-certificates-nyc-20180912-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers who do not identify as male or female will be able to change their birth certificates and select a third option, X, under a bill passed by the City Council Wednesday and expected to be signed into law by Mayor de Blasio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College 'catastrophic' enrollment drop after social justice meltdown...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/09/12/evergreen-state-sees-catastrophic-drop-in-enrollment-after-social-justice-meltdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evergreen State College enrollment plummeted after fallout from the controversial “Day of Absence” in May 2017 when all white people were asked to leave the campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems send 1,278 questions to Kavanaugh, more than all other nominees COMBINED...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/sep/12/democrats-send-1278-questions-kavanaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats submitted a record number of written questions to President Trump’s Supreme Court nominee, in a move Republicans said was the latest attempt to delay confirmation of Judge Brett Kavanaugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Hillary Spreads 'Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/09/12/clinton-pushes-fake-news-about-kavanaugh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinton runs with a Kamala Harris whopper that's already been debunked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>98% of families who illegally entered in 2017 still here...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/98-percent-of-families-who-illegally-entered-the-us-in-2017-are-still-here</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released government data shows 98 percent of families who were apprehended after illegally entering the United States from Mexico in fiscal year 2017 were never deported and remain in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens believe smartphones make more popular, less depressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/teenagers-believe-smartphones-make-them-more-popular-and-less-depressed-2018-09-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smartphone and social media engagement can be dangerous for teens’ mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIMON 2020 TAUNT: I COULD BEAT TRUMP!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/12/jamie-dimon-says-he-could-beat-trump-in-an-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamie Dimon took a swipe at President Donald Trump, claiming that he could defeat the president in a head-to-head election. Within minutes, Dimon addressed the uproar caused by his comments: "I should not have said it. I'm not running for president."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA threatens to pull products off market to combat teen vaping 'epidemic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fda-warns-juul-e-cigarettes-teen-vaping-epidemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA is calling on the industry to address the problem or risk having their flavored products pulled off the market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCNEWS: Manafort Plea Push To AVOID Cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/manafort-seeking-plea-deal-special-counsel-avoid-cooperation/story?id=57777687</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources familiar with negotiations tell ABC News former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort has been in ongoing negotiations with special counsel's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prof SHOOTS HIMSELF in arm -- to protest Trump!</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/shootings/report-las-vegas-professor-shot-himself-in-arm-to-protest-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A longtime College of Southern Nevada sociology professor is facing felony gun charges in connection with an on-campus shooting on the second day of classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodward 'FEAR' fastest selling book in years...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/09/12/media/barnes-noble-woodward-fear/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barnes &amp; Noble said "Fear" has had the "fastest sales for an adult title since Harper Lee's 'Go Set a Watchman' was released in July 2015."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescuers Use 'Jaws Of Life' To Free Bear's Head From Milk Jug...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/black-bear-milk-jug-roseau/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting a black bear’s head out of a 10-gallon milk jug is tricky business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Cop Commits Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/chicago-cop-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female Chicago police officer fatally shot herself Wednesday morning at the Calumet District police station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest -- the best...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/9/12/17843330/new-iphone-xs-max-release-date-screen-features-specs-apple-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not just the biggest iPhone ever, it’s one of the biggest phones out there, period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV titan abruptly dethroned...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/09/12/60-minutes-jeff-fager-harassment-ousts-816460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departure comes just two days after CBS chief Les Moonves was ousted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims fired over a text message...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/09/12/jeff-fager-claims-he-was-fired-over-a-text-message/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “60 Minutes” producer was booted from CBS on Wednesday after sexual misconduct allegations were made against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids Game Apps Collecting Their Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/09/12/technology/kids-apps-data-privacy-google-twitter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit by New Mexico’s attorney general accuses a popular app maker, as well as online ad businesses run by Google and Twitter, of violating children’s privacy law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER blocks 'illegal alien' posts as 'hateful content'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/twitter-blocks-posts-that-use-phrase-illegal-alien-as-hateful-content/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government, U.S. Supreme Court, and lawyers across the country use the word “illegal alien” to describe immigrants who illegally enter the country, because that’s the definition in the law. But Twitter makes its own laws, and the social media giant is now blocking folks from promoting any messages with the phrase, which its …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family arrivals surge at US-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/family-arrivals-surge-us-mexico-border-august-180709080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — A surge in families coming to the U.S. illegally contributed to an increase of illegal crossings from Mexico in August following two months of declines, authorities said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE CEO opposes 'sanctuary' repeal...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/business/index.ssf/2018/09/nike_columbia_sportswear_ceos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Ending Oregon's sanctuary law will damage Oregon's long-standing track record as a place that attracts diverse talent from across the globe," wrote Nike's Mark Parker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN:  Middle-class income hit all-time high of $61,372...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2018/09/12/middle-class-income-hit-an-all-time-high-last-year-us-census-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The median U.S. household earned $61,372 in 2017, a record level and a sizable jump from the prior year, the U.S. Census reported Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POVERTY DECLINES...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-poverty/u-s-incomes-rise-as-poverty-rate-declines-in-2017-idUSKCN1LS2HX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The median U.S. household income rose for a third straight year in 2017 and the poverty rate declined further, government data showed on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD's workers strike over sex harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f70d30d6bcf49bba9eb58cb91f09184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Emboldened by the #MeToo movement, McDonald's workers have voted to stage a one-day strike next week at restaurants in 10 cities in hopes of pressuring management</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author of 'How to Murder Your Husband' arrested for murdering husband...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox4now.com/news/national/nancy-crampton-brophy-how-to-murder-your-husband-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox4now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Crampton-Brophy, an Oregon-based romance author, was arrested September 5 as a suspect in the murder of her husband Daniel Brophy, according to the Portland Police Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backtracks Taunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-12/dimon-says-he-could-beat-trump-in-election-because-i-m-smarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE unveils new iPhone... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apple-event-expected-to-show-off-new-iphones-apple-watch-live-blog-2018-09-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. is expected to launch three new iPhones on Wednesday during the company’s biggest event of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: 'TONIGHT SHOW' cancels Norm Macdonald...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5942a2dbd4441938761579c1001dc19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — "The Tonight Show" canceled an appearance by Norm Macdonald after criticism of his comments about the MeToo movement and fellow comedians Louis C.K. and Roseanne B</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon rock hunter closes in on tracking down missing stones...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1476a6621d24358b70e7ea807198c2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A strange thing happened after Neil Armstrong and the Apollo 11 crew returned from the moon with lunar rocks: Many of the mementos given to every U.S. state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backtracks Taunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/09/12/dimon-says-he-could-beat-trump-in-election-because-i-m-smarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimon Says He Could Beat Trump in Election Because ‘I’m Smarter’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STALL NEAR COAST?</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Hurricane-Storm-Surge-Warnings-Carolinas-Florence-May-Stall-Near-Coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane and storm surge warnings were issued Tuesday afternoon ahead of Hurricane Florence, which is increasingly likely to deliver one of the most destructive and prolonged disasters ever seen in the Carolinas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-FOOT WAVES</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/monster-hurricane-florence-aims-to-drench-carolinas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coastal residents fleeing a potentially devastating blow from Hurricane Florence encountered empty gasoline pumps and depleted store shelves as the monster storm neared the Carolina coast with 140 mph (225 kph) winds and drenching rain that could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Stations Emptied Out... </title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/monster-hurricane-florence-aims-to-drench-carolinas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coastal residents fleeing a potentially devastating blow from Hurricane Florence encountered empty gasoline pumps and depleted store shelves as the monster storm neared the Carolina coast with 140 mph (225 kph) winds and drenching rain that could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer to kill 10 million despite better prevention...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cancer-kill-10-mn-2018-despite-better-prevention-140043457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cancer will kill nearly 10 million people this year, experts said Wednesday, warning the disease's global burden continues to rise in spite of better prevention and earlier diagnosis. An estimated 18.1 million new cancer cases were predicted worldwide for 2018 -- with 9.6 million deaths, said a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo secures animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/latest-news/article218225950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Riverbanks Zoo has begun securing animals from approaching Hurricane Florence. Animals placed in indoor shelters in stages. Zoo begins planning in May for hurricane season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cholera outbreak 'sparked by HOLY WATER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/728988/Cholera-outbreak-Ethiopia-Tigray-disease-holy-water</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHIFTS TOWARD SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article218246655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence is a category 4 moving from the Atlantic Ocean to the North and South Carolina coasts. Get updates on Hurricane Florence’s current path and the latest forecast predictions so you can prepare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Gets Bionic Penis, Loses Virginity at 45...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/09/12/andrew-wardle-bionic-penis-virgin-erection-dick-surgery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An English man born without a penis lost his virginity at 45 after doctors created him a bionic member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Wahlberg gruelling daily regime begins with 30 mins prayer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45497348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor gets up in the middle of the night to perform one of two daily work outs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More YALE freshmen identify as LGBTQ than conservative...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/more-yale-freshmen-identify-as-lgbtq-than-conservative/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queer freshmen greatly outnumber conservatives at the university, according to a survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Starr: President Can Be Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ken-starr-giulianis-wrong-the-president-can-be-indicted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN: USA Now Largest Global Crude Oil Producer...</title>
      <link>https://www.climatedepot.com/2018/09/12/the-united-states-is-now-the-largest-global-crude-oil-producer-surpassed-russia-and-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Obama Motivate Dems Anymore? Or Just Republicans?</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/does-obama-motivate-democrats-anymore-or-just-republicans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to FiveThirtyEight’s weekly politics chat. The transcript below has been lightly edited. micah (Micah Cohen, politics editor): With former President Bar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane flies into eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6157541/Incredible-video-shows-moment-research-plane-flies-eerily-calm-eye-Hurricane-Florence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the moment a plane explored the eye of Florence. The video was released by the Hurricane Research Division on Tuesday, just days before the monstrous storm is set to batter the Carolinas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA puts e-cig makers on notice: Fix 'epidemic' teen use...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/12/teen-e-cigarette-use-product-flavors-come-under-regulatory-scrutiny.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA said it cannot tolerate "a whole generation of young people becoming addicted to nicotine as a trade off for enabling adults to access these products," and so it has launched a crackdown on sales of e-cigarettes to teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THIS ONE REALLY SCARES ME'</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/national-hurricane-center-director-florence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coastal residents fleeing a potentially devastating blow from Hurricane Florence encountered empty gasoline pumps and depleted store shelves as the monster storm neared the Carolina coast with 140 mph winds and drenching rain that could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Solar Observatory Mysteriously Closed As Geomagnetic Storm Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-09-11/national-solar-observatory-mysteriously-closed-geomagnetic-storm-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad Agency Darkens Skin of Students in School Photo to Promote 'Diversity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/agency-darkens-skin-of-students-in-school-photo-to-promote-diversity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White guilt gone mad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Lourdes! Madonna Daughter Funky at Fashion Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6158285/NYFW-Madonnas-daughter-Lourdes-just-protects-modesty-displaying-unshaven-legs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old superstar offspring was showing off her perky assets in a bra-style top complete with chain adornments with just shells covering her modesty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 2017 world's most miserable year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/12/world/2017-negative-year-study-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year was the world's most miserable for more than a decade, according to a survey of people's emotions in more than 145 countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
People 'Fighting For Food'...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/people-are-fighting-for-food-as-authorities-warn-florence-could-produce-a-disaster-comparable-to-2005s-hurricane-katrina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence is about to make a "direct hit" on the east coast, and public officials are making one ominous declaration about this storm after another.  Florence is being called "extremely dangerous", "a monster", "the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing destructive quake, California considers list of buildings likely to collapse...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-earthquake-bill-20180912-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearing destructive earthquake, California considers list of buildings most likely to collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer carcass, mountain lions, lawsuits: Ugly battle escalates over trail in celeb enclave...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-trail-fight-20180912-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A debate over trail access has given rise to fences and “No Trespassing” signs, lawsuits between neighbors and even a state investigation into claims that a deer carcass was dragged onto the Los Robles trail system to lure mountain lions — and in turn to scare off hikers and horseback riders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal income set for Chicago?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/12/chicago-sets-up-universal-income-task-force-as-city-seeks-ways-to-tackle-poverty.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel will form a task force that will consider implementing the so-called “universal basic income” program in the city, as the embattled mayor seeks to cement his progressive legacy after promising not to run for another term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest charged with sexually assaulting young girl...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/catholic-priest-charged-sexually-assaulting-young-girl-115028673.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUINCY, Mass. (AP) — A Roman Catholic priest has been charged with sexually assaulting a young girl while staying in her family's Massachusetts home in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rat in Broth Wipes $190 Million Off Restaurant Chain's Value...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/12/world/asia/china-hotpot-rat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotpot restaurants, which have a serving setup similar to that for fondue, have been enjoying a moment in China. One diner’s video may change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls prevention summit...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/pope-summons-bishops-february-abuse-prevention-summit-57767101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis is summoning the presidents of every bishops conference around the world for a February summit to discuss preventing clergy sex abuse and protecting children — evidence that he realizes the scandal is global and that inaction threatens to undermine his legacy. Francis' key...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter: Don't scare off moderates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/99ad8d49e1e047c7b255dec2dd0cd626</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Former President Jimmy Carter sees little hope for the U.S. to change its human rights and environmental policies as long as Donald Trump is in the White House, but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belongings of missing WIKILEAKS associate found in sea off Norway...</title>
      <link>http://www.radioexe.co.uk/news-and-features/national-news/arjen-kamphuis-belongings-of-missing-wikileaks-associate-found-in-sea-off-norway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.radioexe.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personal belongings of a WikiLeaks associate who has been missing for three weeks have been found at sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dam threat?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-florence-looms-states-check-dam-integrity-1536750000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in the U.S. Southeast are checking dams and urging their owners to lower water levels ahead of Hurricane Florence, which is expected to unleash torrential rains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Shalennials: CEOs Under 40 Making Millions in Oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/09/12/meet-the-shalennials-ceos-under-40-making-millions-in-texas-oil#gs.3QS_QCs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet the Shalennials: CEOs Under 40 Making Millions in Texas Oil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Dems lead by 14 points on generic House ballot...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/406204-poll-dems-lead-gop-by-14-points-on-generic-house-ballot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats hold a 14-point lead over Republicans on the generic House ballot, according to a new poll released by Quinnipiac University on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIEGEL: 3,677 cases in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6158897/3-677-sex-abuse-cases-German-Catholic-Church.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) - A leading German magazine says a report on sexual abuse inside the Catholic Church in Germany details 3,677 abuses cases by Catholic clergy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. distances from 'STAR IS BORN' producer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4907a2600a2d47b79f5c80517089017c/Warner-Bros.-distances-itself-from-'A-Star-Is-Born'-producer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Just as film festival audiences are swooning over Bradley Cooper's celebrated romance "A Star Is Born," the film's studio is distancing itself from a producer of th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU pushes firms to remove extremist content in HOUR...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/eu-internet-content/eu-pushes-internet-firms-to-remove-extremist-content-in-one-hour-idUSL5N1VX5JR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Commission will propose new laws on Wednesday giving Google, Facebook , Twitter and other internet companies one hour to remove extremist content or face fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's top spy under spotlight amid rise of far-right...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180912-germanys-top-spy-under-spotlight-amid-rise-far-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hype sells...</title>
      <link>https://in.finance.yahoo.com/news/won-apos-t-believe-hype-142319283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 2007, the annual Apple iPhone launch event has carved out a special place among all capitalist spectacles, becoming one of the most impactful events in terms of its effects on consumers.While many have been vaguely aware of this phenomenon, a study by BankMyCell has now revealed the viral impact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust Belt house-flipping hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-financial-crisis2008-houseflipping/how-tech-jobs-helped-rust-belt-become-house-flipping-hotspot-idUSKCN1LS1H2?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the run-up to the 2008 financial crisis, millions of amateur investors kept adding fuel to the overheating U.S. housing market by betting on quick profits in hotspots like Las Vegas or Miami. A decade later, house-flipping is making a comeback, but this time in some Rust Belt cities the last boom passed by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champagne in space: Zero-G bottle lets tourists drink bubbly...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180912-champagne-space-zero-g-bottle-lets-tourists-drink-bubbly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Plunge Worse Than Dot-Com Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/09/12/crypto-s-crash-just-surpassed-dot-com-levels-as-losses-reach-80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto's 80% Plunge Is Now Worse Than the Dot-Com Crash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poorest Americans Risk Most in Hopes of Striking it Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/09/12/the-poorest-americans-risk-the-most-in-hopes-of-striking-it-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Poorest Americans Risk the Most in Hopes of Striking it Rich</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biohacker Who Experimented on Self Is Making DIY Mutant Frogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-12/biohacker-makes-diy-mutant-frogs-and-hopes-they-don-t-croak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Blames Devil for Sex Abuse...</title>
      <link>http://www.catholicnews.com/services/englishnews/2018/satan-is-attacking-bishops-they-must-fight-with-prayer-pope-says.cfm </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONG-TERM POWER OUTAGES</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180912011109-rl0a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-FLORENCE/ (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 8-'Monster' Hurricane Florence to pummel U.S. Southeast for days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump promises all-out response...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-promises-response-hurricane-florence-014241035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Tuesday said the federal government would spare no expense in responding to the likely damage from Hurricane Florence, which is forecast to slam the Carolina coast later this week. "Any amounts of money, whatever it takes, we're going to do it," Trump told reporters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Troubles Trip Republican Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/shipwreck-gop-grows-fearful-about-losing-senate-as-candidates-struggle-trump-support-tumbles/2018/09/11/b2cf04ce-b600-11e8-a7b5-adaaa5b2a57f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I hope when the smoke clears, we’ll still have a majority,” said Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell as the party is suddenly worried about reliably Republican Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort in plea talks with prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/manafort-in-talks-with-prosecutors-about-possible-plea-according-to-people-familiar-with-the-discussions/2018/09/11/5b98b64c-b60e-11e8-a7b5-adaaa5b2a57f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In-person jury selection in the second trial of President Trump’s former campaign chairman is set to begin Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W. Bush Hits Fundraising Circuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/09/11/george-w-bush-gop-2018-midterms-815750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Bush recognizes how important it is to keep the Senate and decided to help a few key candidates,” said Freddy Ford, a Bush spokesman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONG-TERM POWER OUTAGES</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/monster-hurricane-florence-pummel-u-southeast-days-012025550--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fierce winds and massive waves are expected to lash the coasts of North and South Carolina and Virginia even before Florence makes landfall on Friday, and its rains will take a heavy toll for miles inland, the National Hurricane Center in Miami warned. Although Florence was still days from arrival,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORENCE THE FURIOUS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c04474fc26d344c99ace7cd8e6bf437d/'Big-and-vicious':-Hurricane-Florence-closes-in-on-Carolinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, N.C. (AP) — Motorists streamed inland on highways converted to one-way evacuation routes Tuesday as about 1.7 million people in three states were warned to get out of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Turning Left?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/will-florida-take-a-left-turn-1536705094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot is riding on Andrew Gillum, the progressive nominee for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL voted best Mexican restaurant in the country...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfsb.com/archives/taco-bell-voted-best-mexican-restaurant-in-the-country/article_c954a2f5-c717-533c-b78f-b9decfa3f6cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfsb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Harris Poll, a nationwide customer survey of their favorite brands, has released its 2018 results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest -- the best?</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2018-09-11/apple-expected-to-unveil-bigger-pricier-iphone-on-wednesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG FIGHT!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/11/us/texas-ted-cruz-beto-orourke.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk erratic behavior rattling Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/09/11/elon-musks-erratic-behavior-continues-to-rattle-wall-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior of Tesla CEO Elon Musk continues to weigh on Wall Street as another analyst cuts his rating and price target on the electric-car maker’s stock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents of New Mexico compound indicted on federal charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6157523/5-residents-New-Mexico-compound-facing-firearms-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) - Five residents of a ramshackle desert compound were indicted Tuesday on firearms and conspiracy charges. Federal prosecutors in New...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could rival 1954 'benchmark storm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6153837/Florence-hit-punch-not-seen-60-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) - The last time the midsection of the East Coast stared down a hurricane like this, Dwight Eisenhower was in the White House and Marilyn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet balloon milestone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/11/alphabets-project-loon-passes-milestone-in-beaming-internet-to-earth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Loon makes internet-delivery balloons to provide access in remote locations, and "graduated" from Alphabet's X research division to become its own independent business in July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No shelters strong enough in entire SC county...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hurricane-florence-south-carolina-charleston-county-has-no-shelters-for-category-4-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charleston County shelters are not designed to withstand hurricane winds above a Category 3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOTING FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.aikenstandard.com/news/s-c-gov-henry-mcmaster-orders-state-offices-schools-closed/article_42887662-b526-11e8-8266-afefb61d6878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aikenstandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;S.C. Gov. Henry McMaster has ordered the closure of state offices and public schools in 26 counties – including Aiken County – ahead of Hurricane Florence's landfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More Than Half of Trans Male Teens Attempt Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/youth/2018/9/11/study-more-half-trans-male-teens-attempt-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to deliver Christmas trees...</title>
      <link>https://fox11online.com/news/offbeat/whats-in-the-amazon-box-maybe-a-real-7-foot-christmas-tree</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox11online.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Watch out for the 7-foot box on the doorstep. Amazon plans to sell and ship fresh, full-size Christmas trees this year. But a live tree is no paperback book. Amazon says the Christmas trees, including Douglas firs and Norfolk Island pines, will be bound and shipped without water in the usual sort of box. Amazon said they'll be sent within 10 days of being cut down, possibly even sooner, and should survive the shipping just fine. Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floods could create toxic brew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ce33c9fc732e49d9badc7e6aec1b3772/Hurricane-could-flood-many-waste-sites,-creating-toxic-brew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heavy rain expected from Hurricane Florence could flood hog manure pits, coal ash dumps and other industrial sites in North Carolina, creating a noxious witches' brew of waste that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sulzberger defends anonymous op-ed... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5563c8d59959478e89980b5cf496c8e7/Times'-publisher-defends-op-ed-in-meeting-of-US-news-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — The publisher of The New York Times said Tuesday that the newspaper's decision to run an anonymous opinion piece criticizing President Donald Trump's leadersh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald eagle lands on fire truck... </title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/bald-eagle-lands-on-firefighters-9-11-tribute-in-minnesota/492968991/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viral video shows the majestic American symbol atop a fire truck in Coon Rapids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick jerseys sell out in less than day...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/406116-kaepernicks-im-with-kaep-jerseys-sell-out-less-than-a-day-after </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick announced on Monday that the “#ImWithKap” jerseys he was selling on his website sold out within hours.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
