<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden policy suddenly in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22573703/biden-cuba-protests-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump-era sanctions are adding to Cuba’s crisis. Biden has to decide whether to keep them in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS GETS READY: BLUE ORIGIN to make history with unpiloted civilian space flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bezos-blue-origin-make-history-with-unpiloted-civilian-space-flight-2021-07-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos may have been beaten to space by rival Richard Branson, but the billionaire American businessman is poised to make history next week aboard what would be the world's first unpiloted suborbital flight with an all-civilian crew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: After days of hiccups, Brazil's Bolsonaro may need surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/brazil-s-bolsonaro-hospitalized-after-10-days-hiccups-won-t-n1274018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro, 66, was diagnosed with an intestinal obstruction on Wednesday evening after being taken to a hospital in São Paulo, according to state-run news agency Agência Brasil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: ANOTHER heat wave to roast western USA, Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/yet-another-major-heat-wave-is-set-to-roast-the-western-us-and-canada-by-the-weekend/ar-AAM9IZq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fourth punishing heat wave in five weeks could break more records this weekend into early next week, this time focusing in the Rocky Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tougher tactics targeting unvaccinated needed to stop new COVID spike, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tougher-tactics-for-the-unvaccinated-needed-to-stop-new-rise-in-covid-19-experts-say/ar-AAM9026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Door-to-door outreach and vaccine requirements at work would help curb coronavirus spread, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who bankrolled?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article252765228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The multinational probe into the brazen, middle-of-the-night assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse broadened Tuesday, with law enforcement in Haiti and South Florida searching for those who provided logistics and arms for the deadly assault — and who bankrolled it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Passport With Bitcoin, Escape Taxes?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2021/07/14/buy-passport-with-bitcoin-escape-taxes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 5,000 Cubans detained during protests, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.fltimes.com/news/nation/more-than-5-000-cubans-detained-during-protests-report-says/article_47b9fd54-1e05-591c-a42c-759dac88704d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA — Thousands of protesters have been detained in Cuba during three days of protests against the government, according to compiled reports. More than 5,000 were detained, including 120 activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREATENED TO KILL SELF...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9790181/Richard-Shermans-wife-Ashley-called-911-reporting-threatening-kill-arrest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Sherman's wife Ashley Moss called 911 reporting her husband had drunk two bottles of liquor and was threatening to kill himself before his arrest on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breyer says hasn't decided retirement plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/15/politics/stephen-breyer-retirement-plans/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Stephen Breyer has not decided when he will retire and is especially gratified with his new role as the senior liberal on the bench, he told CNN in an exclusive interview -- his first public comments amid the incessant speculation of a Supreme Court vacancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Britney Spears wins right to new lawyer in battle to remove dad...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/britney-spears-conservatorship-new-lawyer-matthew-rosengart-court-hearing-1234793152/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with Spears reaction following 3:28 PM update: Less than an hour after becoming Britney Spears’ new lawyer, Matthew Rosengart pledged to push the singer’s father off his perch i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami security firm faces questions in Haiti assassination...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-miami-haiti-assassinations-9ee8e2deb6de5be44d8ed82fe3da932d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — For the owner of a small private security company with a history of avoiding paying debts and declaring bankruptcy, it looked like a good opportunity: Find people with military experience for a job in Haiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Hospitalized for Exams After Days of Hiccups...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-president-bolsonaro-hospitalized-brasilia-says-source-2021-07-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro was transferred to a Sao Paulo hospital on Wednesday to undergo tests for an obstructed intestine, with the president's office saying he could receive emergency surgery in his latest health complication from a 2018 stabbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Taxes and Spending Set MORE Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-and-spending-set-records-through-june</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set new records for taxing and spending through the first nine months of fiscal 2021 (October through June), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Inside Iran's plot to kidnap American journalist...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714202835-2388d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ALINEJAD-UPDATE (TV, PIX):Inside Iran's plot to kidnap an American journalist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May need emergency surgery...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714181321-tjwwi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-BOLSONARO/ (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Brazil's Bolsonaro, who was stabbed in 2018, may need emergency surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of Amazon now emit more carbon dioxide than they absorb...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/amazon-rainforest-carbon-emissions-climate-change-18385660-c842-45cc-99b3-2b4b68546ac6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon region has been a vital climate change buffer by storing atmospheric CO2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARALYZED MAN COMMUNICATES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-science-health-2034d0fff5e63a83b7add3e991df79b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a medical first, researchers harnessed the brain waves of a paralyzed man unable to speak — and turned what he intended to say into sentences on a computer screen. It will take years of additional research but the study, reported Wednesday, marks an important step toward one day restoring more natural communication for people who can’t talk because of injury or illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantula Venom 'Reprogrammed' Into Pain Reliever...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/13/uc-davis-drug-tarantula-poison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tarantulas are normally something you’d scream in horror of at first sight. But researchers at UC Davis are hoping to turn that into screams of joy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN admits Branson never rode bike to launch...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/virgin-galactic-acknowledges-branson-never-rode-his-bike-to-space-launch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ:  Physician sold fake vaccine cards...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-b204c0717e99ffbe03cebb2d4a01ff55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A naturopathic physician in Northern California has been arrested and charged after federal prosecutors said she sold fake COVID-19 immunization treatments and fraudulent vaccination cards that made it seem like customers received Moderna vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 churches engulfed, attacked in ongoing anti-Christian terror campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecountersignal.com/news/45-churches-attacked</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecountersignal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our information shows that since June, there have been 45 attacks on Christian and mainly Roman Catholic congregations. Of those, 17 of them have been scorched or burnt to a crisp in suspicious circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISIS IN CANADA GROWS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/12/us-media-shamefully-justified-a-string-of-canadian-church-burnings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day this month in Canada, 10 Catholic churches were vandalized in a single city, Calgary. In the last month, arsonists and vandals have attacked dozens of Canadian churches, burning s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Locked In 7-YEAR Battle With IRS -- To Prove She's Not Dead!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/13/woman-declared-dead-by-internal-revenue-service-samantha-dreissig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unfortunate mix-up began with her mother's tragic death, and seven years later the situation has not been resolved, causing a tax nightmare for the woman and her father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer to Propose Pot Decriminalization...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/schumer-introduces-measure-for-federal-decriminalization-of-marijuana/ar-AAM9y2B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Democrat vowed to use his clout as Senate majority leader toward reversing decades of policies and laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-Door Progressive Caucus Antitrust Meeting Turns Fiery...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/07/14/congressional-progressive-caucus-antitrust-zoe-lofgren/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You may have other interests you’re trying to protect,” Rep. David Cicilline told Silicon Valley Rep. Zoe Lofgren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE:  41% of high school students earn below 1.0 GPA...</title>
      <link>https://foxbaltimore.com/news/project-baltimore/baltimore-city-schools-41-of-high-school-students-earn-below-10-gpa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foxbaltimore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (WBFF) - Baltimore City Schools has reached an alarming low in student performance. Project Baltimore has learned, during the first three quarters of this year, nearly half of high school students in City Schools earned a grade point average below a D. When Jovani Patterson ran for Baltimore City Council President last year, he ran on a platform that included accountability in education. &amp;ldquo;They take. They take. They take. Yet, despite the amount of money they get.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. citizen...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/14/1015861534/iranian-agents-are-facing-charges-for-their-role-in-a-plot-to-kidnap-a-u-s-journ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors charged five foreign agents working for the Iranian government for their roles in a plot to kidnap U.S. citizen and journalist Masih Alinejad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash for Kids Comes to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cash-for-kids-comes-to-the-united-states/ar-AAM9TSy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new child tax credit will radically reduce poverty, but millions of the poorest children might miss out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIMBLEDON 'MATCH FIXING' STORM: Matches probed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/tennis/3281139/wimbledon-match-fix-investigation-irregular-betting-patterns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TENNIS chiefs are investigating two reports of alleged irregular betting patterns at Wimbledon. The independent International Tennis Integrity Agency (ITIA) confirmed the alerts to possible suspici…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd Mural Collapses After Struck By Lightning...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/07/14/george-floyd-mural-struck-by-lightning-in-toledo-ohio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mural honoring the memory of George Floyd in Toledo, Ohio has collapsed after being struck by lightning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Debt trap' schemes cost nations billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3281851/roads-to-nowhere-china-debt-traps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROADS to nowhere, abandoned railways and half-built bridges – China has been accused of using “debt trap” projects to ensnare poorer countries and expand its power worldwide. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: DOORDASH driver contaminates Brooklyn cop's CHIPOTLE order...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/14/doordash-driver-contaminates-nypd-cops-chipotle-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DoorDash driver’s next run may be from the law after social-media video showed him digging his bare hands into a Chipotle order meant for a Brooklyn cop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  NFL STAR RICHARD SHERMAN ARRESTED FOR 'BURGLARY DOMESTIC VIOLENCE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/07/14/nfl-star-richard-sherman-arrested-for-burglary-domestic-violence-in-county-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sherman was taken down by a police K9 after trying to break into a family member's home in Redmond, Wash. before his arrest on Tuesday morning ... this according to law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HIT AND RUN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31816786/richard-sherman-arrested-domestic-violence-charge-denied-bail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free-agent cornerback Richard Sherman was booked at 6:08 a.m. local time at the King County Correctional Facility for burglary domestic violence, according to King County public records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brace for flooding. Moon 'wobble' coming, NASA warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/brace-for-flooding-a-moon-wobble-is-coming-nasa-warns/ar-AAM7FQg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA says rising sea levels mixed with the increase of high tides because of the moon's orbit will cause major flooding throughout the U.S. coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Protest Health Passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/french-police-quell-protest-against-covid-health-passport-rules/ar-AAM9u8w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests in France against COVID-19 'health pass' rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK spy chief: Hostile powers not behind racist attacks on soccer...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714144758-eft8o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCCER-ENGLAND/HATECRIME-BRITAIN:UK spy chief: hostile powers not behind racist attacks on soccer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some vaccine skeptics now getting the shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article252777353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If I could spare one person what I went through, then it was all worth it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Fines YOUTUBE for Removing Video of Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/germany-fines-youtube-six-figures-for-removing-video-of-anti-lockdown-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German court is ordering YouTube to pay a $118,000 fine for removing the video of a protest against Covid-19 lockdowns filmed in Switzerland last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security Recipients May Get Biggest Cost-Of-Living Bump In Almost 40 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/social-security-cola-2022-increase-biggest-nearly-40-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual benefit hike could top 6% due to fast-rising inflation. But retirees would have to wait until 2022 to see it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Charles says industrial farming ruining planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/prince-charles-says-cheap-food-and-industrial-farming-are-ruining-the-planet/ar-AAM9hk1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His entry into a political conversation marks him as a potentially different sort of monarch than Queen Elizabeth II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Shep Smith Crash on CNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-shepard-smiths-post-fox-news-crash-on-cnbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-Fox anchor’s much-hyped new show has failed to bring in viewers and, per insiders, it has struggled with some internal turmoil, including “regular tantrums” from Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With taxpayers' help, DELTA airlines posts 'profit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/14/delta-air-lines-dal-results-q2-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta's quarterly report came in better than Wall Street estimates as travelers returned and federal aid drove it to its first profit since 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUBAN PROTESTERS SHUT MIAMI FREEWAY</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/14/palmetto-expressway-shutdown-demonstrator-cuban-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parts of the Palmetto Expressway were shut down Tuesday due to demonstrators rallying for freedom in Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe takes another step toward digital euro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-technology-health-coronavirus-pandemic-e94f1022701acb8581c0d1e0f3fd8697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Central Bank said Wednesday it is launching a two-year investigation on whether to introduce a digital version of the euro that would complement cash, taking a cautious step toward introduction as central bankers around the world eye digital currencies and their potential impact on policy and the financial system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain's top court rules pandemic lockdown unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-courts-a0a36ebadb24600e122e2f1fb035011c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain’s Constitutional Court ruled Wednesday that last year’s strict stay-at-home lockdown order by the government under a state of emergency was unconstitutional. The court ruling was in response to a suit brought by the far-right Vox party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELINE DION DRAMA BRINGS FEST TO TEARS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/celine-dion-aline-cannes-premiere-titanic-valerie-lemercier-1235019031/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celine Dion did not make the trip to 74th Cannes Film Festival for the premiere of “Aline,” a French musical drama inspired by the life of the Quebecois superstar. But if she’d attended the premier…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Industry That Unmasks People At Scale...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnmvz/industry-unmasks-at-scale-maid-to-pii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unique IDs linked to phones are supposed to be anonymous. But there’s an entire industry that links them to real people and their address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fighter jets intercept American spy plane again...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3237665/russian-fighter-jets-intercept-us-spy-plane-black-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US spy plane was dramatically intercepted by Russian fighter jets over the Black Sea on Tuesday as experts fear violent escalation amid rising tensions between the US and Russia.  The ground crew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In looted SAfrican mall, man lies dead as poor pick over scraps...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210714-in-a-looted-s-african-mall-a-man-lies-dead-as-the-poor-pick-over-scraps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a looted S. African mall, a man lies dead as the poor pick over scraps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE WARNS ON 'WOKENESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/14/james-carville-warns-democratic-party-letting-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Democratic strategist James Carville said Tuesday that Democrats need to do a better job at not allowing the “noisy” left wing define the party if they want to continue winning elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Shep Smith Crash on CNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/inside-shepard-smith-post-fox-085839959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos CNBCWhether it’s a poor time slot, behind-the-scenes squabbles, an outdated news format, a slower post-Trump news cycle, or just a once-popular anchor taking his frustrations out on staffers, CNBC insiders have a lot of reasons for why Shepard Smith’s show has failed to capture major ratings. But one thing many agree on is that it has not met the bosses’ expectations.In the nine months since he went on the air for NBCUniversal’s financial news netwo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT Predicted in '72 Society Will Collapse This Century. Research Shows on Schedule...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xw3x/new-research-vindicates-1972-mit-prediction-that-society-will-collapse-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 1972 MIT study predicted that rapid economic growth would lead to societal collapse in the mid 21st century. A new paper shows we're unfortunately right on schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of Dogs With Severe Behavior Problems Has Trainers Alarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx5485/a-wave-of-dogs-with-severe-behavior-problems-has-trainers-seriously-alarmed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shunning of Weisselberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/07/donald-trump-allen-weisselberg-removed-from-subsidiaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg has been removed as an officer from dozens of Trump Organization subsidiaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Detained Live On-Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/dina-stars-cuba-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dina Stars, an independent journalist and YouTube star who has been covering the protests in Cuba, was rounded up by police during a TV hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunglass Company at War With Far-Right Extremists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sunglass-company-war-far-extremists-085656827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photo GettyWith an out-there look that wouldn’t look out of place in a 1980s wrestling ring, Pit Viper sunglasses have become a go-to choice for anyone looking to bring some attitude to the pregame. But Pit Viper has a problem: their reflective glasses are also a hit with far-right extremists.On the latest episode of The Daily Beast’s Fever Dreams podcast, hosts Asawin Suebsaeng and Will Sommer discuss Pit Viper’s attempts—so far unsuccessful—to distance t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAD OF RUSSIAN SPACE PROGRAM CRITICIZES 'BILLIONAIRE OLIGARCHS'...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/head-russian-space-program-criticizes-billionaire-oligarchs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jealous much?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation shows scale of big food dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/ng-interactive/2021/jul/14/food-monopoly-meals-profits-data-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation shows scale of big food corporations’ market dominance and political power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for loneliest whale in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/13/loneliest-whale-in-the-world-search</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When people learned he vocalized at a much higher pitch than other whales, they wondered: could other whales hear him? Was he plaintively calling, never hearing a reply? Was he lonely?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush slams Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/14/bush-bidens-afghanistan-withdrawal-499598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president’s criticism comes amid warnings from western officials that the Taliban could soon topple the U.S.-backed government in Kabul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns chaos if mix shots...</title>
      <link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/warns-chaos-people-freedom-choose-104847950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization (WHO) has warned there will be “chaos” if people start mixing different types of Covid-19 vaccine. The organisation’s chief scientist Soumya Swaminathan insists public health authorities must use the available data to decide how vaccines are administered, claiming individuals shouldn't take it upon themselves to mix and match jabs from different manufacturers, or decide when to have them. Some countries are planning to roll out a third vaccine, or a booster shot, to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/delta-variant-now-accounts-58-covid-19-cases/story?id=78834579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The so-called delta variant is estimated to account for about 58% of all COVID-19 cases in the United States, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Buck cast as deadly predator as overdose trial opens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ed-buck-is-cast-as-deadly-predator-as-overdose-trial-opens/ar-AAM7WSA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Hollywood Democratic donor Ed Buck goes on federal trial over fatal "party and play" sexual encounters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 1.8 million turned down jobs due to unemployment benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/high-unemployment-insurance-people-reject-jobs-9e426791-65b6-453b-9803-81aa3d0ca7e7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. businesses have been wrestling with labor supply shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Iconic MERCEDES for modern era...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/an-iconic-mercedes-for-the-modern-era-e94277c7-9e84-4d69-aa42-ac228ddde168.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iconic sports car is remade for the digital age</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The incredible shrinking dollar...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/13/inflation-surges-as-prices-see-biggest-jump-since-2008/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation continued to surge in June, with consumer prices accelerating at the fastest pace in almost 13 years as the economy emerges from the pandemic, the feds said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just another low-paying job' say overtaxed firefighters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714093414-wpkb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As climate change drives worsening U.S. wildfires, federal firefighters say they are underpaid - and some are leaving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney bid for freedom goes back to court...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714084809-0rxwi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-BRITNEY SPEARS/ (PIX, TV):Beset by squabbles, Britney Spears' bid for freedom goes back to court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Dems dig in after exodus; Republicans threaten arrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-democrats-voting-bills-0e475d25bc7c0a8c4019e51619cd5244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Democrats who hurriedly took off to Washington to block sweeping new election laws urged Congress on Tuesday to quickly pass legislation protecting voting rights, while Republican Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti seeks 5 fugitives as president killing probe deepens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-haiti-fugitives-24ed959aaf1018a7246c31f53680feac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — A former Haitian senator, a fired government official and an informant for the U.S. government are the latest suspects identified as part of a sweeping investigation into the killing of President Jovenel Moïse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic athletes to put on own medals at Tokyo ceremonies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/euro-2020-2020-tokyo-olympics-tokyo-coronavirus-pandemic-soccer-06686aa23eccd467616a150ffd556457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Athletes at the Tokyo Olympics will put their medals around their own necks to protect against spreading the coronavirus. The “very significant change” to traditional medal ceremonies in the 339 events was revealed Wednesday by International Olympic Committee president Thomas Bach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Massive flight delays, cancellations prompt finger-pointing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/562879-massive-flight-delays-cancellations-prompt-finger-pointing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines are racking up an unprecedented number of delays and flight cancellations just months after Congress gave the industry $54 billion so that carriers could retain their employees and facilitate a seamless return to air travel as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden team scrambles to address Latin American crises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/562875-biden-foreign-policy-team-scrambles-latin-american-crises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s foreign policy is being upended by a series of cascading crises in the Western Hemisphere and posing significant challenges for a State Department that still doesn’t have its full regional team in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer Set to Propose Decriminalization of Pot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/14/in-a-milestone-schumer-will-propose-federal-decriminalization-of-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Senator Chuck Schumer of New York plans to propose legislation on Wednesday to decriminalize marijuana at the federal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Walking Can Build Up Brain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/14/how-walking-can-build-up-the-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise can freshen and renovate the white matter in our brains, potentially improving our ability to think and remember as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China begins military flights from disputed South Sea bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/13/china-begins-military-flights-disputed-south-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s military recently deployed electronic warning and surveillance aircraft and helicopters on two disputed islands in the South China Sea in what analysts say is a sign the People’s Liberation Army has begun routine air operations from the bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syphilis cases rising around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/15581026/outbreak-syphilis-pandemic-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYPHILIS cases around the world have risen as countries open up again and romances are struck up once more. Currently Ireland is having an outbreak, with “urgent action” required to tac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses Roy Moore defamation suit against Sacha Baron Cohen...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/13/roy-moore-lawsuit-baron-cohen-499505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Alabama chief justice alleged the comedian defamed him in a trick interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agent was supposed to guard checkpoint. He took $400 bribes to smuggle migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-border-patrol-agent-was-supposed-to-guard-a-us-mexico-checkpoint-he-took-24400-bribes-to-smuggle-migrants/ar-AAM8LJN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case highlights a problem that U.S. Customs and Border Protection has faced for years: corruption among its agents guarding the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI beefs up veggie burgers as market booms...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-07-ai-beefs-veggie-burgers-booms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a beef with beef? A burgeoning veggie burger industry is using artificial intelligence to propose alternatives.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
