<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE DNA VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/could-dna-vaccines-be-the-next-tool-in-the-worlds-battle-against-covid-19-680371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India last month said that it had created the world’s first DNA vaccine, ZyCoV-D. While standard vaccines use actual 'hardware' protein, DNA vaccines use the 'software' blueprint of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE CEO Sees Free Speech as Core Value in Russia?</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/company-news/video/youtube-ceo-wojcicki-responds-to-russia-censorship-accusations~2289193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sep.26 -- Susan Wojcicki, chief executive officer at Google’s YouTube, responds to accusations the company is censoring its content in Russia, at the request of the Russian government. She also talks about balancing free speech values with local laws, and discusses regulatory scrutiny facing YouTube in the U.S. She speaks with Bloomberg's Emily Chang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholz, Social Democrats lead... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926202840-8j2vx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 7, TV, PIX):UPDATE 7-German Social Democrats beat conservatives in vote to decide Merkel successor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoarding!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/uk-gas-stations-run-dry-trucker-shortage-3f078d7eb6bbf2b5d130abfa44007278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of British gas stations ran dry Sunday, an industry group said, as motorists scrambled to fill up amid a supply disruption due to a shortage of truck drivers. The Petrol Retailers Association, which represents almost 5,500 independent outlets, said about two-thirds of its members were reporting that they had sold out their fuel, with the rest “partly dry and running out soon.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama lawmakers weigh using virus funds to build prisons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-prisons-alabama-4eb1ebe3327247a923284e0105992bdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — Alabama is weighing the use of $400 million in pandemic relief funds to build new prisons, a proposal that state Republican leaders say would save state taxpayer money but that critics argue is not the intended use of the federal aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland ALMOST elects Europe's first women-majority parliament...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-elections-environment-and-nature-iceland-f9e66907b6e25560a508de0f4b118ddd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REYKJAVIK, Iceland (AP) — Iceland briefly celebrated electing a female-majority parliament Sunday, before a recount produced a result just short of that landmark for gender parity in the North Atlantic island nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN:  Humanity on brink of nuclear annihilation with threat highest for 40 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3737906/human-annihilation-threat-highest-un-chief-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUMANITY is on the brink of “nuclear annihilation” with the threat reaching its highest boiling point in forty years, a top UN chief has warned. The nuclear arms race has the globe teet…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK PRAISES COMMUNIST CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/26/musk-praises-china-says-tesla-will-expand-investments-in-country.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the second time this month Musk was highly complimentary of the nation that's imperative to his electric vehicle company, saying it's a "global leader digitalization."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY DEFIANT: TRUTH BEFORE TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/liz-cheney-donald-trump-wyoming-60-minutes-2021-09-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Cheney tells Lesley Stahl about running for re-election as an anti-Trump Republican in Wyoming, as her own party there has called for her resignation, and joining the House Select committee investigating the January 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT BITES BACK:  Fuel Shortages Pile Pressure on Johnson as UK Crisis Escalates...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/fuel-shortages-pile-pressure-on-johnson-as-u-k-crisis-escalates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY TILTS LEFT:  THE MAN ON TRACK TO REPLACE MERKEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/scholz-has-slight-edge-in-german-election-too-close-to-call/ar-AAOQluh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olaf Scholz of the Social Democrats has inched ahead of Chancellor Angela Merkel’s conservatives and claimed a mandate to lead the country’s next government in an unprecedentedly tight election to decide who will lead Europe’s biggest economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court observers see trouble ahead as public approval of justices erodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-observers-see-trouble-ahead-as-public-approval-of-justices-erodes/ar-AAOPPXC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the court about to open one of its potentially most divisive terms in years, a debate rages over whether the nine justices are too political — and too powerful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS ON THE ROPES?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-outside-washington-worry-party-will-blow-its-chance-of-enacting-historic-agenda-e2-80-94-a-failure-with-grave-political-consequences/ar-AAOPMsG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many Democrats believe that in the end, party leaders will find a way to pass their ambitious plan, some have started contemplating a nightmare scenario, in which the talks fall apart and Democrats are left explaining to voters who gave them the keys to the car why they couldn’t get it out of neutral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'X Date'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-treasury-scrambles-to-pay-bills-pandemic-fuels-uncertainty-over-calamitous-x-date/ar-AAOPGgg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administration officials rule out more heterodox ideas, such as minting $1 trillion coin, to resolve debt ceiling impasse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE HAITIANS WORKING WAY TO BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/thousands-mostly-haitian-migrants-traverse-panama-way-united-states-2021-09-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to 4,000 migrants, most of them Haitians, have passed through the treacherous jungles of the Darien Gap in Panama on the Colombian border as they make their way north to the United States, two Panamanian government sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban hang bodies in four city squares...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10027605/Witness-Taliban-hang-dead-body-Afghan-citys-main-square.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC CONTENT. Wazir Ahmad Seddiqi, who runs a pharmacy beside the main square in Herat, said four alleged kidnappers' dead bodies were brought to the square to be hanged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Democrats lead... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926181407-p4a3q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 6, TV, PIX):UPDATE 6-German SPD edges ahead of conservatives in vote to decide Merkel successor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland votes to make same-sex marriage legal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926155602-soh8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWISS-LGBT/MARRIAGE (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Switzerland votes to make same-sex marriage legal by near two-thirds majority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY may tap National Guard to replace unvaccinated healthcare workers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926145130-syuow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):New York may tap National Guard to replace unvaccinated healthcare workers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland elects Europe's first women-majority parliament...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210926105850-s5pxn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iceland was ranked the most gender-equal country in the world for the 12th year running in a World Economic Forum (WEF) report released in March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/germany-election-angela-merkel-14ddbbb09c8c9ea194155a73de0970e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's center-left Social Democrats were locked in a very close race Sunday with outgoing German Chancellor Angela Merkel’s center-right bloc, which was heading toward its worst-ever result in the country's parliamentary election, projections showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GORY' SCENE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amtrak-crash-montana-c8c3730849f568ca68b455eb23b49cef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOPLIN, Mont. (AP) — Federal officials sent a team of investigators from the National Transportation Safety Board to the site of an Amtrak derailment in north-central Montana that killed three people and left seven hospitalized Sunday, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romans say enough to invasion of wild boars...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/basta-romans-enough-invasion-wild-174208841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rome has been invaded by Gauls, Visigoths and vandals over the centuries, but the Eternal City is now grappling with a rampaging force of an entirely different sort: rubbish-seeking wild boars. Entire families of wild boars have become a daily sight in Rome, as groups of 10-30 beasts young and old emerge from the vast parks surrounding the city to trot down traffic-clogged streets in search of food in Rome’s notoriously overflowing rubbish bins. Posting wild boar videos on social media has become something of a sport as exasperated Romans capture the scavengers marching past their stores, strollers or playgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CIA's secret war plans against WIKILEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kidnapping-assassination-and-a-london-shoot-out-inside-the-ci-as-secret-war-plans-against-wiki-leaks-090057786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2017, as Julian Assange began his fifth year holed up in Ecuador’s embassy in London, the CIA plotted to kidnap the WikiLeaks founder, spurring heated debate among Trump administration officials over the legality and practicality of such an operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Rocket Ship-Like 'Micro-Robots To Deliver Drugs Inside Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/micro-robots-deliver-drugs-human-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using a design inspired by bacteria and sperm, the micro-robots can be moved through the body using ultrasound to help deliver drugs to specific areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 Mexican soldiers briefly detained in El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/573963-14-mexican-soldiers-briefly-detained-in-el-paso</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fourteen Mexican soldiers were detained for several hours on Saturday by U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) agents after crossing into the El Paso, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas COWBOY attempted to bribe NFL drug-test collector...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32280659/sources-dallas-cowboys-lael-collins-attempted-bribe-nfl-drug-test-collector</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cowboys right tackle La'el Collins attempted to bribe a drug-test collector, sources told ESPN, which was one of the reasons for his five-game suspension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Plays Down 'Health Rumors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10029785/Kremlin-issues-photos-Putin-hunting-break-minister-bid-play-health-rumours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin - currently 'self-isolating' due to a Covid-19 'outbreak' in his entourage - is seen with his loyal defence minister on a 72-hour camping trip in the Russian taiga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doc says patients deny virus from deathbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/09/25/dr-matthew-trunsky-says-some-dying-covid-patients-deny-virus/5866695001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan doctor Matthew Trunsky says some dying COVID-19 patients continue to deny their diagnosis or denounce vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holmes Trial Sparks Debate: Why Not Other CEOs?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/25/1040442689/elizabeth-holmes-trial-why-her-not-other-ceos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the former CEO of the blood-testing company Theranos faces fraud charges, some are asking why other tech leaders accused of wrongdoing have avoided criminal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Busts Illicit Vans Used for AIRBNBs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/operation-room-service-nyc-officers-bust-illicit-vans-used-for-airbnb-rentals/3291762/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Manhattan impounded seven van over the course of two days they say were illegally registered and used as Airbnb rentals on city streets. Coined “operation room service,” deputies from the sheriff’s office, in partnership with the NYPD, busted more than half a dozen vehicles Thursday and Friday. Sheriff Joseph Fucito told NBC New York that investigators discovered the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How pandemic unleashed bedlam in vets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/26/pandemic-unleashed-bedlam-veterinary-clinics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff attrition, high demand for appointments and enraged human clients have strained vet practices across the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris, assigned to tackle volatile issues, quietly builds network...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/harris-assigned-to-tackle-volatile-issues-quietly-builds-a-network/ar-AAOONmR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of both parties have noted that Biden has asked Harris to take on often thankless issues, including abortion and immigration. But her meetings with activists in these areas have helped her to build political connections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She bought dream home; 'Sovereign citizen' changed locks...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/she-bought-her-dream-home-a-sovereign-citizen-changed-the-locks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as the Moorish sovereign citizen movement, and loosely based around a theory that Black people are foreign citizens bound only by arcane legal systems, it encourages followers to violate laws in the name of empowerment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-Trading Hamster Performs Better Than Buffett, S&amp;P 500...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/25/1040683057/crypto-trading-hamster-goxx-warren-buffet-s-p-500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hamster named Mr. Goxx enters one of two tunnels in the his cage, which determines whether he will buy or sell. As of Friday, his portfolio is up nearly 20%, according to his Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 DEAD; 'WELL OVER' 50 HURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/amtrak-derailment-at-least-50-hurt-in-montana-official-says/ar-AAOPanm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three people were killed and 50 others were injured after an Amtrak train derailed in Montana on Saturday afternoon, setting off a frantic response by rescuers who scrambled to extricate passengers from cars, the authorities said.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
