<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Squads ordered to kill deserting soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4956617/putin-orders-execution-squads-kill-own-men-desert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has allegedly ordered execution squads to kill his own men if they try to desert his Ukraine invasion. The Russian tyrant expected a swift quick victory when he ordered the invasion …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR ON BORDER: Cartel member spotted 'aiming AK47 at Texas patrol chopper'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4955386/escalating-violence-texas-mexico-border-cartel-shootout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIOLENCE at the US border is escalating as a cartel member has been filmed aiming an AK-47 at a Texas patrol helicopter. The helicopter caught footage of a suspected gunman pointing the weapon in t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan for utopian metaverse city with no rules, cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4953398/plan-utopian-metaverse-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN architecture firm has plans to design a metaverse centering around self-governance. Zaha Hadid Architects (ZHA) – one of the world’s most prominent architecture firms – has shared plans to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad ally warns of nuclear dystopia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-ally-says-united-states-075006672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of President Vladimir Putin's closest allies warned the United States on Wednesday that the world could spiral towards a nuclear dystopia if Washington pressed on with what the Kremlin casts as a long-term plot to destroy Russia. Dmitry Medvedev, who was president from 2008 to 2012 and is now deputy secretary of Russia's Security Council, said the United States had conspired to destroy Russia as part of an "primitive game" since the 1991 fall of the Soviet Union. "It means Russia must be humiliated, limited, shattered, divided and destroyed," Medvedev, 56, said in a 550-word statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Bond Plunge Wipes Out $2.6 Trillion, Exceeding Losses of Financial Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/now-worst-drawdown-record-global-005215542.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global bond markets have suffered unprecedented losses since peaking last year, as central banks including the Federal Reserve look to tighten policy to combat surging inflation.Most Read from BloombergWhere Mornings Would Get Darker Under Permanent Daylight Savings TimeChina Jet’s Nosedive From 29,000 Feet Baffles Crash SpecialistsChina Plane Crash Update: One Black Box Located; Pilot DetailsUkraine Update: Zelenskiy Will Join NATO Summit Via Video LinkThe Bloomberg Global Aggreg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Docs Show DOJ Spying on 'VERITAS' Journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/22/project-veritas-feds-secretly-accessed-emails-00019247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer for hidden-camera-sting producer says prosecutors misled court, improperly prolonged gag orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurch co-founder resigns over complaints of unwelcome behavior to women...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/australian-megachurch-co-founder-resigns-over-complaints-of-unwelcome-behavior-to-women/ar-AAVoy4F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hellscape' in Mariupol where 100,000 trapped...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220323-live-hellscape-in-mariupol-where-100-000-trapped-biden-heads-to-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were injured and buildings damaged in Russian strikes on a residential area of the Ukrainian capital, officials said on Wednesday. US President Joe Biden is heading to Europe on Wednesday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large tornado strikes New Orleans, causing serious damage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tornadoes-storms-new-orleans-hurricanes-weather-1b01d30a0719a44489b159cd6ba92a45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARABI, La. (AP) — A tornado tore through parts of New Orleans and its suburbs Tuesday night, flipping cars, ripping roofs off homes and killing at least one person in an area of Louisiana pummeled by Hurricane Katrina 17 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham asks her to rate religious faith 'on scale of 1 to 10'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sen-graham-presses-ketanji-brown-jackson-to-rate-her-religious-faith-e2-80-98on-a-scale-of-1-to-10-e2-80-99/ar-AAVnsBI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissent Brews Over Putin Leadership...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/22/as-russia-stalls-in-ukraine-dissent-brews-over-putins-leadership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In January, the head of a group of serving and retired Russian military officers declared that invading Ukraine would be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks new sanctions, help for Ukrainians in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-biden-migration-world-war-ii-warsaw-606513344e8f0d96152e43f5ee82b75a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With Europe facing its most precarious future since World War II, President Joe Biden will huddle with key allies in Brussels and Warsaw this week as the leaders try to prevent Russia’s war on Ukraine from spiraling into an even greater catastrophe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton tests positive for covid... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hillary-clinton-covid-19-bill-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinton said former President Bill Clinton has tested negative and that he will quarantine "until our household is fully in the clear."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China jet's nosedive from 29,000 feet baffles crash specialists...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/China-jet-s-nosedive-from-29-000-feet-baffles-17020437.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The China Eastern Airlines jet was flying a normal route to Guangzhou when it suddenly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham asks her to rate religious faith 'on a scale of 1 to 10'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sen-graham-presses-ketanji-brown-jackson-to-rate-her-religious-faith-e2-80-98on-a-scale-of-1-to-10-e2-80-99/ar-AAVnsBI?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspector general identifies 41 LA sheriff's deputies who allegedly belong to gang-like groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/inspector-general-identifies-41-sheriffs-deputies-who-allegedly-belong-to-gang-like-groups/ar-AAVngtx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER CHARGE:  Oral surgeon 'fed' girlfriend's addictions with anesthesia, IV pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/an-oral-surgeon-e2-80-98fed-e2-80-99-his-girlfriend-e2-80-99s-addictions-with-anesthesia-and-an-iv-pole-police-say-now-he-e2-80-99s-charged-with-murder/ar-AAVnEGd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One in Three U.S. Workers Earning Less Than $15 an Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/one-in-three-us-workers-are-earning-less-than-15-an-hour/ar-AAVnBlo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Includes hedge fund manager, judge, NYC elites...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sarah-lawrence-sex-cult-leader-194900677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — The trial of accused Sarah Lawrence College sex cult leader Lawrence Ray descended into chaos Tuesday as the alleged abuser was wheeled out of the courthouse on a stretcher — and the Justice Department mistakenly released a list of well-heeled johns who paid to have sex with one of the leader’s followers. Ray, 62, was put in an ambulance outside Manhattan Federal Court for the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD sued over DNA database that contains genetic profiles...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nypd-sued-over-dna-database-152200342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — The NYPD’s DNA database is comprised of an ever-growing number of genetic profiles of thousands of innocent New Yorkers, including children, a lawsuit alleges. The Legal Aid Society, in a suit filed Monday in Manhattan Federal Court, is asking a judge to declare unconstitutional the “practice of secretly taking, analyzing and maintaining peoples’ DNA in its suspect index.” The ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN'S OBSCENE WEALTH REVEALED</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4954616/inside-vladimir-putin-superyacht-scheherazade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE sickening luxury enjoyed by Vladimir Putin on board his £500million superyacht is today revealed by The Sun — including tasteless gold loo roll holders. Mad Vlad, whose forces are bombing women…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE THE RISE OF 'DAREDEVIL SELFIES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4953792/daredevils-pose-hundreds-of-feet-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAREDEVILS pose for pics hundreds of feet up. One woman stands atop a 2ft-wide pole and balances on a pal’s shoulders while taking a selfie above a city. Another girl sits on a shelf, while a lad b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Megadeals Spark Boom Times for TV Announcers...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/troy-aikman-joe-buck-espn-fox-sports-al-michaels-1235116326/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN’s move to poach Joe Buck and Troy Aikman from Fox Sports rocked the sports media world, while Al Michaels opted to exit NBC when his contract expired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor complains about rampant subway fare evasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-fare-beating-is-rampant-and-mayor-adams-wants-the-crime-prosecuted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Mayor Eric Adams wants minor crimes like fare evasion to get attention and be prosecuted by district attorneys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas now averages $6 a gallon in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/los-angeles-is-1st-major-city-in-u-s-to-reach-6-gas-average</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles on Tuesday became the first major city in the U.S. to reach an average gas price of $6 or more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hiding identity for decades outed after getting covid shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/article259661000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man used his fake identity with his three children and their mother, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Staffers Fear Retaliation Over 'Don't Say Gay' Walkouts...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/disney-walkout-dont-say-gay-hulu-disneyworld-fx-espn-bob-chapek-1234984074/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(UPDATED with more details) The planned full-day walkout at Disney today over the company’s fumbled response to Florida’s discriminatory “Don’t Say Gay” bill has seen …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Contractor working at Navy SEAL Museum tried to steal ballistic vest worn during bin Laden raid...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/navy-seal-heist-274595</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 22--A contractor working at the Navy SEAL Museum was arrested yesterday for allegedly trying to steal a ballistic vest that was worn by a member of the team that raided Osama bin Laden’s Pakist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilians stripped, tied up and beaten...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/ukrainian-civilians-stripped-tied-up-and-beaten-by-vigilantes-in-shocking-videos/news-story/3a2abcc0a87815925dce0db9cee1c09a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: Distressing content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham storms out after Gitmo clash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/22/lindsey-graham-storms-out-of-ketanji-brown-jackson-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lindsey Graham stormed out of the Senate hearing for Biden’s supreme court pick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypersonic missiles used due to low stockpile...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/22/russia-hypersonic-missiles-low-stockpile-00019358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leading theory in Western assessments of the hypersonic missiles attack is that Russia's number of precision-guided munitions are dwindling fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators mull unthinkable: Vlad detonating nuke...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/senators-mull-unthinkable-putin-detonating-nuclear-bomb-rcna21048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Marco Rubio, R-Fla., said such an attack could trigger NATO's Article 5, which requires a collective defense in the event of an attack on any member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol riot suspect wanted by FBI granted asylum in Belarus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/capitol-riot-suspect-wanted-by-the-fbi-is-granted-asylum-in-belarus/ar-AAVnAet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz presses on critical race theory in tense questioning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/599275-cruz-presses-jackson-on-critical-race-theory-in-tense-questioning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICAHN: 'Very well could be recession or even worse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/22/carl-icahn-says-there-very-well-could-be-a-recession-or-even-worse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founder and chairman of Icahn Enterprises said surging inflation is a major threat to the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jon Stewart says heads of news refuse to come on show to defend themselves...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1011636/jon-stewart-says-heads-of-news-divisions-refused-to-come-on-his-show-to-defend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Age for Armchair Generals...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awp9p/its-a-golden-age-for-armchair-generals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s easier than ever to get clout by being extremely online during a war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle students walk out of school, demand mandates be reinstated...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/education-lab/seattle-students-walk-out-of-school-demand-mask-mandates-be-reinstated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 Seattle students rallied at the school district's headquarters Monday, calling for a return to masking in school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China plans to open space station for tourism within decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/china-tiangong-space-station-tourism-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is encouraging commercial space tours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Outgunned Air Force Is Fighting Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-ukraine-s-outgunned-air-force-is-fighting-back-against-russian-jets/ar-AAVmcbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some complain of 'frostbite'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18032931/russian-soldier-complains-of-frostbite-and-victory-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN soldier has complained about his troops getting frostbite and meeting fierce Ukrainian resistance in an intercepted phone call. The dour trooper said conditions had become so bad that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Includes hedge fund manager, judge, NYC elites...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10639767/Sarah-Lawrence-sex-cult-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's business elite was left shaking in its boots Tuesday after a list of alleged clients of the student prostitute in the Sarah Lawrence 'sex cult' case was inadvertently published online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE WILLIAM AND KATE SWIM WITH SHARKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/4952855/prince-william-kate-diving-sharks-caribbean-tour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William and Kate have shared incredible snaps of their deep-sea dive with SHARKS as they enjoy their Caribbean tour. The Duke, 39, and Duchess of Cambridge, 40, got up close and pe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful 6.6 mag quake rattles Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/powerful-66-magnitude-earthquake-rattles-taiwan-1.1647972222329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quake shook buildings in the capital, Taipei</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belarusian military could 'soon' join war...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/22/europe/belarus-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US and NATO believe that Belarus could "soon" join Russia in its war against Ukraine, US and NATO officials tell CNN, and that the country is already taking steps to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors push to shut down newsroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/22/buzzfeed-investors-have-pushed-ceo-jonah-peretti-to-shut-down-newsroom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed's news organization has about 100 employees and loses roughly $10 million a year, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the ozone hole?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220321-what-happened-to-the-worlds-ozone-hole</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back in the 1990s, the hole in the planet's ozone layer was a pressing global crisis – if we had ignored it, today there would be several.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemists cook up way to remove microplastics using okra...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220322-chemists-cook-up-way-to-remove-microplastics-using-okra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extracts of okra and other slimy plants commonly used in cooking can help remove dangerous microplastics from wastewater, scientists said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE LOSSES, MORE CUTS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/22/buzzfeeds-mark-schoofs-reportedly-quits-as-losses-force-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The editor-in-chief of BuzzFeed News and two of his top deputies have reportedly resigned in the latest sign of turmoil at the cash-strapped company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER: APPLE NOW WORTH 11 DISNEYS!</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/big-tech-worth-apple-disney-trillion/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Big Five tech companies have valuations way, way higher than the major oil and media conglomerates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC stars get into wild brawl outside steakhouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4949530/colby-covington-jorge-masvidal-miami-street-fight-ufc-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BITTER UFC rivals Colby Covington and Jorge Masvidal were involved in a brawl at a Miami steak house – less than three weeks after their grudge match. The former best friends turned rivals cl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump STILL Not Using His Own Social Media App Month After Launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-is-still-not-using-his-own-social-media-app-a-full-month-after-its-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been a full month since its launch, and President Donald Trump has yet to post to his newly-unveiled social media platform, TRUTH Social.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KREMLIN LASHES OUT AT POLAND...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-lashes-out-at-poland-for-siding-with-ukraine-134545060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a blistering social media post, former Russian President Dmitry Medvedev, now a top Kremlin security adviser, lashed out at Poland for its support of Ukraine, reviving and escalating decades-long tensions between Moscow and Warsaw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PASSION: RESURRECTION':  Mel Gibson Magnum Opus...</title>
      <link>https://movieweb.com/the-passion-of-the-christ-resurrection-what-to-expect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;movieweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to actor Jim Caviezel, we're in store for Mel Gibson's magnum opus with The Passion of The Christ: Resurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad's superyacht faces seizure from Italian marina...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/03/22/a-superyacht-in-italy-is-said-to-belong-to-vladimir-putin-16319095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The yacht features two helipads, a gigantic pool and a self-playing piano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE PARTY NEEDS TO END'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-party-needs-to-end-miami-beach-police-union-tweets-about-spring-break-crowds/ar-AAVleiZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold, Covid or hay fever?</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/you-covid-cold-hay-fever-26528279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With symptoms of Covid-19, the common cold and hay fever overlapping, it can be hard to tell which you've got. Here health experts explain how to tell the difference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHURCH PROMOTES WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/christianworld/article-701967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opinion by Scott Kenworthy: Church-state history gives a clue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN TROOPS 'WILL RUN OUT OF FOOD IN THREE DAYS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4950994/russian-troops-running-out-of-food-three-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN troops are set to run out of food, fuel and ammunition in just three days and the war could be over in weeks, Ukraine has claimed. Ukraine’s Ministry of Defence said Russia’s ad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools nationwide quietly removing books from libraries...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Schools-nationwide-are-quietly-removing-books-17020176.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANCASTER, Pa. - Samantha Hull was on vacation when she got the call about the missing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book reveals frustrations between Biden, Harris camps...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/599181-new-book-reveals-frustrations-between-biden-harris-camps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upcoming book from two New York Times reporters reportedly reveals tensions between President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris's teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Top Editors to Leave BUZZFEED NEWS Ahead of Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/22/top-editors-to-leave-buzzfeed-news-ahead-of-newsroom-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of BuzzFeed News and two other top editors are departing the company ahead of cuts to the newsroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson faces pointed questions at Senate hearing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ketanji-brown-jackson-hearing-day-2-live-updates-219ce62acd87ca205163781f5b6623a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court nominee Ketanji Brown Jackson will face senators’ questions for the first time Tuesday as Democrats push to quickly confirm the only Black female justice in the court’s 233-year history. Live updates here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas multibillion-dollar border operation raises questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/local/dallas/2022/03/22/texas-border-operations-questions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation Lone Star costs taxpayers more than $2.5 million a week and is a cornerstone of Abbott’s gubernatorial race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hours-long lines seen at gas stations in Cuba amid economic crisis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/599166-hours-long-lines-seen-at-gas-stations-in-cuba-amid-economic-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours-long lines were seen at gas stations across Cuba on Monday as the country continues to face an economic crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to Build More Than 60 Makeshift Hospitals to Tackle Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-to-build-more-than-60-makeshift-hospitals-to-tackle-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China to Build More Than 60 Makeshift Hospitals to Tackle Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Holy Man Pushed for 'Eradication'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vladimir-putins-holy-man-russian-orthodox-patriarch-kirill-pushed-for-the-eradication-of-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Orthodox Patriarch Kirill appears to be just as bloodthirsty as Vladimir Putin himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny, Fiery Putin Critic, Given Additional 9-Year Prison Sentence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-europe-moscow-dbc03c1ada0f2c93e3cadc2657447c48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Imprisoned Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny is facing a lengthy prison term on top of the one he is already serving in a trial Kremlin critics see as an attempt to keep President Vladimir Putin’s most ardent foe in prison for as long as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine leader calls on Pope to mediate...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/ukraine-biden-flags-cyberattacks-says-073237158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskiy held talks with Pope Francis and called on the leader of the Catholic Church to mediate in the conflict, while Germany’s finance chief proposed a “Marshall Plan” to help Ukraine rebuild when the war ends.Most Read from BloombergChina Jet’s Nosedive From 29,000 Feet Baffles Crash SpecialistsXi Risks Leaving China Isolated by Backing Putin to Counter U.S.China Plane Crash Update: Wreckage Found, Airline Grounds JetsChina Eastern Boeing 737 Jet C</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
