<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Police detective divorces wife after she was photographed with another man at MAGA riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386187/Police-detective-divorces-wife-photographed-man-Capitol.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Heinl (left), 55, of Ross Township, Pennsylvania, was photographed inside the US Capitol building alongside Kenneth Grayson on January 6, the FBI alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after drone found with a bag of heroin on board...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-arrested-drone-found-bag-191047706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation is continuing to determine whether the suspect was using the drone to sell drugs, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321235557-he6bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAKISTAN-LGBT/MADRASA (TV, PIX):A transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI BEACH DECLARES EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-19-pandemic-miami-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-4c4ac71405e13f063e38dde30ef260d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Pointing to over 1,000 arrests in one of the nation’s top party spots, Miami Beach officials warned Sunday that the unruly spring break crowd gathering by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys indictment says group leaders used radios and encrypted chats to coordinate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/proud-boys-capitol-riot-coordination-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the men used paramilitary gear, handheld radios and encrypted messaging applications to coordinate with other Proud Boys before and during the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremists in police ranks spark growing concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/elections/2021/03/21/police-charged-capitol-riot-reignite-concerns-racism-extremism/4738348001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Racially biased policing was already a concern. Now, charges against officers in the Capitol riot inflame fears of extremists infiltrating law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global shortage in computer chips 'reaches crisis point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/mar/21/global-shortage-in-computer-chips-reaches-crisis-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer price rises loom while dearth of semiconductors slow production from Samsung to Ford</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH BEACH OVERRUN BY MASKLESS HORDES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/miami-beach-freaks-out-over-massive-spring-break-crowds-declares-state-of-emergency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time and time again during this pandemic, tourists are ruining everything,” a Miami Beach resident said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb's plan to pay Black residents reparations could be national model...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-race-reparations/chicago-suburbs-plan-to-pay-black-residents-reparations-could-be-a-national-model-idUSKBN2BD0B8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, in the Chicago suburb of Evanston, Cordelia Clark ran a restaurant out of her kitchen and parked cabs for her taxi company in her backyard because Black residents were effectively barred from owning or renting storefronts in town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  How 'Owning the Libs' Became GOP's Core Belief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/21/owning-the-libs-history-trump-politics-pop-culture-477203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weird journey of a tongue-in-cheek catchphrase from conservative-mocking putdown to the defining tenet of the Republican Party’s way of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican AGs take blowtorch to President's agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/21/gop-attorneys-general-biden-477365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On everything from climate change to immigration and abortion rights, GOP attorneys general are leading the charge to dismantle White House policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Vaccine Obsession Hasn't Swung Election to Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-vaccine-obsession-hasn-t-swung-election-to-him/ar-BB1eNCYc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine “world champions.” Israel’s “the first” to return to normal life. Other leaders in awe of Benjamin Netanyahu’s achievements in taming the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRAZENECA, once touted as a pandemic slayer, faces challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/astrazeneca-once-touted-as-a-pandemic-slayer-faces-challenges/ar-BB1eODgv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the stakes hadn’t been so high, the saga might have felt like a soap opera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biden's failure to contain the border surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/no-end-in-sight-inside-the-biden-administration-s-failure-to-contain-the-border-surge/ar-BB1eNeEh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration has emerged as one of the administration’s most urgent challenges — seized on by Republicans as a political cudgel, posing risks to Democrats in the 2022 midterms and potentially undermining Biden’s governing agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black leaders react to crackdown: 'Unnecessary force'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/black-leaders-react-to-south-beach-spring-break-curfew-crackdown-unnecessary-force/ar-BB1eOwEy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 21—After weeks of uninhibited partying on South Beach by spring breakers, police turned away throngs of people — many of them Black — from world-famous Ocean Drive with a SWAT truck, pepper balls and sound cannons. The tactics were intended to enforce an 8 p.m. curfew announced only hours earlier on Saturday to rid the city of what police and politicians have described as unruly and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company says ORAL covid vaccine on its way...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-company-says-oral-covid-19-vaccine-on-its-way-662712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oral vaccine could potentially allow for people to self vaccinate at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considering releasing illegals into USA without court date...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-rio-grande-valley-considering-releasing-migrants-into-u-s-without-court-date</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Fox News has learned from a senior source with Customs and Border Protection (CBP) that a plan is under consideration for Border Patrol agents in the Rio Grande Valley Sector (RGV) to begin releasing illegal border crossers who claim asylum without issuing a Notice to Appear (NTA) - meaning they will depart custody without a court date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN VOGUE staffer who supported editor's ousting used 'N-word' in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/senior-teen-vogue-staffer-mccammonds-ousting-used-n-word-in-decade-old-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Teen Vogue staffer who posted a letter expressing concern about Alexi McCammond for past tweets racist against Asian Americans used the N-word in tweets from over 10 years ago herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Germany police clash with protesters against new virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386215/Angela-Merkel-extends-Germanys-Covid-restrictions-month-despite-anti-lockdown-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters angry at Covid-19 restrictions rallied in cities across Europe over the weekend, even as several nations reimposed partial lockdowns to fight new surges in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT TEAMS MOVE IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9384843/Miami-Beach-unveils-curfew-uncontrollable-crowds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring breakers invading Miami Beach have become so uncontrollable that authorities imposed a curfew on Saturday as SWAT teams were seen moving in to clear people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad arrested after taking toddler into elephant enclosure at San Diego Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/21/us/san-diego-zoo-arrest-elephant-toddler/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A visitor at the San Diego Zoo was arrested on Friday shortly after taking his two-year-old daughter into an elephant enclosure, according to a press release from the San Diego Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 unaccompanied children in CBP custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/20/politics/unaccompanied-migrant-children-cbp/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more than 5,000 unaccompanied children in US Customs and Border Protection custody, according to documents obtained by CNN, up from 4,500 children days earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS: Govts 'to insist' on vaccines for flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-56460329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Governments are going to insist" on vaccines for international travellers, Qantas' boss tells the BBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Pilots Bumpy All-terrain Rig On Siberian Holiday...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/putin-pilots-bumpy-all-terrain-rig-on-siberian-holiday-01616327706?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, during a holiday in Siberia with Defence Minister Sergei Shoigu, piloted an all-terrain vehicle through thick woodland and traversed a swaying rope bridge, Kremlin footage showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSH FOR NEW NATIONAL HOLIDAY, 'EMANCIPATION DAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/national-holiday-emancipation-e9e8dc33-04e7-4390-a3bb-c1d867b3e036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a movement to create an official holiday, but not all supporters agree on the best date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/JanineStanwood/status/1373062537332293635?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid long-haulers still suffer extreme symptoms -- year later...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/20/these-covid-long-haulers-suffer-side-effects-a-year-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after getting COVID, these New Yorkers are still suffering shocking complications — forcing them to give up their jobs and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli court upholds school's barring of refusenik teacher...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321125834-n0iq2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-VACCINE (PIX):Israeli court upholds school's barring of COVID refusenik teacher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321113002-71rem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-MAFIA/ (PIX, TV):Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Springs military community works to address 'ideologies'...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/military/colorado-springs-military-community-to-address-extremism/article_effc1e48-839b-11eb-a6ee-03012c27f35d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spurred by the Jan. 6 storming of the U.S. Capitol, the military is taking a hard look at extremism in its ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infections continue to climb in Turkey amid relaxed measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-turkey-istanbul-coronavirus-pandemic-financial-markets-d501dffbb5a9cacedd28d81a3d60aa6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey’s weekly regional COVID-19 figures keep increasing and deaths rising as the country maintains more relaxed restrictions for now. The country's official death toll in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of 1 murder says he really killed 16...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-woodbury-new-jersey-new-mexico-missouri-tigers-mens-basketball-d2ac672be586e5332a7bc36e3b9e47c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODBURY, N.J. (AP) — A man charged with beating to death a New Jersey resident he says sexually abused him as a child now claims he has killed a total of 16 people, including his ex-wife and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON 'OUT INDEFINITELY'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nba-los-angeles-los-angeles-lakers-lebron-james-trae-young-d546428403947a7dbaf21a2b9ff983a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — LeBron James left in the second quarter with a high right ankle sprain that the Lakers said will sideline him indefinitely, and Los Angeles went on to fall 99-94 to the Atlanta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Married 66 years, husband, wife pass minutes apart of virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-florida-fort-lauderdale-lebanon-coronavirus-pandemic-ed9ea972b0ff037952a02aa864399043</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Bill and Esther Ilnisky spent nearly seven decades together as Christian ministers and missionaries, including stints in the Caribbean and Middle East before preaching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ties with Russia, China sink as Biden toes tough lines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-russia-vladimir-putin-china-national-security-550deda11d43e6bb7c1a8230ee8917ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. relations with its two biggest geo-political rivals are facing severe tests as President Joe Biden tries to assert America's place in the world and distinguish himself from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WAR WITHOUT END:   Defense chief arrives in Kabul on 1st trip to Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-afghanistan-lloyd-austin-ashraf-ghani-6d57e76434b146c6dfb93aeb208f3464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, on his first visit to Afghanistan as Pentagon chief, said Sunday that the Biden administration wants to see “a responsible end” to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama-era officials return to White House worth millions...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/obama-era-officials-return-white-house-worth-millions/story?id=76582015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As several Obama-era officials return to the White House under President Joe Biden, they're reuniting with fuller pockets according to new financial disclosure reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
