<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Unique and unprecedented'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/maguire-intelligence-committee-whistleblower-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting DNI says he didn’t forward a whistleblower complaint regarding Trump pressuring Ukraine because he needed clarification on executive privilege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley goes to Vatican to talk tech ethics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-technology-ethics/silicon-valley-goes-to-the-vatican-to-talk-tech-ethics-idUSKBN1WB1RP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican brought together Silicon Valley heavyweights, Nobel laureates and cy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Civil War: How 'SNL' Firing Exposed Growing Rift in Stand-Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/shane-gillis-snl-firing-comics-mixed-reactions-exposes-growing-rift-stand-up-world-1242739</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many cheered Shane Gillis' NBC dismissal four days after he was hired, a slice of the community sneered, revealing an increasing divide over what's legitimate envelope-pushing and what’s "just plain racist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Percentage of foreign-born U.S. residents highest in century...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-census-finds-22-1-100000352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The percentage of foreign-born U.S. residents has reached its highest level in more than a century, according to estimates from the 2018 American Community Survey released today.A record 44.7 million people are foreign-born, or about 13.7% of the U.S. population. That’s the highest rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramedics Save Man Suffering Heart Attack -- After Shocking Him 34 Times!</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/man-shocked-34-times-after-heart-attack-tells-his-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio man who had to be shocked 34 times to stabilize his failing heart is now sharing his near-death experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi murder 'happened under my watch,' Saudi crown prince tells PBS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190926050919-u090r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KHASHOGGI/:Khashoggi murder 'happened under my watch,' Saudi crown prince tells PBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fjrzu37-ljI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon presents this exclusive trailer for Martin Scorsese's The Irishman, starring Robert De Niro, Al Pacino, and Joe Pesci....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Moonves ouster, CBS seeks new programming direction...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/entertainment/article/A-year-after-Les-Moonves-ouster-CBS-seeks-a-new-14469665.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - The veteran producer looked at the priest in disbelief.  "Look, I agreed to give you 20 minutes so (a colleague) doesn't drop a Me Too bomb on me," said the producer.  "So you think you're vulnerable to Me Too?" said the priest.  The producer shook his head. "There's a reason Weinstein went down. I don't use sex. And I'm much more talented."  Then the director yelled cut.  The moment was part of a shoot on the much-anticipated new CBS show "Evil" - the priest was part of a trio investigating a slick entertainment boss for fostering a toxic work culture.  If that last part sounds familiar, it should. "Evil" debuts on a network that spent much of last year dogged by sexual-misconduct allegations against former chief executive Leslie Moonves along with accusations of sexual harassment on multiple sets.  That a CBS primetime series is willing to tackle an incisively modern issue - this incisively modern issue - offers a telling snapshot of just how new a moment the network is looking to create.  CBS launches its fall schedule this week - Thursday's "Evil" premiere is one of a half-dozen new series on the network with blockbuster dreams. But amid the traditional rollout of broadcast hopefuls is one of the trickier balances in modern TV. CBS must advance a diverse and socially conscious post-Moonves form of storytelling without abandoning the middle-of-the-road formula he rode to great success.  "Our goal is to figure out the next generation of shows and make some unexpected moves while still appealing to the core CBS audience," said David Nevins, CBS' chief creative officer and Moonves' programming successor. "We can broaden and we can be more surprising, but without alienating people."  CBS has been the most-watched broadcast network every year for the past 11 - meaning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Franco 'ZEROVILLE' worst film of year?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/sep/26/james-franco-zeroville-review-worst-film-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor-writer-director’s adaptation of Steve Erickson’s 2007 book on 70s Hollywood is a film of staggering incompetence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters react with joy, fury, ambivalence...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-09-25/what-do-voters-think-of-the-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do voters around the country think of the impeachment inquiry into President Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Outrage is a commodity': Director Todd Phillips bashes 'far left' criticism of 'JOKER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Outrage-is-a-commodity-Director-Todd-Phillips-14469623.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since debuting at the Venice International Film Festival earlier this month, "Joker," an R-rated supervillain origin story, has drawn both rave reviews and concerns over its realistic portrayal of a character sliding into a psychosis that leads him to kill.  The film's director, though, fiercely defended his film in a newly published interview, arguing that those worries are little more than the complaints of people looking for something to be angry about.  "I think it's because outrage is a commodity, I think it's something that has been a commodity for a while," director Todd Phillips told the Wrap in a Sept. 20 interview first published Wednesday. "What's outstanding to me in this discourse in this movie is how easily the far left can sound like the far right when it suits their agenda. It's really been eye-opening for me."  Though the film won the top prize in Venice and has been well reviewed before its Oct. 4 release in the United States, it has also stirred fears of gun violence and criticisms that the film glorifies the bloody action at the center of its plot. Some of that uproar has emerged after Phillips originally spoke to the Wrap.  This week, the families of those killed in a mass shooting at a Colorado movie theater in 2012 asked Warner Bros. to donate proceeds to groups supporting victims and urged Congress to pass bipartisan gun-control legislation. The theater in Aurora where the massacre took place during a screening of "The Dark Knight Rises" is refusing to show "Joker," a manager told The Washington Post.  On Sept. 18, a U.S. Army base in Oklahoma warned its service members that online threats had been made to target an unspecified theater during the "Joker" release, Christopher Grey, an Army Criminal Investigation Command spokesman, told The Post in a statement. A second memo sent Monday reiterated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first trans pro boxer face of iconic boxing brand EVERLAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/26/patricio-manuel-the-first-transgender-pro-boxer-represents-everlast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Dec. 12, 2018, Patricio Manuel made history, becoming the first transgender boxer to have a professional fight. On Sept. 26, he made history again when he was named the face of the iconic boxing brand Everlast. But the road to getting there wasn't easy, and Manuel had to risk everything he knew in order to achieve his dream of competing as a male boxer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPLAINT ALLEGES COVER-UP</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cce1f1146f924609912a032c61fd067c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A secret whistleblower complaint at the center of an impeachment inquiry alleges that President Donald Trump abused the power of his office to "solicit interference from a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: 13% trust media 'a great deal'...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/267047/americans-trust-mass-media-edges-down.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-one percent of Americans trust the mass media to report the news "fully, accurately and fairly," marking a four-percentage-point dip since last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO END IN SIGHT FOR 'RETAIL APOCALYPSE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/theres-no-end-in-sight-for-the-retail-apocalypse_09252019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers say Boris rhetoric stirs hate as rancor over Brexit intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Lawmakers-say-Johnson-s-rhetoric-stirs-hate-as-14469414.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON -A raw, noxious session of Parliament that left lawmakers expressing fears for their safety amid death threats has intensified Britain's national rancor over Brexit, while drawing from Prime Minister Boris Johnson a dismissive "humbug."  Johnson was rebuked by lawmakers on all sides for his language in a bombastic performance in the House of Commons on Wednesday night, when the prime minister used terms such as "betray" and "surrender" to describe opponents blocking his path for exiting the European Union.  Long-serving members, veteran journalists and British historians said they had never seen a more toxic session of Parliament than the one that unfolded after Johnson's return to the House of Commons, just a day after the Supreme Court ruled that the new prime minister's suspension of Parliament had been "unlawful."  After cutting short a trip to New York, where he attended the U.N. General Assembly and met with President Donald Trump, the prime minister delivered a statement to the House in which he apparently tried to goad opposition lawmakers into granting him an early election. Johnson called them "cowards." His opponents called him "unfit to serve" and shouted for his resignation.  But it wasn't just the jeering and sneering and clapping that prompted many observers to say it was one of the most extraordinary parliamentary sessions ever witnessed. It was Johnson's choice of words.  Several women lawmakers stood up in Parliament and pleaded with Johnson to moderate his language. Some pointed out the death threats they have received.  Opening Parliament on Thursday, Speaker John Bercow said that the atmosphere on Wednesday was "toxic" and "worse than any I have known in my 22 years in the House."  Bercow urged lawmakers to "treat each other as opponents, not as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-quarter GDP left at 2%; Slower growth seen persisting...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/second-quarter-us-gdp-left-at-2-downshifting-economy-unlikely-to-rev-up-soon-2019-09-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy grew more slowly in the second quarter, updated figures confirm, and is slow growth is expected to persist through the end of the year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARPER: NATIONALS Fans Crossed Line Heckling Me In Loss...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/09/26/bryce-harper-nationals-fans-crossed-line-while-heckling-him-in-phillies-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harper spurned the Nationals and signed a 13-year deal with the Phillies last offseason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Prices In CA Expected To Soar Past $4 Following Saudi Refinery Attack...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/gas-saudi-refinery-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of gas in Los Angeles jumped three cents Wednesday to $3.85 per gallon and was expected to pass the $4 mark in the next few days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAYS OUT OTHER DOCUMENTS AND WITNESSES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4204c450b9542058f0d7764e982dcb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats who reviewed a secret whistleblower complaint involving President Donald Trump Wednesday called it "deeply disturbing" and said it gives them new leads to pursue as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV cure? Scientists discover 'kill switch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10008045/hiv-cure-kill-switch-cells-reproducing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN HIV cure is a step closer after scientists found a molecular “kill switch” that stops infected cells reproducing. Lifelong drug treatment can prevent the virus leading to Aids — but it remains d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No drones, drinking or dissent: Beijing lays down law ahead of 70th anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/26/no-drones-drinking-or-dissent-china-lays-down-law-ahead-of-70th-anniversary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Beijing prepares to mark founding of PRC with a massive military parade, the Chinese leadership faces its most difficult chapter since 1989</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to Face Dems... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spy-chief-face-democrats-disturbing-080000957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The nation’s spy chief who delayed giving Congress a whistle-blower complaint about President Donald Trump will face tough questions from House Democrats on Thursday, an early glimpse of their newly intensified impeachment focus.Acting Director of National Intelligence Joseph Maguire will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap between haves and have-nots highest in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfa51032ee27470c9f908914328eea99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — The gap between the haves and have-nots in the United States grew last year to its highest level in more than 50 years of tracking income inequality, according to Census...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face masks to decoy t-shirts: The rise of anti-surveillance fashion...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190926043446-h9egt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artists and fashion designers are coming up with novel ways to stay private in public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacques Chirac, giant of French politics, dies at 86...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/jacques-chirac-giant-french-politics-101635410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former French President Jacques Chirac, a major force in French politics who opposed the 2003 US-led invasion of Iraq, died in Paris on Thursday at the age of 86. A seasoned politician, Chirac’s career included two presidential terms, two stints as prime minister and nearly two decades as mayor of Paris.Charming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECLASSIFIED -- HOW LONG SECRET?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/463135-whistleblower-complaint-declassified-on-eve-of-high-stakes-maguire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower complaint at the center of the political firestorm involving President Trump's contacts with Ukraine's leader has been declassified, a member of the House Intelligence Committee announced late Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese 'IRISHMAN' Images De-Age De Niro -- And It's Weird...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/irishman-movie-images-de-niro-de-aged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it only cost $159 million to do it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven-day scramble ends with big gamble... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-seven-day-White-House-scramble-ends-with-a-big-14468634.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After news broke that a phone call between President Donald Trump and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky was at the center of an explosive whistleblower complaint, Trump was largely undaunted.  But many of his senior advisers weren't nearly as confident, and an internal debate roiled the White House.  The notes from his call with the Ukrainian leader showed the conversation was not as "perfect" and "totally appropriate" as Trump had declared, and they warned him that sharing it might not be exculpatory. Two of his top Cabinet secretaries argued against disclosure, saying it would set a dangerous precedent to share details of a private phone conversation between two world leaders.  Yet on Wednesday morning - seven days after The Washington Post first reported the nature of the concerns raised by a whistleblower in the U.S. intelligence community and a day after House Democrats opened a formal impeachment inquiry into the president - the White House released a rough transcript of the call, part of a broad gamble by Trump that he could once again beat the forces arrayed against him.  "He didn't see anything wrong with the conversation he had with a foreign leader," said Rep. Mark Meadows, R-N.C., an ally of the president, referring to the call in which Trump offered his Ukrainian counterpart help from the Justice Department in investigating former vice president Joe Biden, a political rival.  The helter-skelter way the administration handled the aftermath of the whistleblower complaint could be a harbinger of the coming impeachment fight, with the White House scrambling to respond to a mercurial and frustrated president, who is increasingly sidelining his aides and making decisions based on gut instinct.  Even some allies of the president worry that his team may not fully understand the potential upheaval...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHISTLEBLOWER FIGHTS TO STAY ANONYMOUS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistle-blower-is-said-to-allege-concerns-about-white-house-handling-of-ukraine-call/ar-AAHR1Cn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAYS SECRET,  FOR HOW LONG?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-view-deeply-disturbing-whistleblower-complaint-about-trump/ar-AAHQCJR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors took newborn baby from parents after they refused vitamin K shot. Now they're suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-vitamin-k-shot-lawsuit-illinois-dcfs-20190924-4qxfsnq4yva5hni36b545yp3bi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More parents are refusing to have their newborn babies receive a vitamin K shot. Now several families the shot are suing after Illinois' child welfare agency investigated them for possible neglect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS GETS FIRST LOOK AT WHISTLEBLOWER COMPLAINT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/25/democrats-trump-whistleblower-complaint-1512968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schumer called for the report to be made public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges epitomize framers' idea of impeachable offense?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-actions-with-ukraine-epitomize-framers-idea-of-impeachable-offense-scholars-say/ar-AAHQe85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  VEGAS SUN Publisher Says Adelson Trying to Kill His Newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/money/vegas-sun-publisher-says-adelson-is-trying-to-kill-his-newspaper/ar-AAHQI2I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But fans the flames...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-tried-talk-way-impeachment-234936096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump tried to squelch the latest threat to his presidency with the release of a transcript of his call with Ukraine’s president. It’s a trick that’s worked for him before, allowing him to claim exoneration and take the attack to Democrats.Yet this time, the gambit backfired. Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favors, dirt, investigations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/favors-dirt-investigations-key-takeaways-193610286.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House released a summary of Trump’s call with Zelenskiy that lies at the heart of the impeachment inquiry  * Trump’s call with Ukraine’s president: read the full memoAccording to the summary, Trump said: ‘The United States has been very very good to Ukraine. I wouldn’t say it’s reciprocal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK unveils virtual social space...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-unveils-virtual-social-space-oculus-users-211924806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Horizon virtual world set for a beta launch in 2020 represents a new initiative for the Oculus virtual reality unit of the leading social network. Oculus users will be able to choose an avatar and interact with others in the virtual social community, Facebook said as it opened its Oculus Connect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All circumstantial evidence?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/plenty-impeachment-worthy-evidence-ukraine-174506756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- A White House memo recording Donald Trump’s July phone conversation with Volodymyr Zelenskiy is damning.Trump’s request that the president of Ukraine initiate a corruption investigation into Joe Biden and his son Hunter wasn’t incidental. On the contrary, it appears to have been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New UCLA institute will study kindness...</title>
      <link>http://newsroom.ucla.edu/releases/ucla-bedari-kindness-institute-humane-societies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsroom.ucla.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gift, from Jennifer and Matthew C. Harris, will support research on building more humane societies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: AI equal with human experts in medical diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/sep/24/ai-equal-with-human-experts-in-medical-diagnosis-study-finds </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research suggests AI able to interpret medical images using deep learning algorithm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting threat at 'JOKER' premiere spurs warning from Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/shooting-threat-at-joker-movie-premiere-spurs-warning-from-army-criminal-investigation-command-1.600375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Army Criminal Investigation Command memo issued Monday put commanders at Fort Sill, Okla., on notice regarding “disturbing and very specific chatter in the dark web” about a possible mass shooting during the Oct. 4 release of the new “Joker” movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICAN CRACKS EMERGE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-republicans-split-over-trump-urging-ukrainian-leader-to-investigate-biden/ar-AAHPJyl?li=BBnbcA0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acting DNI threatened to resign if he couldn't speak to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/acting-director-of-national-intelligence-threatened-to-resign-if-he-couldn-t-speak-freely-before-congress/ar-AAHQfnP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET -- FOR HOW LONG?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article235473167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain chip for soldiers to take out enemies with minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/brain-chip-created-soldiers-take-20168985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American scientists have developed a new 'brain-computer interface strip'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Lauer accusers to tell all in Ronan Farrow book...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/25/matt-lauer-sexual-harassment-accusers-to-tell-all-in-ronan-farrow-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of women with fresh claims of sexual harassment against Matt Lauer has spoken out for the first time to Ronan Farrow, The Post can reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS GETS LOOK AT WHISTLEBLOWER COMPLAINT...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/25/whistleblower-complaint-turned-over-to-select-members-of-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower complaint at the center of the latest standoff between President Trump and Beltway Democrats has been delivered to select members of Congress. Members of the Senate Intelligence C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark web chatter...</title>
      <link>https://io9.gizmodo.com/u-s-military-issues-warning-to-troops-about-incel-viol-1838412331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;io9.gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military has warned service members about the potential for a mass shooter at screenings of the Warner Bros. film Joker, which has sparked wide concerns from, among others, the families of those killed during the 2012 mass shooting in Aurora, Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/i-didnt-threaten-anybody-trump-calls-democratic-impeachment-push-a-joke/ar-AAHQ2Kp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Calls To Be Released...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-impeachment-inquiry-09-25-2019/h_d8bbf5577d0016c25ec63aa60c605a3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said the White House transcript that was released today was from the second call he had with Ukraine president Volodymyr Zelensky and that he would release the first phone call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Police Cruiser Runs Out Of Battery During Pursuit...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/fremont-police-tesla-out-of-electricity-pursuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla electric patrol car by the Fremont Police ran low on electricity in the middle of a pursuit, after the department said someone forgot to plug the vehicle into a charger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator: 'Really, Really Bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/sasse-foreign-involvement-in-u-s-elections-is-really-really-bad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska Republican senator Ben Sasse is reluctant to say much about allegations against Trump until Congress learns more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual health insurance costs hit record high above $20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/annual-health-insurance-costs-hit-record-high-above-dollar20000/ar-AAHPRKp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani goes on 24-hour cable news bender...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/867634</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of the totally incoherent, self-incriminating things Trump's lawyer said in the last day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy court rules assisted suicide not always crime...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-court-rules-assisted-suicide-not-always-crime-193627697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy's Constitutional Court on Wednesday ruled that it should not always be punishable to help someone "under intolerable physical and psychological suffering" to commit suicide. Anyone who "facilitates the suicidal intention... of a patient kept alive by life-support treatments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONTAGE:  Nobody Wants More Than Media...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/nobody-wants-impeachment-more-than-the-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Stormy Daniels to Robert Mueller to Ukraine, the media has hyped impeachment of Donald Trump throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST BUY sees growth in elderly health care tech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/122655ce0c5847268aa874e373e199d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The nation's largest consumer electronics chain, known for selling TV sets, cellphones and laptops, is looking to health care as a big source of its future growth. Best Buy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Meets Ukraine President Zelensky in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/09/25/trump-zelensky-meeting-comes-amid-impeachment-inquiry-over-ukraine/2438140001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump sits down with Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelensky, a meeting fraught with potential to be the most awkward he's has had with a foreign leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr thrust back in harsh glare...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/25/william-barr-ukraine-memo-1512255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scandal marks the latest example of whether Barr is prioritizing Trump’s interests over those of the Justice Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WjIIAOPeFQw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump holds a bilateral meeting with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky at UN General Assembly. FOX Business Network (FBN) is a financial news ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman behind French #MeToo movement fined for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c60602e6c3c493291118bb7e17b70a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A Paris court ruled on Wednesday that the woman who launched the French version of the #MeToo movement must pay 20,000 euros ($22,000) for defaming the man she accused of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrepentant Boris faces raucous Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/172e6d59ff044078865eef0e86679873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — An unrepentant Prime Minister Boris Johnson brushed off cries of "Resign!" and dared the political opposition to try to topple him Wednesday at a raucous session of Parliament, a day...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why immigration system is near collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/2019/09/23/immigration-crisis-migrants-us-mexico-border/2022670001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College student died in dorm room. Took months for anyone to notice...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-college-student-died-in-his-dorm-room-It-took-14466774.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rank odor from the end of the hallway had become too strong to ignore.  For nearly two months, it was faint enough that nobody at the University of Canterbury realized that a young man was dead, and decomposing, in his own room. Students left campus for two weeks of vacation, and returned, and still no one noticed anything.  But on Monday, police finally made it to the Sonoda dorm at the suburban campus outside Christchurch, New Zealand, where authorities discovered the body of a first-year student, local media reported. The student's father, who could not reach the young man through his friends, had also contacted police.  The young man's body had gone untouched for so long that police had to call in a special team to examine fingerprints, DNA and dental records so they could confirm his identity, Detective Senior Sgt. Craig Johnson told reporters. Most details surrounding the incident, including the student's name and age, had not been made public as of early Wednesday, and the coroner is still investigating the cause of death.  Amid an outcry from university students that's gone all the way up to New Zealand's education minister this week, a university is grappling with a grim question: How could a dead student go undiscovered for so long?  For now, no one really seems to know.  "It is inconceivable to imagine how these circumstances could have occurred," Cheryl de la Rey, the university's vice chancellor, said in a statement to The Washington Post.  De la Rey said Wednesday that the university will commission an independent investigation to examine the oversight, despite what she called an "extensive" well-being program to support students.  She declined to comment further to respect the family of the student. "This is an extremely distressing time for University...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School psychologist 'exploited' her role to rape student in classroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article235448657.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop who oversaw Harvey Weinstein probe under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/25/cop-who-oversaw-harvey-weinstein-probe-under-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NYPD sergeant who oversaw the Harvey Weinstein probe is the “focus” of an internal investigation into cops suspected of playing hooky and misusing official vehicles, law-enforcement …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ IT...</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/Unclassified09.2019.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whitehouse.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew role in Epstein scandal 'covered up by FBI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10000546/prince-andrew-epstein-paedo-fbi-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FORMER US cop claims the FBI may be helping cover up Prince Andrew’s alleged role in the Jeffrey Epstein sex abuse scandal. John Mark Dougan – who fled to Moscow following a raid by t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/classic-mob-shakedown-lawmakers-react-summary-trump-s-ukraine-call-n1058631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren, a leading Democratic presidential candidate, referred to the call as "a smoking gun."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel President Gives Netanyahu Mandate to Form Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Rivlin-meeting-with-Netanyahu-Gantz-602868</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Reuven Rivlin formally gave Netanyahu four weeks to form the government after a meeting at the President's Residence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Releases 3,000 'Deepfake' Videos So Researchers Can Learn To Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90409115/google-releases-trove-of-deepfake-videos-so-researchers-can-help-fight-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ll soon live in a world where you might now be able to tell if the video you are watching actually happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asked Ukraine president 'if you can look into' Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/25/trump-asked-ukraine-president-if-you-can-look-into-biden-and-his-son-in-phone-call.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The call with Zelensky is reportedly a central part of the whistleblower complaint that prompted Nancy Pelosi to support an impeachment inquiry against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Manhattan prosecutors face off in court over tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/25/judge-delays-trump-tax-returns-subpoena-by-manhattan-prosecutors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance Jr.'s office is investigating how the Trump Organization â€” President Donald Trump's company â€” recorded a hush-money payment made to porn star Stormy Daniels by Trump's former fixer Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate again votes to end Trump emergency declaration on border wall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/462983-senate-again-votes-to-end-trump-emergency-declaration-on-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate again voted on Wednesday to end President Trump’s emergency declaration on the U.S.-Mexico border wall, paving the way for a veto showdown with the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANSCRIPT RELEASED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/273e46e2fa324eb9ba5d69ab2a2c69cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump repeatedly prodded Ukraine's new leader to work with the U.S. attorney general and lawyer Rudy Giuliani to investigate Democratic political rival Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushed him to work with U.S. Attorney General Barr...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/transcript-trump-call-ukraine-includes-talk-giuliani-barr/story?id=65848768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transcript of a call President Donald Trump had in July with Ukraine's president includes talk of Rudy Giuliani and Attorney General Barr investigating Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICAN CRACKS EMERGE</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/senate-republicans-split-over-trump-urging-ukrainian-leader-to-investigate-biden/2019/09/25/48ec0e64-dfa6-11e9-be96-6adb81821e90_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Republicans were stunned by the revelations in the rough transcript the White House released Wednesday and questioned the decision to make it public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CREATES DEFENSE TASK FORCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trump-ive-done-nothing-wrong-creates-impeachment-defense-task-force</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first reaction to the release of phone call transcript between President Trump and the president of Ukraine that sparked new calls for impeachment hearings, Trump has declared that he did nothing wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANSCRIPT RELEASED</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-asked-ukraine-leader-phone-call-look-why-investigation-biden-n1058551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's phone call — made from the White House residence to Zelenskiy — lasted for 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Hip-Hop Competition Series Takes to Streets:  'This Ain't THE VOICE, Motherf*ka!"</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/09/25/rhythm-and-flow-trailer-netflix-hip-hop-cardi-b-chance-the-rapper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re looking for a nice, soothing, Norah Jones-ish singing competition to lull you to sleep… well, Rhythm + Flow ain’t it, OK?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT 2019</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a57d80e32904356874bbe090e159694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump repeatedly pushed Ukraine's president to open a corruption investigation into Democratic rival Joe Biden, according to a rough transcript of a phone call...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
