<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Israeli warplanes prepare for simulated attack on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10292027/Israeli-warplanes-prepare-simulated-attack-Iran.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drill will involve Israeli warplanes flying 600 miles over the Mediterranean to simulate the distance require to attack Iran's nuclear facilities, as talks with Tehran over its nuclear programme stall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS faces union test as worker votes counted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-buffalo-us-news-c7dc3c2ec8b838e9f4ed641f54fc9035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing effort to unionize Starbucks stores — despite company resistance — is facing its first major test. The National Labor Relations Board is scheduled to count ballots Thursday from union elections held at three separate Starbucks stores in the Buffalo, New York, area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California AG launches probe into police over racist texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/california-ag-launches-probe-police-department-allegations-racist-text-rcna8155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's attorney general has launched an independent review into a police department in Los Angeles County after allegations of 'racist' text messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES Beats TESLA to Hands-Free Driving on Autobahn...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/mercedes-beats-tesla-to-hands-free-driving-on-german-autobahn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercedes Beats Tesla to Hands-Free Driving on German Autobahn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Near 40-Year High Shocks Americans, Spooks Washington...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-near-40-high-shocks-120000359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. is poised to enter Year Three of the pandemic with both a booming economy and a still-mutating virus. But for Washington and Wall Street, one Covid aftershock is starting to eclipse almost everything else.Most Read from BloombergThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsAnatomy of a Bad RoadThe 15 Best Beers We Drank This YearFormer Oil Trader Is Now Betting on Lumber for SkyscrapersAl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence courting voters, activists in NH...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-elections-campaigns-capitol-siege-5177af3b3090defc022368d77d1ea0c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. (AP) — It had all the traditional trappings of a day on the presidential campaign trail. There was a fundraiser, time spent schmoozing with local activists, two holiday parties, a speech and a visit to a local bakery, where Mike Pence posed for pictures and bought a slice of cake for a driver who was celebrating her birthday while ferrying his staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate votes to scrap Biden order...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/senate-votes-to-scrap-biden-vaccine-mandate-as-republicans-eye-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legislative action is likely to further politicize the pandemic response, particularly as Republican leaders have struggled to quell vaccine misinformation and skepticism in their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Christmas Tree arson suspect free on no bail...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/fox-square-christmas-tree-arson-suspect-free-no-bail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 49-year-old suspect who was arrested Wednesday in connection with the alleged torching of a Christmas tree outside the New York City headquarters of Fox News and other News Corp. units has been freed on no bail, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flush with cash, states planning big cuts to taxes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/585020-flush-with-cash-states-planning-big-cuts-to-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — State lawmakers preparing to convene legislative sessions in the new year are confronted with a scenario unlike any they, or most of their predecessors, have ever experienced: budgets that are flush with cash after a year of record-set</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SHE TAKE STAND?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/09/will-ghislaine-maxwell-take-the-stand-in-sex-trafficking-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not long after prosecutors announce that they are resting their case in the trial of Ghislaine Maxwell, which could happen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed Journalists Reach Record High for Sixth Year...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/09/jailed-journalists-reach-record-high-for-sixth-year-in-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increased government intolerance of independent reporting pushed the number of imprisoned journalists worldwide to a record high of 293 this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Supply Chain Upheaval Became Life-or-Death Threat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/09/how-the-supply-chain-upheaval-became-a-life-or-death-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For much of this year, Joseph Norwood’s next breath was locked in a zero-sum competition with people eager to upgrade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Athlete's Blood Enhance Brainpower?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/08/can-an-athletes-blood-enhance-brainpower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if something in the blood of an athlete could boost the brainpower of someone who doesn’t or can’t exercise?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine makers racing to update shots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-coronavirus-vaccine-ea635d3e28d208ab1e4083537506bb99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine makers are racing to update their COVID-19 shots against the newest coronavirus threat even before it’s clear a change is needed, just in case. Experts doubt today’s shots will become useless but say it’s critical to see how fast companies could produce a reformulated dose and prove it works -- because whatever happens with omicron, this newest mutant won’t be the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows sues Pelosi as Jan. 6 panel moves against him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/08/meadows-sues-pelosi-jan-6-select-panel-523968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's former chief of staff has claimed he can’t discuss matters that could be covered by executive privilege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negative covid result needed for international travel. But can cost more than flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/coronavirus-tests-are-needed-for-international-travel-but-they-can-cost-more-than-a-flight/ar-AARDSud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In need of baby boom, China clamps down on vasectomies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-need-of-a-baby-boom-china-clamps-down-on-vasectomies/ar-AARDlgL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work From Home Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-issues-work-from-home-guidance-to-curb-omicron-in-u-k/ar-AARC91G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Building up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.koin.com/news/environment/earthquakes/swarm-of-earthquakes-recorded-off-oregon-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (KOIN) – Upwards of 60 earthquakes have been recorded off the Oregon coast – starting Tuesday and continuing through Wednesday. The quakes occurred along the Blanco Fault Zone …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Swarm of 60 quakes rattles northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/10-earthquakes-occur-off-oregon-coast/FYF7U67QQJCTRPYHTYWQDGQEM4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-six earthquakes were recorded Tuesday into Wednesday off the Oregon coast, the largest reaching magnitude-5.8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand bans cigarettes for next generation to stub out smoking...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-59589775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No New Zealander born after 2008 will be able to buy tobacco under proposed new health laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body pulled from submerged car above falls in Niagara rescue attempt...</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/person-pulled-from-car-submerged-at-brink-of-niagara-falls/article_0d083f24-5850-11ec-b1d6-ff1659596882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rescue attempt ended with the somber news that the woman in the vehicle was already dead before the diver was lowered by helicopter to the vehicle, opened the passenger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/hillary-clinton-chokes-up-as-she-reads-parts-of-the-victory-speech-she-hoped-to-deliver-in-2016/3440944/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, Hillary Clinton is sharing the speech she would have made if she had won the 2016 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plumber who found cash and checks in toilet wall of Joel Osteen's church is rewarded $20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/plumber-who-found-cash-and-checks-in-toilet-wall-of-joel-osteen-e2-80-99s-church-is-rewarded-2420000/ar-AARC9aK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary delivers victory speech that never was...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-the-first-time-hillary-clinton-publicly-delivers-the-victory-speech-she-would-have-given-in-2016/ar-AARCvuA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packs of thieves targeting San Fran area cannabis businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/oakland-cannabis-business-hit-twice-in-back-to-back-burglaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oakland marijuana delivery service is the latest in the Bay Area's cannabis industry to be hit by a gang of thieves. They struck Presto Canna in the city's Fruitvale neighborhood, not once, but twice this week, in back to back days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett Jury Goes Home With No Verdict As Prosecutors Claiming 'Overwhelming' Proof Of Faked Attack...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/jussie-smollett-verdict-jury-trial-hate-crime-empire-1234887442/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though prosecutors said there was “overwhelming” evidence that Jussie Smollett staged an assault on himself in late January 2019, there will be no verdict today in the ex-Empire star’s trial. After…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Failure Revealed In Secret CDC Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/danvergano/covid-test-false-positive-failure-cdc-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigation records obtained by BuzzFeed News show how one of the most pivotal mistakes of the pandemic fell on an overburdened CDC lab with only three full-time employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancun tourists flee beach after 5 on jet skis open fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4233704/tourists-flee-holiday-hotspot-gunmen-jet-skis-open-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOURISTS scrambled for cover after gunfire broke out on a beach at the family-friendly Mexican resort in Cancun. Five attackers pulled up to the beach outside the four-star Oasis Palm hotel on jet …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Married in the Metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/08/getting-married-in-the-metaverse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traci and Dave Gagnon met in the cloud, so it only made sense that their wedding took place in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERIES MAY NEVER BE SOLVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4233002/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-relationship-pregnancy-ranch-frozen-penis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein’s strange relationship has been in the spotlight during her sex trafficking and abuse trial. One of the mysteries that’s emerged is a claim by one of Max…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians outraged by sperm-smuggling drama film...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/palestinians-outraged-by-sperm-smuggling-drama-film-688186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:   Prosecution Fumbling Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/12/the-prosecution-is-fumbling-its-case-against-ghislaine-maxwell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say they plan to rest their case against Jeffrey Epstein’s associate by week’s end—a shocking move from a team that appears to have failed on a number of other fronts already.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George W. Bush victim of Havana Syndrome?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10288759/George-W-Bush-Havana-Syndrome-G-8-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intriguing new report on Wednesday suggests that former President George W. Bush could have been a victim of Havana Syndrome when he fell ill at a G8 conference in Germany in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee crisis in Central America fuels record exodus north...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coffee-crisis-central-america-fuels-120809292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four sons of María Bonilla and Esteban Funes all embarked on the treacherous journey north, one of them aged 10, preferring the life of an unauthorized migrant in America to a coffee farmer in Central America. Coffee doesn't pay for many of the hundreds of thousands of Central American farmers who produce the delicate arabica beans for the world's finest grounds. Increasingly, they are giving up, becoming part of a broader migrant flow to the U.S.-Mexico border that U.S. data shows has hit a record high this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of camels barred from 'beauty' contest over Botox...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/12/8/dozens-of-camels-barred-from-saudi-beauty-contest-over-botox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organisers say they will impose strict penalties on ‘manipulators’ as they attempt to halt ‘all acts of tampering’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury begins deliberations in Smollett case...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/jury-begins-deliberating-in-jussie-smollett-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors in the Jussie Smollett trial began deliberating Wednesday over whether he staged a race-hate attack on himself and then lied to cops about being the victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alt-Jihad' Rising On Socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/alt-jihad-rising-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The playbook of the “alt-right” is guiding a new generation of fringe jihadists, showing just how complicated extremism is about to become online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Moves Step Closer to Geoengineering Oceans...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/were-a-step-closer-to-geoengineering-the-oceans-1848179300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Academy of Sciences released a major report chronicling six techniques to turn the oceans into carbon dioxide vacuums.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Man Has Watched Hundreds of Executions. Now He's Next...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93ba3a/oklahoma-executions-bigler-stouffer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bigler Jobe Stouffer has spent 36 years on death row in Oklahoma and witnessed 133 executions. Now, it's his turn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends account providing updates...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/twitter-account-ghislaine-maxwell-trial-suspended</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twitter account that closely monitored the trial of former Jeffrey Epstein partner Ghislaine Maxwell Epstein was suspended on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  Extramarital sex sins NOT that 'serious'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/pope-says-extramarital-sex-sins-arent-that-serious/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Sins of the flesh are not the most serious,” the 84-year-old religious leader said. Top transgressions instead include pride and hatred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest lab-grown steak unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/dec/08/worlds-largest-lab-grown-steak-unveiled-by-israeli-firm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MeaTech 3D created the 4oz steak using 3D printing with real bovine cells that mature into muscle and fat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person pulled from car submerged at brink of Niagara Falls...</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/person-pulled-from-car-submerged-at-brink-of-niagara-falls/article_0d083f24-5850-11ec-b1d6-ff1659596882.html#tracking-source=home-top-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dark-colored compact vehicle was roughly 100 feet from the brink and about 30 feet from the edge of land in the park. It was mostly submerged in the river</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems begin souring on mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/west-wing-playbook/2021/12/07/dems-begin-souring-on-vaccine-mandates-495358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary SOBS as she reads '16 victory speech that never was...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10288375/Hillary-Clinton-gets-tearful-reads-speech-given-won-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton revealed the victory speech she would have given had she won that year, and admitted she did not even bother to write a concession speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How US Military Could Mobilize If Russia Invades Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/12/08/how-us-military-could-mobilize-if-russia-invades-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. paratroopers landing in the Baltics, Army cavalry and artillerymen convoying in from Germany and an armored brigade massing its forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Top Gun' Training Aims to Keep China at Bay...</title>
      <link>https://insidesources.com/can-top-gun-training-give-u-s-taiwan-leverage-to-keep-china-at-bay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insidesources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was an image that got the Pentagon’s attention: Satellite photos of targets shaped like an American aircraft carrier and at least two Arleigh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California to be abortion sanctuary if Roe overturned...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-plans-to-be-abortion-sanctuary-if-Roe-16685072.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — With more than two dozen states poised to ban abortion if the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland PM sorry for clubbing after virus contact...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59577371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanna Marin went on a night out on Saturday, hours after her foreign minister had tested positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods announces return to golf...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/tiger-woods-announces-golf-return-10-months-after-horrific-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods announced Wednesday that he will participate in the upcoming PNC Championship with son Charlie, less than a year after a horrific car wreck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2 million quit jobs in October...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2021/12/08/october-employees-quitting-jolts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high quits numbers are a reflection of what is perhaps the most worker friendly climate in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels Hiring Kids to Be Hitmen...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/jgmpmy/mexico-drug-cartels-recruit-children-to-kill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend of children and teens being recruited to kill by the cartels is widespread in Mexico, and the government is struggling to prevent or stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell gives Epstein foot massage in never-before-seen pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4229772/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-foot-massage-relationship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CREEPY pictures have emerged showing Ghislaine Maxwell giving Jeffrey Epstein a foot massage. The never-before-seen images reveal the intimate relationship between the 59-year-old socialite and the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Hollywood wants to become Amsterdam of far West...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/west-hollywood-wants-to-become-amsterdam-of-the-far-west-jay-z-seems-to-approve/ar-AARBIb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 40 quakes in 24 hours causing buzz in northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/08/weather/earthquake-swarm-oregon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of North America's most active fault lines sprung to life on Tuesday after a swarm of more than 40 earthquakes -- ranging from a magnitude 3.5 to 5.8 -- rattled off the coast of Oregon, catching the attention and concern of millions in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Tiniest Camera -- Size Of Grain Of Salt!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tiniest-camera-grain-of-salt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of tiny devices could cover the whole surface of a smartphone to become one giant camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BLOOD IN LA: Brazen assault in middle of day leaves boy dead, neighborhood shaken...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/brazen-assault-in-the-middle-of-the-day-leaves-a-boy-dead-a-neighborhood-shaken/ar-AARBAyg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments set in Smollett trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jussie-smollett-entertainment-lifestyle-arts-and-entertainment-crime-644f875e61b3ea9c7e8eefd1c227bf91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Closing arguments are scheduled for Wednesday morning in the case against former “Empire” actor Jussie Smollett, who is accused of staging a racist, anti-gay attack against himself in downtown Chicago to get publicity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
