<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Election crackdown runs into speed-tweeting human 'bots'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06efed5ede4d461fb2eac5b2c89e3c11/Election-crackdown-runs-into-speed-tweeting-human-'bots'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Nina Tomasieski logs on to Twitter before the sun rises. Seated at her dining room table with a nearby TV constantly tuned to Fox News, the 70-year-old grandmother</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's largest wildfire surges...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180804160626-bewyg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's California wildfire season has been more destructive than in years past</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Obama take on president?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/08/04/obama-step-up-midterm-elections-but-mostly-avoid-trump/889411002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama will increase his presence ahead of November elections but Democratic insiders predict he is unlikely to take on Trump more directly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert E. Lee statue vandalized in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/robert-e-lee-statue-vandalized-richmonds-monument-ave-151453658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A statue of Confederate Gen. Robert E. Lee on Richmond's famed Monument Avenue has been vandalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's worst political nightmare? Dems with subpoena power...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-s-worst-political-nightmare-Democrats-with-13131981.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A Democratic takeover of either chamber of Congress stands to set off investigations into President Donald Trump and his personal finances, members of his family, and senior administration officials, an onslaught that raises the stakes for the midterm elections. While some Democrats have pressed for Trump's impeachment, what would be certain is that Democratic committee chairs would swamp Trump and his deputies with subpoenas, document requests and public hearings that would bog down his administration and distract from his agenda ahead of the 2020 elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rainbow Wave? More Gay Candidates Running Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/04/us/politics/gay-candidates-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record number of lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgender candidates are running for office in November, as the Trump administration and state-level politicians have moved to roll back some legal protections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTLAND TENSE: FEARS OF BLOODSHED AT RALLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fears-violence-ahead-us-far-rally-155147050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Portland, Oregon braced for violence at a rally Saturday by two far-right groups that has raised fears of a replay of last year's deadly "Unite the Right" protests in Charlottesville, Virginia. "It is particularly troubling to me that individuals are posting publicly their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metro Considers Separate Trains for Opposing Groups for DC 'Unite the Right' Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Metro-Planning-for-Unite-the-Right-Rally-490010251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metro is considering providing separate trains for opposing groups when demonstrators come to Washington, D.C., for a 'Unite the Right' rally Aug. 12, Metro Board Chairman Jack Evans said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FRIDAY NITE TWITTER BLITZ:  LEBRON, DRUDGE, ECONOMY...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-blasts-dumbest-man-on-television-don-lemon-lebron-james-dianne-feinstein-in-late-night-tweet-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INTENT TO ACT VIOLENTLY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kgw.com/article/news/local/we-dont-want-this-here-mayor-warns-against-violence-at-portland-rally/283-580137841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kgw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are reminding demonstrators that weapons are not allowed in city parks, and acts of violence will lead to immediate arrest during Saturday's Patriot Prayer rally and counter-protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 Emergency: Call Centers Can't Find Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/911-emergency-call-centers-cant-find-workers-1533398401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities across the U.S. are struggling to find 911 dispatchers as a historically tight labor market makes it harder to fill a job that was already a tough sell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate rages over Trump tweets and obstruction...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/400309-debate-rages-over-trump-tweets-and-obstruction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump may have given special counsel Robert Mueller a new gift this week: tweets that could help build an obstruction of justice case against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTTEST DAY EVER?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/04/europe-faces-hottest-day-ever-temperatures-soar-48c-7797463/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dangerous temperatures are expected to hit Spain and Portugal this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi confuses millions, billions, trillions...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/pelosi-confuses-millions-billions-trillions-has-trouble-saying-debilitating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it any wonder the U.S. government has a $21.3 trillion debt when politicians can’t tell the difference between a number with 6 zeros and one with 12? Nancy Pelosi made an appearance this week at San Francisco’s Mission Neighborhood Health Center, and during a brief media appearance afterward, she confused millions with billions with …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judged sued over refusal to OK trans teens' new names...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcpo.com/news/local-news/warren-county/parents-of-three-transgender-teens-sue-warren-county-judge-to-allow-name-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcpo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of three minor trangender teens  are suing a Warren County judge to allow their children to change their legal names from female to male. The parents claim that Probate and Juvenile Court Judge Joe Kirby discriminates against transgender minors in refusing to allow them to select a name that reflects their gender identity. The plaintiffs in the suit, filed last month include  the parents of two transgender teens Kirby has already ruled against, as well</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Shortage BIG Problem for Small Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/labor-shortage-single-biggest-problem-small-businesses-record-37-report </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands expected to protest contentious Israel nation bill...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6026519/Thousands-expected-protest-contentious-Israel-nation-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) - Organizers of a protest against contentious Israeli legislation that critics say sidelines the non-Jewish population expect tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
'Tough guys' urged to audition for new Mark Wahlberg movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/entertainment/movies/2018/08/tough_guys_urged_to_audition_for_new_mark_wahlberg_movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON — Mark Wahlberg is looking for a few tough guys to appear in his latest movie.         Boston Casting says auditions will be held Saturday at its offices in the city's Allston neighborhood, and it's encouraging "real people" with "tough faces" to answer the call.The company says it's looking for construction workers, blue collar workers, public works workers, "fishermen, mob guys, etc.," for speaking roles and on-camera extras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran protesters attack religious school as tensions mount...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180804-iran-protesters-attack-religious-school-fars-news-agency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German politician starts new leftist 'movement'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/18266e0f4acd4742ad5f4dcd344e911d/German-politician-starts-new-leftist-'movement'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — One of Germany's most prominent left-wing politicians on Saturday launched a self-styled new "movement" that she says is aimed at reviving the fortunes of the countr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael boyfriend Fadi Fawaz says 'George I hate you' in rambling rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/6941365/george-michaels-boyfriend-fadi-fawaz-says-george-i-hate-you-in-rambling-twitter-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s boyfriend Fadi Fawaz appeared to tweet “George I hate you” in several rambling social media posts. The tweet came after it was revealed the late superstar left no…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melted asphalt, shoes for dogs: Europe wilts in heat...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180804-melted-asphalt-shoes-dogs-europe-wilts-heat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Lula launches presidential candidacy from prison...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180804-brazil-lula-launches-presidential-candidacy-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even behind bars, Brazil's Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva will secure his leftist party's nomination Saturday and continue to overshadow more likely candidates in the country's most unpredictable presidential election for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portugal battles wildfire, power outage...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180804110214-r069f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-WEATHER/ (PIX, GRAPHIC):At peak of European heatwave, Portugal battles wildfire, power outage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hector vs. Kilauea: Hurricane on track to skirt past Hawaii's erupting volcano...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180804031256-jw0rt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAWAII-VOLCANO/HURRICANE (PIX):Hector vs. Kilauea: Hurricane on track to skirt past Hawaii's erupting volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Injured From Flaming Cocktail at Vegas Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/two-injured-by-cocktail-at-gordon-ramsays-vegas-restaurant-1132230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drink in question is a flaming tiki-style cocktail called Rum Donkey with ingredients such as Cruzan Single Barrel Rum, falernum, brown sugar, ginger beer and torched passion fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Virus Cripples IPhone Chipmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/08/04/tsmc-takes-emergency-steps-as-operations-hit-by-computer-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSMC, the world’s largest contract chipmaker, had contained the problem and found a solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Godfather of GMOs Wants Consumers to Be Less Afraid of His Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/04/godfather-of-gmos-wants-consumers-to-be-less-afraid-of-his-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Godfather of GMOs Wants Consumers to Be Less Afraid of His Food</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on 'right-hand man'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/eyes-hand-man-manafort-trial-resumes-57028185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bookkeeper said Paul Manafort submitted fake financial documents. The accountant testified he hid foreign bank accounts. And a series of businessmen said he used international wire transfers to pay for millions of dollars in luxury items. On Friday, a tax preparer even admitted that she...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Hector Hawaii Threat?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-08-01-threat-tropical-storm-hurricane-hector-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Hector could be a threat to Hawaii next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rappers ordered held in custody for month pending trial after airport brawl...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-france-rappers-court/celebrity-rappers-ordered-held-in-custody-for-a-month-pending-trial-after-french-airport-brawl-idUKKBN1KP0B6 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French judges ruled on Saturday that two celebrity rappers should be held in custody ahead of their trial in a month's time following a brawl in the departure lounge of a Paris airport earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange in 'solitary confinement' at embassy, fears possible extradition to USA...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/assange-solitary-confinement-embassy-fears-extradition-us-lawyer/story?id=57018760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer for Wikileaks publisher Julian Assange talks to ABC News about her client's feared extradition to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Canada's Grocery Carts, Boycott USA Movement Starts Rolling...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-canadas-grocery-carts-a-boycott-u-s-a-movement-starts-rolling-1533384001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadians irked by U.S. metals tariffs and President Trump’s harsh words for their prime minister are boycotting American products and buying Canadian goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Tattoos Go Mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/blink-and-you-won-t-miss-it-face-tattoos-go-mainstream/17746101/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Chicago Tattoo &amp; Piercing Co., which has been in business in that city since 1973, the employees have a name for tattoos on the hands, neck and face. “We call them job stoppers,” said Joel Jose Molina, a tattoo artist at the shop. “Your possibilities are cut down. You’re going to be working at the Trader Joe’s putting groceries away or working that bar job.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cosmic orgasm': Rise of conscious breathing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/aug/04/cosmic-orgasm-rise-of-conscious-breathing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You do it more than 23,000 times a day, but are you breathing properly? From a rebirthing session to holotropic breathwork, Richard Godwin inhales the latest wellness craze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right, antifa prepare to face off; Portland braces for violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/72be678fb5a748c388128269a10f24f4/Portland-prepares-for-right-wing,-anti-fascist-rallies </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Portland, Oregon, is bracing for what could be another round of violent clashes between a right-wing group and self-described anti-fascist counterprotesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump bashes Lebron, CNN Lemon in late-night tweet...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/04/trump-tweet-slams-lebron-james-don-lemon-over-cnn-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump responded by Twitter on Friday night to a CNN anchor's recent interview with an NBA superstar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India's human-elephant war deadly for both sides...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/south-asia/article/2158106/indias-growing-population-draws-elephants-and-humans-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian government told parliament last year that 1,100 people had been killed in the previous three years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab-grown lungs transplanted into pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencenews.org/article/scientists-transplant-lab-grown-bioengineered-lungs-pigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencenews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pigs implanted with lab-grown lungs recovered from surgery with no breathing problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Production of 'DIARY OF ANNE FRANK' Replaces Nazis with ICE Agents...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/08/03/l-a-production-of-the-diary-of-anne-frank-replaces-nazis-with-ice-agents-hunting-for-latinx-illegals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A modernized theatrical production of The Diary of Anne Frank in Los Angeles Replaces Nazis with ICE agents and Jews with LatinX Illegals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Flotillas of Putrid Seaweed...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/massive-flotillas-of-putrid-seaweed-washing-up-in-caribbean-and-s-florida-threaten-beaches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn of the potential for ecological and socioeconomic disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTTEST DAY EVER?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/03/today-could-be-the-hottest-day-in-the-history-of-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LISBON — Temperatures in Spain and Portugal soared to near-record highs Friday as part of Europe’s heat wave, and governments put emergency services on alert for forest fires. Iberia’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accountant concedes wrongdoing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/03/paul-manafort-trial-2018-761300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They never told us about any income deposited in foreign accounts,“ Manafort's accountant told jurors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds line up for gushing West Texas oil jobs...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/hundreds-line-gushing-west-texas-oil-jobs-171815372--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Liz Hampton ODESSA, TEXAS (Reuters) - Job fairs are stocked with people hungry for better opportunities, but inside the MCM Grande Hotel in Odessa, Texas, oil services giant Halliburton is the one doing the wooing. “We need to hire you is our message,” said Chris Redman, a field services manager</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK fakers get better at covering tracks...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/facebook-fakers-better-covering-tracks-security-experts-173944965--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Christopher Bing WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Creators of fake accounts and news pages on Facebook are learning from their past mistakes and making themselves harder to track and identify, posing new challenges in preventing the platform from being used for political misinformation, cyber security experts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris races to define herself before opponents do...</title>
      <link>http://www.postbulletin.com/news/politics/kamala-harris-challenge-in-a-presidential-bid-defining-herself-before/article_85fffd2f-64c7-59c7-a939-9bd33f1c9cdd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Shortly after she won a seat in the U.S. Senate in 2016, Kamala Harris said she expected to follow the traditional freshman lawmaker playbook: “Listen and watch, and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media firms could face deathmatch for survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/31/media-firms-could-face-a-deathmatch-for-survival.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ultimate prize for Disney's bid for Fox is competitive scale and superior content for the coming war over internet streaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUROPE ON BROIL!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6938664/europe-hottest-day-spain-portugal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE is braced for its hottest day since records began today with temperatures likely to soar above the 118F high set 40 years ago. Thousands of Brit holidaymakers and expats in Spain and Portuga…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Cory Booker Rants About Gaining 'Wisdom' From 'Moons'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/03/cory-booker-america-savagely-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA TROUBLE$: May Be 'Unable to Exist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/nra-financial-trouble-706371/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new legal filing by the powerful gun group against the state of New York paints a grim picture</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
