<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Norway Eases Measures as It Prepares to Live With Virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2022/01/13/covid-19-spike-felt-across-europe-as-vaccination-remains-stagnant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's a round-up of the COVID situation across Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses Strike Across Nation to Protest Working Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/health-care/were-overwhelmed-nurses-strike-across-us-protest-covid-working-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago protest, organized by National Nurses United, a labor union boasting 175,000 members nationwide, was part of a day of action across 11 U.S. states and Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Targets Your Side Hustle in Crackdown on Transactions Over $600...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/uncle-sam-wants-a-piece-of-your-side-hustle-in-irs-crackdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRS Targets Your Side Hustle in Crackdown on Transactions Over $600</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish diocese apologizes for asking if sex abuse victim is gay and if he enjoyed sex encounters with priest...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/polish-diocese-apologizes-asking-sex-015500348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Catholic diocese in Poland has apologized for asking the court whether a man who was sexually abused by a priest as a young boy was gay and whether he might have enjoyed the sexual encounters. Janusz Szymik, 48, was an altar boy when the abuse began in the 1980s. Last year he sued the diocese of Bielsko-Zywiec, in southern Poland, in a civil court claiming that a priest in a local church had ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot mic on internet livestream catches judge viciously ridiculing attorney...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hot-mic-internet-livestream-catches-183800642.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cook County judge this week was caught on a YouTube livestream mocking an attorney who had appeared before him for arguments earlier in the day. “Can you imagine waking up next to her every day? Oh, my God,” Judge William Raines said of attorney Jennifer Bonjean. “... I couldn’t have a visual on that if you paid me.” A link to the video of Tuesday’s livestreamed court call was available for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henry Kaufman, 1970s Wall Street Dr. Doom, Blasts Powell on Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/henry-kaufman-1970s-wall-street-183629857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Henry Kaufman is one of the rare Wall Street veterans who can authoritatively draw parallels between the inflation scare of the 1970s and today’s alarming run-up in prices. And he has zero confidence Chair Jerome Powell’s Federal Reserve is ready for the battle it now faces. Most Read from BloombergCannabis Compounds Prevented Covid Infection in Laboratory StudyFrequent Boosters Spur Warning on Immune ResponseSupreme Court Blocks Biden’s Shot-or-Test Rule for WorkersSay Goodbye to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of Cuba, Venezuela deployment if tensions mount...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-moscow-473d4b2eebff4dc59d8e7dff9e8653ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia raised the stakes Thursday in its dispute with the West over Ukraine and NATO's expansion when a top diplomat refused to rule out a military deployment to Cuba and Venezuela if tensions with the United States escalate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  'Kingmaker' Trump heads to rural Arizona, where candidates are eager for his backing...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2022/01/13/kingmaker-trump-heads-to-rural-arizona-where-gop-candidates-are-eager-for-his-backing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans scored victories last year with Donald Trump on the sidelines. But GOP candidates in Arizona are jockeying for his support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The strange case of the casino, the Senate leader and the defense bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2022/01/12/the-strange-case-of-the-casino-the-senate-leader-and-the-defense-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Schumer-Graham casino amendment’s inclusion in the fiscal 2022 NDAA is an example of two Washington truisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keepers founder charged with seditious conspiracy in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/oath-keepers-leader-charged-with-seditious-conspiracy-in-jan-6-investigation/ar-AASL6K0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers brutally beat DELTA worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/delta-airlines-security-officer-brutally-attacked-at-jfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Long Island women are accused of assaulting a Delta Air Lines security officer at JFK who was hit with his own radio, punched in the face, and kicked. Another airline employee was also injured in the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina surpasses single-day record for hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.eagletribune.com/region/north-carolina-surpasses-single-day-record-for-covid-19-cases-hospitalizations/article_cda9e957-9b4d-5296-9281-24e1fff876f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eagletribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. — North Carolina's saw its COVID-19 numbers continue their week-long soar Thursday, breaking records for both single-day reports and hospitalized patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds used encrypted SIGNAL messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/13/feds-say-they-used-encrypted-messages-to-charge-oath-keepers-leader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unclear how investigators gained access to the messages, but encryption has been a point of tension between law enforcement and tech for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Playoff game will be among the most frigid in NFL history...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/sports/bills-patriots-playoff-game-will-be-among-coldest-in-nfl-history/1125138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a handful of games in post-season history have been played in weather colder than the matchup set to take place in Buffalo. Here's how one of the NFL's most rabid fanbases prepares for the unforgiving conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE FAIL:  Biden's hopes for voting rights bill dashed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-joe-biden-voting-elections-wv-state-wire-28fce7f5190404f5091158c912bf8d5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — All but acknowledging defeat, President Joe Biden said Thursday he’s “not sure” the Democrats' major elections and voting rights legislation can pass Congress this year. He spoke at the Capitol after a key fellow Democrat, Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDLESS WAVES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/sick-staff-endless-covid-patients-doctors-just-scraping-by-as-omicron-sweeps-hospitals/ar-AASJBRZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIPPED OF ALL MILITARY TITLES BY  QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1549872/queen-news-prince-william-prince-andrew-emergency-meeting-titles-latest-ont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUEEN ELIZABETH II held an emergency meeting with Prince William before stripping Prince Andrew of his military affiliations and royal patronages, a report has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ROCKED:  SUPREMES BLOCK VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/supreme-court-vaccine-mandate-eb5899ae1fe5b62b6f4d51f54a3cd375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court has stopped a major push by the Biden administration to boost the nation's COVID-19 vaccination rate, a requirement that employees at large businesses get a vaccine or test regularly and wear a mask on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parties at Downing Street as Queen mourned death of Prince Philip...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2022/01/13/two-parties-held-downing-street-queen-country-mourned-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaving events for No 10 staff were held on eve of the Duke's funeral, at which Her Majesty was forced to grieve alone due to Covid rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy assassin, Sirhan Bishara Sirhan, denied parole by Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/robert-f-kennedy-assassin-sirhan-bishara-sirhan-denied-parole-californ-rcna10311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom denied parole Thursday for Sen. Robert F. Kennedy's assassin, Sirhan Bishara Sirhan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein brought 8 young women to see Clinton in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10394863/Jeffrey-Epstein-brought-eight-women-Clinton-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visitor logs obtained by DailyMail.com reveal Jeffrey Epstein was not always alone when he visited the Clinton White House multiple times between 1993 and 1995.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why town requires residents to remove appendix to live there...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/13/town-requires-residents-to-remove-appendix-before-moving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Villas Las Estrellas requires prospective residents to literally have their appendix removed before settling down there for a specific reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-empty classrooms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-education-las-vegas-nevada-82295195809aa720e54e7ba96d3bdae8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teachers around the U.S. are confronting classrooms where as many as half of students are absent because they have been exposed to COVID-19 or their families kept them at home out of concern about the surging coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Josh Allen's secret playoff weapon could be VIAGRA...</title>
      <link>https://www.sbnation.com/nfl/2022/1/13/22882143/bart-scott-josh-allen-viagra-nfl-playoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sbnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good thing a game doesn’t last more than four hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill rollout stymied by shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxcarolina.com/covid-19-pill-rollout-stymied-by-shortages-as-omicron-rages/article_874d7d0a-50ff-50b4-a8db-9c3189ac93f5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxcarolina.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the supply is expected to improve dramatically in the coming months, doctors are clamoring for the pills now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Committee subpoenas GOOGLEFACEBOOKTWITTERREDDIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/13/january-6-committee-subpoenas-google-facebook-twitter-and-reddit-in-probe-of-capitol-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are So Many House Dems Leaving Congress?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kb49q/why-house-democrats-are-retiring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s become a toxic work environment,” a chief of staff to one retiring Democrat told VICE News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs Debate Whether Trans Teens Need Therapy Before Hormones...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/13/doctors-debate-whether-trans-teens-need-therapy-before-hormones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upsurge in teenagers requesting hormones or surgeries to better align their bodies with their gender identities has ignited a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School investigated for naked 'fat test' claims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-basketball-education-rhode-island-coaching-b47dc6ed2ad35f3b6b85c697c5e8e628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRANSTON, R.I. (AP) — Rhode Island attorney general's office is probing into the North Kingstown School Department after student-athletes filed a complaint that the school violated students’ civil rights by allowing a former boys’ basketball coach to disrobe athletes for “fat tests” for two decades .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SISTER: BRITNEY 'LOCKED ME IN ROOM AND ATTACKED WITH KNIFE!'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4458054/britney-spears-jamie-lynn-claims-star-locked-room-knife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ sister Jamie Lynn claimed the “erratic” singer “locked them in a room with a knife” as her “scary behavior spiraled.” The 30-year-old tearf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big, weird moon in far-off star system?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/13/1072570125/kepler-large-exomoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have found many planets orbiting distant stars, but so far no proof that any have moons. Now, researchers have detected signs of a large exomoon orbiting a Jupiter-like world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Embassy in Baghdad says it was attacked...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/589627-us-embassy-in-baghdad-says-it-was-attacked-attacked</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Embassy in Baghdad said Thursday that it was attacked by terrorist groups, the latest amid a series of attacks targeting US personnel in Iraq and Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Rainy Days Really Bad For Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/rainy-days-bad-for-economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings have implications for climate change policies worldwide as extreme weather events occur more frequently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainer slams dog to ground, DA investigating abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/13/da-investigating-trainer-slams-dog-viral-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;District Attorney Investigating After Trainer Slams Dog In Viral Video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Urges Reversal of Troop Buildup...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-at-an-impasse-with-the-west-warns-it-is-ready-to-abandon-diplomacy/ar-AASJUqy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keepers Leader Charged With Conspiracy in Jan. 6 Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/13/us/politics/oath-keepers-leader-arrested-in-jan-6-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The F.B.I. arrested Stewart Rhodes, the founder of the far-right militia, in a major step forward in the investigation into the attack on the Capitol by supporters of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema scuttles hopes for filibuster reform...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/589598-sinema-doubles-down-on-support-for-filibuster-citing-disease-of-divison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye under investigation for allegedly punching fan...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/01/13/kanye-west-under-investigation-for-alleged-battery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West allegedly punched a fan in the face after he asked the Yeezy designer for an autograph while he was sitting in his SUV outside of Soho Warehouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden orders 500 million more tests to meet demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/exclusive-biden-directs-us-procure-500-million-more-covid-tests-meet-demand-2022-01-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden said on Thursday he is directing the U.S. government to procure an additional 500 million COVID-19 tests to help meet demand across the country amid the spread of the Omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge threatens elderly cancer patient with jail for messy lawn...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wwjnewsradio/news/local/hamtramck-judge-shames-elderly-cancer-patient-for-messy-lawn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A district judge in Hamtramck is facing public scrutiny following a ruling in which she shamed an elderly cancer patient for struggling to keep up with his yard work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry Investors Sue Kardashian, Mayweather Over 'Pump and Dump'...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2022/01/crypto-investors-sue-kim-kardashian-floyd-mayweather-coin-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unheard-of digital token surged 1,300% in its first month, thanks to celebrity endorsements, and then crashed 99% overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIPPED OF ALL MILITARY TITLES BY THE QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4456659/prince-andrew-queen-titles-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew has been STRIPPED of all of his military honours by the Queen following the sex assault lawsuit. The bombshell news was announced by Buckingham Palace this evening. The Duke of York’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew will likely be asked about 'private parts' in sex case...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-andrew-warned-quizzed-on-25931442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew now faces being deposed, during which he could be asked intimate questions under oath about his marriage, sex life and body. A lawyer said nothing is 'off limits'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC BROADBAND Dumps NEWSMAX: Business as Usual, or Corporate Censorship?</title>
      <link>https://nhjournal.com/atlantic-broadband-dumps-newsmax-business-as-usual-or-corporate-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nhjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some Granite State fans of Newsmax, 2021 ended with a fizzle, not a bang. On December 31, Atlantic Broadband, a cable provider that serves 18 states, including New Hampshire, dropped the conservative news channel from its lineup without notice. Newsmax immediately responded to that decision with full-throated charges of censorship. “Despite our high ratings… it is clear that Atlantic doesn’t … Read more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hacker Controlled Dozens of Teslas Using Flaw in App...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akv7z5/how-a-hacker-controlled-dozens-of-teslas-using-a-flaw-in-third-party-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A security researcher found flaws in a third-party open-source app that allowed him to track and unlock some Teslas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANXIETY SPIKING</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anxiety-and-pandemic-fatigue-are-spiking-amid-latest-covid-surge/ar-AASJiz2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black box could record civilization's collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/black-box-could-record-collapse-25936553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The black box, which is set to built on the west coast of Tasmania, will be connected to the internet and will record information to help a future civilisation if humanity suffers a major apocalyptic event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami couple accused of kidnapping, torturing man for 3 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/miami-couple-accused-of-kidnapping-torturing-man-for-3-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Miami say the couple kidnapped a man, then chained him and tortured him for three days in their apartment. At one point, investigators said the suspects forced the victim to drink a mixture of rum and bleach. When a good Samaritan found him, they initially thought he had been shot or stabbed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple club at elementary school spurs outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/nation-world/national/article257283327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The club is drawing controversy, but the school is required to allow the meetings to take place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up to fail?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/kamala-harris-was-set-up-to-fail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's progressive about a failed black woman?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN APPROVAL SINKS TO 33%...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/poll-release?releaseid=3831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad fined for having two mates in garden demands money back...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/dad-fined-having-two-mates-25929343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kieron McArdle is asking for his £100 back which he paid after police arrived at his house and found two of his friends sitting with him in his garden during the second lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Life Ratings Retreat...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/388682/life-ratings-retreat-close-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An estimated 55.1% of U.S. adults rate their lives well enough to be classified as "thriving," down four points from the record high measured in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANDEMIC FATIGUE SPIKES</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/anxiety-and-pandemic-fatigue-are-spiking-amid-latest-covid-surge/article_e7719576-df4d-5885-9d2d-ef804a29cf5c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Like so many COVID-weary Americans, Kyle Hopwood thought the pandemic was winding down over the summer, as virus case counts in the Chicago area waned and life seemed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA trauma center shut down due to blood shortage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/589551-trauma-center-at-la-hospital-shut-down-for-hours-due-to-blood-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles trauma centers closed to new patients this week as a result of blood supply shortages, according to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALIFIANAKIS: Celeb-obsessed culture 'mental illness'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/589481-zach-galifianakis-celebrity-culture-how-we-ended-up-with-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zach Galifianakis is slamming celeb-obsessed culture as a “mental illness,” saying it’s the reason the country “ended up” with former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Little Lasers Might Light Our Way to Extraterrestrials...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-laser-seti-projects-that-might-find-intelligent-alien-civilizations?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve been keeping our ears open for aliens for half a century. It’s time to use our eyes as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The A-Listers Embarrassingly Shilling Digitial Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/reese-witherspoon-matt-damon-and-the-hollywood-a-listers-embarrassingly-shilling-crypto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reese Witherspoon recently asked: “In the (near) future, every person will have a parallel digital identity... Are you planning for this?” Our answer: “Uhhh.....?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Film Living Brain Storing Memories...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/film-how-brain-makes-memories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tailor-made microscope is helping scientists take the first snapshots of a living brain storing memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew will likely be asked about 'private parts' in sex case...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-andrew-warned-quizzed-on-25931442'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 military health workers to deploy to hospitals...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220113142509-sd6ji</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-1,000 military health workers to deploy to U.S. hospitals -White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 states have fewer than 15% of ICU beds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/13/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a record number of Americans are infected with Covid-19, largely due to the rapidly spreading Omicron variant, some states' health care systems are beset with nearly full intensive care units.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesale prices jump record 9.7%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-economy-prices-inflation-4849c1e0301c226d480049c17c5aa88c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.7% for all of 2021, setting an annual record and providing further evidence that inflation is still present at all levels of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew will likely be asked about 'private parts' in sex case...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comPrince Andrew warned he will be quizzed 'on private parts' as nothing is 'off limits'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comPrince Andrew warned he will be quizzed 'on private parts' as nothing is 'off limits'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Beck Says He Has COVID Again and It's Hit His Lungs...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4452882/glenn-beck-covid-lungs-unvaccinated-radio-host/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNVACCINATED conservative commentator Glenn Beck revealed that he has contracted Covid-19 for a second time. The radio host, 57, said the virus has “moved to his lungs” during an appear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors call out SPOTIFY over 'false and societally harmful assertions' on Rogan show...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/media/589526-doctors-call-out-spotify-over-false-and-societally-harmful-assertions-on-joe-rogan-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coalition of doctors and science educators is calling for Spotify to take action against misinformation spread on "The Joe Rogan Experience" podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI5 warns agent of Chinese government active in Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/4454644/major-chinese-spying-row-to-hit-parliament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTMINSTER has been rocked by a major spying scandal after MI5 accused a Labour donor of being a suspected Chinese agent targeting MPs. Labour donor Christine Lee is accused of trying to influence…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran releases video of Trump assassinated by drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4454518/iran-video-trump-assassinated-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has released a bizarre animated video showing former US President Donald Trump being assassinated by a drone as he plays golf. The short video, published on the website of Iranian Supreme Lead…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transplant surgeon used electric beam to burn his initials into patients' organs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-transplant-surgeon-used-an-electric-beam-to-burn-his-initials-into-patients-organs-he-just-lost-his-medical-license/ar-AASJPMi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance will follow us into 'metaverse,' and bodies could be new data source...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/surveillance-will-follow-us-into-e2-80-98the-metaverse-e2-80-99-and-our-bodies-could-be-its-new-data-source/ar-AASJWht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French teachers walk out over confusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220113-french-teachers-walk-out-over-covid-confusion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Huge numbers of French teachers went on strike Thursday, with the biggest teachers' union saying half of primary schools were closed as staff demand clarity from the government on coronavirus measure…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to detail 'surge' of military teams to hospitals in 6 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/01/13/covid-omicron-variant-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden will announce six teams are heading to New York, New Jersey, Ohio, Rhode Island, Michigan and New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Ability-To-Infect Plunges 90% After 20 Mins In Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.planet-today.com/2022/01/covids-ability-to-infect-plunges-90.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.planet-today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One recent study found that SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID and its many variants, actually isn't as infectious as "the science" - and, more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe at greatest risk of conflict in 30 years, Poland warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-692382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force technician came face-to-face with 'shadow person' while guarding nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/air-force-technician-came-face-25932532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former USAF nuclear weapons technician Adrian Reister describes glowing 'orbs' hovering around the high-security Missouri base – and coming face-to-face with a 'shadow person'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX-style abortion bans proliferate as court battle looms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/589416-texas-style-abortion-bans-proliferate-as-court-battle-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State legislators who oppose abortion rights are preparing legislation to mirror a Texas law passed last year that would allow residents to sue doctors who perform abortions, as the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Special Forces Will Simulate Insurgency On U.S. Soil In Warfare Exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43854/special-forces-will-simulate-an-insurgency-on-u-s-soil-in-upcoming-unconventional-warfare-exercise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin Sage exercises held in the Carolinas prepare Green Berets for the complex missions they will be called upon to accomplish when deployed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid omicron and flight cancellations, earnings to shed light on health of airline industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Amid-omicron-and-flight-cancellations-earnings-16772165.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Air Lines on Thursday will be the first U.S. airline to report financial results...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid tests hard to find -- unless work for GOOGLE, play in NBA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/rapid-coronavirus-tests-are-hard-to-find-e2-80-94-unless-you-work-for-google-or-play-in-the-nba/ar-AASJGEo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates at Rikers Island host 'FIGHT NIGHT' in empty cell as guards refuse to step in...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10397201/Moment-inmates-Rikers-Island-host-FIGHT-NIGHT-cell-guards-watch-helplessly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man injured in the fight was released last month, with a judge blasting the Department of Correction and Mayor Bill de Blasio for failing to protect the public and the detainee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police used tracing app to scout crime witnesses. Some fear that's fuel for covid conspiracists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/german-police-used-a-tracing-app-to-scout-crime-witnesses-some-fear-that-e2-80-99s-fuel-for-covid-conspiracists/ar-AASJr1z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep in Australian bush, scientific quest to uncover hidden koala enclave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/deep-in-the-australian-bush-a-scientific-quest-to-uncover-a-hidden-koala-enclave/ar-AASJmLg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSTED BORIS SORRY FOR ANOTHER LOCKDOWN BREACH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10393563/Time-face-music-Boris-PM-braces-Partygate-mauling-Commons.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Conservatives flooded broadcast studios and social media with praise for the PM following his admission in the Commons that he attended a party in No10 on May 20, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RUST' armorer sues ammo supplier after deadly shooting on Baldwin set...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rust-armorer-hannah-gutierrez-reed-sues-seth-kenney-pdq-arm-prop-ammo-supplier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film's armorer sued the man who supplied the ammunition and guns for the movie. Alec Baldwin fatally shot the film's cinematographer as it was being made.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
