<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>5G 'can spy on you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/5g-can-spy-you-critic-21083745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vocal 5G critic who makes Youtube videos describing the technology as "weapons" has claimed it can be misused to listen and watch people in their own homes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN climate talks unraveling, face failure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-climate-talks-unraveling-face-failure-110423955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UN climate summit in Madrid risked collapsing Saturday after all-night negotiations between countries left them more divided than ever over on how to fight global warming and pay for its ravages. Diplomats from rich nations, emerging giants and the world's poorest countries -- each for their own</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas mayhem feared as French transport strike continues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/christmas-mayhem-feared-french-transport-strike-continues-143133316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France reeled under a crippling public transport strike for a 10th day Saturday aimed at forcing the government to scrap a pension revamp, as fears grew of travel mayhem during Christmas. Train traffic was severely disrupted with only one out four high speed long-distance trains and three of 10 regional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reparations Mark New Front for Colleges Tied to Slavery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f390bd047c87a71d372e38ffbf477ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The promise of reparations to atone for historical ties to slavery has opened new territory in a reckoning at U.S. colleges, which until now have responded with monuments,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Was One of Mexico's Deadliest Assassins. Then He Turned on Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-was-one-of-mexicos-deadliest-assassins-then-he-turned-on-his-cartel/ar-AAK7nnX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PATRIOTS Season of Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://postofasia.com/the-patriots-season-of-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;postofasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots are 10-3. They at present maintain the No. 2 seed within the A.F.C. In all chance — a 76 p.c probability, in accordance with The New York Occasions’s playoff simulator — they are going to earn a first-round bye for the 10th consecutive postseason. And but an uneasy feeling has settled …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts another test at long-range rocket site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a65ce1c9102331e8e0036be11cb4d872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Saturday that it successfully performed another “crucial test” at its long-range rocket launch site that will further strengthen its nuclear deterrent....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST ACTOR?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791443/Harvey-Weinstein-MeToo-monster-looked-bit-broken-man.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM LEONARD: Shirt collar askew, ill-fitting suit and grey face a picture of misery and forbearance, Harvey Weinstein shuffled into a Manhattan court this week hunched over a walking frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's not fair!' </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791387/Trump-whines-impeachment-says-unjust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It's not fair that I'm being Impeached when I've done absolutely nothing wrong! The Radical Left, Do Nothing Democrats have become the Party of Hate. They are so bad for our Country!' Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church investigated over claims pastors pushed members into 'selling their blood to raise funds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7790197/Charity-Commission-investigates-Spac-Nation-Church-Bling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charity Commission has opened an inquiry into SPAC Nation after allegations emerged that pastors had told worshipppers to take out loans and even sell their blood to raise money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT WEEK*</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/hidden-by-impeachment-one-of-trumps-best-weeks-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the media and his critics focused on the bitterly divided House impeachment hearings, President Trump this week collected the most agenda wins yet, policy victories, including some backed by Democrats, that bolster arguments he’s making for reelection, according to advisers and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA high schools to open sexual and mental health clinics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/13/los-angeles-high-school-planned-parenthood-sexual-mental-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partnership between officials and Planned Parenthood will offer birth control, STI testing and care for anxiety and depression</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction of Navy ship 'Harvey Milk' begins in San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2019-12-13/construction-of-navy-ship-harvey-milk-kicks-off-with-ceremony-at-san-diego-shipbuilder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future USNS Harvey Milk, being built by General Dynamics NASSCO, has value and symbolism beyond its deckplates, advocates say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sets Off Furor... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/matt-bevin-ousted-in-kentucky-sets-off-furor-with-extreme-pardons/ar-AAK705V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept Investigates Experiments on People With Disabilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/health/2019/12/11/federal-justice-investigation-sexual-arousal-studies-glenwood-patient-disabilities/4401890002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Rea, the Glenwood Resource Center's superintendent, is on paid leave amid a DOJ investigation into potential federal rights violations at the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791533/Megyn-Kelly-breaks-silence-Bombshell-Watching-movie-incredibly-emotional-experience.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News anchor Megyn Kelly took to Instagram to post a photo of her son, Thatcher, at a movie theater, looking at a Bombshell poster, which featured Charlize Theron made up to look like Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans mayor declares state of emergency after cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/new-orleans-reports-cyberattacks-after-other-attacks-in-louisiana.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a series of widespread cyberattacks in Louisiana, which led to two statewide emergency declarations this year, New Orleans was hit on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom charged with leaving son at hospital draws sympathy...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/mom-charged-with-leaving-son-atlanta-hospital-draws-sympathy/U1dTc2HHQm2eiHGRjq0gII/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diana Elliott stands accused of abandoning her mute 14-year-old son, who police say has Down Syndrome, at Grady Memorial Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outgoing Kentucky governor pardons a man convicted of beheading  woman and stuffing her in  barrel...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/news/world/outgoing-kentucky-governor-pardons-man-convicted-of-beheading-a-woman-stuffing-her-in-a-barrel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEXINGTON, Ky. — It’s not clear if Betty Carnes was killed by asphyxiation or by the eight blows to her head that Delmar Partin delivered with a metal pipe. The coroner couldn’t tell which killed the mother of three first, but it was very clear that her head was then</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Cent and Russell Simmons bash Oprah over #MeToo documentary...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/13/50-cent-and-russell-simmons-bash-oprah-over-metoo-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media mogul’s forthcoming #MeToo documentary is already sparking controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington pulled apart by partisan divide over 'facts'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/washington-pulled-apart-partisan-divide-over-facts-015743807.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Washington these days, there are facts, alternative facts and disputed facts. The acrimonious impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump have put the spotlight on the stark partisan split in the nation's capital over where the truth lies. "There's always been a divide between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tepid reception...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-china-trade-deal-gets-tepid-reception-015910263--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials announced a truce in the trade war with China with much fanfare, but economists and trade experts call it largely a victory for Beijing. After a dispute that raged for close to two years, with several fumbled efforts at a resolution, the US agreed to cancel planned tariffs and rollback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubts Surface on $50 Billion in Farm Buys...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/doubts-surface-50-billion-china-205327779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump says China will spend $50 billion a year for U.S. farm products as part of a “phase one” trade deal between the countries. But doubts are surfacing whether that’s even possible, bolstered by China’s reluctance to confirm the figure.While the president expressed confidence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tightens info control after leaks on prison camps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1d08873154907be8a3dd93562d6785c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police chief admits anonymously trolling critic on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95e4cc24311eabad66df0cb4166b0fa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. (AP) — The police chief in Vermont's largest city used an anonymous Twitter account to troll a government critic, he admitted this week. Burlington Police Chief Brandon del...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How US-China trade deal achieved a little but left out a lot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/415cc91f3bb305ddb08620c53eea2d58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The limited trade deal that the Trump administration and Beijing announced Friday means Americans will avoid a holiday tax increase on imported toys, clothing and smartphones....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHADOW GOVT:  BLACKWATER Erik Prince held secret talks with top Venezuelan official...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191213191513-biyza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ERIKPRINCE (PIX):Blackwater founder Erik Prince held secret talks with top Venezuelan official -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES WILL HEAR TRUMP CASES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6bdd9fa291f4523ce0ef823775fba19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Friday it will hear President Donald Trump's pleas to keep his tax, bank and financial records private, a major confrontation between the president and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL SHOWDOWN  2020...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191213210422-l182n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TRUMP-RECORDS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. Supreme Court takes up Trump bid to shield financial records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt's strongman extends crackdown to new foe: Soap operas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/egypt-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By buying up TV channels, creating a tough new censor and banning edgy content, Sisi has gained an even tighter grip on Egypt than his predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Way Out, Kentucky Gov Pardons Murderers, Rapists, Hundreds More...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/12/13/787811560/on-his-way-out-kentucky-gov-matt-bevin-pardons-murderers-rapists-hundreds-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one case that has drawn particular attention, he pardoned a murderer whose family raised big money to pay off Bevin's campaign debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Cent accuses Oprah of only 'going after black men' in #MeToo cases
...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/entertainment/ct-ent-50-cent-oprah-black-men-comment-20191213-6uw3iigmfzh7zea3p24jtvryya-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper 50 Cent targeted Oprah Winfrey in an Instagram post, accusing the beloved TV host and super-producer of singling out black men, such as Michael Jackson and Russell Simmons, in her #MeToo activism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL SHOWDOWN  2020</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/supreme-court-agrees-hear-trump-appeals-subpoena-fights-over-financial-n1101901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By granting review of these cases now, the justices made it possible for them to be heard during the current court term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic data on military suicide shows no clear link with combat operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2019/12/13/historic-data-on-military-suicide-shows-no-clear-link-with-combat-operations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study tracks Army suicide from the 1840s until today and finds a decrease in rates of self-harm during war time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How fake accounts went viral -- with help of YOUTUBE algorithms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/13/tech/youtube-fake-accounts-viral/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube channels posing as American news outlets racked up millions of views on false and inflammatory videos over several months this year, all with the help of YouTube's recommendation engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES WILL HEAR TRUMP CASES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/supreme-court-will-hear-three-cases-over-trumps-financial-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court said on Friday that it will hear three cases over President Donald Trump's financial records next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow War With NKorea Likely To Intensify...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-administrations-shadow-war-with-north-korea-likely-to-intensify-in-coming-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of the year, a trio of events in the North are likely to threaten President Trump's hopes for progress in U.S.-North Korea relations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Pursues Mystery Buyer of Iranian Nuke Materials...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-pursues-mystery-buyer-of-contested-iranian-nuclear-materials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is considering sanctions to prevent Tehran from exporting materials that could power an atomic weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters march on Downing Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-election-protests/not-my-prime-minister-protesters-march-in-london-against-johnson-idUSKBN1YH28F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several hundred noisy protesters marched through central London on Friday to pro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden's wife pregnant right after former girlfriend gives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7789433/Hunter-Bidens-new-South-African-wife-pregnant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Biden's new wife Melissa Cohen Biden, 32, is pregnant and in her second trimester, DailyMailTV can reveal. She was seen grabbing groceries in LA on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much entertainment 'stressing' people out...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/883299/anxious-press-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have more entertainment options than ever before. That's stressing a lot of people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshman who led charge now unsure how she'll vote...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/archives/allahpundit/2019/12/13/freshman-dem-led-impeachment-charge-let-get-back-next-week-im-going-vote-okay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians arrive in waves at Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06c09bc61c3cbd4432d1dfe751e90914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas (AP) — Growing up along the U.S.-Mexico border, hotel clerk Joe Luis Rubio never thought he'd be trying to communicate in Portuguese on a daily basis. But with hundreds of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent publisher in China sentenced 10 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.rfa.org/english/news/china/publisher-jailed-12132019124146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rfa.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He Linxia was behind the publication of an expose of behind-the-scenes machinations by Mao Zedong later banned from public sale in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: 'I'll do whatever I want' during Senate trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ill-do-whatever-i-want-during-senate-impeachment-trial/ar-AAK6qp1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belichick in fight for his reputation...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/bill-belichick-is-in-a-fight-for-his-reputation-182002674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is Bill Belichick suddenly chatty? Because he knows with this latest spying accusation that his reputation is on the line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Township's Ad For Town Clerk Says Only Dems Can Apply...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/12/12/joliet-township-job-ad-asked-for-applicants-who-voted-in-a-democratic-primary-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A help-wanted ad in the suburbs raised eyebrows this week – with its suggestion that only Democrats need apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIANTS star cut after TWITTER rant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0c01a7195325b369be9250f89845d6f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J (AP) — The New York Giants waived-injured cornerback Janoris Jenkins on Friday, days after he engaged in a Twitter conversation in which he used offensive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Surgery 'Wild West'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthcare-of-tomorrow/articles/2019-12-13/training-for-robotically-assisted-surgery-evolves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Poised to Act on Trump Bid to Shield Financial Records... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-trump-records/trump-poised-for-supreme-court-battle-over-financial-records-idUSKBN1YG199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court may have a conservative majority that includes two justic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Agree on One Thing: They're Very, Very Nervous...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/democrats-agree-on-one-thing-theyre-very-very-nervous/ar-AAK5nO8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72,000 Anchor Babies a Year Born in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/12/study-foreign-workers-tourists-deliver-72k-anchor-babies-a-year-in-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 72,000 U.S.-born children are delivered every year to foreign tourists, visa workers, and foreign students and given U.S. citizenship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU warns of post-Brexit rival Britain...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eu-warns-post-brexit-rival-britain-johnson-win-150128383.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European leaders warned Friday that Britain could become a formidable rival, just hours after a big victory by Prime Minister Boris Johnson's conservatives all but sealed the UK's Brexit divorce. Led by France and Germany, EU member states said they would pursue a swift trade deal with a tight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France braces for holiday misery as pension strike persists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/christmas-plans-threatened-french-strike-drags-103743704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French commuters endured a ninth day of public transport strikes Friday, with little relief expected in coming days as unions vow to keep up their protest against a pension overhaul through the holidays unless the government backs down. Unions are hoping for a repeat of 1995, when they forced a rightwing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro: God made me president...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-god-made-president-160100610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Jair Bolsonaro said on Friday God, a fellow Brazilian, had handed him the election victory that propelled him to office in South America's largest economy. "I believe that God is Brazilian," added the right-wing leader, who came to power on January 1. Bolsonaro, who served in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Bernie the new Corbyn?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/12/why-bernie-sanders-no-jeremy-corbyn/603550/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Bernie Sanders is no Jeremy Corbyn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where the real battle for votes lies...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/opinion/real-battle-votes-lies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The struggle for 2020 hearts and minds is more than a referendum on the tweeter-in-chief’s behavior — it’s about the “future of work.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY CHEERS IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hillary-clinton-cheers-impeachment-says-trump-waging-war-against-democracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, who famously lost the 2016 election to now-President Trump, swiftly gave her public support to articles of impeachment against her political rival after they were announced by House Democrats Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stabs elderly husband inside Atlantic City casino...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/police-woman-stabbed-husband-in-atlantic-city-hotel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was hospitalized under police guard Friday after authorities said she stabbed her husband and herself in a casino hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Humans have natural lifespan of only 38 years... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7785761/Humans-genetically-hardwired-live-38-YEARS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Australia's national science agency used genetic markers of different vertebrates to identify the lifespans of living and extinct animals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans agree to massive spending bill, despite record deficits...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/republicans-agree-massive-spending-bill-despite-record-deficits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do deficits only matter under Democrats?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC:  Seems far off where Trump set the bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/13/us-china-trade-deal-negotiations-wto-markets-squawk-box-panel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Rosen, Rhodium Group founding partner, and Matthew Slaughter, dean and professor of international business at the Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth, join "Squawk Box" to discuss the prospects for a U.S.-China trade deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer says President 'sold out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/chuck-schumer-says-trump-caved-with-phase-one-china-trade-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chuck Schumer says President Trump has "sold out" by agreeing to a limited trade agreement with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell promises 'total coordination' with White House on trial strategy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/474399-mcconnell-says-hell-be-in-total-coordination-with-white-house-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell: Everything I do during this, I’m coordinating with White House Counsel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panel vote sends  charges to full House...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ffdf93f9ea109a1c3006eb7c4e46d029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats propelled President Donald Trump’s impeachment toward a historic vote by the full U.S. House on Friday, as the Judiciary Committee approved charges of abuse of power...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS WIN BIGGEST SINCE 80S...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f972f14e0fdaf579c43dd3e2ea36bfd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Boris Johnson's gamble on early elections paid off as voters gave the UK prime minister a commanding majority to take the country out of the European Union by the end of January, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER PUMP: Fed to Flood Market With $500 Billion In Liquidity...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/avoid-repo-crisis-fed-will-flood-market-gargantuan-365-billion-year-end-liquidity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shattered dreams of global far-left revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/anti-semitism-and-brexit-shatter-corbyns-dreams-of-global-far-left-revolution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labour leader attracted young supporters but wider public failed to warm to him over his refusal to take a position on Brexit, accusations of Jew hatred and sympathy for terrorists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS IN A BLOWOUT!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10541284/election-exit-poll-boris-johnson-on-course-for-a-majority-as-polls-predict-tory-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRIUMPHANT Boris Johnson struck a conciliatory tone by promising today to give the nation “closure” over Brexit after winning a landslide election victory. Speaking from Downing Street,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Vatican Spent Millions on Elton John Biopic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-the-vaticans-charity-spent-millions-on-elton-johns-rocketman-biopic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lord works in mysterious ways, and so do the Vatican’s finances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift Blasts Scooter, Soros During Award Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/taylor-swift-scooter-braun-billboard-women-in-music-926589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer also addresses how private equity allowed her music to be sold off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lackluster retail sales cast shadow on fourth-quarter economic growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy/lackluster-u-s-retail-sales-cast-shadow-on-fourth-quarter-economic-growth-idUSKBN1YH1O2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. retail sales increased less than expected in November as Americans cut back...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans Latina makes history as Evangelical Lutheran pastor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/transgender-latina-makes-history-evangelical-lutheran-pastor-n1100831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Nobody can question my faith, my devotion to Christ, my devotion to the church,” Pastor Nicole Garcia said. “Being trans is secondary.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Name-calling, insults and scandals... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/name-calling-insults-and-scandals-dominate-all-day-impeachment-hearing/ar-AAK4AZS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He might skip debates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/will-trump-debate-a-democrat-in-2020-hes-not-so-sure/ar-AAK4H8p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish prayer has returned to the Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Jewish-prayer-has-returned-to-the-Temple-Mount-exclusive-610781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Wakf official: Any change would spark strong response from Arabs and Muslims. Jewish activists: Final goal is to rebuild the Temple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy 'covered up' new technology by saying USS Nimitz UFO was unidentified...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/navy-covered-up-new-technology-21066844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A UFO researcher believes the USS Nimitz craft belongs to top-secret US Navy technology which has been covered up to stop other countries copying it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSANGE BLOCKED FROM SEEING EVIDENCE IN EXTRADITION CASE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7788673/WikiLeaks-founder-Julian-Assange-BLOCKED-seeing-key-evidence-authorities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange appeared at Westminster Magistrates' Court over video-link from HMP Belmarsh today and is yet to be shown key evidence in the case against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY:  CLEAR MAJORITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7786809/Exit-poll-shows-Boris-Johnson-track-WIN-crucial-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Labour's 'red wall' of Leave-backing strongholds imploding, Boris Johnson said he had been given a 'powerful' vote of confidence by the British people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of Cecil the Lion as Botswana Research Elephant Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/echoes-of-cecil-the-lion-as-botswana-research-elephant-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Echoes of Cecil the Lion as Botswana Research Elephant Shot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army's Secret Flights Over Washington Now 'Enduring' Mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/army-s-secret-flights-over-washington-now-an-enduring-mission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€œWithout additional funding, the Army will not be able to perform this classified mission,â€� the Defense Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy Math Makes American Companies Look More Creditworthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/fuzzy-math-makes-american-companies-look-more-creditworthy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting creative with earnings adjustments helps sell deals.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most active flu season in 15 years wreaking havoc... </title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/health-wellness/most-active-flu-season-since-2003-is-already-wreaking-havoc-in-the-us/644427</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun quietest since 1913...</title>
      <link>https://wattsupwiththat.com/2019/12/12/deep-solar-minimum-on-the-verge-of-an-historic-milestone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wattsupwiththat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guest post by Paul Dorian Daily observations of the number of sunspots since 1 January 1900 according to Solar Influences Data Analysis Center (SIDC). The thin blue line indicates the daily sunspot…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Enters Unknown as Magnetic North Pole Continues Shift...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201912131077566386-earth-enters-unknown-as-magnetic-north-pole-continues-push-toward-russia-crosses-greenwich-meridian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this year, US National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration and the British Geological Survey (BGS) were forced to update the World Magnetic Model a year ahead of schedule due to the speed with which the magnetic north pole is shifting out of the Canadian Arctic and toward Russia’s Siberia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein spotted with no walker, sparking speculation...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/12/12/harvey-weinstein-spotted-sans-walker-sparking-speculation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He’s just using it for sympathy,” a spy said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  THIS IS THE WHISTLEBLOWER...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/12/heres-the-likely-whistleblower-and-the-questions-he-should-answer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower is most likely CIA analyst Eric Ciaramella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' fans camp outside theater week before film opens...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/star-wars-fans-camp-outside-la-theater-week-001646156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obsessed Star Wars fans with sleeping bags and a portable movie projector have started camping outside Hollywood's Chinese Theatre, more than a week before the blockbuster begins playing. Organizers expect that number to swell to 150 in the coming days, with fans of all ages traveling from as far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seizes on crushing defeat as proof only centrist can win...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joe-biden-allies-seizing-lefts-111804366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centrists such as Biden will argue that the election has stark messages for US Democrats, but progressives will draw different conclusions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corbyn most unpopular opposition leader in generation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-votes-pivotal-brexit-election-193917058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson vowed Friday to "get Brexit done" after his thumping election victory cleared the way for Britain to leave the EU after years of political paralysis. With all results declared for the 650-seat parliament in Thursday's momentous election, Johnson's Conservative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal groups outraged...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/botswana-animal-groups-outraged-elephant-killing-150857933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animal campaigners demanded on Friday that a Botswana hunter's licence be revoked after an elephant was killed despite being protected, raising tensions over the country's new hunting rules. Officials confirmed that an elephant wearing a collar -- which marks it as a protected animal -- was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexander Boris de Pfeffel Johnson!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnson-britains-divisive-brexit-champion-224357768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson persuaded British voters to back Brexit in 2016 and if exit polls are correct now has a chance to deliver, but he stands accused of Trump-style populism that risks further dividing the country. The Conservative leader campaigned relentlessly on a promise to "Get Brexit Done",</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI puts final notes on Beethoven's Tenth Symphony...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ai-puts-final-notes-beethovens-tenth-symphony-042729352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few notes scribbled in his notebook are all that German composer Ludwig van Beethoven left of his Tenth Symphony before his death in 1827. "The progress has been impressive, even if the computer still has a lot to learn," said Christine Siegert, head of archives at Beethoven House in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Culture War Escalates as Era of Transparency Wanes...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-culture-war-escalates-era-100005580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Each morning, workers at Google get an internal newsletter called the “Daily Insider.” Kent Walker, Google’s top lawyer, set off a firestorm when he argued in the Nov. 14 edition that the 21-year old company had outgrown its policy of allowing workers to access nearly any internal document</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY THE 13TH COMES FOR LABOUR; HISTORIC LOSS...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/uk/live-news/uk-election-day-2019-dle-ge19-gbr-intl/h_3e4b6e44c3cb11706033ac8f219c8194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson's Conservatives have stormed to victory in a pivotal election in the UK. Get the latest developments here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Agree on One Thing: They're Very, Very Nervous...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/12/13/democrats-agree-on-one-thing-theyre-very-very-nervous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon tests ballistic missile over Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/92c9f6922c7f9f97dbfdda970ba998e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a story December 12, 2019, about a U.S. missile test, The Associated Press erroneously reported that the missile flew more than 500 miles. The correct distance is more than...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
