<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>As feds target CA's homeless crisis, state braces for fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/23/trump-takes-aim-californias-homeless-leaving-governor-wary/4276242002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump administration officials appear poised to release a new homelessness strategy, which has California officials wary and poised for battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picassos in the Garage? Artist's Handyman Convicted of Hiding Stolen Works...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/picassos-in-the-garage-artists-handyman-is-convicted-of-hiding-stolen-works/ar-BBXdso4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Virginia, and elsewhere, gun supporters prepare to defy new laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-virginia-and-elsewhere-gun-supporters-prepare-to-defy-new-laws/ar-BBXdIYd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malls now targeting millionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/23/economy/luxury-malls-holiday-shopping/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suburban malls in the middle of America have been hit hard due the financial woes of anchor tenants like Macy's and JCPenney and the slow death spiral at Sears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget the Oval. The real action is in the President's residence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/24/trump-white-house-residence-power-epicenter-073139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fixated on impeachment proceedings against him, Trump is increasingly taking his official business to the White House’s executive residence to escape perceived risks of his formal office space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's college basketball player arrested on murder charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/breaking-ksu-women-basketball-player-arrested-murder-charges/WR8aRO7P50bQpu2Xl4yEZL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The starting point guard for Kennesaw State University’s women’s basketball team has bee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>800 men 'asked' to give DNA to solve violent 1996 murder...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/men-from-german-village-called-up-to-help-solve-claudia-rufs-murder-11868473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claudia Ruf was 11 when she was murdered in 1996 but, despite an extensive investigation, her killer has not yet been found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope: Possession of atom bomb 'immoral'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc54b85007614cd283b3eb23f32ab6a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIROSHIMA, Japan (AP) — Pope Francis traveled to Hiroshima and Nagasaki on Sunday to demand that world powers renounce their nuclear arsenals, declaring the use and possession of atomic bombs an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FROZEN 2' FIASCO: '100-strong machete-wielding gang storm cinema sparking huge brawl'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10409135/birmingham-star-city-fight-evacuated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FIVE teens were last night arrested after a gang of 100 youths armed with machetes stormed a cinema in front of horrified families. Seven cops were hurt as they desperately tried to control brawlin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD-YALE game ends in near-darkness after climate change protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/college-football/story/_/id/28147080/harvard-yale-game-ends-darkness-climate-change-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second half of Saturday's Harvard-Yale game was delayed after a number of spectators rushed the field to stage a climate change protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix to stop using red-light, speed-enforcement cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/phoenix-traffic/2019/11/23/phoenix-stop-using-red-light-speed-enforcement-cameras/4279975002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal to extend the contract for the cameras beyond Jan. 1, 2020, failed by a 4-5 City Council vote this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch this: China surveillance tech seeks to go global...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/watch-china-surveillance-tech-seeks-global-030241832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese firms are omnipresent at a Paris homeland security trade show, capitalising on their vast experience in developing surveillance systems for Beijing to conquer the global market despite concerns the technology has been used to violate human rights. With 89 out of 1,100 companies demonstrating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX SPORTS analyst says 'sieg heil' during live TV show...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/24/marco-van-basten-fox-sports-analyst-says-sieg-heil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retired Dutch football star Marco van Basten has apologized for saying “sieg heil” during a live television show after a German coach was interviewed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes could face second ethics investigation... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Rep-Devin-Nunes-could-face-second-ethics-14858221.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A high-ranking House Democrat said Saturday it's "quite likely" Rep. Devin Nunes, R-Calif., will face an ethics investigation over allegations that he met with an ex-Ukrainian official to obtain information about former vice president Joe Biden and his son.  Rep. Adam Smith of Washington, the chairman of the House Armed Services Committee, appeared on MSNBC where he was asked whether Nunes could face a House inquiry. "Quite likely, without question," Smith said.  The allegation that Nunes, the top Republican on the House Intelligence Committee, met with a former Ukrainian prosecutor last year to discuss the Bidens came from the attorney for Lev Parnas, one of two Soviet-born associates of Rudy Giuliani who were indicted on charges they broke campaign finance law.  Parnas' attorney, Joseph Bondy, told The Washington Post that Ukraine's former top prosecutor, Viktor Shokin, informed Parnas that he had met with Nunes in Vienna in December 2018.  Bondy also said that a top aide to Nunes, Derek Harvey, sometimes joined a group that met frequently in spring 2019 at the Trump International Hotel in Washington, District of Columbia, to discuss the Biden matter among other topics. The group, according to Bondy, was convened by Giuliani, President Donald Trump's personal attorney, and included Parnas, his business associate Igor Fruman, as well as journalist John Solomon and the married legal team of Joe diGenova and Victoria Toensing.  The information about Nunes' meeting with Shokin and Harvey's meetings with Giuliani were first reported by CNN on Friday.  Nunes declined to comment. He did, however, strongly push back on the story to the conservative outlet Breitbart News and threatened to sue CNN for reporting it. He also threatened to sue the Daily Beast for a story...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden lists FOUR potential female VP picks --  but can't remember any of their names!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7718511/Embarrassing-moment-Joe-Biden-lists-FOUR-potential-female-VP-picks-remember-names.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former VP, main, was speaking a campaign stop in Winterset, Iowa, on Friday. He appeared to refer to Stacey Abrams, top inset, and Sally Yates, bottom inset, but not by name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  TRUMP'S WHITE WHALE...</title>
      <link>https://trendingpress.com/trumps-white-whale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trendingpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme surfers catch record waves in Portuguese town...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/extreme-surfers-catch-record-waves-portuguese-town-014628289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nazaré (Portugal) (AFP) - Big wave surfers have been flocking to a formerly sleepy Portuguese fishing town, chasing monster waves that are some of the highest ever surfed. Earlier this month the news broke that a set of fearsome 20-metre (65-feet) waves were coming to the small town of Nazare on Portugal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy hurricane season does less damage but leaves ominous signs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/busy-hurricane-season-does-less-130000694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Atlantic Ocean has spawned lots of storms this season while doing much less damage than prior years. But warming waters promise trouble ahead.The 2019 Atlantic hurricane season, which ends Nov. 30, has been the eighth most-active in named storms based on records going back to 1851.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary of Navy says Trump tweet is not formal order...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa25ecd5399b45529ece8f77ff71cfcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HALIFAX, Nova Scotia (AP) — The secretary of the U.S. Navy said Saturday he doesn't consider a tweet by President Donald Trump an order and would need a formal order to stop a review of a sailor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg hospitalized for treatment of chills and fever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59ece692dd804865bac9df546549ab70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was hospitalized after experiencing chills and fever, the court said Saturday. In a statement, the court’s public information...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Graham Says Opposition To President 'Demonic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/franklin-graham-claims-demonic-power-behind-attacks-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelist Franklin Graham claimed the political turmoil fracturing the country in the wake of impeachment proceedings into President Trump likely has a supernatural origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With impeachment looming, both parties anxious </title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2019/nov/23/with-impeachment-looming-both-republicans-and-demo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Washington moves toward an impeachment showdown, members of both parties seem wracked with insecurity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI:   THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO KILL ME</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/23/rudy-giuliani-fox-news-ed-henry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani snapped at Fox News host Ed Henry during an interview Saturday, accusing Henry of covering up news about Joe Biden and Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg vows to refuse donations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/faeb0397465948cea256367867c7efb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michael Bloomberg will not accept political donations if he runs for president and he will not take a salary if he wins, according to senior aides who offered new details on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds fight back as conspiracy theories swirl...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a1ef16a612bd4130a18479c01bd72586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — At another time in history, the indictment of two jail guards responsible for monitoring Jeffrey Epstein the night he killed himself might have served as an emphatic rebuttal to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NH May Test Durability of Sanders Popularity...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-11-23/new-hampshire-may-test-durability-of-sanders-popularity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 teams want to sign Kap?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/two-nfl-teams-interested-colin-kaepernick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former San Francisco 49ers quarterback Colin Kaepernick is being looked at closely by two teams in the NFL after holding his own workout over the weekend, his attorney Mark Geragos said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ticket Trump doesn't want?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/471368-the-democratic-ticket-trump-doesnt-want-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic voters finally are paying attention to Gabbard and Buttigieg, she a more centrist candidate and he more left of center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans skeptical Pelosi will go through with it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/471744-trump-gop-skeptical-pelosi-will-go-through-with-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even President Trump, while insisting he wanted an impeachment trial, predicted Friday that Pelosi would not go through with impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare curfew after violence in Colombia puts people on edge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rare-curfew-violence-colombia-puts-people-edge-175058161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombia's first curfew in decades turned its capital city into a nervous ghost town, as people armed with machetes, bats and knives guarded doorways against hooded looters thought to be running wild. Acts of vandalism broke out in some areas of Bogota late Friday, a day after a general strike and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lion cub mummies feature in huge ancient Egypt find...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lion-cub-mummies-feature-huge-ancient-egypt-175155573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt on Saturday unveiled a cache of 75 wooden and bronze statues and five lion cub mummies decorated with hieroglyphics at the Saqqara necropolis near the Giza pyramids in Cairo. The Antiquities Ministry announced the find at the foot of the Bastet Temple, dedicated to the worship of cats among ancient</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Taylor Swift, Scooter Braun bad blood may reshape industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/nov/23/taylor-swift-scooter-braun-amas-old-music-masters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer’s dispute with the new owner of Big Machine Records over her first six albums challenges who owns what in the industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Decision From Congress Will Leave Voters With Final Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/23/us/politics/trump-impeachment-voters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike Presidents Richard M. Nixon or Bill Clinton, Mr. Trump will face an election after his impeachment battle if he isn’t removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. GENERAL WARNS OF IRAN ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-commander-warns-of-iranian-attack-in-middle-east/ar-BBXd3PW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue actors gain power as experts lose relevance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-trumps-washington-the-rogue-actors-are-the-real-players-%e2%80%94-and-the-experts-are-increasingly-irrelevant/ar-BBXeqEi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: YOU THINK I'M AFRAID?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/rudy-giuliani-donald-trump-indicted-joe-biden-liar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's personal attorney and former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani said Saturday that he is not afraid of being indicted and that he has absolutely no business interest in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone supervolcano hit with 193 quakes in month...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1208292/yellowstone-park-volcano-earthquake-earthquakes-2019-usgs-news-volcanoes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YELLOWSTONE has seen almost 200 earthquakes rock the region in the past month, begging the question: is it about to erupt?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MISERABLE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/is-tom-brady-getting-frustrated-qb-apparently-said-he-was-miserable-during-recent-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady's frustrations might finally be starting to boil over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mister Rogers And The Dark Abyss Of The Adult Soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/annehelenpetersen/mister-rogers-beautiful-day-neighborhood-movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood is a movie about how startling it is to be brought back to an open-heartedness that most of us spend our lives unlearning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron farts at fans after they ask for his autograph...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/23/lebron-james-farts-at-fans-after-they-ask-for-his-autograph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The King has tooted. Basketball star LeBron James responded to a fan request for an autograph by farting at him while leaving an Oklahoma steakhouse. LeBron and fellow basketballer Chris Paul were …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posthumous Leonard Cohen album offers apt final waltz...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/posthumous-leonard-cohen-album-offers-apt-final-waltz-063600771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nine tracks on "Thanks for the Dance" blend coherently into his oeuvre with forward-looking contemplations, examining the past not with nostalgia but with an inner drive to explore his own psyche. In "Moving On" -- an elegy to his one-time love and muse Marianne Ihlen, the inspiration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY DOUBTS MOUNT...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001079418/article/pats-doomed-with-tom-brady-at-qb-michael-thomas-for-opoy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots are 9-1, but Bucky Brooks says the defending Super Bowl champions are a quarterback away from claiming their seventh Lombardi Trophy. Plus, overlooked candidates for two major awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE NIRO: Mayor Pete What We Need Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-de-niro-on-piece-of-sht-trump-whether-the-mob-killed-jfk-and-why-buttigieg-is-what-we-need-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film icon and star of “The Irishman” sat down with Marlow Stern to discuss his beautiful new film with Scorsese, the Dems’ 2020 chances, and why Trump has gotta go—and fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 230-year-old Mount Vernon tree, witness to history, is no more...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-230-year-old-Mount-Vernon-tree-a-witness-to-14855890.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was probably a sapling when George Washington returned to Mount Vernon in 1783, triumphant after his victory in the Revolutionary War.  It was probably there on the Virginia estate in 1787 when he left for the Constitutional Convention in Philadelphia, and it grew during his terms as the country's first president. It was there when he came home for good, and when he died in 1799.  Droughts came and went, along with two centuries of American history. (Civil War soldiers carved insignia in its bark.) Then, late one night earlier this month, the tired old white oak gave out and came crashing down across a road in the woods.  Caretakers on the grounds of Mount Vernon heard it fall just before midnight on Nov. 4.  "Middle of the night," Dean Norton, Mount Vernon's director of horticulture, said Thursday. "No wind. It just falls over."  It was about 115 feet tall, 12 feet around, and at roughly age 230, it was almost as old as the United States.  Witness to so much history, "trees just give up, on occasion," Norton said. It wasn't sick. "It just was its time."  The tree dated at least to 1780, he said. Once it had fallen, and was cut, he was able to carefully measure the tree rings that help date a tree and tell its story.  "Oak tree rings are probably some of the easiest rings to count," he said. "They're really distinctive." He said his count is conservative. "The tree could be older than 1780, but I can honestly say that it at least goes back to that."  George Washington owned the Mount Vernon plantation, along with its home and more than 100 enslaved people, from 1761 until he died. He and his wife, Martha, are buried on the property, which is on the Potomac River about 15 miles south of Washington.  Norton said there is also a possibility that Washington had purposely...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER Helicopter Rides to JFK Were Briefly Cheaper Than Its Cars!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-23/uber-helicopter-rides-to-jfk-were-briefly-cheaper-than-its-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unveils animal mummies of lion cubs, crocodiles, birds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9e4dd8a0667d499d89d0ba70b07ba1d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAQQARA, Egypt (AP) — Egypt's Ministry of Antiquities on Saturday revealed details on recently discovered animal mummies, saying they include two lion cubs as well as several crocodiles, birds and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'Large Fireball Falling to Earth' Crashes in Oregon, Police Investigate...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mysterious-large-fireball-salem-oregon-sighting-1473469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 2020 candidates, eating tacos is the kissing babies of stumping for Latino votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-23/2020-elections-mexican-restaurants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For presidential candidates on the campaign trail, hitting up Mexican restaurants has become as American as kissing bebés.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glut of homes about to hit market -- who will buy them?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/baby-boomers-may-put-21m-homes-on-market-but-who-will-buy-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is at the beginning of a tidal wave of homes hitting the market on the scale of the housing bubble in the mid-2000s. What happens when so many homes post ‘For Sale’ signs around the same time?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL HE FILL THE GAPS?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-22/bolton-dangling-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ousted national security advisor John Bolton seems to be hinting at possibly testifying late in the impeachment process about President Trump’s actions regarding Ukraine, which could provide crucial information to fill in any gaps in the record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG YEARS ARE MYTH AND PUPPIES ARE MIDDLE-AGED, SCIENTISTS CLAIM...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/dog-years-myth-research-age-seven-years-humans-university-california-a9214911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence on surprise Iraq trip to reassure Kurds, greet troops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iraqi-official-pence-visits-us-124321365.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence made an unannounced visit to Iraq on Saturday in the highest-level American trip since President Donald Trump ordered a pullback of U.S. forces in Syria two months ago. Flying in a C-17 military cargo jet to preserve the secrecy of the visit to the conflict zone, Pence landed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defector claims rare glimpse into life as Chinese spy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/defector-claims-rare-glimpse-life-chinese-spy-091827506.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black ops, abductions and betrayal -- the Chinese operative who defected to Australia has provided an unverified but chilling glimpse into the life of an apparent spy who came in from the cold. In interviews with Australian media, Wang "William" Liqiang described how he gave Canberra a trove</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 years old and on brink of death from vaping...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/22-years-old-brink-death-vaping-060358046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a raging fever, vomiting and diarrhea, Gregory Rodriguez thought he had some kind of bug when he checked himself into the emergency room at a New York hospital in September. Two days later, he was unconscious, hooked up to an artificial lung and a candidate for a double lung transplant. "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. GENERAL WARNS OF IRAN ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/11/23/very-possible-iran-will-attack-again-top-us-general-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threat from Tehran continues to increase despite U.S. military buildup, U.S. Central Command’s Gen. Kenneth McKenzie says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi inner circle key to criminal cases...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191123035652-b4qu0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-NETANYAHU/INVESTIGATION (PIX):All King Bibi's men: Netanyahu's inner circle key to criminal cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran faces most critical moment since 1979 Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/23/iran-faces-its-most-critical-moment-since-the-1979-revolution.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unclear whether Iran will respond to this historic test, which includes Trump's maximum pressure, with more military escalation, diplomatic compromise â€“ or a combination of both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men would rather see team win Super Bowl than candidate win election...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/22/men-would-rather-see-favorite-team-win-super-bowl-than-candidate-win-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to politics, these guys are dropping the ball! More than a quarter of men in the US would rather their favorite football team win the Super Bowl than their preferred candidate win the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil ex-president, out of jail, vows to make 'lives hell'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aae8b5a3395a416eb65f58cf7946dee2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO (AP) — A fired-up former President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, freshly out of jail, vowed to fight Brazil’s far-right government and the forces he says unjustly incarcerated him, saying...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
