<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Military eyes 16 year olds as ranks and candidates dwindle...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/18/military-recruiting-woes-spur-debate-over-enlistme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best way to fix the U.S. armed forces’ recruiting challenges may involve dipping further into the nation’s high schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVISION Awards Show Beat All English-Language Broadcast Networks in Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/univision-2019-premios-juventud-awards-show-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Univision and its "2019 Premios Juventud" awards show topped all of the English-language broadcast channels in Thursday's primetime ratings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President tells aides to look for big spending cuts in 'second-term'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/President-Trump-tells-aides-to-look-for-big-14109681.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump has instructed aides to prepare for sweeping budget cuts if he wins a second term in the White House, five people briefed on the discussions said, a move that would dramatically reverse the big-spending approach he adopted during his first 30 months in office.  Trump's advisers say he will be better positioned to crack down on spending and shrink or eliminate certain agencies after next year, particularly if Republicans regain control of the House of Representatives.  But this second-term ambition is already seeding confusion about how the White House should approach the current slate of negotiations, in which some conservatives want Trump to push for spending restraint.  Instead, Trump is advocating swiftly lifting the federal debt ceiling, which would allow for more spending and borrowing. Trump, who was once a fierce promoter of refusing the raise the debt ceiling without winning concessions, said the opposite on Friday, telling reporters that "it's a sacred element of our country. They can't use the debt ceiling to negotiate."  Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin has said the debt ceiling needs to be increased by early September to avoid a potentially catastrophic default. That puts enormous pressure on Congress to act, because lawmakers leave at the end of next week for the remainder of the summer.  Mnuchin has forged several parts of a new budget agreement with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., but the talks bogged down in recent days after other Trump advisers sent Democrats a request for $150 billion in spending cuts.  With Mnuchin pushing for a deal and the other advisers, largely acting chief of staff Mick Mulvaney and acting budget director Russell Vought, seeking big cuts, the White House has lacked a consistent argument during the debates, something that is likely to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOP GUN' Sequel Drops Japanese, Taiwanese Flags to Appease China?</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/07/20/asia-pacific/top-gun-sequel-appears-remove-japanese-taiwanese-flags/#.XTNN5ehKhEY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eagle-eyed viewers have spotted a curious discrepancy in the first trailer for "Top Gun: Maverick," the sequel to the beloved '80s classic "Top Gun," which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New US-led war looming?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190720-new-us-led-war-looming-with-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is a new US-led war looming with Iran?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: RELEASE HIM A$AP</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7267981/Trump-honors-promise-call-Swedens-PM-behalf-jailed-rapper-AP-Rocky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump says he 'personally vouched' for A$AP Rocky's bail in a phone call with Sweden's Prime Minister, less than a day after vowing to secure the rapper's release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon landing was giant leap for movies, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7b5b3ba566714c31a2c5258d1e354028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Develop Groundbreaking 'Trojan Horse' Anticancer Drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/strategic-medicine-researchers-develop-trojan-horse-drug-that-tricks-then-kills-cancer-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same tactics used by the ancient Greeks thousands of years ago in battle are being applied by researchers at Northwestern University to fight cancer today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Ask Residents To 'Hold Off' On Criminal Activity Amid Dangerous Heat...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/07/20/braintree-police-hold-off-on-crime-this-weekend-due-to-extreme-heat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Braintree Police Department had some fun explaining to residents that they should "hold off" on any crimes they are planning this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside New York's World of Burlesque...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-york-citys-burlesques-your-guide-to-this-wild-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shows start late and can stretch to the wee hours of the morning, work next day be damned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong actor stabbed in mainland China...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190720-hong-kong-actor-stabbed-mainland-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong actor stabbed in mainland China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation celebrates 50th anniversary of 1st lunar footsteps...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1c89d2a4e1e447668b120055a4f18580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has not built single mile of border fence after 30 months in office...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-has-not-built-a-single-mile-of-new-border-fence-after-30-months-in-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO, California — The Trump administration has not installed a single mile of new wall in a previously fenceless part of the U.S.-Mexico border in the 30 months since President Trump assumed office, despite his campaign promise to construct a “big beautiful wall.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Drew Warns of Imminent Bubonic Plague Outbreak In LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/dr-drew-warns-of-imminent-bubonic-plague-outbreak-starting-in-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nightmare scenario could be result of Democrat policies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World at risk of Ebola 'plane plague' spreading on flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792951/ebola-outbreak-plane-plague-spread-flights-WHO-global-emergency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Computer failure cripples subway lines in latest NYC chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nyc-subway-suspended-service-resumes-after-trains-halted-mta-2019-07-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stoppage affected the No. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 and 6 trains that serve swaths of Manhattan, the Bronx and Brooklyn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has socialism already failed in United States?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/453913-has-socialism-already-failed-in-the-united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is there an example in recent memory on your own doorstep?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegals try to rush into US in 'waves'; Showdown with agents...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/19/undocumented-immigrants-try-to-rush-into-us-in-waves-spark-showdown-with-cbp-agents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the biggest ports of entry along the US-Mexico border had to be shut down on Friday after a group of undocumented immigrants — nearly 50 of them — attempted to rush into the Unit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'HALLOWEEN' Reboot Turns Into Trilogy...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/more-halloween-horror-franchise-reboot-193644714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamie Lee Curtis' Halloween Reboot Will Be a Trilogy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK warns of 'serious consequences'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/07/20/britain-warns-iran-over-seized-oil-tanker-strait-hormuz-us-iran-tensions/1784626001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's seizure of a British oil tanker potentially marksÂ a major escalationÂ in tensions between Iran and the West since they began rising in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran says USA may have shot down own drone!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/07/19/iran-disputes-trump-claim-u-s-navy-destroyed-its-drone/1775051001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran deniedÂ itÂ lost a drone in the Strait of Hormuz after the United States said it had 'destroyed'Â an Iranian drone that was threatening a U.S. ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second one released...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/british-oil-tanker-seized-iranian-forces-being-guided-strait-hormuz-n1031866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Foreign and Commonwealth Office issued a statement advising U.K. vessels to steer clear of the area as tensions between Iran and the West heighten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials Flocking to Pacific Northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/millennials-are-flocking-to-the-pacific-northwest-study-finds-1.1289773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS IRAN</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6c36f5aa1ba942569e5efcfd48e33324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subway Service Suspended in Latest NYC Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/2019/07/19/several-subway-lines-delayed-due-to-network-communications-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANHATTAN — A large portion of the New York City subway system was finally returning to normal service Friday evening after screeching to a halt during the rush hour when six subway lines were suspended for over an hour and multiple trains were stopped between stations. Thousands of passengers were stuck on platforms and in trains on one of the hottest days of the year in the second major infrastructure failure in New York in less than a week, following a Con Edison-related power outage on Manhattan's West Side last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Political Chaos Deepens With Third Claim to Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-political-chaos-deepens-third-182040763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- If Venezuelan politics weren’t convoluted enough, they just got a bit more complicated this week.The opposition-aligned Progressive Advance party hired Ari Ben-Menashe, a Montreal-based lobbyist, to “pursue Henri Falcon’s election as President of Venezuela,” according to a contract filed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/video/iran-footage-of-detained-uk-oil-tanker-stena-impero-emerges-11766969</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian state media have released footage of the British-flagged oil tanker detained in the Hormuz strait by Iranian authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS IRAN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e8f432e5ef5247d8af8865310e88348a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAUNTS 'DELUSIONAL' TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-u-shot-down-193411478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump said the U.S. “immediately destroyed” an Iranian drone that approached the USS Boxer near the Strait of Hormuz, but officials in Tehran denied losing one.The drone was a threat to the amphibious assault ship and its crew, Trump said at the White House on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clash with Royal Navy...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190719193123-mxi42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-IRAN/USA (WRAPUP 4, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 4-Iran says it seized British tanker, denies U.S. brought down drone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's our America'... </title>
      <link>https://www.indopremier.com/ipotnews/newsDetail.php?jdl=_It_s_our_America___reminds_Michelle_Obama&amp;news_id=1439609&amp;group_news=ALLNEWS&amp;taging_subtype=UNITEDSTATES&amp;name=&amp;search=y_general&amp;q=UNITED%20STATES,%20&amp;halaman=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indopremier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next person to land on moon may not be American...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/18/the-next-person-to-land-on-the-moon-may-not-be-american/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Neil Armstrong took his “one small step” on July 20, 1969, the future of manned space exploration seemed bright — yet the moon has spun untrampled by humans since Apollo 17 blasted off in Dece…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho music event canceled amid immigration enforcement fear...</title>
      <link>https://idahonews.com/news/local/idaho-music-event-canceled-amid-immigration-enforcement-fear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;idahonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEROME, Idaho (AP) - A music festival in southern Idaho has been canceled because organizers say they feared potential raids by Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents. The music festival called the El Tour de Idaho de Los Inquietos was supposed to take place in Jerome on Saturday. Event organizers with the Colombia Event Center posted the cancellation notice on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD informant infiltrated left-wing activists during Trump protests, records show...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jul/19/los-angeles-police-informant-anti-trump-activist-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Case is one of several across the US of police targeting anti-Trump and anti-fascist groups with monitoring and criminal trials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots 'roam streets' with humans after upgrade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792924/sex-robots-walking-tech-news-ai-realbotix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murderer released after being deemed too old to kill again, kills again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/murderer-released-after-being-deemed-too-old-kill-again-kills-n1031736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took a Maine jury less than an hour to find Albert Flick guilty of murdering Kimberly Dobbie with her twin sons nearby in July 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists kicked out of Venice for making coffee on bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190719-venice-coffee-costs-rule-breaking-german-tourists-950-euros</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice coffee costs rule-breaking German tourists 950 euros</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS IRAN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7266349/Trump-says-Iran-big-trouble-seized-TWO-British-tankers-Persian-Gulf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Iran is showing their true colors,' the president told reporters on the South Lawn of the White House has he departed for a weekend in New Jersey. 'Iran is in big trouble.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 years after deadly Chappaquiddick crash, mystery letter claims Kennedy had ANOTHER woman in car...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7263395/Letter-claims-Ted-Kennedy-didnt-realize-Mary-Jo-Kopechne-car-Chappaquiddick.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The information in the letter contradicts Kennedy's story, which was that he had been driving Kopechne to the ferry, made a wrong turn and went off a bridge into a tidal pond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jumps on wing as plane prepares for takeoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/19/africa/nigeria-man-climbs-plane-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who climbed onto the wing of a plane as it prepared for takeoff at the airport in Nigeria's Lagos city has been arrested, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Releases footage it claims disproves...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-49052302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran airs footage which it says refutes US claims to have destroyed an Iranian drone in the Gulf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church Wants To Build Cell Tower Disguised As Bell Tower...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/07/18/sacramento-church-bell-tower-cell-tower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Sacramento's historic churches wants to add a 50-foot bell tower to its property, with a bell that won't work. That's because it will actually be a cell tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAMPERS Launching 'Smart' Diapers...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/07/19/pampers-creating-smart-diaper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pampers is developing a "smart diaper" that will track how much a baby goes to the bathroom and even its sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK calls 'escalation'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48237d0b56374bcfa857cceca9adf977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
