<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PALIN OFFERS ADVICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1294489/sarah-palin-advises-kamala-harris-joe-biden-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SARAH Palin advised Kamala Harris to “trust no one” as she became the third woman on the presidential ticket. On Tuesday, Biden announced Harris would be his running mate as he attempts…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAR HOLDS ON!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/ilhan-omar-beats-primary-challenger-in-minnesota-394053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omar is the third member of the liberal 'Squad' to defend her seat successfully this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  She's 'nasty' and 'disrespectful'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/phony-kamala-trump-campaign-responds-harris-vp-pick-n1236467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and his campaign focused their attention Tuesday on Harris' criticism of Biden during the Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES in Crisis: Digital Subscription Goals Missed, Top Editor 'Asleep in Meetings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/los-angeles-times-stalled-subscriptions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Times lags far behind national competitors in its attempt to build a robust digital subscription base, TheWrap has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech millionaire McAfee arrested for wearing lacy thong as mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1288314/tech-millionaire-john-mcafee-arrested-thong-coronavirus-mask-norway/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  'Nailed' it...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-Latest-Trump-campaign-blasts-Kamala-Harris-15476254.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - The Latest on Democratic presidential contender Joe Biden's selection of California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate (all times local):  6 p.m.  President Donald Trump says he's "a little surprised" that his Democratic rival, Joe Biden, has selected Kamala Harris as his running mate.  Trump told reporters at a White House briefing that Harris "was very disrespectful to Joe Biden" during the Democratic primaries, and said "it's hard to pick somebody that's that disrespectful."  He's also noting that Harris "did very poorly" when she ran for the nomination - she dropped out in December - and says, "That's like a poll."  Trump is trying to paint Harris as too far left, saying she wants to raise taxes, slash funds for the militarily and ban fracking. He's also noting her tough questioning of now-Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh during his Senate confirmation hearing.  Trump says, "She was my No. 1 draft pick and we'll see how she works out."  Biden's campaign announced his decision to pick Harris as his running mate earlier Tuesday.  Trump last month had said she would be "a fine choice."  __  5:50 p.m.  Vice President Mike Pence is welcoming his Democratic rival to the race after former vice president Joe Biden named California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate.  Speaking in Arizona, the Republican used the opportunity to attack the Biden-Harris ticket. "As you all know, Joe Biden and the Democratic Party have been overtaken by the radical left," Pence said. "So given their promises of higher taxes, open borders, socialized medicine and abortion on demand, it's no surprise that he chose Senator Harris."  Pence plugged the Oct. 7 vice presidential debate, scheduled to take place in Utah....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S KAMALA</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/joe-biden-vp-pick-kamala-harris-393768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris, the daughter of immigrants from Jamaica and India, was the wire-to-wire frontrunner for Biden’s No. 2 job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Escape Illness, Grandma's Living in Backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/to-escape-covid-19-grandma-s-living-in-the-backyard/ar-BB17Ppzd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  CNN's Jeff Zucker once feted...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article233256089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD:  Picked as 'do no harm' candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/opinions/why-kamala-harris-won-vp-content-axelrod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Axelrod writes that Joe Biden chose Kamala Harris, the charismatic and telegenic Black politician, as his vice president because, as a former prosecutor, she is best prepared to play a lead role in bringing the case against Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN-HARRIS First Appearance Set For Wednesday In Delaware...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kamala-harris-joe-biden-vice-president-democratic-presidential-running-mate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden campaign made the announcement in a text message to supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cartel Flooding U.S. with Meth at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/08/11/jaeson-jones-exclusive-mexican-cartel-labs-are-flooding-u-s-with-meth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increases in seizure data represented a significant tripwire from normal production amounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious in primary, now Kamala and Joe as one...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/11/kamala-harris-and-joe-biden-beefs-when-the-running-mates-clashed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody knows better than Joe Biden that his veep pick Kamala Harris can be a pit bull — she regularly went after him while still vying for the top spot on the Democratic presidential ticket. Harris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$250 Fine in Hoboken For Not Wearing Mask  -- Outside!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/11/hoboken-new-jersey-mask-fines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks are already mandated in New Jersey, but one city is taking it a step further, saying if you don't wear one outside where you can't social distance, you could face a fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First black woman on party ticket!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ac8fff8bbe1c70479604e3ff62ecb10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden named California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate on Tuesday, making history by selecting the first Black woman to compete on a major party’s presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bans blackface, anti-Semitic stereotypes in 'hate' speech update...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/8/11/21363890/facebook-blackface-antisemitic-stereotypes-ban-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This type of content has always gone against the spirit of our hate speech policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ten pulls plug on fall football season...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/college-football/story/_/id/29640222/sources-big-ten-pulls-plug-fall-football-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Big Ten Conference has decided to postpone all fall sports, including football, and will look to play those sports in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pac-12 cancels too...</title>
      <link>https://www.conquestchronicles.com/2020/8/11/21363837/usc-football-pac-12-cancels-football-fall-sports-season-2020-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conquestchronicles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s over — USC’s re-emergence into a national powerhouse will have to wait another year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following conservative playbook, progressives look to Supreme Court to motivate voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/conservatives-progressives-supreme-court-voters-2020-presidential-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll found that 57% of Democratic voters said the Supreme Court was "very important" in deciding which candidate to vote for in the presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot near White House had shouted threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/321832b186f689e6d8ce20087a6b1c0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A man shot and wounded by a uniformed Secret Service officer, prompting President Donald Trump to be abruptly escorted out of a briefing room during a televised news conference,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarium Washing Old Wishes To Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/08/10/901014658/aquarium-is-washing-old-wishes-to-pay-bills-during-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No coin shortage here: While it's closed for the pandemic, the North Carolina Aquarium at Pine Knoll Shores has drained a 30-foot waterfall and cleaned off 100 gallons of pocket change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PICK IS IN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/politics/biden-vp-pick/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has selected his running mate, revealing to top advisers on Tuesday the woman he will invite to join his Democratic presidential ticket, two people familiar with the matter tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida deaths reach another grisly record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/11/florida-coronavirus-deaths-reach-another-grisly-record-as-state-grapples-with-testing-constraints.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is one of the hardest-hit states in the country by the coronavirus, but daily new cases have appeared to decline in recent days. Testing, however, has fallen even faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines: Rodrigo Duterte Volunteers to Take It...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/08/11/philippines-duterte-volunteers-take-putin-approved-russian-coronavirus-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte volunteered to be the first person to receive Russia’s new coronavirus vaccine on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simon Cowell Walking Again After Back Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/simon-cowell-is-walking-again-after-back-surgery-151128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'America's Got Talent' judge is continuing to recover in the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'taken off suicide watch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8614925/Ghislaine-Maxwell-moans-conditions-hell-hole-Brooklyn-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell says she is under constant surveillance at Brooklyn's Metropolitan Detention Center despite recently being taken of suicide watch, and wants to be moved out of solitary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PICK IS IN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/2020-election-biden-vp-pick/h_afa9a64115c1cc49f873a18670b7cce6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden, the presumptive Democratic nominee, is expected to announce his running mate for the 2020 election ballot. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California BLM Leader Charged With 5 Felonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2020/08/10/tianna-arata-charged-five-felonies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtag #FreeTianna and a petition have gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo adds more states to quarantine list...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/11/gov-cuomo-adds-2-more-states-virgin-islands-to-ny-travel-advisory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY — Visitors from Hawaii, South Dakota and the US Virgin Islands coming into New York will have to quarantine for two weeks, as Gov. Andrew Cuomo announced the additions to his travel ad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court wary of ordering dismissal of Flynn case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5197ecacce9125418a68d3a7bf24917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal appeals court in Washington appeared inclined Tuesday to let a judge decide on his own whether to grant the Justice Department's request to dismiss the criminal case...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  DC-Area Real Estate Had Record-Breaking July...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2020/08/11/dc-area-real-estate-had-a-record-breaking-july/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The market has more than rebounded from the Covid-19 slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-Altered Squid Could Be Next Lab Rats...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/08/10/900886442/gene-altered-squid-could-be-the-next-lab-rats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first genetically-altered squid is here. NPR's Nell Greenfieldboyce explains how this breakthrough was made and why it's a game changer for scientists who study these critters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apt Bible passage at Catholic Mass coincides with temblor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33478d1002b8d27a590e51460d223ae0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — The Scripture quite literally came to life for several Catholic churches in North Carolina as a rare earthquake rattled portions of the state over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How pet chihuahua rushed to save life of man having stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnct.com/local-news/man-shares-how-his-pet-chihuahua-saved-his-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnct.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORIENTAL N.C. (WNCT) – People say dogs are a man’s best friend.  That is proving to be especially true for a Pamlico County man. Rudy Armstrong spends most of his time with his chi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID Becoming Worldwide Earthquake Detection Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/8/11/21362370/android-earthquake-detection-seismometer-epicenter-shakealert-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google starting small, but the implications are huge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii seeing fastest rate of spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/08/10/experts-covid-is-spreading-hawaii-faster-rate-than-anywhere-else-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s just a glaring example of how we need to be serious about this."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China increases military drills as tensions with USA heat up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/asia/china-taiwan-guam-military-exercises-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is stepping up military drills around East Asia as a war of words with the United States heats up over Washington's military activities and the visit of a US cabinet secretary to Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain again grapples with Europe's worst infection rate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-again-grapples-europes-worst-155113562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just seven weeks after bringing its first coronavirus wave under control, experts say Spain is once again in a &amp;quot;critical&amp;quot; situation with the worst infection rate in Western Europe. The country reported an average of 4,923 new daily cases of the respiratory disease during the last seven days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no end to pandemic in sight, coronavirus fatigue grips nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/With-no-end-to-the-pandemic-in-sight-coronavirus-15475104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabe Rice began sheltering in his suburban Phoenix home with his wife and three youngest children in March. They worked remotely, learned remotely and put social events on hold to hunker down alongside much of the country.  It was challenging and frustrating, but, Rice initially assumed, temporary. It seemed like a plausible plan to help the nation get the pandemic under control within a couple of months.  But Arizona's economic reopening in May, urged by Republican Gov. Doug Ducey, was soon followed by a spike in coronavirus infections in June, which became a terrible surge in hospitalizations and deaths by July.  Then came August, and the devastating realization for many Americans that the pandemic, which has killed at least 159,000 people across the country and sickened more than five million, is far from over.  "It's difficult when you think you have a light at the other end of the tunnel to look forward to, and then all of a sudden you realize it's a train," said Rice, 44, a program coordinator at Arizona State University.  An exhausted, exasperated nation is suffering from the effects of a pandemic that has upended society on a scale and duration without parallel in living memory.  The Rice family and millions of other Americans are wrestling with difficult questions about how to juggle school, pay their bills and look after their mental and physical health.  Parents lie awake, their minds racing with thoughts of how to balance work with their newfound role as home-schoolers. Frontline health workers are bone tired, their nerves frayed by endless shifts and constant encounters with the virus and its victims. Senior citizens have grown weary of isolation. Unemployed workers fret over jobs lost, benefits that are running out, rent payments that are overdue. Minority...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Quentin disaster exposes dangerous road to 'herd immunity'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/san-quentin-coronavirus-disaster-exposes-120059867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disastrous situation unfolding at California&amp;#39;s oldest prison over the last two months is shaping up to be the latest of several cautionary tales of how many people must get infected before &amp;#39;herd immunity&amp;#39; might be achieved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defiance of law, protesters in Thailand demand curbs on king's powers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/illegal-criticize-thailands-king-theyre-103403046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Student-led protests are calling for curbs on King Maha Vajiralongkorn&amp;#39;s wealth and power, openly defying laws against insulting the monarchy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Delay dental checkups until risk known...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200811130634-e0bs0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-DENTAL (TV, PIX):Delay routine dental checkups, WHO urges, until COVID-10 risk is known</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disinformation for profit: How Florida 'dealmaker' turns conservative outrage into cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Disinformation-for-profit-How-a-Florida-15474775.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality curated by "The Bearded Patriot" and "The Wolf of Washington" is dismal.  The websites tell of nonstop riots and "crazed leftists." They warn of online censorship and the wiles of an "anarchist billionaire," a reference to George Soros, the liberal investor and Holocaust survivor.  The material is tailor-made to inflame right-wing passions. But its underlying purpose is to collect email addresses and other personal information from impassioned readers, whose inboxes then fill up with narrowly targeted ads. The effect is to monetize the anger stoked by misleading political content - for as much as $2,500 per list of contacts.  An investigation by Alethea Group, an organization combating disinformation that draws its name from the Greek word for "truth," has linked the operation to Mark S. Evans Jr., a self-proclaimed "online multimillionaire" who affixes "DM," for "dealmaker," to his name. The network of 178 sites, at least half of which are politically themed and share visual as well as technical features, is designed to harvest email addresses, which are then sold to commercial brands, according to Alethea Group's analysis, and possibly also to political campaigns.  The findings, which were provided to The Washington Post, illuminate the financial motives behind the spread of hyperpartisan, low-quality news. And they reveal how merchants of misinformation are exploiting techniques of data collection to more efficiently capitalize on polarization and falsehoods and more effectively target specific communities.  "This is for-profit fearmongering enhanced by aggressive data collection," said Cindy Otis, Alethea Group's vice president of analysis. The digital marketing apparatus made possible by the sites, including lucrative data profiles of their visitors, "comes with the capability to support political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rice conspicuously left off DNC speakers list...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/930546/susan-rice-conspicuously-left-dnc-speakers-list-ahead-bidens-veep-announcement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats announced the lineup of speakers at next week's Democratic National Convention on Tuesday, and all the usual suspects are included â€” former President Barack Obama, Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.), and several ex-presidential candidates, like Sens. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) and Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.). But there's one name missing from the list that has pundits in a tizzy: Susan Rice, the Obama-era diplomat who is reportedly a top pick for vice president. Presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden hasn't announced his runningmate yet, and as he continues to punt the announcement, speculation has been escalating. He's already committed to selecting a woman, and is under some pressure to select a Black woman. But while another top contender, Harris, is listed as a speaker at the DNC, Rice is nowhere to be seen, despite her prominence and renewed spotlight as a VP possibility. Could she be the unnamed 'Vice Presidential Nominee' slotted to speak on Wednesday? Based on the official line up of the DNC convention, can we safely say @AmbassadorRice is the VP pick? pic.twitter.com/W2QL2GoxXR â€” Fernand R. Amandi (@AmandiOnAir) August 11, 2020 It's far from hard evidence, but with analysts hungry for an update in the veepstakes, it's hard to ignore. The DNC is set to begin on Monday, and will largely consist of pre-recorded videos and virtual appearances, to avoid the originally-planned gathering in Milwaukee. Delegates have been asked to stay home, though Biden is still expected to accept the nomination on stage in Wisconsin. Summer Meza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New poll shows tight presidential race in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511440-new-poll-shows-tight-presidential-race-in-georgia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden holds a slim lead over President Trump in Georgia, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankruptcies on track for 10-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-bankruptcies-on-track-for-10-year-high-with-more-than-100-consumer-companies-already-filing-2020-08-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. bankruptcies are en route to a 10-year high with 424 companies filing as of August 9, according to S&amp;P Global Market Intelligence. The group's analysis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: COMCAST Bans Laura Loomer From Sending Texts, Emails to Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/comcast-bans-laura-loomer-from-sending-texts-emails-to-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election meddling 101.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Highest-Paid Actors Of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/maddieberg/2020/08/11/the-highest-paid-actors-of-2020-dwayne-johnson-ryan-reynolds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never mind the box office. This year’s top-earning movie stars have a new way of filling their pockets with massive paydays</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Looting is reparations': BLM protesters defend unrest in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8614105/Chicago-goes-lockdown-bridges-raised-freeway-exits-closed-restrict-access-downtown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago is bracing for another night of looting and violence, after a wave of lawlessness in the early hours of Monday. Drawbridges to downtown were closed and SWAT police patrolled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameras to Detect Maskless Fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/mlb-baseball-coronavirus-new-camera-tool-could-detect-maskless-fans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB Teams Explore Using Cameras to Detect Maskless Fans at Games</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA CLAIMS VAX VICTORY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fcda62ad992db414d65f23b2adb78e44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia on Tuesday became the first country to clear a coronavirus vaccine and declare it ready for use, despite international skepticism. President Vladimir Putin said that one of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: George mocks Trump supporters suckered by lies...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2020/08/george-conway-burns-to-the-ground-trump-supporters-who-are-suckered-by-his-lies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, writing for The Washington Post, conservative attorney and Lincoln Project co-founder George Conway excoriated Trump supporters, by writing a parody of what one might say in defense of the president. “I believe Joe Biden is ‘Sleepy’ and ‘weak.’ I believe Biden could ‘hurt God’ and the Bible,” wrote Conway, the husband of White […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham Actually in Trouble in SCarolina?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/08/11/jaime-harrison-lindsey-graham-south-carolina-391886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anger at his support for Trump and a strong Democratic challenger have some wondering if the three-term Republican is in real jeopardy of losing in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kiwi media mogul challenging online giants...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200811-the-kiwi-media-mogul-challenging-online-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kiwi media mogul challenging online giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Escape Illness, Grandma's Living in Backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-11/to-escape-covid-19-grandma-s-living-in-the-backyard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omar faces tough primary test... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/primary-day-omar-minnesota-georgia-wisconsin-vermont-393389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her race in Minneapolis and a controversial GOP runoff in Georgia headline another busy primary day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT expands Republican target list, winning Trump ire...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511401-lincoln-project-expands-gop-target-list-winning-trump-ire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former GOP operatives behind the Lincoln Project are expanding their list of Republican targets, infuriating allies of President Trump and national Republicans scrambling to preserve the GOP majority in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook Hits Billionaire Status With APPLE Nearing $2 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tim-cook-hits-billionaire-status-161014685.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Nine years after Steve Jobs stepped down and thrust Tim Cook to the top of Apple Inc., the company is more valuable than ever -- and so is Cook.Apple’s share price rose almost 5% last week, leaving the company Jobs co-founded 44 years ago in his parents’ California home on the cusp of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Police Chief to Resign as Council Pursues Ambitious Plan to Cut Budget...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/11/seattle-police-chief-to-resign-as-council-pursues-ambitious-plan-to-cut-budget/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — As City Council members in Seattle pursue an ambitious plan to cut dozens of police officers and create</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Wake of Lockdowns, Troubling Surge in Homicides...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/11/in-the-wake-of-covid-19-lockdowns-a-troubling-surge-in-homicides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. — It started with an afternoon stop at a gas station. Two customers began exchanging angry stares</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York's true nursing home death toll cloaked in secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/212ccd87924b6906053703a00514647f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Riverdale Nursing Home in the Bronx appears, on paper, to have escaped the worst of the coronavirus pandemic, with an official state count of just four deaths in its 146-bed...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
