<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Super Jabs in the Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-super-coronavirus-vaccine-could-be-in-your-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more pathogens like the one that causes COVID-19. That’s why a team of scientists began work on what you might call a “super-vaccine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Clapton blasts vaccine safety 'propaganda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9583109/Eric-Clapton-hits-propaganda-vaccine-safety.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary guitarist Eric Clapton, a lockdown sceptic, said his hands and feet became 'useless' - prompting fears he would never play again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey making calls as he weighs TX gov run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/16/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-governor-run-488536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s a beloved home-state star, but pundits are skeptical that the acclaimed actor has a chance at unseating Republican Gov. Greg Abbott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No alternative to passports, says airport boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57108969</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubai is the world's busiest airport and its boss says vaccine passports will get us flying again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lands on Mars in major advance for space ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-technology-business-science-e1c1d0679aa78a8cc79c04a4d1375322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China landed a spacecraft on Mars for the first time on Saturday, a technically challenging feat more difficult than a moon landing, in the latest step forward for its ambitious goals in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware a national security threat, big business -- and wreaking havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ransomware-is-a-national-security-threat-and-a-big-business-and-it-s-wreaking-havoc/ar-BB1gLSP7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 2,400 health care facilities, schools and governments in the United States were hit by ransomware attacks last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 3 Dead Prostitutes Triggered Wild Satanic Panic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-dead-prostitutes-triggered-wild-074213822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EpixThe Satanic Panic of the ’80s and early ’90s was fueled by wild stories about ritualistic killings, human and animal sacrifices, and pledges of allegiance to dark demonic lords. Most of those claims turned out to be tall tales, but that doesn’t mean they didn’t result in criminal justice system convictions. One such example involved the nightmare that befell Fall River, Massachusetts, (the birthplace of Lizzie Borden) in1979-1980, when three young prostitutes were found bound, bludgeoned to death, and, in one instance, horribly mutilated. Though the victims were all killed in a strikingly similar manner, police didn’t investigate them as the work of a single fiend. And in the case of the third slaying, they decided that the perpetrator’s motivation had less to do with personal impulses than with getting in good with a higher power: Satan.Premiering on Epix May 16, the Jason Blum-produced Fall River revisits this tumultuous episode in traditional docuseries fashion, employing archival photos and videos, newly recorded interviews, graphical flourishes, and unnecessary dramatic recreations to try to assemble a puzzle whose pieces, decades later, don’t quite fit. Director James Buddy Day’s four-part docuseries begins with the Oct. 13, 1979, murder of 17-year-old prostitute Doreen Levesque, who was found under a high school’s bleachers with her head brutally caved in by a blunt object. At the time of Doreen’s death, there was a turf war in the area between two rival pimps: notorious Carl Drew and 17-year-old Robin Murphy. The latter was dating a prostitute named Karen Marsden, who said that she was present at Doreen’s murder, which had been carried out by Carl. Karen, however, refused to outright finger Carl to the cops, and on Feb. 9, 1980, she was found murdered in Freetown-Fall River State Forest. Horrific: D.C. Sniper Boasts of Post-Shooting Sex ‘High’ With Accomplice in New DocLike Doreen, Karen had also been bludgeoned to death with a rock. And thanks to Robin’s testimony, police soon came to believe that Karen was the victim of a Satanic ritual orchestrated by Drew, in which he forced Robin to kill her girlfriend, perform oral sex on her corpse, and decapitate her so he could kick her head around the woods.This was a bombshell accusation, and it eventually led to Robin pleading guilty to second-degree murder in exchange for testimony against Carl, who received a life sentence for his mastermind role in the affair. Fall River’s recap of these events is bolstered by a thorough contextualization of Fall River’s street culture, where prostitutes and drug addicts operated out in the open mere blocks away from the police station, and where officers frequently plied informants with booze and drugs. To detectives Alan Silvia and Thomas Joaquim (both of whom participate throughout), it was clear that Carl was this milieu’s de facto “Satan,” and while they knew that Robin was a formidable figure not to be messed with, they were sure that Carl was the culprit they sought.Fall River, however, isn’t so sure about that. As the series lays out, there was no physical evidence against Carl, much less any real proof about Satanism; the only thing linking him to Karen’s murder was the eyewitness testimony of Robin, their driver Carol Fletcher, and Carl’s prostitute-girlfriend Leah Johnson, who revealed that Carl gifted her Karen’s ring shortly after the crime. More problematic still, in later years, all three of these women recanted their statements—most explosively Robin, who admitted at a 2004 parole hearing that she had made the entire Satanic story up. As if that weren’t enough to muddy the waters, Robin was also involved in a third homicide, in November 1979: that of Barbara Raposa, who was killed by Andy Maltais, a notorious pedophile who’d been terrorizing pre-teen girls for years, including Robin beginning when she was 11.Everyone who had any role in this tangled saga (and is still alive) participates in Fall River, including Carl. Yet clarity remains constantly out of reach. The fact that Robin was told about (or related in some way to) three different murders, ostensibly committed by three different men, that all were executed according to the same M.O., makes her look mighty suspicious. It also suggests that there was a serial predator on the loose—thus potentially exonerating Carl, who comes across as a shady and violent pimp but not, in the final tally, the man who ended Karen and Doreen’s lives. Day’s docuseries ultimately makes a compelling argument that there was one monster responsible for this reign of terror: Andy Maltais, because he knew all three victims; they were bound-and-bludgeoned in a manner that aligned with his kinky proclivities; and he had a motive to kill Karen, whom he might have wanted to silence before she exposed him as Doreen’s attacker.It’s a nice theory that makes more sense than any of the show’s other hypotheses. Unfortunately, though, Day doesn’t quite come up with explanations for all of the case’s outstanding questions. Chief among them has to do with Robin, who states that she lied to the cops in order to make sure Andy was convicted of Barbara’s murder, but who also supposedly lied to cover up Andy’s possible involvement in her girlfriend Karen’s killing in order to implicate Carl. Why Robin would have done that, or accepted jail time for a second-degree murder charge if she was totally innocent—and when there was no evidence linking her to Karen’s death—is similarly baffling, and contributes to an air of impenetrable confusion that Fall River is forced to embrace, to both haunting and frustrating effect, as it speeds toward a finale full of additional wannabe-explosive revelations.There’s at least one apparent miscarriage of justice to be found in Day’s docuseries, but by its closing installment, one gets the sense that there may be more story here to tell—especially in light of Carl’s ongoing efforts to secure a new trial. The abruptness of Fall River’s ending goes hand-in-hand with a formal approach that’s conventional at best and rickety at worst, undermined by cheesy chapter headings featuring scary devil-ish book illustrations. Nonetheless, as a mystery marked by inextricably knotted-up untruths, it’s a non-fiction work that’s been well-designed to spark heated debate and incite further inquiry—as well as, perhaps, beget a sequel.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Being Falsely Accused of Exchanging Money for Naughty Favors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/matt-gaetz-jokingly-compares-sex-trafficking-scandal-to-earmarks-at-ohio-rally-im-being-falsely-accused-of-exchanging-money-for-naughty-favors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz’s (R-FL) “wingman” may have signed a plea agreement in the federal case that is broadly rumored to involve Gaetz, but the possibility of pending criminal prosecution didn’t seem to put a damper on the Florida Congressman’s mood Saturday, as he spoke to a crowd of Trumplican faithful in Strongsville, Ohio, even cracking […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From gas to chicken: Supply chain woes bring soaring prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/15/business/supply-chain-price-increases/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Used cars, homes, lumber, gas and chicken: What do they all have in common? They're all getting more expensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100 million NJ deli fires wrestling coach CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/15/100-million-new-jersey-deli-company-fires-ceo-paul-morina.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hometown International has a massive stock market capitalization despite owning just a small New Jersey deli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the honor system work?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-new-mask-guidance-relies-on-an-honor-system-16179400.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That ongoing politicization of the pandemic tears at the fabric of a public-health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book cancelled for 'not including enough black academics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9583887/Acclaimed-British-author-Richard-Cohens-new-book-historians-cancelled-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British author Richard Cohen's book The History Makers has been dropped by its US publisher after concerns were raised that the book did not include enough black academics, reports the Guardian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugs coming back. Not everyone thrilled...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/hugs-are-coming-back-not-everyone-is-thrilled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research and development unit, military intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-defends-strike-on-gaza-media-building-noting-hamas-pij-assets-in-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-flag burning outside German synagogues...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/germany-vows-no-tolerance-after-israel-flag-burning-outside-synagogues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FM Heiko Maas promises 'unwavering' protection for Jewish houses of worship, following anti-Israel protests amid fighting in Gaza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews assaulted during protest in Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/jews-assaulted-during-a-pro-israel-protest-in-toronto-watch-668300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video footage shows pro-Palestinian activists beating pro-Israel counter-demonstrators during a protest in Toronto on Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press advocates condemn...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/553706-press-advocates-condemn-israeli-missile-strike-on-media-building</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press, Al Jazeera and other press advocates condemned the Israeli airstrike on Saturday that blew up the building housing them and other media outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask? No Mask? New Rules Leave Americans Recalibrating, Hour by Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mask-no-mask-new-rules-leave-americans-recalibrating-hour-by-hour/ar-BB1gM7FO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — For Americans whose bare faces had scarcely been seen in public for a year, there were suddenly options.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palisades Fire grows to 750 acres, prompts evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/crews-continue-battling-pacific-palisades-brush-fire-that-scorched-at-least-100-acres/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alongside water-dropping helicopters and fixed-wing aircraft, more than 110 firefighters continued to battle a brush fire in Pacific Palisades that has now scorched 750 acres and has prompted area …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL HAMMERS HAMAS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hamas-middle-east-israel-israel-palestinian-conflict-7bba1abb8a7bd0aadc2e796275ecb469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israeli airstrikes on Gaza City flattened three buildings and killed at least 26 people Sunday, medics said, making it the deadliest single attack since heavy fighting broke out between Israel and the territory's militant Hamas rulers nearly a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rombauer pulls Preakness upset, Baffert's Medina Spirit 3rd...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-sports-asia-sports-europe-bob-baffert-horse-racing-e8b7865ce0b837afd6bc36f306492da7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — Rombauer left Medina Spirit behind — and put horse racing’s latest controversy on the back burner. Little-known Rombauer sprung an 11-1 upset to win the Preakness on Saturday, passing Bob Baffert's Kentucky Derby winner to end a potential Triple Crown bid that would have carried a giant asterisk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Force commander fired after comments made on conservative podcast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/15/politics/space-force-lohmeier-fired-after-comments/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Space Force lieutenant colonel has been removed from his command after appearing on a conservative podcast criticizing the United States military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95-year-old might have found key to longevity: Purposeful life...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/95-year-old-might-have-found-the-key-to-longevity-a-purposeful-life/ar-BB1gLMHS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olga Murray, co-founder of a nonprofit group aiding Nepalese children, is still active, fit and happy — possibly because she’s helping others in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Internal Memo...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/read-internal-associated-press-memo-on-gaza-bureau-air-strike-an-incredibly-disturbing-development/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite has obtained an internal Associated Press memo on the Israeli Defense Force’s attack on a building that housed the AP’s Gaza bureau. On Saturday, the IDF gave a warning to evacuate before fighter jets then attacked and completely destroyed a 12-story building that housed offices for some international media outlets, including the AP and […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House says safety of journalists 'paramount'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/553701-white-house-says-safety-of-journalists-is-paramount-after-gaza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said Saturday that it communicated its concerns to Israel over an airstrike launched in Gaza that destroyed a building that housed several news organizations, including The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL HAMMERS HAMAS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210515162743-dgf7u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 9, PIX, TV):UPDATE 9-Israel-Hamas conflict rages as Israeli strike demolishes tower housing media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Cheney purging about more than Republicans' future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-purging-of-liz-cheney-is-about-much-more-than-the-future-of-the-gop/ar-BB1gLzws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheney’s removal from leadership post highlights a broader assault on truth and democracy led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Secret VENMO Found...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/we-found-joe-bidens-secret-venmo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The peer-to-peer payments app leaves everyone from ordinary people to the most powerful person in the world exposed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: DeSantis to change gambling landscape in Florida with sweeping new deal with Seminoles...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/let-deal-florida-legislature-sweeping-120800047.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis is on the verge of hitting a political jackpot that will bring legal sports betting to Florida and generate billions of dollars of new revenue for the state. The Florida Legislature on Monday will take up a 30-year gambling deal signed by DeSantis and the Seminole Tribe of Florida. It could be the moment in DeSantis’ governorship that cements him as a dealmaker. The ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP 'horrified' by attack on its office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-business-israel-palestinian-conflict-f595d0ea0a7e21a4e4974ae55e00024d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — An Israeli airstrike destroyed a high-rise building in Gaza City that housed offices of The Associated Press and other media outlets on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tells Israel to protect media after tower hit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210515150341-6oucn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV):UPDATE 8-Israel-Gaza conflict rages, U.S. tells Israel to protect media after tower hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUTONOMOUS TAXI GOES ROGUE, ESCAPES FROM RESCUE CREW...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/autonomous-taxi-goes-rogue-escapes-rescue-crew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An autonomous vehicle from Waymo got stuck in traffic after a glitch — and when roadside assistance showed up, it drove off and escaped them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash windfall helps Newsom shake recall election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-california-health-coronavirus-pandemic-elections-6cbcd71423f644dde623e85585bbb293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A fading coronavirus crisis and an astounding windfall of tax dollars have reshuffled California’s emerging recall election, allowing Democratic Gov. Gavin Newscom to talk about an end to most COVID-19 restrictions and propose billions in new spending as he looks to fend off Republicans who depict him as a foppish failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Have a little empathy': Bali tires of badly behaved foreign influencers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2021/may/14/have-a-little-empathy-bali-tires-of-badly-behaved-foreign-influencers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists threaten the island’s economic recovery by ignoring Covid protocols, including refusing to wear masks and even making a porn film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Lemon announces show ending...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-don-lemon-cnn-show-ending-20210515-gqfuumirl5dfng3zcqlp4bea4e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lemon clarified in a follow-up video that he is not leaving CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security threat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/14/former-navy-pilot-recalls-seeing-ufos-calls-them-security-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could UFOs be a danger to the United States’ national security? Former Navy Lieutenant Ryan Graves said he believes they are, in an upcoming “60 Minutes” interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing death: End-of-life doulas growing in popularity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-business-3b4e6af60889b69fde4f8fc14d01f7af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AURORA, Colo. (AP) — Ashley Scott describes the emotional side of her job as a death doula like a fountain in the middle of a lake. Her job is to help shepherd a dying person through an experience that is so intimate, common and yet mostly taboo in American culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands in London, Madrid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210515-thousands-in-pro-palestinian-protests-in-london-madrid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands in pro-Palestinian protests in London, Madrid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'SAW' Film to Top Box Office as Moviegoing Picks Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-15/new-saw-film-to-top-box-office-as-moviegoing-picks-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Gaetz Snorted Cocaine With Escort Who Had 'No Show' Gov't Job...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rep-matt-gaetz-snorted-cocaine-224503239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos via GettyWhen Rep. Matt Gaetz attended a 2019 GOP fundraiser in Orlando, his date that night was someone he knew well: a paid escort and amateur Instagram model who led a cocaine-fueled party after the event, according to two witnesses.The Florida congressman’s one-time wingman, Joel Greenberg, will identify that escort to investigators as one of more than 15 young women Gaetz paid for sex, according to a source familiar with the investigation.But what distinguishes this woman, Megan Zalonka, is that she turned her relationship with Greenberg into a taxpayer-funded no-show job that earned her an estimated $7,000 to $17,500, according to three sources and corresponding government records obtained by The Daily Beast.On Oct. 26, 2019, Gaetz attended the “Trump Defender Gala” fundraiser as the featured speaker at the Westgate Lake Resort in Orlando. Two witnesses present recalled friends reconvening at Gaetz’s hotel room for an after-party, where Zalonka prepared lines of cocaine on the bathroom counter. One of those witnesses distinctly remembers Zalonka pulling the drugs out of her makeup bag, rolling a bill of cash, and joining Gaetz in snorting the cocaine.While The Daily Beast could not confirm that Gaetz and Zalonka had sex that night, two sources said the pair had an ongoing financial relationship in exchange for sex. "She was just one of the many pieces of arm candy he had,” said one source familiar with the encounters between Gaetz and Zalonka.The congressman—who has declared that he “never paid for sex”—wrote off the stay at the hotel as a campaign expense, with his donors picking up the tab. Handout The U.S. Secret Service, which initiated the Greenberg investigation over allegations that Greenberg used county resources to mine Bitcoin, would not comment on the ongoing probe. Federal prosecutors with the Middle District of Florida would not say if investigators have questioned Zalonka. Greenberg’s attorney declined comment, citing attorney-client privilege.Gaetz’s office did not respond to a request for comment. However, his hired public relations firm, Logan Circle Group, did issue this statement: “Congressman Gaetz won’t be commenting on whether he dated or didn’t date specific women. The privacy of women living private lives should be protected.” Harlan Hill, the president of that firm, did not address questions about cocaine, the party, or the fundraiser.After repeated calls and messages to Zalonka over the last five weeks, her attorney told The Daily Beast on Thursday night that she “is not speaking to any media outlet.” Mark J. O’Brien, a criminal defense lawyer, said the allegations were not “accurate” but would not elaborate further. He did not respond to a list of detailed questions about the fundraiser party, Zalonka’s county contract, or her relationships with Greenberg and the congressman.Federal investigators are exploring Greenberg’s alleged role as the congressman’s go-to contact for arranging paid sexual encounters, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the probe. Greenberg is slated to plead guilty on Monday to six felonies and is expected to cooperate as a witness against his former friend.The Strange Friendship That May Bring Down Matt GaetzZalonka, who is an amateur fashion model and the communications director for the American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association, received $4,000 on Venmo from Greenberg during his first year in office in 2017—mostly in $500 installments. And Greenberg, who is married, listed various explanations for why he paid Zalonka. In the memo fields of his Venmo payments, he paid her $500 for “Stuff,” another $500 for “Orher stuff” [sic], and $1,000 for “Pool.” On a single day in November, he paid her $500 for “Food” and another $500 for “Appetizers.”But Zalonka’s interactions with Greenberg in 2017 morphed into a business relationship with the air of legitimacy. In December of that year, she was in close communication with him as she created her own company, MZ Strategy Group LLC, according to emails between Greenberg and Zalonka that were viewed by The Daily Beast. The next month, Greenberg awarded her a county contract, agreeing to pay her $3,500 a month for “management of digital content” and “production of social media engagements.”Zalonka’s firm received $3,500 installments in Seminole County taxpayer funds in January and April 2018, according to an analysis of Greenberg's government spending obtained via a public records request. Those payments would later be flagged as a “questioned or unaccounted for purchase” by county-contracted auditors with the Florida forensic accounting firm MSL. Even the tax office’s own chief financial officer, who processed the payments, noted in her reports: “do not know what it was for.”Auditors flagged other $3,500 installments in February, March, and May of that year, in the form of suspicious cash advances directly to Greenberg—but Greenberg never specified the purpose of those withdrawals. The charges appear to have ceased after that point.Four people familiar with Zalonka’s arrangement said it was a “no-show” contract. Zalonka never worked at the office, and it was unclear what service she provided, they said. Accountant Daniel J. O'Keefe, who led the forensic audit of Greenberg’s alleged self-dealing, said tax collector employees told him the woman behind the company was a mystery. O’Keefe added that he found no proof Zalonka ever provided the services itemized in her contract with Greenberg.“I have no idea what they were doing. And employees wouldn't know what they were doing. Totally a no-show job,” O’Keefe said. “There's no work product, no evidence work was done. It's just unbelievable.”Zalonka also features prominently in a tranche of Greenberg’s Venmo transactions, which include his payments to more than 40 women. Those women received hundreds of dollars at a time for memo items such as “salad,” “lemons,” and “ass,” according to financial records. The Daily Beast spoke to 12 of those women, who all said the payments were at least in part because Greenberg intended to have sex with them.Three young women paid by Greenberg, who spoke to The Daily Beast under condition of anonymity, placed Zalonka in the room during a 2018 encounter at the Duval Hotel in Tallahassee.One of the women—all of them 19-year-old students attending nearby Florida State University at the time—said Greenberg and a number of “well-connected Republican men” bought them drinks at the hotel bar, knowing how old the students were, then led them to a room furnished with “a huge pile of coke.” The men wanted to have sex with the teens and implied that Zalonka, who was in the room, would join in, one of the women recalled. When the teens refused, Greenberg, Zalonka, and another man went into a connected room to have sex, according to one of the former students and screenshots of a conversation between the three women reviewed by The Daily Beast.Zalonka had signed her marketing contract weeks before the encounter, and financial records show that Greenberg paid for a flight to Tallahassee with Seminole County taxpayer money around that time. American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association Executive Director Savara Hastings (left) and Megan Zalonka with Rep. Matt Gaetz. via Twitter Zalonka’s interactions with Greenberg’s circle extended to Gaetz as well. In mid-2018, Zalonka became a spokesperson for the American Medical Marijuana Physicians Association (AMMPA), a cannabis legalization group with close ties to Gaetz. The congressman was feted as a guest of honor at two of its conferences in 2018, and attended the previous year’s annual conference in October. The 2017 conference, which Greenberg also attended, featured Republican operative and Trump loyalist Roger Stone, who appeared at a Gaetz fundraiser after the congressman’s keynote speech. That day, Oct. 5, Greenberg used Venmo to send Zalonka $500 around midday—for “Rent.”Other AMMPA officials have close ties to Gaetz and Greenberg. In Gaetz’s book, Firebrand, published last September, the congressman singles out executive director Savara Hastings and her boyfriend, AMMPA chairman Jason Pirozzolo, as some of his “best friends.” Gaetz also says he has spent New Years Eve with the couple in the Florida Keys, and he has posted Instagram pictures featuring Hastings in Pirozzolo’s private plane as far back as 2014.Investigators with the Justice Department’s Public Integrity division are now examining Gaetz’s interactions with young women and cannabis industry contacts, CNN reported, as part of a probe into whether Gaetz was provided with sex from escorts in exchange for political favors. The sprawling criminal inquiry that originated with Greenberg has since morphed into an investigation into Gaetz’s role in an alleged prostitution ring that includes potential sex crimes with a 17-year-old girl.The probe could soon have a valuable new asset if Greenberg finalizes a cooperation agreement that could turn him into a government witness against Gaetz and others. While Greenberg was out on release during his final months of the Trump administration, he wrote a confession letter that said he saw acts “occur first hand” involving Gaetz and the underage teen.However, Gaetz has not been charged with a crime, and the government has not publicly acknowledged a case against him. Gaetz has also denied all charges, and told The Daily Beast on March 31 that the last time he had sex with a 17-year-old, he was 17 himself.In August 2020, the month federal prosecutors filed a superseding indictment against Greenberg to include the sex trafficking charges, Zalonka received a grand jury subpoena, according to news reports, as well as a person with knowledge of the subpoena. In a Facebook post the next month, AMMPA canceled its annual October conference for the first time, citing concerns related to COVID. The group hasn’t posted since.Gaetz, however, continued to engage with Zalonka online. As recently as March 11, he commented “Smiling ninjas!” on an Instagram photo of Zalonka. After The Daily Beast published its first report about Greenberg’s mysterious Venmo transactions, Zalonka made her Instagram private. In recent weeks, her account appears to have vanished entirely.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian march to defy Paris ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-paris-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-government-and-politics-e415198646e3752ed63f1c9627b8cafe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Marches in support of Palestinians in the Gaza Strip were being held Saturday in a dozen French cities, but the focus was on Paris, where riot police got ready as organizers said they would defy a ban on the protest.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
