<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Losing control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/18/fed-loses-control-of-its-own-interest-rate-on-day-of-big-decision-this-just-doesnt-look-good.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Fed was meeting to consider cutting interest rates, it lost control of the very benchmark rate that it manages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA JOLTED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74aaf4cf7ef148fdb75dfe977b99eb3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Canadian leader Justin Trudeau's campaign for national elections was hit Wednesday by the publication of a yearbook photo showing him in brownface makeup at a costume party in 2001....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDS TURN BLOOD BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/common-numbing-medication-turned-woman-s-blood-blue-n1055991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm weak and I'm blue," the woman told ER doctors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Stallone Kills Scores of Mexicans in Greusome 'RAMBO: LAST BLOOD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/rambo-last-blood-1240902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly four decades after the original, Sylvester Stallone returns as the iconic character for the fifth and supposedly final entry in the action-movie franchise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK auto-generating pages for Islamic State, al-Qaida...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3479209d927946f7a284a71d66e431c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the face of criticism that Facebook is not doing enough to combat extremist messaging, the company likes to say that its automated systems remove the vast majority of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  This Is Clearly Coming From Outside the Solar System...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/09/interstellar-comet-oumuamua/598204/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second known visitor to our cosmic neighborhood from another star is making quite an entrance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI WARNS:  BACK OFF IMPEACHMENT!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/18/pelosi-nadler-schism-impeachment-1501755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longtime allies are increasingly in conflict over the push to oust President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton unloads on President...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/18/bolton-trump-foreign-policy-1501932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recently fired national security made little secret of his disagreements with the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Crisis: Rash of Injuries to Elite QBs Could Imperil TV Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/09/18/nfl-crisis-rash-injuries-elite-qbs-could-imperil-tv-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has a big problem: Star quarterbacks are dropping like flies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater Chains Aren't Budging for NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/netflix-the-irishman-theater-chains-info-details/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day may come when Netflix and major exhibitors work together, but today is not that day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Hasidic Man Ambushed, Attacked By Group Of Men On NYC Street...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/18/caught-on-camera-jewish-man-ambushed-attacked-in-gang-style-assault-on-brooklyn-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance cameras caught the disturbing incident on Warsoff Place between Flushing and Park Avenues Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg Heads to Capitol Hill to Push His Version of Internet Regulation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zuckerberg-sets-talks-washington-future-regulation-204702314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook chief executive Mark Zuckerberg was expected in Washington Thursday for private talks with policymakers as the leading social network faces a myriad of regulatory and legal issues. Zuckerberg's visit comes five months after his stormy appearance before Congress, where he was grilled on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is NY Fed pumping billions into market?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-ny-fed-pumping-billions-money-market-220629543.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in more than a decade, the US central bank this week stepped into financial markets to keep interest rates on short-term lending from popping above its target range. The New York Federal Reserve Bank conducted money market interventions on Tuesday and Wednesday and planned another</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell downplays concerns about cash crunch... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-feds-powell-downplays-concerns-cash-crunch-financial-201952651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell downplayed concerns in recent days about a cash crunch in US financial markets, saying the situation says little about the real economy. Powell said the need to pay quarterly tax payments was a factor, which prompted the New York Federal Reserve Bank twice this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIKE!  GM drops workers' health care during walkout...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/gm-longer-paying-striking-workers-health-insurance-negotiations/story?id=65690103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Motors is no longer paying the health care costs for the tens of thousands of auto workers who went on strike on Monday, shifting the costs instead to a union fund. More than 49,000 union workers walked off their jobs on Sunday night, starting a nationwide strike at General Motors. As...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen sets apartment on fire trying to burn love letters from ex...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/torched-love-letters-295873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 18--The next time Ariauna Lillard decides to destroy some love letters from an ex-boyfriend, she will probably opt for a shredder, not a small butane torch. The 19-year-old Nebraska woman s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES mechanic accused of sabotaging jet may have terrorist ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article235199172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Exec: Trump Doesn't Drive Web Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/digital/news/cnn-digital-chief-trump-traffic-success-1203339480/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No subject might get as much attention across CNN’s digital properties as Donald Trump, but that doesn’t mean the news network is dependent on him for web traffic. Andrew Morse, executi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Asks Americans To Confess Their Climate Change Sins...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/18/nbc-news-climate-confessions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News is asking Americans to confess their climate change sins with their &amp;quot;Climate Confessions&amp;quot; project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis couldn't stop, even with top US defenses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44d47f54f8e14d5291b68c70028e2c77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Saudi Arabia spent billions to protect a kingdom built on oil but could not stop the suspected Iranian drone and missile attack, exposing gaps that even America's most advanced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 immigrants rescued from 18-wheelers since Oct...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/smuggling-of-migrants-in-tractor-trailers-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents have found many more migrants hidden inside tractor-trailers this year than last, suggesting smugglers are increasingly relying on the practice to move people throughout the country after they elude capture at the Mexican border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly mosquito virus reaches 10-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/deadly-mosquito-virus-has-michigan-urging-people-stay-indoors-n1055806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mosquitoes that spread eastern equine encephalitis like to feed at dusk, prompting a call from some health officials to stay inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Iger: If Steve Jobs Were Alive, Companies Would've Combined...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/09/bob-iger-remembers-steve-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he exits Apple’s board, the Disney chief reminisces about his relationship with its mercurial founder—and how their radical visions aligned to save two companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES mechanic accused of terror ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/airline-news/2019/09/18/american-airlines-sabotage-mechanic-accused-terrorism-ties/2365985001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the American Airlines mechanic has made concerning statements and has a brother who may be tied to the Islamic State extremist group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions may risk jail as Indonesia to outlaw sex outside marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-rights/millions-may-risk-jail-as-indonesia-to-outlaw-sex-outside-marriage-idUSKBN1W32BV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesia is poised to pass a new penal code that criminalizes consensual sex ou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA casts doubt on 2024 moon landing by astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d387ee26191c48d68a7390544beb5c9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A top NASA manager cast doubt Wednesday on the space agency's ability to land astronauts on the moon by 2024. Kenneth Bowersox, acting associate administrator for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ANGER</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/18/federal-reserve-cuts-interest-rates-1501881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed officials didn't forecast another rate reduction, but they didn't rule out the option completely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaccine protesters liken themselves to civil rights activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/18/california-anti-vaccine-civil-rights-1500976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The approach reflected the level of desperation among families staunchly opposed to vaccinating their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn actress turned reality TV star found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-porn-actress-turned-reality-20092943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jessica Jaymes was pronounced dead at her home in San Fernando Valley, LA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP 2.2%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/18/fed-ups-its-gdp-forecast-for-2019-slightly-to-2point2percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve dialed up its growth expectations slightly while keeping its inflation projection unchanged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Develop Groundbreaking Brain Implant...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scientific-breakthrough-may-eventually-allow-many-blind-people-to-see/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of volunteers are already seeing the promise of a new device, about 18 months into a five-year clinical study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican authorities find 29 bodies in a hundred plastic bags...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190918035251-dynpq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/:Mexican authorities find 29 bodies in a hundred plastic bags</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED CUTS RATES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/18/fed-decision-interest-rates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors largely expected the FOMC to cut rates by a quarter point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancels trip to UN...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-election-benjamin-netanyahu-un-general-assembly-0fb1e089-641d-48bc-9b0c-e7b0d57c0dce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu failed to gain a parliamentary majority in Tuesday's elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'America was never great': Communist group torches flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/18/communist-group-torches-us-flag-in-protest-of-trumps-los-angeles-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A self-described communist group burned an American flag outside a Los Angeles hotel Tuesday in protest of President Trump’s arrival in the city, sparking a series of fights with pro-Trump co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Brawl, Teens Gawked as Boy Lay Dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/they-videoed-his-death-after-a-brawl-teenagers-gawked-as-a-boy-lay-dying/ar-AAHrauw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POMPEO:  Oil attacks were 'act of war' by Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/saudi-oil-attack-act-of-war-iran-pompeo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo described the weekend bombing on Saudi oil facilities as an "act of war" and that they were an "Iranian attack" on one of the world's largest oil processing facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China driving rise of AI surveillance across Africa...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/africa/1711109/chinas-huawei-is-driving-ai-surveillance-tools-in-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Carnegie Endowment for International Peace says at least 75 nations are actively using AI technologies for surveillance purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIN AT PUMP: Gas Prices Spike...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/09/17/gas-prices-jump-10-cents-after-attacks-on-saudi-oil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone attack that happened halfway around the world is having an impact in Dallas-Fort Worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov't Collects Almost Everything About Everyone Entering USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/09/inside-look-all-data-cbp-collects-about-everyone-crossing-us-borders/159946/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency is putting more data in the cloud and integrating more of its collection efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart TVs leaking your data...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/smart-tvs-smart-home-devices-found-be-leaking-sensitive-user-n1055796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Nearly all TV devices in our testbeds contacts Netflix even though we never configured any TV with a Netflix account," the researchers wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO confidence sinks to lowest level since Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ceo-confidence-trade-war-uncertainty-319fb6a7-0f43-4928-a9cb-f08a3a9aa6a8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Business Roundtable's gauge of CEO confidence has declined for 6 straight quarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Can Now Gauge Your Risk of Cardiovascular Death...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/artificial-intelligence-cardiovascular-death-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new AI tool can determine whether certain patients will die within 30 days or up to a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON's Answer to Gun Violence: Ban Ads for Books About Ending Gun Violence...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/amazon-bans-ads-books-ending-gun-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By ending all weapons advertising—lethal and non-lethal alike—tech platforms are cutting off the chance to reshape a hidebound industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians protest over crackdown in growing solidarity campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190918-russians-protest-over-crackdown-in-growing-solidarity-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russians protest over crackdown in growing solidarity campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Views from top of world's tallest residential building; 1,550ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7477211/Manhattan-views-worlds-tallest-residential-building-Central-Park-Tower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skyscraper had its 'topping off' ceremony on Tuesday to celebrate the structure reaching its maximum height as it looms over Billionaires' Row. It will be opened in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massage therapist who accused Kevin Spacey of sexual assault dies...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/18/massage-therapist-who-accused-kevin-spacey-of-sexual-assault-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of death is unclear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS Release Video Of Brady, Brown Celebrating First Touchdown: 'I Love You, Baby!'</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/18/antonio-brown-tom-brady-micd-up-celebrate-touchdown-patriots-dolphins-week-2-nfl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before we move on to Week 3 of the NFL season, the Patriots are giving us a look at the sights and sounds of their blowout win over the Miami Dolphins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American Spends $7,400 Over Budget Annually...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/average-american-spends-7k-over-budget-every-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — Sticking to a strict budget is never easy, but it’s a necessary fact of life for tens of millions of Americans trying to save for their future. It’s usually not the end of the world if one goes a few dollars over budget or treats themselves to something nice, but a new survey…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Navy says it's tracking UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2019-09-17/u-s-navy-says-its-tracking-ufos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy acknowledged for the first time last week that 'unidentified aerial phenomena' shown in widely-disseminated videos are real</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BREAKING BAD' Returns: Movie Shot in Total Secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/breaking-bad-movie-aaron-paul-series-creator-revisiting-amc-show-1240406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their first interview about the new movie, star and creator reveal why they risked messing with their defining show ("Is there another story to tell?") and how they shot the hot Netflix project in near-total secrecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Brien replaces Bolton...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/18/trump-names-state-dept-official-robert-obrien-as-national-security-advisor-replacing-john-bolton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's announcement of his fourth national security advisor comes eight days after the abrupt departure of John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arabs poised to gain new voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4afb54069bff44a1b0e0564dd5adb917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel's Arab coalition appears poised to emerge as the main opposition bloc following Tuesday's election, a historic first that would grant a new platform to a long-marginalized...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMART FAUCET, TOILETS USE ALEXA TO LISTEN TO CONVERSATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/smart-faucets-and-toilets-use-alexa-to-listen-to-your-conversations_09182019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why it will be hard for Trump to win Wisconsin again...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/18/trump-wisconsin-suburbs-milwaukee-1501805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milwaukee’s Republican suburbs have never really warmed up to the president. That could be a big problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay man says churchgoers attacked him to pray away sexuality...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/church-under-investigation-allegedly-holding-down-gay-man-pray-away-n1055466 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They hold me down, pin me down, and I’m crying, and the Holy Spirit just comes through me, and they keep speaking in tongues," the alleged victim said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PROMISES TO 'PUT 720 MILLION WOMEN BACK IN WORKFORCE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/joe-biden-promises-to-put-720-million-women-back-in-the-workforce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wait, what?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doomsdays that didn't happen: Decades of dire 'climate' predictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/failed-climate-change-predictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While data from NASA and other top research agencies confirms global temperatures are indeed rising, a newly compiled retrospective indicates the doomsday rhetoric is perhaps more overheated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 51 has 'secrets that deserve to be protected'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/area-51-secrets-deserve-protected-20084954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Dave Goldfein has issued a strong warning to anyone planning to storm Area 51 to 'see them Aliens'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiker rescued after 'carrying' broken leg for two days...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-49737335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neil Parker began his agonising trip to safety after falling 6m (20ft) down a waterfall in Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cliffhanger Leaves Israel in Mess...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cliffhanger-election-leaves-israel-mess-95119323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero dog dies in fire after alerting family about blaze...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox13news.com/news/local-news/dog-dies-in-fire-after-alerting-family-to-danger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leroy Butler woke up around 2 a.m. to the sound of the fire alarm in his hallway.&amp;nbsp;That alarm did its job as the fire spread through Butler's home, but only for a short time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart TVs Sending Sensitive User Data To NETFLIX, FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/technology/smart-tvs-caught-sending-sensitive-user-data-facebook-and-netflix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP: NY Fed Doubles-Down on Repo Intervention as Bank Cash Crisis Rattles Markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/fixed-income/ny-fed-doubles-down-on-repo-intervention-as-bank-cash-crisis-rattles-markets-15094169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu hits early; Nasty season ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/year-s-flu-season-may-be-bad-one-here-s-n1054856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are already signs the U.S. may be in for a nasty flu season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Overweight people more likely to have overweight dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190918-overweight-people-more-likely-to-have-overweight-dogs-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overweight people more likely to have overweight dogs: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preferably dead: Duterte offers cash for capture of freed felons...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190918094053-n6wsu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILIPPINES-PRISONS/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Preferably dead: Duterte offers cash for capture of freed Filipino felons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After more than decade, why is Britney Spears still under court-approved conservatorship?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-britney-spears-conservatorship-20190625-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than a decade, why is Britney Spears still under a court-approved conservatorship, which leaves decisions involving her estate and everyday life to others?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World faces increasing risk of pandemics that could kill millions, panel says...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/world-faces-increasing-risk-of-pandemics-that-could-kill-millions-panel-says-1.4022186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitoring board warns warned epidemic-prone viral diseases are increasingly tough to manage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, rightist allies appear to fall short of majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0184d4c11e0a495780d5f780632da855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel's two main political parties were deadlocked Wednesday after an unprecedented repeat election, with Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu facing an uphill battle to hold on to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor arrested after third man overdoses at home...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/09/17/dem-donor-ed-buck-arrested-after-3rd-mans-overdose-charged-with-operating-west-hollywood-drug-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Buck, a prominent Democratic donor and political activist, was arrested Tuesday and charged with operating a drug house and providing methamphetamine to a 37-year-old man who suffered an overdose at Buck's West Hollywood apartment last week, the Los Angeles County District Attorney's Office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-september-18-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miki Zohar says legislation blasted as racist backfired on Likud by lulling its supporters while energizing minority Netanyahu hoped would not turn out on election day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL DEADLOCKED</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious drug dealer sets up YOUTUBE account -- from jail!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7475605/Notorious-inmate-taunted-police-run-sets-YouTube-account-jail-cell.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted drug dealer Sam Walker has been able to maintain multiple social media accounts while serving time in Leeds. His Twitter account has around 19,000 followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Car plows into lobby of Trump Plaza condominium complex...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/17/car-plows-trump-plaza-new-rochelle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The black Mercedes left a trail of destruction and broken glass in the front of the building on Huguenot Street before coming to a stop inside Trump Plaza's main entrance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of abortions falls to lowest since 1973...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e45fe6f70cf45f1823a45ef9ad2187c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The number and rate of abortions across the United States have plunged to their lowest levels since the procedure became legal nationwide in 1973, according to new figures released...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon tribe in Brazil patrols territory, braces for fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d819f7ee60849c6bf850e53cec04cfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALTO RIO GUAMA INDIGENOUS RESERVE, Brazil (AP) — Deep in the Amazon rainforest, there is talk of a looming conflict over land. The men in the Tembe indigenous group sometimes daub themselves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning could be only way to avoid prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/For-Netanyahu-winning-reelection-could-be-the-14446537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time in five months, Israelis went to the polls on Tuesday to decide whether Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu will maintain his grip on power. A narrow win for Netanyahu in April failed to produce a governing coalition and led to the unprecedented do-over.  But for Netanyahu, the longest-serving prime minister in Israeli history, the election is about more than just keeping his seat. Winning could be the only way he avoids criminal prosecution.  Looming over Netanyahu are potential charges of fraud, bribery and breach of trust. Attorney General Avichai Mandelblit announced in February that he intended to indict Netanyahu on the charges which stem from three separate cases in which he allegedly agreed to political favors in exchange for gifts, in one case, or, in the other two, favorable media coverage.  But even if he emerges the victor from Tuesday's vote, Netanyahu could make Israeli history by becoming the first sitting prime minister to stand trial.  Analysts say this very possibility is what prompted the prime minister to call for early elections in December.  "He wanted to try and head off the indictments - if he could win an election before they were announced, he would have a stronger platform from which to face the indictments," said Yaël Mizrahi-Arnaud, a research fellow at the Forum for Regional Thinking, an Israeli think tank.  In the first case, called Case 1000, Mandelblit alleges Netanyahu accepted almost $280,000 worth of gifts, including champagne and cigars, from Hollywood producer Arnon Milchan. In exchange, Netanyahu allegedly helped Milchan, an Israeli citizen, extend his U.S. visa and asked his finance minister at the time for income tax exemptions to benefit Milchan.  In Case 2000, prosecutors allege that a conversation recorded by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando most dangerous place to walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/florida/os-ne-central-florida-most-dangerous-place-to-walk-in-united-states-20190917-5q5fm6ig25fpvdcm7eni46jeau-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central Florida is the most dangerous place in the United States to walk, according to a report by Smart Growth America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivors urge Congress to let them sue European insurance companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article235153132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas A&amp;M researchers quietly bred sick dogs in hopes of finding human muscular dystrophy cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/education/2019/09/12/texas-am-researchers-quietly-bred-sick-dogs-in-hopes-of-finding-human-muscular-dystrophy-cure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEGE STATION -- A colony of golden retrievers and Labrador mixes lives in an unmarked building at Texas A&amp;amp;M. Few Aggies will ever see them,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New focus on crowd size as  event rivals Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/New-focus-on-crowd-size-as-Warren-event-rivals-14447838.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle began on the first full day of Donald Trump's presidency, when the newly elected president instructed his minions to publicly exaggerate the size of his inauguration crowds.  The fight raged on as Trump continued to obsess and fret over crowd size - boasting, touting and sometimes inflating his own adoring masses at campaign rallies and presidential events.  Then finally this week, the Democrats - who have long tried to ignore Trump's bigger-is-better ethos - offered a tangible response of their own in the form of Elizabeth Warren's Monday evening rally in New York City's Washington Square Park, where the senator from Massachusetts showed that she, too, could match the spectacle of Trump, right down to the large cheering throngs.  "Yeah, the lines keep getting longer," Warren told reporters in New York on Tuesday, when asked about the four-hour wait for photos with her that capped her Monday rally, which was attended by more than 20,000 people. "That's a good thing!"  Once widely regarded as an interesting but ultimately inconsequential novelty of political campaigns, crowd size is now a potentially meaningful metric of electability - one that can translate into volunteers, donors and, as Trump demonstrated in 2016, actual momentum. Ever since, Trump has consistently drawn large audiences to his rallies, many of them held in less populated parts of the country and attracting supporters who often drive hours, across multiple states, to attend.  Speaking to reporters on Air Force One on Tuesday en route to California, Trump rejected the significance of Warren's Monday night masses - and with no evidence rebutted her crowd count - saying that "anybody" can attract crowds "standing in the middle of Manhattan in the most densely populated area of the country."  "I get these crowds in areas that nobody's ever seen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young White Liberals Flipping Red State Cities Blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/09/17/analysis-young-white-liberals-helping-to-turn-red-state-cities-deep-blue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities in red states are becoming increasingly deep blue as a wave of millennials and white liberals move from blue state cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> NKorea Could Have '40 Nuclear Bombs by End of Year'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2019/09/17/expert-north-koreas-nuclear-arsenal-may-grow-up-to-40-bombs-by-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An expert told South Korean reporters on Monday that North Korea may have as many as 40 nuclear weapons by the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot cleans floors, tells jokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/business-49717668/the-robot-that-cleans-floors-and-tells-jokes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 fully autonomous cleaning robots are coming to Singapore this year, made by local manufacturer Lionsbot. Ella's job is cleaning the floors at the National Gallery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election turnout 69.4%...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-votes-netanyahus-political-survival-013344588.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and his main challenger Benny Gantz were locked in a tight race in the country's general election after polls closed Tuesday, exit surveys showed, raising the possibility of another deadlock. Three separate exit polls carried by Israeli television stations</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
