<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Self-driving cars to function as moving brothels?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/07/brothels-could-move-self-driving-cars-academics-predict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brothels could move into self-driving cars, British academics predict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000-year-old art discovered in remote cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/11/news-oldest-animal-drawing-borneo-cave-art-human-origins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Southeast Asian island of Borneo joins a growing number of sites boasting early cave art innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sues for legal age change to help meet women on TINDER...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/07/man-69-wants-to-legally-change-age-to-49-to-help-him-pull-women-on-tinder-8115524/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘When I'm on Tinder and it says I'm 69, I don't get an answer. When I'm 49, with the face I have, I will be in a luxurious position.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former allies unload on 'selfish' Paul Ryan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/07/us/politics/democrats-republicans-house.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite warnings from within the GOP, Republicans lost their unity and grip on messaging, allowing the Democrats to gain a majority of congressional seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says he cannot save Brazil alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/far-bolsonaro-says-cannot-save-brazil-alone-184802795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - Brazil's President-elect Jair Bolsonaro said Wednesday that he alone cannot rescue the country from economic hardship and spiraling violent crime, as he met with outgoing head of state Michel Temer and the country's Supreme Court chief. Bolsonaro won an election run-off 10 days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada sorry for turning away Jews fleeing Nazi Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/canada-apologizes-turning-away-jews-fleeing-nazi-germany-211424218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Justin Trudeau apologized in parliament on Wednesday for Canada's refusal to admit Jewish asylum seekers fleeing Nazi Germany just months before the outbreak of World War II. On May 15, 1939 the ocean liner MS St. Louis departed Germany and crossed the Atlantic with 907 German Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortgage applications fall to 4-year low...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/real-estate/2018/11/07/housing-market-slows-mortgage-applications-fall-4-year-low/1919026002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The volume of mortgage applications last week fell to the lowest level since December 2014, providing another sign that the housing market is slowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Dem Indicates Impeachment Looming...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/senior-dem-indicates-impeachment-of-president-trump-may-be-looming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' wants a hug: Seeks court OK for tenderness...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/el-chapo-hug-alleged-kingpin-seeks-momentary-greeting/story?id=59030968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s most notorious drug lord, whose trial begins in New York City next week with opening statements, sought permission from the court to hug his wife. Defense attorneys asked that Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman be allowed to give his wife, Emma Coronel Aispuro, “a brief, momentary greeting to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramedics forced to watch porn, give sexual favors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7679364/female-ambulance-workers-porn-sexual-favours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEMALE paramedics were forced to watch porn and give sexual favours at an ambulance service where women were called “fresh meat”, according to a damning report into bullying. An indepen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Americans take out $50 billion in payday loans a year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ec19f9ce0684a3f9ce96711f4006ba1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Americans take out roughly $50 billion in payday loans a year, each racking up hundreds of dollars in fees and interest. But a small and growing service that allows its users to take an advance on their paycheck might be giving the payday loan industry a run for its money. San Francisco-based financial technology company Even made headlines late last year when Walmart, the nation's largest private employer, announced it would start offering Even's service as part of its employee benefits package. Along with providing tools that allow employees to track their spending and save money, Even features Instapay, which allows users to advance some of their next paycheck up to 13 days before payday. Because the Even user is tapping into his or her already accumulated hours, Even doesn't charge the employee interest on the advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gas tax increase here to stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article220929475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proposition 6, the ballot measure to repeal increases to California gas and diesel taxes, was defeated in the Nov. 6 midterm election. The initiative would have eliminated billions in transportation funding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramedics forced to watch porn, give sexual favors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/07/female-paramedics-say-they-were-forced-to-watch-porn-give-sexual-favors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Female paramedics were forced to watch porn and give sexual favors at an ambulance service where women were called “fresh meat,” according to a damning report into bullying. An independ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPPER:  GANGSTER...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/cnns-tapper-compares-trump-gangsters-press-conference-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN anchor Jake Tapper compared President Donald Trump to mafia bosses Wednesday, saying his leadership is reminiscent of films such as The Godfather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  Change 'won't come in one election'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/obama-change-wont-come-one-election-cycle-165606358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former US president Barack Obama spoke of his pride Wednesday over Democratic gains made in the midterm congressional elections -- but warned the battle for much-needed reforms had only just begun. Democrats won the House of Representatives on Tuesday but Republicans increased their majority in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest animal drawing found in remote cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/oldest-known-animal-drawing-found-remote-indonesian-cave-180318778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have found the oldest known example of an animal drawing: a red silhouette of a bull-like beast on the wall of a remote Indonesian cave. The sketch is at least 40,000 years old, slightly older than similar animal paintings found in famous caves in France and Spain. Until a few years ago,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT Study Proposes Shooting High Powered Laser Into Space To Attract Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/07/mit-space-laser-aliens-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The laser beacon could be "something of a planetary porch light."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WH staffer wrestles microphone away...</title>
      <link>https://www.abcactionnews.com/news/trump-scolds-cnn-reporter-for-being-rude-as-wh-staffer-wrestles-microphone-away-during-presser</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abcactionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A White House official wrestled a microphone away from a CNN reporter at a press conference with President Trump in the East Room of the White House Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rips Republicans who defied him...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-calls-midterms-big-win-tweets-goodbye-republicans/story?id=59028453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Those that worked with me ... did very well," the president tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>113 million voted, 33 flips, 110 female winners, $5.2 billion spent...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-numbers-113-million-voter-turnout-33-flipped/story?id=59028795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bottom line, elections are about how many votes candidates get, but other numbers can also tell us a lot about the trends that make up the two-year election cycle. Here are five of the most memorable from this election: 1. 113 million people voted About 113 million Americans are estimated to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midterms TV Ratings Boom: CBS, NBC, ABC Up Double Digits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/midterm-elections-jimmy-kimmel-live-tv-ratings-tuesday-nov-6-2018-1158936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early numbers have ABC, CBS and NBC collectively up by double digits versus the 2014 midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida voters approve amendment to end greyhound racing...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/opinion/audience/george-diaz/os-ae-greyhound-racing-amendment-13-vote-20181106-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greyhound racing Amendment 13 passes in Florida, phasing out sport by 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Cuq-hoCl0A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems plan to bring in for televised hearings if Trump fires him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/07/mueller-house-democratic-majority-970325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are primed to help the special counsel shed light on any illicit behavior by the president and his allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Pelosi's victory dance...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/nancy-pelosi-urges-cheers-for-pre-existing-conditions-breaks-into-awkward-victory-dance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something may seriously be wrong with House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi. On Tuesday night, Democrats won back control of the U.S. House of Representatives. While Republicans gained four seats in the U.S. Senate and won crucial gubernatorial races in Florida and Georgia, that didn’t stop the mainstream media from collectively airing Pelosi’s speech. During her …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAMS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6363625/Trump-ready-work-midterms-order-business-news-conference.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said he was looking forward to getting 'back to work' on Wednesday now that the mid-term election is over and suggested his first order of business would be trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS KEEP SENATE; +3</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fullpage/midterm-election-map-2018-live-results-58723598?whichMap=SenateMap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow hourly state-by-state senate, governor and house results and see who is in the lead Democrats or Republicans. House forecast in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS TAKE HOUSE; +34</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fullpage/midterm-election-map-2018-live-results-58723598?whichMap=HouseMap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow hourly state-by-state senate, governor and house results and see who is in the lead Democrats or Republicans. House forecast in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust Belt Defeats Are Warning for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/stinging-defeats-in-the-rust-belt-flash-a-2020-warning-for-trump#gs.D5ct4EM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stinging Defeats in the Rust Belt Flash a 2020 Warning for Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clear evidence cell phone radiation causes cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/scientists-find-clear-evidence-phone-13549308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rats exposed to radiation from 2G and 3G smartphones developed heart and brain tumours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI speakers will have face...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/weird-robotic-head-friendly-face-13549058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furhat's robotic head promises to give people a more friendly AI experience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recount on way in Florida Senate race?</title>
      <link>https://www.floridatoday.com/story/news/2018/11/07/election-results-rick-scott-recount/1917570002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.floridatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As votes were counted overnight, the margin of difference tightened to within the margin that triggers an automatic recount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin unloads on Trump after win; 'Junkyard dog'...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/joe-manchin-west-virginia-senate-win-trump-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I’m not angry because he came here so many times," Manchin said of Trump. "Why should he be angry that I’m telling the truth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's stinkiest fruit causes flight delay...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/07/worlds-stinkiest-fruit-causes-flight-delay/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indonesian airliner was delayed for an hour after passengers complained of an overpowering stench released from a load of the notorious thorny fruit durian, according to reports. About two tons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Robot 'KNOCKED medic's hand' during heart operation that went catastrophically wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6363243/Pioneering-robot-KNOCKED-medics-hand-middle-heart-operation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the assisting medics in Newcastle had his arms knocked by the robot which was being used to repair retired music teacher Stephen Pettitt's heart valve, an inquest was told today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco approves homeless tax on businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/07/san-francisco-proposition-c-homeless-tax-passes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's Proposition C, a measure to increase taxes for the city's biggest businesses to fund homelessness initiatives drew ardent support from Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff and criticism from Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey and other tech CEOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrats-biggest-gain-subpoena-power-090000272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Two can play that game!" Trump wrote Wednesday on Twitter. Now that Democrats have won control of the U.S. House of Representatives, they will be able to force administration officials to testify and provide documents. “The American people voted to give the House of Representatives a mandate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE set for another hefty fine?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-google-antitrust/eus-vestager-says-probe-into-google-adsense-case-nearing-end-idUSKCN1NC1S3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU regulators are close to wrapping up their third case against Alphabet unit Go...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP leadership fight begins...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/election-2018/415464-house-gop-fight-begins-jordan-challenges-mccarthy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Rep. Jim Jordan (R-Ohio) announced his bid for House minority leader on Wednesday, challenging Rep. Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) hours after Democrats regained control of the lower chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The homes on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/homes-mars-gyms-spas-wont-13544402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mansion on Mars could set you back £2.5 million - better start saving!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Welcome to gridlock'...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/stock-market-reaction-to-us-midterm-elections-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US stocks set to gain, Chinese stocks and dollar slip, Europe stocks rally. "Trump may now fall back on policy areas that do not require Congress."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff can't wait...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/abcarian/la-me-abcarian-schiff-20181107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much depends on what happens on Election Day. We spend the day with Democratic US Rep. Adam Schiff, who has become the calm voice of opposition to the Trump Administration. If Democrats take the House, Schiff will be positioned to become one of the biggest, most powerful thorns in Trump's side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks set to rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/stock-futures-open-flat-as-investors-await-midterm-elections-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures rose in early morning trade Wednesday as the U.S. midterm elections played out just as investors expected with the Democrats winning back the House of Representatives and splitting Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With election done, expect Mueller to make his move...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/07/with-the-election-done-expect-mueller-to-make-his-move/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the smoke from the midterm election clears, one thing is certain: You will be seeing the name of Robert Mueller a lot more than you have for the past two months, no matter whether the Democrat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three red states vote to expand Medicaid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/07/utah-idaho-and-nebraska-approve-medicaid-expansion-ballot-measures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Utah, Nebraska and Idaho were all projected to pass ballot measures to expand the federal and state health insurance program, according to NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils stealth combat drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/china-stealth-combat-drone-ch-7-under-development-middle-east/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has won drone deals in the Mideast and elsewhere with lower prices and fewer conditions than U.S. attaches to sales of military hardware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballot measures taking aim at 'climate change' fall short...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ballot-measures-taking-aim-at-climate-change-fall-13370355.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Efforts to nudge the nation away from burning fossil fuels and toward harnessing renewable source of energy were rejected by voters Tuesday across a swath of resource-rich states in the western United States. Voters in Arizona, one of the nation's most sun-soaked states, shot down a measure that would have accelerated its shift toward generating electricity from sunlight. Residents in oil- and gas-rich Colorado defeated a measure to sharply limit drilling on state-owned land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/07/2020-presidential-candidates-955261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The list of 2020 presidential candidates stretches across a wide spectrum of the left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PRESS CONFERENCE 11:30 AM EST...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-will-hold-press-conference-at-1130-am-eastern-2018-11-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbugs to 'kill millions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181107-superbugs-kill-millions-2050-unless-countries-act</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked memo gives taste of May's possible Brexit finale...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu/leaked-british-memo-gives-a-taste-of-pm-mays-possible-brexit-finale-idUSKCN1NC1JF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A memorandum leaked from within the British government gives a taste of a possib...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next in grocery wars: Mini-robot supermarkets...</title>
      <link>https://www.nasdaq.com/article/focusahold-ups-stakes-in-us-grocery-war-with-minirobot-supermarkets-20181107-00011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nasdaq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting gun sounds on 2020 White House race...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181107062554-n4blh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/2020 (PIX, TV):Next up? Starting gun sounds on 2020 White House race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust Belt Defeats 2020 Warning for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/stinging-defeats-in-the-rust-belt-flash-a-2020-warning-for-trump#gs.QSYtD08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stinging Defeats in the Rust Belt Flash a 2020 Warning for Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placebo Effect Isn't Trick?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/07/magazine/placebo-effect-medicine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research is zeroing in on a biochemical basis for the placebo effect — possibly opening a Pandora’s box for Western medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban-rural chasm deepens...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/415441-americas-urban-rural-divide-deepens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deeply divided electorate delivered a split verdict on President Trump’s first two years in office on Tuesday, one that reflects growing chasms along geographic and ideological faults. On one hand, suburban voters de</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human drugs flowing into animal kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/7dayarchive/article/Human-drugs-flowing-into-the-animal-kingdom-13367091.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millbrook  Modern medicines are moving through sewage treatment systems and into aquatic insects and the animals that eat them, according to an environmental study in Australia that involved a Hudson Valley environmental researcher.  Tests of six Australian streams near the city of Melbourne found animals there contained high doses of painkillers, antidepressants and other drugs that had gotten into the water after passing through municipal sewer systems that are unequipped to remove them.  "Stream life is swimming in a mixture of pharmaceuticals," said Emma Rosi, an aquatic ecologist at Cary Institute of Ecosystem Studies, based in Milbrook, Dutchess County. "While this study was in Australia, there is no reason to think it would be any different in the Hudson River, or any other place where there are people and drugs."  Rossi, along with Australian and Swedish researchers, examined caddisflies, spiders, and other insects, as well as platypus and brown trout, which are predators of such aquatic life in that region, for 98 different medical drugs between 2014 and 2015. They found 69 of the drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead brothel owner wins...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/dennis-hof-brothel-owner-who-died-last-month-wins-election-n933366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality TV star was found dead on Oct. 16 after a weekend of parties celebrating his 72nd birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Saudi journalist tortured to death?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6362321/Another-journalist-Saudi-Arabia-killed-torture-custody.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turki Bin Abdul Aziz Al-Jasser, who was critical of the royal family, is said to have been murdered in jail a month after Jamal Khashoggi was slaughtered in Istanbul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walker ousted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/07/politics/wisconsin-governor-scott-walker-tony-evers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Tony Evers will oust Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker from office, CNN can project, denying the Republican a third term and accomplishing something Democrats have long looked to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuses To Concede...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/history-trump-partisan-bitterness-collide-georgia-052057913--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Georgia's hotly contested and potentially historic governor's race may not be over yet, with Democrat Stacey Abrams saying ballots remain to be counted in her fierce battle with Republican Brian Kemp as she tries to become the first black woman elected governor in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hits ICE in victory speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/video/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-full-victory-speech-1363830339549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez' full victory speech after she won New York's 14th District becoming the youngest woman elected to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drops F-Bomb on Live TV During Concession Speech...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/politics/news/beto-orourke-drops-f-bomb-on-live-tv-during-concession-speech-1203021779/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O’Rourke was too proud to hold back an f-bomb on national television late Tuesday. Following a narrow defeat to Senator Ted Cruz in Texas, O’Rourke, the celebrity-backed Democrat a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems poised to slam Trump with subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2018/11/house-dems-already-have-their-list-of-trump-scandals-to-investigate-here-it-is/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subpoenas are coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax returns already in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trumps-tax-returns-already-in-democrats-crosshairs-as-they-take-the-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are eager to peak into President Trump's tax returns with their newfound power in the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY TO RUMBLE!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/38045/here-come-crazies-nancy-pelosi-speaker-maxine-joseph-curl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump just got an early Christmas present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems poised to slam Trump with subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/6/donald-trump-braces-investigations-galore-dems-tak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In September alone, Rep. Elijah E. Cummings, the ranking Democrat on the House Oversight Committee, called for the panel to issue subpoenas to the Trump administration on seven different investigations, ranging from immigration to Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABRAMS DOWN IN GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/georgia-governor-race-results-polls-vote-counts-stacey-abrams-brian-kemp-live-updates-2018-11-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race between Democrat Stacey Abrams and Republican Brian Kemp is a toss-up as votes start to be counted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM STARS WIPEOUT:  BETO LOSES...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/politics/article/Beto-challenge-to-Cruz-in-Texas-enters-final-hours-13368051.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke's national star power brought him closer to a statewide election win than any other Texas Democrat in decades, but in the end it was not enough drive home his long-shot quest to unseat Republican U.S. Sen. Ted Cruz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM COMES UP SHORT...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/ron-desantis-florida-governor-andrew-gillum-concedes/story?id=58904451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Racial tensions flared in the Florida gubernatorial race, with both President Donald Trump and former President Barack Obama stumping for their party's pick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans candidate falls short...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonblade.com/2018/11/06/hallquist-falls-short-in-vt-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christine Hallquist on Tuesday fell short in her race against incumbent Vermont Gov. Phill Scott. Hallquist would have been the first openly transgender person elected governor in the U.S. if she would have won.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Muslim congresswoman...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2018-midterm-elections-races-made-history-0c44017a-7a09-4429-90b0-ca25a2629fbf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first Muslim woman, first openly gay man, youngest person ever elected, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY TO RUMBLE!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c0be062914e048d79f70bcf120e1ccbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats were gaining ground in the battle for House control Tuesday night, while setbacks in Indiana, Tennessee and Texas squeezed their already narrow path to a Senate majority. With control of Congress, statehouses and President Donald Trump's agenda at stake, some of the nation's top elections were too close to call. Democrats won half of the seats they needed to claim House control with dozens additional competitive contests remaining. Victories in contested House races across Florida, New York, Virginia, Pennsylvania and Minnesota gave them cause for optimism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native American lesbian woman wins house seat...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/political-newcomer-davids-longshot-campaign-turn-republican-leaning/story?id=58853204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News partner FiveThirtyEight forecasts Sharice Davids with a five in six chance of turning the seat in a Republican-leaning Kansas district blue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABRAMS DOWN IN GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/georgia/governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Georgia Governor election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM COMES UP SHORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/florida/governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Florida Governor election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVIDED STATES OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/midterm-election-results-2018-n931571?DFsa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Ted Cruz held off a strong challenge from Beto O'Rourke for Senate in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM STARS WIPEOUT:  BETO LOSES...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/ted-cruz-democrat-beto-orourke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Senator Ted Cruz has hung on to defeat Rep. Beto O'Rourke, CBS News projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobach Goes Down in Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/democrat-laura-kelly-projected-to-beat-republican-kris-kobach-for-kansas-governor-nbc-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race was in a dead heat days before the election, with Kobach either up by 1 point or in a tie with Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shalala in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/democrat-donna-shalala-will-beat-maria-salazar-in-florida-27th-district.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shalala, Bill Clinton's HHS secretary, is the second Democrat to flip a Republican-held House district in the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD Republican Governor Reelected...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/gov-larry-hogan-wins-maryland-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Larry Hogan has won Maryland's governor's race. He is the first GOP governor to win a second term in Maryland since 1954.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez to be youngest woman ever elected to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/06/politics/ocasio-cortez-youngest-woman-ever/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Democratic congressional nominee Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez will win her general election race easily and become the youngest woman ever in Congress, CNN has projected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT FAILS TO ELECT DEMOCRAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/06/taylor-swift-fails-to-take-out-marsha-blackburn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop superstar Taylor Swift's endorsement of Democratic Senate candidate Phil Bredesen and Congressional candidate Jim Cooper failed to persuade the great people of Tennessee Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida votes to restore ex-felon voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/6/18052374/florida-amendment-4-felon-voting-rights-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victory means more than 1 million people will regain the right to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp political divide, rising hostility propel heavy voter turnout...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/6/sharp-political-divide-rising-hostility-propel-hea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans stormed the polls Tuesday to send an angry message, driven by a sharp political divide that fuels hostility toward the other side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC PROJECTS DEMS TAKE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/2018-house-election-results-n931416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats could take as many as 31 seats currently held by Republicans, according to the estimate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll chaos - busted machines, 3hr lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7677741/us-midterms-broken-machine-flip-votes  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE claim broken polling machines ‘flipped their vote in front of their eyes’ as chaos hit US midterms. Voters in South Carolina said their candidate picks, including in the governor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Discussion Turns to What Went Wrong...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/election/fox-news-throwing-in-the-towel-discussion-turns-to-what-went-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News Throwing in the Towel? Discussion Turns to What Went Wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Warns: 2018 Thanksgiving Travel Will Be Unprecedented, Busiest Season On Record Expected...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/transportation-security-administration-thanksgiving-holiday-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travel experts are already predicting the busiest Thanksgiving season at the airport on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2018-election/midterms/fl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find real-time results and maps for the 2018 Florida midterm election. Follow NBC News' coverage &amp; results of FL Senate, House and Governors elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First HOUSE seat flip: Wexton Beats Comstock...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/wexton-beats-comstock-va-10-nbc-news-projects-n932671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Jennifer Wexton has defeated Barbara Comstock in the race for Virginia's Tenth Congressional District, NBC News projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS:  HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 House election results &amp; live maps by state. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Rebukes Its Hosts for Participating in Trump Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/06/us/politics/trump-fox-news-hannity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The line between the Trump White House and Fox has always been a little blurry, but in one moment at least, the fusion of president and network seemed complete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2018-election/midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get election results in real-time as NBC News covers state results, exit polls, maps and candidates. View the House estimate, Senate balance and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVS... </title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/midterms-2018/gubernatorial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gubernatorial elections will be held in 36 states and three territories in 2018. Fox News is monitoring the governor races in the 2018 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://graphics.axios.com/2018-11-06-midterm-election/index.html?view=S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;graphics.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://graphics.axios.com/2018-11-06-midterm-election/index.html?view=G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;graphics.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fullpage/midterm-election-map-2018-live-results-58723598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow hourly state-by-state senate, governor and house results and see who is in the lead Democrats or Republicans. House forecast in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record high turnout for nonwhites in Georgia races...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-2018-exit-poll-analysis-56-percent-country/story?id=59006586&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_3_hero_headlines_bsq_hed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the polls are set to close in many states, preliminary exit poll results show a deep divide along party lines: Georgia In preliminary exit poll results, turnout among nonwhites is a record 40 percent, including 30 percent black voters. The previous high among nonwhites was 36 percent in 2014 –...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden issues surveillance warning to Israelis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/snowden-issues-surveillance-warning-israelis-225042347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US whistleblower Edward Snowden urged Israelis to be on guard against heavy-handed government and private surveillance in a speech by video link Tuesday and defended his 2013 massive leak of classified documents. Snowden highlighted Israel's high-tech capabilities, but warned that accepting too</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meat tax' to save lives, say health experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-meat-tax-apos-almost-180000966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ‘meat tax’ which would almost double the price of a packet of sausages should be brought in to prevent thousands of Britons dying each year, health experts have said. Researchers at Oxford University set out to determine the level of tax needed to offset the healthcare costs of eating red and processed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to become world's No. 1 travel destination...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2018/11/06/china-become-worlds-no-1-travel-destination-beating-france/1905119002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.4 billion trips will be made to China in 2018, up 5 percent from last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient dies 'after robot surgery error'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/05/heart-surgeon-turned-training-pioneering-robot-used-operation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A heart surgeon turned down the chance to train on a pioneering robot he used in an operation in which the patient later died, an inquest has heard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more associates of Roger Stone testify before Mueller grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Two-more-associates-of-Roger-Stone-testify-before-13368109.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more associates of Roger Stone, the longtime adviser to President Donald Trump, testified recently before a grand jury hearing evidence in the investigation into Russia's interference in the 2016 presidential election - the latest in a series of witnesses connected to Stone whose testimony has been sought by the special counsel. David Lugo, a filmmaker who interviewed Stone for a movie, told The Washington Post Tuesday that he has turned over hundreds of text messages, emails and Facebook messages to the grand jury. Lugo, who was a co-producer on the 2015 Oliver Stone film, "A Good American," also said he testified on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin Talk Show Bumped to Saturdays Amid Historically Low Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/alec-baldwin-show-bumped-saturdays-december-abc-1158835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news follows the actor's arrest and dismal ratings for the talk show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ORANGE planet: Stunning NASA image from Space Station shows Earth enveloped in rare 'airglow'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6360453/The-ORANGE-planet-Stunning-NASA-image-ISS-reveals-Earth-rare-airglow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The orange hue enveloping Earth is known as airglow, a diffuse bands of light that stretch 50 to 400 miles into our atmosphere,' NASA explained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI detects Alzheimer's disease SIX years early...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6359979/AI-detects-Alzheimers-disease-SIX-years-early-100-accuracy-small-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new AI system is 100% accurate in its predictions of Alzheimer's made based on subtle metabolic brain changes - and it catches the the disease six years early, a University of San Francisco study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More bones unearthed at Vatican embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bfc2871b2cc540c8a6ca3f490fbf3e5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — More bones were found on the grounds of the Vatican embassy in Italy, adding grisly new evidence to the growing mystery over who was buried on Holy See territory and why. As police returned to the compound Tuesday, coroner Giovanni Arcudi said preliminary examinations of bones found last week indicated they belonged to a woman likely in her 30s, "not an adolescent." The finding is significant since speculation has focused on whether the bones were Emanuela Orlandi's. She was the daughter of a Vatican employee who disappeared in 1983 at age 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanzania: 10 men arrested for being 'gay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.amnesty.org/en/latest/news/2018/11/tanzania-10-men-arrested-in-zanzibar-for-being-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amnesty.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were found at a party sitting in pairs, the police said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS at Crossroads as CEO Search Begins to Ramp Up...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/cbs-board-redstone-moonves-viacom-1203021104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two months after Leslie Moonves’ ouster from CBS Corp., the search for his successor has been sluggish and only now starting in earnest. But it won’t be a speedy process. The word that the C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>*Clinton campaign manager cautions against exit polls: 'They may break your heart'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/415312-clinton-2016-campaign-manager-cautions-against-exit-polls-they-may-break</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robby Mook, the former campaign manager for Hillary Clinton's 2016 Democratic presidential bid, cautioned ahead of Tuesday's midterms to treat exit polls "like online dating profiles."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEALTH CARE TOP ISSUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/watch-health-care-replaces-economy-most-important-issue-voters-early-n932536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 sailors busted for LSD on US nuclear carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2018/11/06/officials-ronald-reagan-lsd-probe-bigger-than-you-think-14-nuke-sailors-snagged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fourteen sailors from the Ronald Reagan's nuclear reactor department face discipline in connection to hallucinogenic drug abuse, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl Scouts sue Boy Scouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/girl-scouts-sue-boy-scouts-for-trademark-infringement-2018-11-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Girl Scouts say a Boy Scout rebranding effort is cutting into their turf, causing confusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% disapprove of Trump performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/exit-polls-show-trump-a-major-factor-in-2018-midterm-election-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of voters said President Trump was a factor in their vote, and a majority do not approve of his job performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly two-thirds said president was a reason for their vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/222fd1571d744aec903604542eb11b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Health care and immigration were high on voters' minds as they cast ballots in the midterm elections, according to a wide-ranging survey of the American electorate conducted by The Associated Press. AP VoteCast also shows a majority of voters considered President Donald Trump a factor in their votes. Control of the Senate and the House of Representatives is at stake in the first nationwide election of Trump's presidency. Democrats are hoping to take over one or both chambers to put a check on the president. At the same time, Trump is encouraging voters to view the election as a referendum on his leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats flip Republicans in first result of night...</title>
      <link>https://www.guampdn.com/story/news/2018/11/06/guam-general-election-results/1900152002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.guampdn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% disapprove of Trump performance...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-day-2018-americans-set-vote-historic-contest/story?id=58907692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are voting Tuesday in historic midterms, with control of the House, the Senate and 36 governorships at stake in a vote seen as a referendum on President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXITS:   56% say country on 'wrong track'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-2018-exit-poll-analysis-56-percent-country/story?id=59006586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump and control of Congress are front and center in this election, and preliminary results from the national exit poll touch on both of them: In results so far, 44 percent of voters approve of Trump’s job performance, while 55 percent disapprove. And while the House races will be fought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia plans moon base inhabited by 'avatar robots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/russia/443196-russia-space-avatar-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After unveiling an ambitious plan to install a permanent base on the moon, Russia’s space boss Dmitry Rogozin has now added a truly sci-fi-esque detail: humans will control it from Earth through sophisticated ‘avatar robotics.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wearing CROCS survives crocodile thrashing after breaking into farm, jumping into pond...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/florida/st-johns-county/st-augustine/man-bitten-after-jumping-into-st-augustine-alligator-farm-exhibit-authorities-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who broke into the St. Augustine Alligator Farm after hours and jumped into a crocodile exhibit was bitten and had to be taken to a hospital, according to St. Johns County authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Holiday sales predicted to surpass $1 Trillion for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/us-christmas-retail-sales-to-surpass-1-trillion-this-year-emarketer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total retail sales in the U.S will hit $1.002 trillion during the Christmas holiday period, marking the "strongest growth since 2011," according to eMarketer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Donde votar' spikes to top of searches...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/donde-votar-spikes-to-top-of-Google-Searches-13366861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Google Trends, 'Donde votar' - or 'where to vote - shot up to the top search term Tuesday morning, with search frequency jumping 3,350%, according to Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Physicists Write 'Perfect Pizza' Equation...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64016-physics-of-perfect-pizza.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physicists and food historians teamed up to create the ultimate pizza equation. The verdict: find a brick oven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T to cut off customers' service in piracy crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-att-to-terminate-service-over-piracy-for-first-time-1541465187-749442e3-7b71-4cc7-a694-865779b6fb96.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The copyright infringers are often illegally pirating hundreds of hours of stolen content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Soda Takes Cues From Tobacco To Combat Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/11/05/664435761/big-soda-and-the-ballot-soda-industry-takes-cues-from-tobacco-to-combat-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Oregon and Washington will decide Tuesday whether to strip cities of their ability to tax sugary drinks, thanks to ballot initiatives backed by Big Soda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils 'Heavenly Palace' space station...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-china-unveils-heavenly-palace-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China unveiled on Tuesday a replica of its first permanently crewed space station, which would replace the international community's orbiting laboratory and symbolises the country's major ambitions beyond Earth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
