<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wrongfully arrested man sues over false facial recognition match...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2021/04/13/michigan-man-sues-over-arrest-based-facial-recognition-software/7203369002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawsuit the latest in string of controversies surrounding Detroit police use of the software</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL to require jabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/nfl-to-require-employees-to-get-vaccinated-with-some-exceptions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL says that getting vaccinated is the fastest way to get back to normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nielsen, networks clash on stats showing fewer viewers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-television-coronavirus-pandemic-us-news-march-madness-ebcea77185f34f488b2f140d155094e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — People have been stuck at home for a year due to COVID-19 restrictions, with movie theaters closed, concert venues closed, restaurants closed, sports attendance restricted — yet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/live-updates-minnesota-police-and-protesters-clash-following-daunte-wright-fatal-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota authorities arrested about 40 people after rioters and police clashed for a second night in Brooklyn Center, Minn., authorities said during a press conference early Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France moves to ban short-haul domestic flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-56716708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MPs vote to stop flights where the journey could be made by train in under 2.5 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SIMPSONS' Star Hank Azaria Apologizes to 'Every Single Indian Person' for Voicing Apu...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/simpsons-star-hank-azaria-apologizes-190928978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hank Azaria has issued an apology for voicing Kwik-E-Mart owner Apu on “The Simpsons,” a controversial role he played for 30 years despite Apu being Indian. “I apologize for my part in creating that and participating in that,” Azaria said. “Part of me feels I need to go round to every single Indian person in […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE to sell used shoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nike-launches-refurbished-sneaker-program-11618327663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion brands are facing increased scrutiny about their impact on the environment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious UFO encounters could be 'hypersonic drones from China or Russia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2694546/ufo-us-navy-hypersonic-china-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIZARRE flashing objects caught on camera buzzing US warships may be hypersonic drones from China or Russia, a leading UFO expert has claimed. It comes after the Pentagon revealed to The Sun Online…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS anchor praises 'iconic' speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-anchor-moved-by-biden-speech-honoring-slain-officer-he-is-iconic-with-kindness-and-empathy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Harris Faulkner was moved by the emotional address President Joe Biden gave at the memorial ceremony for Billy Evans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Succession Turns Nasty With Mudslinging and Threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/merkel-succession-turns-nasty-with-mudslinging-and-threats/ar-BB1fC0ur</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bavarian Premier Markus Soeder presented himself as a force for change who can revive the fortunes of Germany’s conservatives as he made his bid to follow Chancellor Angela Merkel at the top of the bloc’s election ticket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Strike at Eastern Canada's Biggest Port to Clog Shipping...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/partial-strike-at-eastern-canada-s-biggest-port-to-clog-shipping/ar-BB1fCexC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A partial strike scheduled to start Wednesday by Port of Montreal dockworkers threatens to increase congestion in other parts of North America and further waylay shipments at a time of surging shipping costs and delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop who 'mistakenly' used gun resigns; Police chief too...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/13/kim-potter-tim-gannon-resign-brooklyn-center-daunte-wright-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Elliott, the city's first Black mayor, announced Monday night that the City Council had fired the city manager and voted to give the mayor's office “command authority” over the police force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA APPROVES ABORTION BY MAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/fda-lifts-restrictions-on-abortion-pill-amid-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA’s latest decision applies only to the pandemic and does not detail how the rules will be enforced after it has subsided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NM Gov Pays $62,500 to Settle Sex Mistreatment Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gov-campaign-settles-ex-spokesman-140400557.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apr. 13—SANTA FE — Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham's gubernatorial campaign has paid at least $62,500 as part of a settlement with a former staff member who had accused her of sexual mistreatment during a staff meeting, according to documents filed Monday. The payments went to a law firm representing James Hallinan, a spokesman for Lujan Grisham during her 2018 general election campaign. The five ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK panel to review requests to remove 'harmful' content...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210413-facebook-panel-to-review-requests-to-remove-harmful-content</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook panel to review requests to remove 'harmful' content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's plea for masks will fail. Blame political polarization...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Biden-s-plea-for-masks-will-fail-Blame-political-16096570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the immediate measures to combat a fourth wave of coronavirus cases, wearing masks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFER TO BE OUTSIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-year-into-the-pandemic-its-even-more-clear-that-its-safer-to-be-outside/ar-BB1fB80J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many scientists and public health experts say that the outdoor spaces warming under spring sun should be viewed as havens in the battle against coronavirus and restriction-induced fatigue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Staffer Duped Into TINDER Dates With PROJECT VERITAS Spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-james-okeefe-releases-secret-recordings-of-cnn-staffer-calling-network-pro-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James O'Keefe's Project Veritas has new footage that reveals CNN employees describing how the network worked to support President Joe Biden's campaign during the 2020 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Asian Man Attacks Asian Woman -- Believing She Was White!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/04/12/police-michael-rhee-lake-forest-attacked-asian-woman-believing-she-was-white-retaliation-rise-hate-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Sangbong Rhee, 37, was arrested Thursday night at his home in Lake Forest. Irvine police say Rhee may have attacked a woman, believing she was white, in retaliation for the rise in hate crimes against Asian people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Biden tells kids their dad is 'hero' as cop lies in Rotunda...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2692987/cop-william-billy-evans-lies-honor-rotunda-killed-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE slain Capitol cop lies in honor at the Rotunda and is praised as a hero who put the safety of others first. President Joe Biden attended the ceremony for William “Billy” Evans, 41, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Digital Nomads' Fleeing Big Cities And Office Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/04/what-inspired-digital-nomads-flee-americas-big-cities-may-spur-legions-remote-workers-do-same/173295/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before the pandemic, there were people asking whether office life jibed with their aspirations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food cost jumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/consumer/get-ready-higher-grocery-bills-rest-year-n1263897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest spike in grocery bills comes on the back of prices that rose during last year’s pandemic stockpiling — and never went down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Aaron Rodgers Gets High Praise From Key 'JEOPARDY!' Exec After First Week Of Hosting Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/aaron-rodgers-gets-high-praise-from-key-jeopardy-executive-after-first-week-of-hosting-iconic-game-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Packers quarterback could be a front-runner to permanently host 'Jeopardy!'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal spray 'kills off 99.99% of virus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2689351/nasal-spray-kills-off-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-busting nasal spray has been proven to kill 99.99 per cent of the virus, research shows. It could prevent the transmission of coronavirus. For those infected it could shorten the duration o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk brain chips to be implanted in humans THIS year...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2691160/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-chip-humans-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk’s brain chip start-up could begin inserting technology into people’s minds later this year. The implants built by California-based Neuralink will one day allow those with phys…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can cup of yogurt cure your case?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/could-a-cup-of-yogurt-cure-your-case-of-covid-19-664976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pre-clinical research by Israeli scientists, published in Microbiome, indicates that Kefir could be used to treat cytokine storms caused by coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fireball captured streaking through Florida sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/massive-14ft-fireball-captured-streaking-23903685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expert said the asteroid measured about the size of a car as it hurtled towards Earth and burned up in flames. The space rock emitted a flash of bright light in the sky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBEr Jake Paul Accused of Sexual Assault...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/tv/youtuber-jake-paul-accused-of-sexual-assault-by-tiktok-star-justine-paradise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justine Paradise, a TikTok star with over 524K followers, has accused YouTuber Jake Paul of sexual assault in a 20-minute video of herself detailing the alleged incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Level in Office Amenities: Wild Horses...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/13/the-next-level-in-office-amenities-wild-horses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOREY COUNTY, Nev. — You can’t ride the wild mustangs at the Tahoe-Reno Industrial Center in Nevada, but you’re nearly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to enrich uranium to 60%, highest level ever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-iran-iran-nuclear-united-arab-emirates-dubai-5ee1f4cdca4ea2470c564ff3908015a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran will begin enriching uranium to 60% purity, higher than the program ever has before though still short of weapons grade, after an attack on its Natanz...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Already in New Normal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arizona-already-normal-090724749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clark/GettyEach night at precisely 8 p.m., in the Mule Mountains of Arizona and the quirky town of Bisbee, a joyful fracas echoes across the steep walls of Tombstone Canyon. Some howl, some bark, some yip, like scattered coyotes caterwauling in the desert night.At the start of the pandemic, this ritual was like many across the country, fashioned as a vocal appreciation of frontline health-care workers risking their lives to care for the tens of thousands of people battling COVID-19 in health clinics and hospitals.Now, it feels like something else. A release. A clearing of the cobwebs that have for the past year cluttered the imaginations and inclinations of shut-ins everywhere. A roaring call to reawaken the lively spirit that courses through the veins of this old mining town, back to bustling outdoor dining and racing up and down the staircases that snake from one funky little tucked in house to the next, back to packed bars and roof-shaking rowdy live music. The spirit of these nightly calls, now, is “We’re back.” Or maybe, “We’re still here.”Thanks in part to a prevalent laissez-faire attitude from citizens and government officials alike, Arizona has been rocked by the pandemic, often finding itself in the dubious category of states with the highest rate of transmission, cases per capita, and deaths. In mid-January, the state led the world in average new confirmed COVID-19 cases per capita.When I flew into Phoenix in early November for a quick stay at the charming Hermosa Inn, it was with plenty of trepidation, despite the consistency of mask-wearing and careful restaurant and hotel policies I saw throughout Maricopa County. When I returned for a road trip across the state this month, the vibe had clearly shifted, the tension I could once read in the eyes of masked service workers markedly softer.I barreled straight through Las Vegas and into Phoenix, stopping for a few nights at dispersed camping spots near mountain bike trailheads before heading on for a few nights in hip Tucson and then south to Bisbee, near the Mexican border. As a glimpse at the near-term future of post-pandemic travel, Arizona is a fascinating petri dish, a state with ample Trump supporters and COVID deniers but newly outnumbered by progressive city dwellers who helped flip the state from red to blue in the 2020 election. While travelers were far less likely to don masks in small towns like Bisbee and far more likely to do so in the capital the tone throughout has clearly morphed, from wariness to a refreshing brand of ease.Small towns were consistently the most relaxed, both in the fall and on this trip. Maybe half the travelers I saw strolling the shops of Bisbee were maskless, a number much lower than in Phoenix and Tucson, where even as new case counts dropped from a seven-day average in January that soared above 10,000 to just 630 at the beginning of April, most travelers and nearly all service workers were vigilant.Last fall, restaurant servers and hotel clerks had unmistakeable looks on their faces as they served tapas and tacos on outdoor patios, looks that said “I get to either risk my life to serve people food or lose my job.” On this trip, the cheeriness had returned, even as the masks remained.I stayed at several hotels across the state, both in November and March. In November, the Hermosa Inn, nestled into the Camelback Mountains north of Phoenix, was at maybe half its peak occupancy, by the looks of it. Now, the hotel is selling out night after night, says Director of Guest Experience Pam Swartz, with guests arriving from across the country.On my first night in Bisbee, I had dinner at Contessa’s Cantina, but only after a 20-minute wait. At gas stations throughout the state, patrons and clerks alike milled about maskless, a circumstance that would have driven me straight out of the store last year but that induced little more than an eye roll this spring. On hiking trails, where I’ve regularly seen people wear masks throughout the pandemic, trekkers were far more likely to breathe free, and I caught no glares for blazing by on a mountain bike with my own face unsheathed.At other hotels, people wore masks at all of them and shared elevators at none of them, but pools were open, mask-free, and packed. My girlfriend recounted walking into a bathroom at the JW Marriott Camelback Inn in Scottsdale to discover a woman at the sink, whose mask had fallen beneath her nose. She apologized, adding “clearly, my body is done with this,” meaning the mask, or the pandemic, or all of it.A couple nights later, a curious bellhop at the Omni Montelucia, his mask unapologetically below his nose, nearly climbed into my newly built camper van and peppered me with questions about what it was like to live in it, petting my exuberant pup before giving us a ride in a golf cart to the room. We were outside, so I didn’t mind the protocol slip. Masks had begun to feel obligatory and unnecessary, even though I know they’re not actually either. But this is how the new normal is playing out: we’re abiding by the rules, but less because we’re terrified and more because we’ve become accustomed to them, because we know the social order demands it, and because it’s the right thing to do.The last time I entered a public sauna was back in my hometown of Portland in March. The pandemic was new and real and scary but the yoga studio and spa I’d bought a monthlong membership to had enacted careful disinfecting protocols and I felt if I entered the space, I’d be alone and safe. What I wasn’t was welcome. The front desk clerk was clearly confused and probably terrified that I was selfish enough to visit a spa at the onset of a viral outbreak we didn’t know much about at the time, other than it was killing people at a rapid pace.Her concern wasn’t lost on me, and though I did go on a few short trips mostly by road and mostly by myself in the coming year, I did so as carefully as I could, and with people risking their lives to serve me in mind. I secured a COVID test and traveled to Hawaii in November, following to the letter the protocols outlined by local and state lawmakers to safely but cautiously reopen tourism, even as across the country covid counts were surging and traveling around the holidays was roundly shamed. My logic for the trip to Hawaii was that I’d arrive with a negative test result in hand, I’d be moving about in a state with the lowest case count in the nation, and I’d be supporting businesses that desperately needed my money.I felt welcomed in Hawaii, but nervously. No one really knew then whether even the most careful reopening of a state (that took the pandemic more seriously than any other) would be a sound idea. I was part of an experiment, and the tension I felt as a traveler was palpable.Now, I don’t feel that tension at all. That’s not to say travel is safe, even now that I’m halfway vaccinated. Cases in several states across the U.S. are surging, driven largely by a COVID variant my vaccine might or might not protect against. The CDC has issued confusing maxims in recent days about whether it’s OK to travel once you have a vaccine, and there are plenty of reasons to stay home, or at least stay off of airplanes.Barring another significant surge in cases that leads to overwhelmed hospitals and overwhelming deaths, that’s unlikely. Hotels across the country saw their highest occupancy rates since the start of the pandemic, Wyndham Hotels and Resorts CEO Geoff Ballotti said on CNBC. Spring break in Arizona was officially canceled at most colleges and universities, to avoid the mayhem that took place in locales like Miami. Events, like baseball spring training and festivals that typically lure visitors to the state, aren’t happening. But still, says Swartz, people are coming in droves. “They’re golfing, dining out, the restaurants in town are booming,” she said. Swartz went to dinner at a Scottsdale restaurant, Grassroots, for her birthday on Tuesday. Every table was full.Mandy Heflin’s fresh seafood business, Chula Seafood, survived the pandemic in part because the restaurant’s counter-service model made the transition to take-out only seamless. Now, her challenge isn’t finding customers; it’s finding employees willing to work. “There’s just no one coming in,” she said. “We’re putting ads out that normally would lead to five or 10 applicants per ad. Now it’s nothing.”Arizona is in its high season now, pleasantly warm and not yet searing to its infamous 115-degree summer temperatures. If, as officials are now predicting, a fourth surge in COVID cases is coming, that might coincide with the natural slowdown in summer tourist traffic, as the lah-dee-dah feeling I experienced last month melts away in the heat.If nothing else, I hope the nightly howls of Bisbee don’t abate anytime soon.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now people can see when GOOGLE spying on them!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2684643/website-reveals-google-spying-ad-tracker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HANDY web tool lets people know if their internet activity is being snooped on by Google’s controversial new “FLoC” ad-tracking system. The website “Am I FLoCed” fla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer patient saw tumors disappear after infected?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1422460/Coronavirus-Covid-patient-cancer-tumours-disappear-Hodgkin-lymphoma-blood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CANCER patient who caught COVID-19 saw his tumour disappear, a new medical report claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEVASTATING BLOW'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/jj-covid-shot-pause-will-delay-us-vaccination-efforts-says-dr-kavita-patel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supply of the two-shot vaccines from Pfizer and Moderna won't be able to quickly make up the demand created by the J&amp;J pause, Dr. Kavita Patel told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Daunte Wright's death, gun-Taser mix-up blamed for another police killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Before-Daunte-Wright-s-death-a-gun-Taser-mix-up-16096686.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a decade before Daunte Wright was fatally shot during a Minnesota traffic stop...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Longest Rabbit Stolen from Owner's Garden...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/pets/world-longest-rabbit-stolen-owner-garden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's longest rabbit title holder from the Guinness World Records was stolen over the weekend and its owner is offering a reward</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 15% of Americans worse off year into pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-personal-finance-poverty-coronavirus-pandemic-1c7c127f90cae6fe652a78364763fbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most Americans have weathered the pandemic financially, about 38 million say they are worse off now than before the outbreak began in the U.S. Overall, 55% of Americans say their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Brushing Teeth Twice A Day Keeps Alzheimer's Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gum-disease-alzheimers-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say having more "bad" bacteria in your gums shows a connection to one of the key biomarkers for Alzheimer's disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts baffled by spike in livestock shootings...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2021/04/12/shootings-utah-cows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah saw a huge spike in livestock being killed last year. The reasons are unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Prices Increase by More Than Forecast in March...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/us-consumer-price-index-march-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CPI for March was expected to rise 2.5% over the past year and 0.5% over the previous month, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia calls USA adversary, warns warships to avoid Crimea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210413103817-sjzzo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-CRISIS/RUSSIA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Russia calls US an adversary, warns its warships to avoid Crimea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan to release Fukushima treated radioactive water into sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/japan-says-release-fukushima-treated-radioactive-water-sea-n1263893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan Fisheries Cooperatives chairman said the decision was “absolutely unacceptable," and protesters demanded the plan be retracted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO urges halt to sale of live wild mammals in food markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210413-who-urges-halt-to-sale-of-live-wild-mammals-in-food-markets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO urges halt to sale of live wild mammals in food markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Times Square crowds show NYC returning to life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/12/times-square-crowds-show-nyc-returning-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s something we never expected to cheer: The Mickey Mice are back in Times Square, along with the Batmen and other buskers, including the accept-no-substitutes Naked Cowboy. It’s a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 not sole cause of excess U.S. deaths in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-covid-sole-excess-deaths.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the year 2017, the United States was already suffering more excess deaths and more life years lost each year than those associated with the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020, according to research from demographers Samuel Preston of the University of Pennsylvania and Yana Vierboom of the Max Planck Institute for Demographic Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India reels amid surge, affecting world vaccine supply...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-pune-united-kingdom-india-coronavirus-pandemic-55b7313c688b9a4c05a68a9c13e499da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — The Indian city of Pune is running out of ventilators as gasping coronavirus patients crowd its hospitals. Social media is full of people searching for beds, while relatives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Kremlin Mouthpiece Warns of 'Inevitable' War With USA Over Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-kremlin-mouthpiece-warns-inevitable-105301739.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John MacDougall/AFP via Getty ImagesAll-out cyber-warfare, nation-wide forced black-outs, and the targeted disruption of internet services—for one of the Kremlin’s top propagandists, all of those tactics are fair-game in what she describes as a fated war-to-come against the U.S.“War [with the U.S.] is inevitable,” declared Margarita Simonyan, editor-in-chief of the state-funded media outlets, RT and Sputnik, who believes the conflict will break out when, not if, Putin moves to seize more territory from Ukraine.As Russia’s military buildup on Ukraine’s doorstep mounts, Kremlin loyalists have been urging for even more overt aggression and bloodshed in the campaign to annex Ukraine’s Donbas region. The only thing standing in the way, they say, is U.S. support for their beleaguered neighbor.The club of G7 nations, which includes the U.S., issued a joint statement on Monday demanding an end to Russia’s troop build up on the border with the disputed territory of Donbas in eastern Ukraine, reminiscent of the build-up prior to Russia’s annexation of Crimea in 2014. The U.S. underlined those words by deploying two warships to the Black Sea.On Tuesday, Russia’s deputy foreign minister Sergei Ryabkov threatened retaliation. “We warn the United States that it will be better for them to stay far away from Crimea and our Black Sea coast. It will be for their own good,” he said.The escalation was foreshadowed on state television’s Sunday Evening with Vladimir Soloviev over the weekend. Simonyan explained that it was time for Russia to gear up for a showdown against the U.S., and prophesized a kind of war driven by hacking, the forced disruption of internet access, the shutting down of power supplies, and an all-out offensive on U.S. infrastructure.“I do not believe that this will be a large-scale hot war, like World War II, and I do not believe that there will be a long Cold War. It will be a war of the third type: the cyber war,” said Simonyan.She warned that—in this theoretical battle—the U.S. would plot to cut off the electricity of entire Russian cities. In turn, she speculated, Moscow would be able to force a black-out in Florida or Harlem at the flip of a switch.“In conventional war, we could defeat Ukraine in two days,” Simonyan said, “but it will be another kind of war. We’ll do it, and then [the U.S.] will respond by turning off power to [the Russian city] Voronezh,” she said.The top RT editor asserted that “[Russia] needs to be ready for this war, which is unavoidable, and of course it will start in Ukraine,” arguing that the Kremlin is “invincible where conventional war is concerned, but forget about conventional war... it will be a war of infrastructures, and here we have many vulnerabilities.”Her solution consists of Stalin-type measures to eliminate “vulnerabilities” in the run-up to another escalation, emphasizing the need for a hack-proof, government-controlled internet. “We still don’t have a sovereign internet, but god-willing, we will,” she said.She wholeheartedly endorsed a suggestion from Vladimir Zhirinovsky, the leader of one of Russia’s Liberal Democratic Party, who argued that all of Russia’s opposition must be eliminated by May 1, 2021. With imprisoned opposition leader Alexei Navalny on a hunger strike—and suffering from severe health ailments after being denied appropriate medical treatment—the Kremlin seems to be firmly set on that course.Simonyan argued that once Russia minimizes its vulnerabilities and renders Putin’s opposition powerless—which she argued could happen in a matter of months—the Kremlin will finally be ready to annex Ukraine’s eastern region.“I’ve been agitating and even demanding that we take Donbas. We need to patch up our vulnerabilities as fast as we can, and then we can do whatever we want,” she boldly proclaimed. The host, Vladimir Soloviev, wholeheartedly agreed: “We only lose if we do nothing.” He argued that by absorbing parts of Ukraine—or the entire country—Russia would be able to remove the zone of American influence further away from its borders.As one of the Kremlin’s most valued propagandists, Margarita Simonyan is notoriously close to the Russian president and has received multiple awards directly from Vladimir Putin. After accepting one such award in 2019, Simonyan thanked Putin “for the most important reward in life… this honor to serve one’s Motherland.”Her “service” has involved RT and Sputnik-driven disinformation operations aimed at influencing the 2016 U.S. presidential election, which she often boasts about by pointing to the inclusion of her name in various U.S. intelligence reports.Russia’s recent cyberspace activities seem to serve as good practice for the “inevitable war” foreshadowed by Simonyan.Last year, six Russian intelligence officers were criminally charged by the U.S. for using the world’s most destructive malware to force blackouts in Ukraine and damage the critical infrastructure of multiple countries, which caused nearly $1 billion in losses. On Monday, hackers operating from Russia targeted France's homeschooling platform.The Kremlin is prepared to intensify its offensive against the West, but fears of the retaliation that would follow. The idea of a bullet-proof “sovereign internet”—completely under government control within Russian borders—is already on the books, with Moscow having introduced the idea as a preventative measure against retaliatory hacking attempts from other nations.Simonyan argued that Russia will surely be able to exploit the U.S.’s “catastrophic” educational standards, and referred to American military analysts and specialists as incompetent and stupid. She heartily laughed about news that more than 200,000 U.S. service members experienced hearing loss due to defective earplugs.“We can never come to any agreements with [Americans],” Simonyan said, arguing that instead, Russia can just as easily defeat the U.S. in a cyberspace war.She added, mockingly: “We don’t even need the nukes.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Cuomo's White-Knuckle Ride...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/13/andrew-cuomos-white-knuckle-ride/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo lives, still, in a 40-room Victorian mansion on Eagle Street in downtown Albany, despite the television correspondents descending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop who 'mistakenly' used gun 25-year vet...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2690090/senior-female-cop-identified-daunte-wright-death-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE senior female cop who allegedly shot and killed Daunte Wright by accident was named, as a state of emergency was declared in Minneapolis. Kimberly Potter, a 25-year veteran of the force, allege…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to anger, and stakes, as Chauvin trial nears end...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/minnesota-killing-adds-to-the-anger-and-the-stakes-as-chauvin-trial-nears-its-end/ar-BB1fA1Ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting death by police of Daunte Wright added to fears of unrest after the verdict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN reporter confronted in heated on-air interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cnn-reporter-confronted-during-minnesota-protests-in-heated-on-air-interview-get-away-from-here/ar-BB1fB3tF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A demonstrator confronted CNN’s Sara Sidner in a live interview during protests over Daunte Wright's fatal police shooting, demanding that CNN leave the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: More clashes in Minnesota after Black motorist shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/13/us/daunte-wright-minnesota-shooting-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious over the fatal shooting of a Black man by a police officer during a traffic stop, demonstrators gathered Monday night to protest outside the police department of a Minneapolis suburb for a second night in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian priest hangs up cassock for love...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/italian-priest-hangs-up-cassock-for-love-01618308317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Churchgoers in a small town in central Italy assembled for mass as usual were hardly expecting a confession from their own parish priest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan's spike highlights fatigue over restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/547815-michigans-spike-highlights-fatigue-over-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes are on Michigan as the state endures a surge of COVID-19 cases, underscoring how fatigue with coronavirus restrictions, and political divisions, have disrupted the response to the pandemic across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers urged to re-think police calls for low-level crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/retailers-urged-to-re-think-police-calls-for-low-level-crimes-after-george-floyd-s-death/600044887/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the trial over George Floyd's death unfolds, many are hoping the case will prompt retailers to reassess how they treat Black and other minority customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii allows nurses perform abortions...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/hawaii-to-allow-nurses-to-perform-abortions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii law previously said only physicians could perform early, in-clinic abortions. But because of a doctor shortage, several smaller islands lack abortion providers which forces residents of those islands to fly to Honolulu if they need the procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battleground: Concrete barriers erected...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9463537/Twins-Wolves-Wild-postpone-games-following-police-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz announced a curfew from 7 p.m. Monday until 6 a.m. Tuesday for three counties following the death of Daunte Wright.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boehner says 'unemployed' Trump has nothing else to do but 'cause trouble'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/547712-boehner-says-unemployed-trump-has-nothing-else-to-do-but-cause-trouble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Monday said the "unemployed" former President Trump has nothing better to do than stir up trouble following his departure from Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: PANDEMIC AT 'CRITICAL POINT'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-hits-critical-point-europe-202237675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe passed the grim milestone of one million coronavirus deaths on Monday, as the World Health Organization warned that infections are rising exponentially despite widespread efforts aimed at stopping them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Minneapolis under curfew after officer shoots Black motorist dead...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/judge-refuses-sequester-floyd-trial-170813221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Minneapolis curfew was set to begin Monday after a police officer fatally shot a young Black man when she confused her handgun with her taser, fueling tensions in a US city already on edge because of the George Floyd murder trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:   Iconic Hollywood Cinemas Shutter Due To Economic Woes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/arclight-cinemas-and-pacific-theatres-wont-be-reopening-1234732936/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The last thing we needed to hear as the box office and exhibition are rebounding from the pandemic was a piece of bad news, but word spread like wildfire in distribution and exhibition c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINO'S using robots to deliver pizza...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/dominos-pizza-announces-autonomous-delivery-nuro-r-2-self-driving-car/10510677/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gone are the days of having your pizza delivered by someone. Now, Domino's is launching its on-road robot in this part of Houston. Here's how it works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne plastic pollution 'spiralling around the globe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/12/airborne-plastic-pollution-spiralling-around-the-globe-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising levels of microplastic pollution raise questions about the impact on human health, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal spray 'kills off 99.99% of virus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2689351/nasal-spray-kills-off-covid/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-busting nasal spray has been proven to kill 99.99 per cent of the virus, research shows. It could prevent the transmission of coronavirus. For those infected it could shorten the duration o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students at North Texas school disciplined for 'slave trade' held over socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/education/article250615554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Aledo school district confirmed students cyberbullied and harassed other students based on their race, but did not provide further specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen to meet with prosecutors FOR NINTH TIME in Trump probe; Have given 300 hours of testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-michael-cohen-meeting-manhattan-prosecutors-ninth-time-300-hours-cooperation-20210412-pr34536bkzbtpmlxpalg4rcvby-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen's latest rendezvous with Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance’s team of investigators — headed by veteran white-collar prosecutor Mark Pomerantz — will add to more than 300 hours Cohen’s already spent cooperating against his former boss in various investigations, the source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to anger, and stakes, as Chauvin trial nears end...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/minnesota-killing-adds-to-the-anger-and-the-stakes-as-chauvin-trial-nears-its-end/ar-BB1fA1Ef?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting death by police of Daunte Wright added to fears of unrest after the verdict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bicyclist killed in crash tweeted just hours earlier about danger of riding in DC!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bicyclist-killed-in-crash-tweeted-just-hours-earlier-about-the-danger-of-riding-in-dc/ar-BB1fA1aX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Pagels, an economics PhD student, was passionate about biking and advocated for road safety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish population at lowest percentage since founding of Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jews-make-up-smallest-percentage-of-population-since-founding-of-israel-664899</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close to the establishment of the state, the Jewish percentage of the population stood at 82.1%, while today it stands at only 73.9%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lachlan Murdoch Rejects ADL Calls To Fire Tucker Carlson...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/tucker-carlson-lachlan-murdoch-fox-news-anti-defamation-league-1234732832/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Corp. CEO Lachlan Murdoch responded to the Anti Defamation League’s call for the ouster of Tucker Carlson, concluding that the Fox News host was not advocating for “white replacemen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Indicted on 11 Sex Assault Charges in LA...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/harvey-weinstein-new-indictment-rape-charges-los-angeles-extradition-hearing-1234732596/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a new indictment coming down from a Los Angeles grand jury, Harvey Weinstein’s long delayed extradition hearing in upstate New York to face West Coast justice just hit the pause button anew. D…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Ellison bought $80 million Palm Beach tear down...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2021/4/12/22380192/larry-ellison-lanai-hawaii-palm-beach-mansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oracle founder moved to Hawaii late last year. He’s not coming back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario hospitals may have to withhold care as hospitals fill...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-canada-hospitals-idUSKBN2BZ205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors in the Canadian province of Ontario may soon have to decide who can and cannot receive treatment in intensive care as the number of coronavirus infections sets records and patients are packed into hospitals still stretched from a December wave.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
