<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HOCKNEY: Painting and sex secret to staying young...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8587481/David-Hockney-reveals-painting-nights-nice-sex-secret-keeping-spirit-youth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The English artist made the comments as part of the documentary David Hockney: A Bigger Picture and the unused clip has been released as part of a behind-the-scenes series called Hockney Unlocked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baboons Prowl Safari Park 'Carrying Knives and Chainsaws'...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/health/baboons-prowl-uk-safari-park-carrying-knives-chainsaws-sparking-chaos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans prep for leadership battle if he goes down...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/03/republican-leadership-battle-trump-389789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump loyalists and establishment-aligned conservatives in the House are already jockeying ahead of November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC debuts design of Mach 3 high-speed aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/08/03/virgin-galactic-debuts-design-of-future-mach-3-high-speed-aircraft-signs-deal-with-rolls-royce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic is making strides towards its goal of creating high-speed commercial aircraft that operates a little closer to Earth than its existing passenger spacecraft. The company revealed the initial design of the commercial passenger airplane it’s creating that’s designed to fly …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents struggle as schools reopen amid surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1bd44b60f9bb9ea769146c97e5fcd0f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shannon Dunn has to report to her job this week as a cafeteria manager at an elementary school in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, but she has no idea what she will do when her daughter starts kindergarten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug-Smuggling Cat Escapes High-Security Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/drug-smuggling-cat-escapes-welikada-prison-high-security-sri-lankan-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cat that broke out of prison is on the run after being apprehended with heroin and SIM cards it was smuggling to Sri Lankan inmates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The downward spiral of Ellen: A complete guide...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-downward-spiral-of-Ellen-DeGeneres-s-public-15453872.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did "50 Shades of Grey" star Dakota Johnson bring down one of the most popular talk show hosts in history?  Well, no - but you might have recently seen a lot of jokes on Twitter that say as much. Ellen DeGeneres's reputation has been on a downward slide since roughly last fall, when, during a particularly awkward interview, DeGeneres accused Johnson of not inviting her to a birthday party and Johnson replied with the now infamous quote, "Actually, no, that's not the truth, Ellen."  But that was just one in a series of controversial incidents surrounding DeGeneres, which culminated in a much more serious way last week after a pair of BuzzFeed articles alleged a toxic work environment on the daily talk show, as well as allegations of sexual harassment and misconduct by producers. Warner Bros. launched an internal investigation. DeGeneres sent an email to staff that said she took responsibility as the face of the show, but criticized her employees for not "do[ing] their jobs as they knew I'd want them done." As a result, she wrote, she and the production company will be "taking steps, together, to correct the issues."  If you're curious about how things got to this point, here's a guide to how DeGeneres's public persona went from the "new Queen of Nice" to even fellow celebrities calling her out for treating people "horribly."  - December 2018: The New York Times profile  Even if you don't regularly tune in to the comedian's hugely successful talk show (on the air since 2003), you probably know one thing: She's known for being super nice! Not only is her daily sign-off "be kind to one another," she used to open each episode with some goofy dancing, which endeared millions of viewers to her every afternoon. She frequently gives money and gifts to people in need, and has had many viral segments involving adorable small...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tlaib trouble...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510026-squad-member-rashida-tlaib-faces-strong-primary-challenger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) is facing a formidable challenge from former Rep. Brenda Jones (D-Mich.) in Tuesday's primary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore to make travellers wear electronic tags to enforce quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200803034958-vm6ei</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The devices will track wearers' movements, and any attempt to leave home will trigger an alert to the authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sturgis expecting 250K, stirring virus concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0d75610e63ef911674297c509be80d4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — Sturgis is on. The message has been broadcast across social media as South Dakota, which has seen an uptick in coronavirus infections in recent weeks, braces to host...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Former Pope Benedict seriously ill...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-benedict-health-idUSKBN24Z0RK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Pope Benedict XVI, the first pontiff in 600 years to resign instead of ruling for life, is seriously ill, a German newspaper reported on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Slide Is Warning America Lost Grip...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/dollar-s-10-slide-is-a-warning-that-u-s-has-lost-grip-on-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After hitting an all-time high in March, a gauge of the dollar has lost 10% of its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds gather for secret rave under NYC bridge...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/03/hundreds-gather-for-secret-rave-under-nycs-kosciuszko-bridge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Party like it’s COVID-19 — phase four. An illicit rave took place under the Kosciuszko Bridge in Brooklyn Saturday night, as bars and clubs remain on lockdown from the coronavirus. Some revel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Talking to Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/03/the-benefits-of-talking-to-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m a lifelong extrovert who readily establishes and relishes casual contacts with people I encounter during daily life: while walking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=32.750000000000:-86.750000000000:24.250000000000:-72.750000000000&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://apps.sfwmd.gov/sfwmd/common/images/weather/noaaport/radar_flanim.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.sfwmd.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yxkLe_86-rU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAR ON THE ROPES: Ilhan fights off tough primary challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/01/ilhan-omar-primary-challenge-381206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota freshman and "Squad" member faces criticism that she’s too divisive to effectively represent her district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transition Integrity Project games four possible scenarios!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/02/business/media/election-coverage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We may not know the results for days, and maybe weeks. So it’s time to rethink “election night.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to give TIKTOCK's Chinese owner 45 days to reach deal to sell...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200802230851-zffi7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TIKTOK/TRUMP (EXCLUSIVE, URGENT):EXCLUSIVE-Trump to give TikTok's Chinese owner 45 days to reach deal to sell-sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain to roll out millions of 90-minute corona tests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200802221349-mtir2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-TESTS:Britain to roll out millions of 90-minute coronavirus tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest tests positive after urging people not to 'cower in fear'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/washington_post/national/d-c-priest-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-as-health-officials-struggle-to-stop-its-spread/article_7ae10116-689e-55fb-b53c-92b66150bbdf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The pastor of a Catholic church who urged people not to “cower in fear” of the novel coronavirus has contracted the disease that it causes, prompting District of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine will not change world right away... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/coronavirus-vaccine-will-not-change-world-right-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the public imagination, the arrival of a coronavirus vaccine looms large: It's the neat Hollywood ending to the grim and agonizing uncertainty of everyday life in a pandemic. But public health experts are discussing among themselves a new worry:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area avoided spikes until fatigue...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/bay-area-had-avoided-spikes-until-shutdown-fatigue-early-reopening-and-prison-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - The Bay Area was supposed to be exceptional. It was one of the first metro areas in the United States to fully shut down to slow the spread of the novel coronavirus. Nearly everyone wears masks, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to Draft Reservists to Help Fight Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-to-draft-reservists-to-help-fight-coronavirus-outbreak/ar-BB17tsb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Plans 'Emergency' to Stay in Office, Top Dem Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-plans-emergency-to-stay-in-office-top-democrat-says/ar-BB17tUm9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective in as few as 50%?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/those-coronavirus-vaccines-leading-race-120006184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first wave of coronavirus vaccines might be like a flu shot, experts say, curbing symptoms in some patients but not protecting them from COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Could Get Election Story Wrong...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/02/how-the-media-could-get-the-election-story-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picture this Thanksgiving: Turkey, football (maybe), tenser-than-usual interactions with relatives. And perhaps a new tradition: finding out who actually won</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surges in India, Philippines; Australia imposes curfew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a92be68eb840ee875648f1de0110f3da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Surges of new coronavirus cases continued Sunday in India and the Philippines, which recorded another daily high to surpass 100,000 total infections, as officials across the globe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIRX: Virus 'extraordinarily widespread'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/02/politics/birx-coronavirus-new-phase-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Deborah Birx on Sunday said the US is in a new phase in its fight against the coronavirus pandemic, saying that the deadly virus is more widespread than when it first took hold in the US earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E </title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H-l6f4wcv2I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 62 days in space, approximately 1,024 orbits around our planet and four spacewalks, our #LaunchAmerica crew members are on their way home! Watch our li...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaias to track along I-95 corridor...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/isaias-to-track-along-i-95-northeastern-us-corridor-with-flooding-damaging-wind/787721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHEAST COAST ON STORM ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-02-tropical-storm-isaias-forecast-florida-carolinas-east-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the latest complete forecast briefing on Isaias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SET FOR SPLASHDOWN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf77af89c527340793d15a9957d30c84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The first astronauts to ride a SpaceX capsule into orbit headed toward a retro-style splashdown in the Gulf of Mexico on Sunday afternoon to close out a two-month test...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
