<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHARLIE ROSE: Accusers Exploiting #MeToo Movement...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/charlie-rose-metoo-exploit-dismiss-1202932044/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for Charlie Rose say his accusers are trying to spin “routine interactions” into a claim for sexual harassment, and are looking to have their lawsuit thrown out. Rose was sued…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheers in France as court blocks MCDONALD's sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cheers-southern-france-city-court-blocks-mcdonalds-sale-170732284.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees of a McDonald's in a deprived neighbourhood of Marseille, southern France, erupted in joy Friday after a court blocked the restaurant's sale. "We won, we won!" dozens of the 77 employees at the "McDo, as it is known in France, shouted after learning of the court'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crazy stuff' coming from White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/obama-slams-crazy-stuff-coming-out-trump-white-house-hits-n907546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president launched his strongest attack on the current president Friday, two months ahead of the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most important election in lifetime...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/obama-receive-ethics-government-award-university-illinois/story?id=57657053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Barack Obama is set to receive an award on ethics in government from the University of Illinois on Friday, as he is set to begin campaigning for Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China wants landing strip near US base in Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/global/europe/2018/09/07/how-a-potential-chinese-built-airport-in-greenland-could-be-risky-for-a-vital-us-air-force-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is China really buying with its investments in Greenland?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXERBRIEFS:  Beto livestreams laundry...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/boxers-briefs-beto-orourke-livestreams-laundry-57673137</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most ardent supporters know where Beto O'Rourke stands on single-payer health care (he's for it), legalizing marijuana (ditto) and a border wall (against). But anyone watching his Facebook Live feed as the Democratic Senate candidate tossed wet laundry into the dryer on a recent Sunday learned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular MAC App Acts Like Spyware...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/adware-doctor-mac-app-store-spyware/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adware Doctor has long been one of the top-selling apps in the Mac App Store. But researchers say it harvested browsing data, and sent it to China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants Sessions to investigate anonymous op-ed author...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/07/trump-wants-jeff-sessions-to-investigate-writer-of-anonymous-nyt-op-ed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president also said he was looking into the prospect of taking legal action against The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France says Russia satellite spied in 'Star Wars' hostility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3eb6e868cdec44f08dca288a034dff86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France's defense minister is claiming that a Russian satellite cozied up to a French one last year to eavesdrop on secure military communications, in what she said am</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUGUST JOBS: +201K</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-adds-201000-jobs-as-wage-growth-accelerates-to-nine-year-high-2018-09-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States created 201,000 new jobs in August, keeping the unemployment rate at an 18-year low and generating the fastest increase in worker pay since the end of the Great Recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUGUST JOBS: +201K</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/07/us-nonfarm-payrolls-aug-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Average hourly earnings rose 2.9 percent in August as the economy added 201,000 jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Roulette, Where Movies Never End; Algorithm Traps...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/netflix-roulette-where-the-movies-never-end/17824909/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In David Foster Wallace’s 1996 novel “Infinite Jest,” a filmmaker creates a movie so entertaining that it reduces viewers to dribbling catatonia. In the 1999 movie “The Matrix,” humanity is enslaved by machines that maintain a simulation of reality to keep everyone compliant. Nightmare visions in which slick entertainment anesthetizes the populace are nothing new. But no one could have predicted binge-watching, which means that once again reality has outstripped our wildest, grimmest imaginings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Security Expert Tied to WIKILEAKS Vanishes, and Internet Is Abuzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/07/world/europe/wikileaks-arjen-kamphuis-disappearance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arjen Kamphuis was last seen on Aug. 20 in a remote Arctic town in Norway. Online theories range from C.I.A. abduction to a secret mission for Julian Assange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Obama prosecuted leakers, gave lie-detector tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/flashback-obama-prosecuted-staff-leakers-gave-lie-detector-tests-paranoid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should President Trump need a model to use to track down leakers inside his administration like the “anonymous” insider who challenged his authority in a New York Times op-ed, he need go no further back than the Obama administration that prosecuted leakers and shutout the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living in Simulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/41749-elon-musk-living-in-simulation-rogan-podcast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're all probably trapped in a "Matrix"-like pseudoexistence, SpaceX chief Elon Musk said early Friday (Sept. 7) during a long, wide-ranging and very entertaining appearance on comedian Joe Rogan's podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren on Warpath: Time For 25th Amendment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/06/politics/elizabeth-warren-25th-amendment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren, seizing on an explosive op-ed from an anonymous administration official, said Thursday that it's time to use constitutional powers to remove President Donald Trump office if top officials don't think he can do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK GOES LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/07/tesla-sinks-8percent-after-bizarre-musk-podcast-appearance-cao-exit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock plunge extends a painful week for the automaker. As of Thursday's close, the stock had already lost 7 percent on the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120 Utilities Have Lowered Rates Thanks to Tax Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/thanks-tax-reform-utilities-are-lowering-rates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University hosts separate orientation for black freshmen...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/university-hosts-separate-orientation-for-black-freshmen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Mason University hosts 'Black Freshman Orientation.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK UNEMPLOYMENT NEAR RECORD LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/susan-jones/63-record-low-african-american-unemployment-august</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The midterm election is about "safety and jobs," President Trump told a campaign rally in Montana Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirty dozen: President has list of prime suspects...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6142895/Trump-list-dozen-suspects-furious-hunt-op-ed-writer-torched-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has a list of a dozen suspects who may have penned a New York Times op-ed that trashed President Trump, according to the paper, as the furious mole hunt continued Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama ready to roar... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/obama-won-t-hold-punches-he-kicks-midterm-campaign-push-n907241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president is expected to frame election as choice between an "inclusive" or "fearful" America, aides say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Rose files motion to dismiss harassment suit; Women 'exploiting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/charlie-rose-files-motion-to-dismiss-sexual-harassment-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rose was accused of "blatant and repeated sexual harassment," but says "none of the three plaintiffs alleges a cognizable claim of gender discrimination, harassment or retaliation"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: President WON'T answer 'obstruction' questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/giuliani-ap-trump-not-answer-232432807.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will not answer federal investigators' questions, in writing or in person, about whether he tried to block the probe into Russian interference in the 2016 election, one of the president's attorneys told The Associated Press on Thursday. Giuliani's statement was the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery builds over anonymous Trump official's identity...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/405458-mystery-builds-over-anonymous-trump-officials-identity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hunt for the identify of the senior administration official who penned a scathing and anonymous op-ed in The New York Times picked up steam on Thursday, as dozens of high-ranking Trump officials issued statements denying they were behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How eight elite San Fran families funded Newsom's political ascent...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/projects/la-pol-ca-gavin-newsom-san-francisco-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's wealthiest have supported Newsom for decades, spending big on his political career since his earliest days in public office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Malone cheats death AGAIN as high speed crash destroys ROLLS ROYCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7200956/post-malone-cheats-death-again-as-high-speed-crash-destroys-rolls-royce-two-weeks-after-plane-scare/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER Post Malone’s luxury Rolls Royce Wraith has been wrecked in a high speed crash near Beverly Hills in Los Angeles this morning, according to reports. There were reportedly no injures as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Hearing: How Booker's 'Spartacus' moment fizzled out...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/06/how-cory-bookers-spartacus-moment-fizzled-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Democratic Sen. Cory Booker turned a Supreme Court nomination hearing into a starring film role for himself Thursday — ­bizarrely claiming “this is the closest I’ll get to an ‘I am Spart…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader receives death threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/swedish-far-leader-receives-death-threat-party-113525268.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-right Sweden Democrats (SD) on Friday said their leader Jimmie Akesson has received a letter with a death threat as the party is on course to win record support in Sunday's legislative election. "We hope that this threat is not real," party spokesman Oskar Cavalli-Bjorkman told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Defies USA Bid to Curb Middle East Influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/iran-defies-u-s-bid-to-curb-its-middle-east-influence-1536318002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran is signaling that it will buck U.S. efforts to roll back its military presence in the Middle East, moving to cement foreign alliances and continuing to project power abroad despite sanctions that have helped put intense pressure on its economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, Russia, Turkey begin summit on Syria as bloody offensive looms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71aa04bb72b04fbca861eafba990859c/Iran-summit-holds-key-to-looming-battle-in-Syria's-Idlib</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — The presidents of Iran, Russia and Turkey began a meeting Friday in Tehran to discuss the war in Syria, with all eyes on a possible military offensive to retak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey jails filmmaker for movie portraying execution of Erdogan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180907110406-yp8cj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-ERDOGAN/FILM (PIX):Turkey jails filmmaker for movie portraying execution of Erdogan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore: This is war...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-filmfestival-tiff-fahrenheit-11-9/michael-moore-compares-trump-to-hitler-in-new-documentary-idUSKCN1LM318</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Michael Moore compares U.S. President Donald Trump to Adolf Hitler in his provocative new documentary, "Fahrenheit 11/9" that got its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on Thursday to a sold-out audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks turn to espressos, robots to keep branches alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-banks-branches-focus/banks-turn-to-espressos-dancing-robots-to-help-keep-us-branches-alive-idUSKCN1LN0FK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free Wi-Fi, discounted cappuccinos, artwork, and a dancing robot are among the features banks across the United States are touting to convince customers that even in an era of smartphones it is still worth it to visit a bank branch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election plunged into chaos...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180907085951-ge966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ELECTION/ (PIX, TV):Brazil election plunged into chaos by attack on far-right frontrunner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Far-right seen surging as Swedish election outcome uncertain...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180907-far-right-seen-surging-swedish-election-outcome-uncertain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Briefed Media Ahead of Alex Jones Blacklisting?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/09/06/twitter-briefed-establishment-media-ahead-of-alex-jones-blacklisting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter appears to have notified a number of establishment media publications ahead of its permanent ban of Alex Jones, while neglecting to inform conservative media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Angry; Indictment of system...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fahrenheit-11-9-review-michael-moores-new-movie-lot-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Film Festival 2018: The angry film starts with the president but grows into a sprawling indictment of the system that led to his election, and maybe even a prescription for change</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could reshape race...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8738209663040b29488f41c0a3fcd48/Stabbing-of-a-leading-Brazilian-candidate-could-reshape-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — The wounding of a leading Brazilian presidential candidate has the potential to reshape the election contest after dramatically exposing the deep polarizatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST warns of measles exposure on flights...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/health/southwest-passengers-in-texas-possibly-exposed-to-measles/4167077/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers on four flights between Dallas, Houston and Harlingen shared a plane with a passenger later diagnosed with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wounds reach liver, lung, intestines...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/06/brazil-jair-bolsonaro-far-right-presidential-candidate-stabbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right candidate injured in abdomen after stabbing on campaign trail in Juiz de Fora</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's top presidential candidate stabbed in street...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-election-bolsonaro/brazil-far-right-candidate-bolsonaro-stabbed-while-campaigning-idUSKCN1LM2YJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leading candidate in Brazil's presidential election is in serious but stable condition after being stabbed by an assailant at a campaign rally on Thursday, doctors said, pushing an already chaotic campaign into further disarray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Wild and wide-ranging podcast...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/09/07/elon-musk-joe-rogan-share-thoughts-laughs-and-a-joint-during-youtube-podcast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk’s appearance on The Joe Rogan Experience came on the heels of an audacious August in which he tweeted about taking Tesla private, publicly apologized to analysts for bad conference-call …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Socialist' attacker on 'mission from God'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6142245/Brazils-far-right-presidential-candidate-survives-life-saving-surgery-stabbed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking footage showed the moment far-right election hopeful Jair Bolsonaro was knifed in the stomach in the midst of a crowd in Juiz de Fora, Minas Gerais, south east Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk muses about life over whiskey and weed...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6142193/Elon-Musk-smokes-JOINT-live-Joe-Rogan-Experience-podcast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Tesla founder Elon Musk was seen smoking a joint in Joe Rogan's studio while they were recording a podcast which was streamed live on YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid cries, bleeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/hal-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new robot named Hal is sending medical training straight into the uncanny valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears humans will lose basic skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7196329/prince-charles-robots-human-skill-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Charles has revealed his secret fury at robots taking over the world — warning that humans are losing basic skills as a result. The 69-year-old has spoken out against society’s increasing re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico finds 166 bodies in mass grave...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180907-mexico-finds-166-bodies-mass-grave-veracruz-drug-cartels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican authorities discovered at least 166 bodies at a mass grave site in Veracruz state, prosecutors said Thursday, the latest horrifying find in a region hit by bloody drug cartel turf wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Charles Issues Robot Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/728023/prince-charles-gq-interview-robots-ai-human-machine-artificial-intelligence-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN:  Construction Worker Wages Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/09/06/trumps-tight-labor-market-wins-u-s-construction-workers-higher-wages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction workers are seeing rising wages as Trump's "Buy American, Hire American" agenda has tightened the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Hope Gets Crushed in Delaware...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kerri-harris-progressives-next-big-hope-falls-short-against-tom-carper-in-delaware</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-term incumbent Sen. Tom Carper beat back a progressive primary challenge in his toughest race in years—and will now serve what he has said could be his last term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportations up 9%; Still below Obama peak years...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/sep/6/deportations-9-percent-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration arrests and deportations are rising under the Trump administration, according to the latest statistics released Thursday — though they’re still far shy of the levels during the peak years of President Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army vet tried helping stranded driver -- a hitman hired to kill him...</title>
      <link>http://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-murder-for-hire-volusia-county-20180906-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Carlos Cruz-Echevarria was found dead along the side of a Deltona road in November, authorities believed he was a good Samaritan, randomly shot as he tried helping a stranded driver. An investigation soon revealed that the story went much deeper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record September cold Minnesota...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/record-breaking-september-cold-hits-northern-minnesota-165017798.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIBBING, Minn. (AP) — The mercury is falling in northern Minnesota, with cold air bringing in a record-breaking chill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the Mediocre QB...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-rise-of-the-nfls-mediocre-quarterback-1536250384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As teams pass more, they’re also throwing shorter--allowing quarterbacks who struggled in the past to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 5 states that will decide House majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/five-states-that-will-decide-the-house-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch these states to tell if Democrats are having a good election night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama ready to roar... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/obama-won-t-hold-punches-he-kicks-midterm-campaign-push-n907241 A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> More Baby Boomers smoking weed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/more-baby-boomers-generation-xers-are-smoking-weed-n907236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marijuana users were also more likely to abuse alcohol and illegal drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange in very poor health, needs treatment, says WIKILEAKS lawyer...</title>
      <link>https://www.itwire.com/strategy/84366-assange-in-very-poor-health,-needs-treatment,-says-wikileaks-lawyer.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life After Baba...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/2018/09/06/billionaire-jack-ma-prepares-for-life-after-alibaba#gs.a3YNiLA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Jack Ma Prepares for Life After Alibaba</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK JOLT:  Boris Johnson splits from wife over 'cheating' claims...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6140893/Boris-Johnson-splits-lawyer-wife-Marina-accuses-fling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Johnson's daughter Lara, a fashion journalist, is claimed to have said that the former London mayor's wife was 'finished with him' and would 'never take him back now' after his latest fling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak spreads to new city... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/405395-ebola-outbreak-in-congo-spreads-to-new-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An outbreak of the deadly Ebola virus in two eastern provinces of Congo has spread to a major international trading hub with almost a million residents, Congolese health officials said Wednesday.  Health officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Michael Moore hopes film is 'beginning of end' for Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180906201734-xfdvo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FILMFESTIVAL-TIFF/FAHRENHEIT 11/9 (TV, PIX):Michael Moore hopes his film is 'beginning of the end' for Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Thais arrested for sharing FACEBOOK post on rape allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/thai-police-arrest-12-sharing-facebook-rape-allegation-131903094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Police in Thailand have arrested 12 people who shared a Facebook post about a rape allegation by a British tourist who claims that the police refused to accept her complaint when she reported the crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Explore Fraud Charges Against Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/federal-prosecutors-exploring-new-charges-against-harvey-weinstein-1536268233</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors are investigating whether former Hollywood producer Harvey Weinstein violated wire fraud or other laws in any efforts to silence women who accused him of sexual misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric ankle zap boosts sex drive?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6139007/Zapping-ANKLES-boosts-womans-sex-drive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Michigan team already proved their technique worked on mice, and decided to ramp up their scientific efforts by testing the electrode stimulation of ankles on nine women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists To Investigate Own Paper?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-asks-new-york-times-journalists-to-investigate-themselves-over-op-ed-written-by-his-one-of-his-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sirens blare as explosions heard near US Embassy in Baghdad...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1014207/Baghdad-explosion-US-Embassy-Iraq-mortar-attack-Green-Zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR explosions have taken place in Baghdad near the US Embassy, targeting the highly fortified Green Zone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC bike-path terrorist's lawyers use Trump tweets in defense...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/06/alleged-bike-path-terrorists-lawyers-use-trumps-tweets-in-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s tweets criticizing the Justice Department are being used against him in the case of “bike path terrorist” Sayfullo Saipov, who stands accused of mowing down dozens of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN: Passengers Ill On International Flights Into Philly...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/09/06/philadelphia-international-airport-cdc-investigating-multiple-passengers-sick-international-flights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not yet known what caused the people to become sick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Uses NYPD Mass Surveillance Footage of Unknowing Citizens To Build ID Tech...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/09/06/nypd-surveillance-camera-skin-tone-search/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City served as IBM’s “primary testing area” for developing software that enables police to search surveillance video footage for skin color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academy Drops New 'Popular' Oscar Category After Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/academy-postponing-new-popular-oscar-category-1140423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The award was to have been introduced at the 91st Oscars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley so pricey that university asks faculty to house students...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1381382/silicon-valley-is-getting-so-pricey-a-university-is-pleading-with-professors-to-house-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting accepted was the easy part. Finding a place to live is even harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER BANS ALEX JONES FOR LIFE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2521ccbe3b5a43d68d66c21c030a7f2d/Twitter-permanently-bans-Alex-Jones,-Infowars-citing-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Twitter permanently banned right-wing conspiracy theorist Alex Jones and his Infowars show for abusive behavior — a day after CEO Jack Dorsey testified befor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Rancher Documents Stream of Illegals Crossing Property...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/09/06/illegal-aliens-chilton-ranch-arizona-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cartel scouts, drug mules and human smugglers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Slated to Stump for Candidate Accused of Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/obama-dems-mum-plans-stump-cisneros/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Obama will hit the campaign trail this weekend in California, where he is expected to campaign for Gil Cisneros, accused of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina: Raid at school for deaf...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/argentina-raids-school-deaf-clerical-abuse-probe-190750959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — Argentine authorities raided a Catholic-run school for youths with hearing disabilities Thursday as part of an investigation into alleged sexual abuse of vulnerable children that has shocked Pope Francis's homeland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit mastermind Boris Johnson splits from wife over 'cheating' claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-boris-johnson-splits-long-13205203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Foreign Secretary and his wife, both 54, are reportedly no longer living together, and don't socialise as a couple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Anxiety Over NFL Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.sportsbusinessdaily.com/Daily/Issues/2018/09/06/NFL-Season-Preview/Ratings-Analysts.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportsbusinessdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem complains 'out-of-state socialists' blitzing state...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/overheard-on-amtrak-tom-carper-complains-of-out-of-state-socialists-trying-to-beat-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Tom Carper (D., Del.) complained about the "out-of-state socialists" working to unseat him as he rode the Amtrak train back to Delaware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELAWARE: Liberal challenger threatens Dem Senator's 42-year run...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/news/politics/2018/09/06/delaware-primary-day-thursday-already-historic/1200935002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polls are open today from 7 a.m. to 8 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Capsule housing' sparks outrage in Spain...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/capsule-housing-project-sparks-outrage-spain-184804051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company argues the project called Haibu -- which means beehive in Japanese -- is a solution to a shortage of affordable housing in the Mediterranean city but Barcelona city hall has refused to issue a licence for it, saying such tiny accommodation is unfit for humans. The law does not allow this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of spiders, scorpions, rare insects stolen in musuem heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/09/06/stolen-insects-7-000-animals-vanish-philadelphia-museum-heist/1211887002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whereabouts of 7,000 crawlers from the Philadelphia Insectarium and Butterfly Pavilion are unknown following what police described as an inside job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Jury Looking Into Case Of Andrew McCabe...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/09/06/645308583/grand-jury-looking-into-case-of-ex-fbi-deputy-director-andrew-mccabe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McCabe faces potential criminal charges after the outcome of an internal investigation. McCabe says he has done nothing wrong and broken no law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 90% of GOOGLE Employee Contributions Went To Dems...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/election/bombshell-report-90-percent-of-google-employee-political-contributions-went-to-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You probably won't be surprised by this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind and solar farms make own weather, including extra rain...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-wind-solar-farms-precipitation-20180906-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You already know that using solar and wind power can influence the climate by reducing our dependence on heat-trapping fossil fuels. Now scientists say these renewable forms of energy can change the climate more directly — and do it in ways that might surprise you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police raid couple's home after $400,000 raised for homeless vet disappears...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/09/06/police-raid-new-jersey-couples-home-after-400g-in-gofundme-cash-raised-for-homeless-veteran-disappears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police investigating a New Jersey couple ordered by a judge to appear in court to explain what happened to the $400,000 they raised online for a homeless Good Samaritan had their home raided by authorities Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER BLOCKS JONES PERMANENTLY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/06/twitter-permanently-bans-alex-jones-and-infowars-accounts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ban comes weeks after Jones was banned or suspended by other major tech companies like Apple, Facebook and YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War of the Los Angeles Megamansions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-war-of-the-los-angeles-megamansions-1536248650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of Los Angeles developers are betting their over-the-top creations will outrun the market and sell for hundreds of millions of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul: Lie-detector tests justified...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/rand-paul-trump-justified-lie-detector-tests-find-anonymous-new-york-times-author</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul, R-Ky., said Thursday afternoon that he believes President Trump would be justified in using lie detector tests to figure out which senior administrative official wrote the anonymous New York Times op-ed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY:  Papadopoulos Spills on Mueller Cooperation in First TV Interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/exclusive-george-papadopoulos-spills-on-mueller-cooperation-in-first-tv-interview-with-jake-tapper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Probiotics 'useless'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-45434753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study suggests "good bacteria" have little or no effect inside the body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS in negotiations for Moonves exit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/06/cbs-board-in-negotiations-for-ceo-moonves-exit-from-the-company-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's David Faber has learned that CBS' board is deep in settlement talks with CEO Les Moonves that would result in his departure and the appointment of COO Joe Ianniello as his interim replacement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURT REYNOLDS DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/burt-reynolds-dead-deliverance-boogie-nights-star-was-82-831093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-jock from Florida starred in 'Deliverance' and 'Boogie Nights' but preferred making such populist, fun fare as 'Smokey and the Bandit,' 'The Cannonball Run' and 'Starting Over.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIRAFFE attack horror: Mother, son fight for lives after trampled...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6138047/US-wife-son-three-British-scientist-fighting-lives-South-Africa-giraffe-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrified Katy Williams, 35, and son Finn, 3, were left close to death near their home on the Blyde Wildlife Estate near Hoedspruit after the terrifying encounter with the giraffe in South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Removes NIKE Uniforms To Protest Kaepernick Ad...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/09/06/college-of-the-ozarks-removing-nike-uniforms-colin-kaepernick-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One college is removing all uniforms purchased from Nike that feature the company's logo in response to the company's deal with Colin Kaepernick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will espresso-loving Italy embrace country's 1st STARBUCKS?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3df1afd3b0f6443991d2113b8aa5dfaf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Will the country that gave us espresso embrace the company that gave us grande Frappucinos?        Starbucks is about to find out as it opens its first store i</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
