<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rich Americans Flock To Caribbean Ahead Of Election Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/rich-americans-flock-caribbean-ahead-us-presidential-election-turmoil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's lost summer: Focused on FOXNEWS, not on battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/09/trump-summer-ad-spending-409075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An analysis of his campaign's TV spending reveals that the president has sacrificed targeting swing-state voters in favor of his favorite station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese fighter jets enter Taiwan airspace in 'threat to regional peace'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-taiwan-jet-fighters-regional-space-dispute-tsai-ing-wen-b420945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skies turn blood-red above Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/skies-turn-blood-red-above-22653854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fires were started by felled trees that knocked down power lines in the Santiam Canyon areas in Oregon and have so far scorched an estimated 200,000 acres of land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Record-setting motorcycle racer dead after 252 mph crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ralph-hudson-crash-at-bonneville-record-setting-motorcycle-racer-dead-252-mph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ralph Hudson, 69, crashed August 14 while trying to set a speed record on the Bonneville Salt Flats in Utah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County Prohibits Trick-Or-Treating, Halloween Parties...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/09/08/los-angeles-county-halloween-no-trick-or-treating-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gatherings or parties with non-household members are not permitted, even if held outdoors, and neither are carnivals, festivals, live entertainment or haunted house attractions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands evacuated as fires burn through Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Thousands-evacuated-as-once-in-a-generation-15552873.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As wildfires stretching for thousands of acres ripped through southwestern Oregon late Tuesday, the state's governor declared an emergency and tens of thousands of residents faced mandatory evacuation orders to escape the Almeda Fire, the latest blaze to devastate the region in recent days.  By early Wednesday, the fire was burning its way toward the central neighborhoods of Medford, Ore., a city of 82,000 people, where many have now been forced to flee their homes.  "Pray for Medford," tweeted resident Jeff Carpenter. "We are on fire tonight."  Oregon Gov. Kate Brown's emergency order for Jackson County, which includes Medford, came after the National Weather Service placed all of southwestern Oregon an under an extreme fire danger warning for the first time, according to the Oregon Climate Office. Brown, D, had declared emergencies for three other blazes - the Beachie Creek, Lionshead, and Holiday Farm fires - earlier Tuesday.  Pointing to winds with 25 mph gusts as the catalyst for fueling the fires, the governor, in a news conference, described the weather contributing to the wildfires as "a once-in-a-generation event."  "People's homes, lives &amp; land are at risk," Brown tweeted. "If you are in an evacuation area, please pay close attention &amp; listen to local calls to evacuate - this can save your life &amp; the lives of our firefighters."  Authorities haven't released new information on structural damage or potential injuries in the area.  The Oregon Department of Forestry estimated that the Almeda Fire has now burned 2,500 to 3,000 acres. As of late Tuesday, the fire was at zero percent containment, according to Jackson County Emergency Management.  Also referred to as the Glendower Fire, the blaze started as a brush fire about 14 miles away around Ashland, Ore.,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators launch 150 probes in French horse mutilations, killings spate...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-horses-minister/investigators-launched-over-150-probes-in-french-horse-mutilations-killings-spate-idUSKBN2601DL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators have opened more than 150 probes into a spate of killings and mutilations of horses across France, Agriculture Minister Julien Denormandie said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials to redistribute wealth in 'age of disorder'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-world-is-on-the-cusp-of-a-new-era-says-deutsche-strategist-and-heres-what-it-means-for-markets-11599589831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What new era means for markets: Deteriorating US/China relations and the reversal of unfettered globalization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'MULAN' enters battle DISNEY didn't want...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Mulan-enters-a-battle-Disney-didn-t-want-15552761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two decades ago, the release of Disney's animated film "Mulan" did not feel like a geopolitical event. The Western adaptation of an ancient Chinese legend charmed audiences in the United States with its tale of a courageous girl who turns into a heroic warrior. It also cheered some Asian Americans eager for more representation in popular culture. But it was a box office flop in China, where audiences seemed unimpressed by the film's affectations, from a title character who didn't "look" Chinese enough to the strangeness of a sardonic talking dragon voiced by Eddie Murphy.  In 2020, the picture is different in more ways than one. China has gone from being a sleeping giant - whose potential market piqued U.S. companies and politicians alike - to a power now locked in tense competition with the United States. And Disney's new live-action reboot of "Mulan," a humorless successor to the more beloved cartoon, is now in the middle of that confrontation. "Mulan" debuted on Disney's streaming platform last Friday, and has already been released in theaters in parts of Asia, with plans to open in China later this week. Activists elsewhere, though, are calling for a global boycott.  The trouble began last year, when Liu Yifei, the film's Chinese-born lead actress, posted on Chinese social media site Weibo in defense of Hong Kong's police cracking down on pro-democracy protesters. It was one of the earlier shots across the bow in a brewing global culture war that has forced U.S. companies and organizations invested in China, from Hollywood to the NBA, to reckon with the widening divide between Beijing and Western governments.  Yet Liu's remarks seem minor when set against what's in the film's closing credits, which offer "special thanks" to eight political entities, including four propaganda departments and a public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope removes mask, touches worshippers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8713515/Pope-Francis-removes-mask-touches-worshippers-vows-defeat-coronavirus-love.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pope, 83, removed his mask when he arrived at San Damaso, he smiled and chatted, shook hands and touched the foreheads of congregants who crowded close together at the barriers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare earthquake strikes New Jersey...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/earthquake-strikes-new-jersey-today-2020-09-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents took to social media to express their shock at the rare occurrence as numerous reports of shaking have been reported across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEAR COMRADE': Konchalovsky's tribute to 'pure' Soviet soul tipped for Venice win...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/konchalovskys-tribute-pure-soviet-soul-111124387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A paean to the &amp;quot;pure&amp;quot; soul of the Soviet people by Russian master Andrei Konchalovsky has emerged as one of the frontrunners for the top prize at the Venice film festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cloud over NFL as season kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-cloud-over-nfl-season-021624288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL kicks off its new season shrouded in trepidation on Thursday as America&amp;#39;s most popular sport grapples with the new realities of life in the age of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another showdown set this week over Georgia voting machines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67df846bacacefe8e33b31cd14258190</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Voting integrity activists will try this week to convince a federal judge that Georgia should scrap its brand new touchscreen voting machines in favor of hand-marked paper ballots....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire guts Greek refugee camp, forces thousands to flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-greece-lesbos-idUSKBN26002M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire broke out at Greece's overcrowded migrant camp of Moria on the island of Lesbos in early hours of Wednesday, fire brigade officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven Election Day Nightmares...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/09/seven-election-day-nightmares/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election night, by now, has a well-established run of show: the state-by-state results, the declaration of a winner, the concession</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped by Pandemic, Ships' Crews Fight Exhaustion and Despair...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/09/sailors-trapped-by-covid-19-fight-exhaustion-and-despair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK — Ralph Santillan, a merchant seaman from the Philippines, hasn’t had shore leave in half a year. It has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As California burns, winds arrive and lights go out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e293277165179809eab95c8b139a67c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAVER LAKE, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires raged unchecked throughout California Wednesday, and gusty winds could drive flames into new ferocity, authorities warned. Diablo winds in the north and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit hits record $3 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/515582-us-budget-deficit-hits-record-3-trillion-cbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal budget deficit hit an unprecedented $3 trillion in August, with another month to go before the end of the fiscal year, according to estimates from the Congressional Budget Office (CBO).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England bans gatherings of more than 6 as virus cases spike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3a8a0998c2093181934c51bd0c92a95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain's government is banning gatherings of more than six people in England, as officials try to keep a lid on daily new coronavirus infections after a sharp spike across the U.K....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny critically endangered gorilla baby born in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36dbbfca227b7f3163e5c2029571ed25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — A tiny baby gorilla has been born at the zoo in New Orleans. Keepers don’t yet know the sex of the critically endangered western lowland gorilla born Friday to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLE TROUBLE:  The Fed Now Owns Nearly One Third of All Mortgages...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/mishtalk/economics/the-fed-now-owns-nearly-one-third-of-all-us-mortgages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed's balance sheet is ballooning out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress probes 'alarming pattern' of Fort Hood tragedies...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/news/20200908/congress-probes-lsquoalarming-patternrsquo-of-fort-hood-tragedies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two U.S. House subcommittees have launched a joint investigation into "an alarming pattern of recent tragedies" at Fort Hood, giving Army</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Cast Doubt on Russia Results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/scientists-cast-doubt-on-results-from-russian-covid-vaccine/ar-BB18PkOG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stock suffers biggest-ever drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-tumbles-toward-2nd-bear-market-in-6-months-2020-09-08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Tesla Inc. suffered Tuesday their biggest loss since going public to kick off the second bear market this year, as investors rode a roller coaster...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOSEMITE GLOWS ORANGE AS FIRES RAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article245559400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer air travel down nearly 76% from year ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/08/coronavirus-travel-labor-day-travelers-hit-nearly-6-month-high-but-weekend-caps-dismal-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air travel hit a nearly six-month high during Labor Day weekend but pandemic kept many would-be travelers out of the skies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHASE probing fraud in covid bailout programs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jpmorgan-chase-probing-fraud-us-195727099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US financial behemoth JPMorgan Chase said Tuesday it was working with authorities after learning of unethical conduct by customers and employees connected to huge government pandemic relief programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Loses $16 Billion With Wild Wealth Swings...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-loses-record-16-205623505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elon Musk’s net worth plunged $16.3 billion Tuesday, the largest single-day wipeout in the history of the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, as the Tesla Inc. rout continued.The electric-carmaker fell 21% in New York trading -- the most ever -- on news of a partnership between competitors Nikola</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Adverse reaction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/09/08/astrazeneca-covid-19-vaccine-study-put-on-hold-due-to-suspected-adverse-reaction-in-participant-in-the-u-k/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The large, Phase 3 study testing the vaccine has been put on hold due to a suspected serious adverse reaction in a participant in the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford trial put on hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/oxford-vaccine-trial-hold-due-safety-issue-n1239581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oxford COVID-19 vaccine trial has been paused because of a safety issue. It's unclear what happened, and it may be minor. When will Oxford trial start again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Lana del Rey?</title>
      <link>https://www.interviewmagazine.com/culture/who-is-lana-del-rey-jack-antonoff-september-poetry-cover</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interviewmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War is 'last resort,' Army chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/08/war-is-a-last-resort-army-chief-trump-409934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McConville acknowledged today's "political environment," but noted that the military needs to remain an "apolitical organization."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen ran household like boot camp, tormenting workers, ex-staffer claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8699317/Ellen-DeGeneres-ran-household-like-military-style-boot-camp-tormented-workers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former staffer for Ellen DeGeneres told DailyMail.com: 'Ellen was the worst person that I've ever met in my life. She takes pleasure in firing people... She treated you like you were nothing.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:  'KARDASHIANS' Done After 20 Seasons on E!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/keeping-up-with-the-kardashians-ending-season-20-e-kuwtk-1234762635/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 20 seasons, “Keeping Up With the Kardashians” will be coming to an end with the final season airing in early 2021. The decision to end the show was made by the Kardashian-Jenner f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sturgis motorcycle rally was 'superspreader event'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sturgis-motorcycle-rally-spread-coronavirus-across-the-nation-leading-to-12-billion-in-healthcare-costa-182736696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A month after 460,000 motorcycle enthusiasts converged on Sturgis, S.D., researchers have found that thousands have been sickened across the nation, leading them to brand the rally a “superspreader” event that will involve more than $12 billion in health care costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic priest says Dems going to hell -- and Texas bishop backs him up...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article245560245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton becomes a podcaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/radio/bill-clinton-to-launch-a-podcast-with-iheartmedia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton is reportedly parenting with iHeartMedia to launch a podcast in 2021, which will build on one he hosted last year for the Clinton Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Disorders Thrive In Anxious Times...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2020/09/08/908994616/eating-disorders-thrive-in-anxious-times-and-pose-a-lethal-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eating disorders strike nearly 1 in 10 Americans, with the second-highest death rate of all psychiatric disorders. The pandemic's food insecurity, stockpiling and stress are triggering flare-ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacy 'most lethal threat' to USA, 'Homeland' says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/08/politics/white-supremacy-dhs-draft-assessment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White supremacists will remain the most "persistent and lethal threat" in the United States through 2021, according to Department of Homeland Security draft documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodies of missing CA couple found at bottom of well in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/08/bodies-of-missing-california-couple-found-at-bottom-of-mexico-well/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bodies of a retired California couple who vanished in northern Mexico last month have been found at the bottom of a well there, authorities say. Ian Hirschsohn, 78, and Kathy Harvey, 73, both o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earliest Freeze On Record...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/09/08/denver-earliest-freeze-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just before 8:30 a.m. Tuesday, the official weather station for Denver recorded 32 degrees. It's a tie with Sept. 8, 1962 for the earliest freeze on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links Falwell's 2016 endorsement to suppression of racy photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-falwell-endorsement/ex-fixer-for-trump-links-falwells-endorsement-in-2016-to-suppression-of-racy-photos-idUSKBN25Z2S0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his book released today, Michael Cohen, the former fixer for U.S. President Donald Trump, ties for the first time the 2016 presidential endorsement of Trump by American evangelical leader Jerry Falwell Jr to Cohen’s own role in helping to keep racy “personal” photographs of the Falwells from becoming public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race boils down to 6 swing states...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200908-portrait-of-an-election-us-race-boils-down-to-six-swing-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portrait of an election: US race boils down to six swing states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  'Unlikely' vaccine will be ready by Nov 3...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/08/coronavirus-vaccine-dr-fauci-says-its-unlikely-it-will-be-ready-by-us-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infectious disease experts and scientists have said they worry the vaccine approval process in the U.S. could be polluted by politics, not science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer glitches disrupt classes as schools return online...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06f5fdc1f7cdf62621a2539a1433bd21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — As millions of American youngsters start the school year with online classes at home because of the coronavirus, they are running into technical glitches and other headaches that have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Many Americans Planted 'Mystery Seeds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/akz9qk/hundreds-of-americans-planted-chinese-mystery-seeds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What I learned by reading thousands of internal emails about the Chinese mystery seeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: FLORIDA TIED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/amp/ncna1239510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden overperforms with seniors but lags with Latinos in the key battleground state according to a new NBC News/Marist poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why real unemployment rate is likely over 11%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/08/why-the-real-unemployment-rate-is-likely-over-11percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official unemployment rate fell to 8.4% in August. But the true jobless figure is likely much higher, perhaps remaining at a level higher than any other period since the Great Depression, according to economists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA RAMS to kickoff in new, $5 billion stadium -- without fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/08/la-rams-ready-to-play-in-new-sofi-stadium-without-fans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rams will play in their brand new, cutting edge stadium on Sunday, but they won't play in front of fans just yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>178 mph on highway? Police don't even try to stop motorcyclist...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/178-mph-on-ga-400-police-dont-even-attempt-to-stop-motorcyclist/4ZN6O4QXDBGGRLX5T7ZKEOZ5DQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Alpharetta Department of Public Safety is urging motorists to slow down after a police officer clocked a motorcyclist going 178 mph on Ga. 400 on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5G lie: The network of the future is still slow... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2020/09/08/5g-speed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We speed tested 5G phones against 4G ones. America’s new nationwide 5G networks weren’t much faster — and in some places they were slower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer hauled off in cuffs for hitting beach 'while infected with Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1439154/female-surfer-arrested-beach-spain-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FEMALE surfer has been dramatically dragged off a beach in cuffs by hazmat-clad cops after riding waves while infected with coronavirus. The woman was arrested on a Spanish beach after going alle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Spends Morning Rage-Tweeting About Michael Cohen, Chris Cuomo, NBA Ratings and BLM...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-spends-morning-rage-tweeting-about-michael-cohen-chris-cuomo-nba-ratings-and-blm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was all over the place on Tuesday morning as he started the day by going on a Twitter rampage against all his political enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Toronto Fest Goes Mask-Optional, Attendees Fear 'Superspreader' Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/as-toronto-film-fest-screenings-go-mask-optional-attendees-fear-event-will-be-a-coronavirus-super-spreader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue monkey bites more than 40 people during wild rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-goes-rampage-bites-over-22640606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An out-of-control monkey in Uttarakhand, India, is thought to have been released back into the wild after wreaking havoc across a residential area in a northern state of the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia boss swallows guard's finger in jail fight... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8709609/Mafia-boss-EATS-prison-guards-finger-attacking-cell-inspection.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guiseppe Fanara, 60, who was serving a life sentence at Rome's Rebibbia prison, allegedly attacked seven guards in June when they came to inspect his cell, biting on of their fingers off and swallowing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds file charges over 'Zoom-bombed' ISIS threat to students...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-files-charges-over-zoom-160524346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas man is facing charges of threatening an attack on the University of Houston after he &amp;quot;Zoom-bombed&amp;quot; an online class and praised the Islamic State group, the Justice Department said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine developers pledge to uphold scientific integrity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nine-covid-19-vaccine-developers-144934150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEOs of nine companies developing vaccines against Covid-19 on Tuesday pledged to &amp;quot;uphold the integrity of the scientific process&amp;quot; amid concern Donald Trump will pressure regulators to approve a vaccine ahead of the presidential election in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fanning flames?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hes-just-fanning-flames-trumps-110059589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump&amp;#39;s stoking fear about urban violence risks alienating many voters in the suburbs, home to a diverse range of ethnicities and political views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Lloyd Webber warns arts 'at point of no return'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df22e45fcf31b124bb7c34198381343e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — “The Phantom of the Opera” composer Andrew Lloyd Webber has told British lawmakers that the arts are “at the point of no return,” and urged the government to set a date for theaters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark kills surfer on Australia's Gold Coast tourist strip...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54c7c82ea44a9694409276727add588c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — A shark fatally mauled a surfer on Tuesday on Australia’s Gold Coast city tourist strip in a rare attack off a beach protected by shark netting, officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left Secretly Preps for Violence After Election Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-left-secretly-preps-for-violence-after-election-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The progressive coalition Fight Back Table has been meeting to game out what happens if Joe Biden doesn’t win by a landslide. It’s not pretty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL COHEN: President should resign; 'Let Pence pardon you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/cohen-calls-trump-racist-cult-leader-says-he-disparaged-obama-n1239445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's former lawyer spoke out in an exclusive interview with NBC News' Lester Holt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salmon May Harbor Covid For Week, Study Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/salmon-may-harbor-infectious-coronavirus-for-a-week-study-shows/ar-BB18Ox3R?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Trashes 'Incoherent' Trump For Disparaging Generals...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/john-bolton-trashes-incoherent-trump-for-disparaging-top-generals-as-captive-to-defense-industry-elizabeth-warren-really-couldnt-have-said-it-better/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton trashes 'incoherent' Trump for disparaging Pentagon as captive to defense industry during WH briefing: 'Elizabeth Warren couldn't have said it better'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKIES TURN RED...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/09/07/creek-fire-raging-wildfire-grows-to-73278-acres-town-of-big-creek-devastated-the-skys-turning-red-it-looks-like-mars-out-there/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive Creek Fire, burning in a timber-rich area of the Sierra, had grown to 135,532 acres by Monday evening but heavy smoke thwarted the efforts of California National Guard helicopters to rescue trapped people in Lake Edison and China Peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTLAND: PROUD BOYS CHASE DOWN, BEAT BLM PROTESTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/09/08/trump-supporters-portland-chase-down-blm-protesters-beat-proud-boys-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump supporters chased down BLM protesters and beat them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Warns Assange to Shut Up After Shouts of 'Nonsense' at Extradition Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/judge-warns-julian-assange-to-shut-up-after-shouts-of-nonsense-at-extradition-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the second day of a four-week hearing at the Old Bailey, the judge was already threatening to throw the WikiLeaks founder out of court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Taking TYLENOL Makes People Take Greater Risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tylenol-side-effect-acetaminophen-makes-people-take-risks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that taking acetaminophen may also cause an individual to take greater risks than they would otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer turns winter in west...</title>
      <link>https://www.perspectaweather.com/blog/2020/9/8/1045-am-the-wild-wild-westan-abrupt-change-from-summer-to-winter-in-the-rockiestropics-remain-active-in-the-atlantic-basin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.perspectaweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not too often that this early in September that you see significant accumulating snow on the map in the US at the same time there is an active scene in the tropical Atlantic, but that is exactly what we have going on right now. A dramatic temperature plunge in the Rocky Mountain States has bro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 'to bring people back to life' with digital clones...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ai-to-bring-people-back-22647058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech boss Eugenia Kuyda says The Simpson have got it right again and that "really creepy" AI will soon use selfies to create 3D digital avatars to "bring people back to life"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest fire season could get much worse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-biggest-fire-season-could-144620924.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intense diablo winds are forecast for parts of Northern California while Santa Ana winds are expected in Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MLK/FBI' Doc Draws Disturbing Parallels With Current Moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/toronto-mlk-fbi-doc-draws-disturbing-parallels-with-the-current-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado prepares for SNOW with temps plummeting up to 70F in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8708887/Colorado-prepares-SNOW-amid-wildfires-biggest-single-day-temperature-drop-150-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denver is set to experience the biggest temperature drop for nearly 150 years as raging wildfires turn to snow overnight in Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer dragged away from ocean by hazmat-wearing officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8708863/Coronavirus-infected-female-surfer-dragged-away-Spanish-beach-hazmat-wearing-officials.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed woman had been working on the San Sebastian beach in Spain as a lifeguard when her colleagues informed the police she was surfing while infected with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA shares crater...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/08/tesla-shares-slump-10percent-in-premarket-trading-after-sp-500-snub.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 Index Committee added Etsy, Teradyne and Catalent to the index, but stopped short of including Tesla.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
