<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Apologizes to Cherokee Nation for DNA Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.tulsaworld.com/news/local/we-are-encouraged-by-her-action-sen-elizabeth-warren-apologizes/article_251d480f-1211-5e92-a445-4a2a5a2b0036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tulsaworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reportedly planning to make her presidential bid official this month, U.S. Sen. Elizabeth Warren has apologized to the Cherokee Nation for publicizing a DNA test that shows she has distant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How police make millions by seizing property...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenvilleonline.com/in-depth/news/taken/2019/01/27/civil-forfeiture-south-carolina-police-property-seizures-taken-exclusive-investigation/2457838002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenvilleonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.6 Mag Quake Rocks Southern Mexico; Mexico City Evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/02/01/6-6-magnitude-earthquake-rocks-southern-mexico-causes-buildings-to-sway-in-capital-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strong earthquake jolted southern Mexico on Friday, rattling nerves and swaying tall buildings hundreds of miles away in the capital, but there were no reports of serious damage, injuries or deaths. The U.S. Geological Survey reported that the quake had a magnitude of 6.6. It was centered about 10 miles (16 kilometers) from the city of Tapachula in Chiapas state and struck at a depth of 40 miles (68 kilometers).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan building massive border fence...</title>
      <link>https://aminewswire.org/stories/pakistan-works-finish-border-fence-along-disputed-afghan-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;aminewswire.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Joseph Hammond While President Trump is having trouble adding a few miles of fence to America’s incomplete border with Mexico, Pakistan is busy building one of the world’s longest border fences. Climbing over some of the world’s toughest terrain, Pakistan’s border fence will stretch more 1,800-miles and ascend more than 12,000-feet above sea level. It will march over mountains, span gorges, and descend into desert plains—halting, at last, on the Chinese border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives head to Texas to try to build their own wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/conservatives-head-texas-try-build-own-wall-202821370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — What started as an online fundraiser to provide President Donald Trump with donations for his southern border wall has morphed into a foundation whose members vow to build a wall themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100th Straight Month of Increased Employment...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-employers-added-304-000-jobs-in-january-unemployment-ticked-up-due-to-shutdown-11549028008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tested in January by a government shutdown, market volatility and uncertainty about global growth, the U.S. labor market notched its 100th straight month of increased employment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During Shutdown, Federal Employees Considered Leaving Govt Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/during-shutdown-federal-employees-considered-leaving-government-work-11549038667</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government shutdown and resulting furloughs of workers touched off a wave of searches on private jobs websites, though there’s no evidence it led to an actual exodus from the federal government’s payrolls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE tracking shoes?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/01/alphabet-verily-built-health-tracking-shoes-prototype.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet's Verily has pitched potential retail partners on the health-tracking shoes, which are still early in development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: VA Governor Affirms Post-Birth Abortion Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/31/va-gov-northam-no-regrets-childbirth-abortion-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northam refused to recant his comments in support of a bill that would allow women to request an abortion at the moment of birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/02/01/manufacturing-unexpectedly-soars-higher-in-january/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Factory activity increased and, despite all the worries about tariffs, prices of raw materials used by manufacturers fell. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' star breaks silence on attack...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/jussie-smollett-statement-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson Invites American People 'To Get Deep with Me'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/election/oprahs-spiritual-guru-running-for-president-inviting-the-american-people-to-get-deep-with-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marianne Williamson stressed that she's "not trying to figure out what to say to get people to vote for me" and "not trying to get shallow or superficial so people will hear me."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG:  Selling fake social media engagement is illegal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/31/ag-letitia-james-selling-fake-social-media-engagement-is-illegal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A settlement reached earlier this week by New York Attorney General Letitia James marks the first time that a law enforcement agency has found that selling fake social media engagement is illegal —…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slams Media For Inaccuracies... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/jussie-smollett-breaks-silence-attack-chicago-empire-1202547468/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days after allegedly being attacked in a racist and homophobic barrage in Chicago, Empire star Jussie Smollett says he is “ok” &amp; believes “justice will be served” as pol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deluge of drones fly over stadium, despite ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21f228bfeee34c9a916106ebe0ffce1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The FBI says that security officials are being "inundated" with drones flying around the Atlanta stadium that will host Sunday's Super Bowl 53. That's despite an ongoing restriction that bans the use of drones in the area of Mercedes-Benz Stadium downtown. FBI spokesman Kevin Rowson said Friday that officers have confiscated several drones in recent days. He says their pilots could face jail time and fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to suspend nuclear treaty with Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/13bee012befd4f989ab9ae108d1ca729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States announced Friday that it was pulling out of a landmark nuclear arms control treaty with Russia, accusing Moscow of violating the Cold War-era pact with "impunity" by continuing to develop banned missiles. President Donald Trump said Russia has been secretly developing "a prohibited missile system that poses a direct threat to our allies and troops abroad." He said the U.S. had adhered to the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces treaty since it was signed in 1987, but Russia has not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limo shortage in Atlanta!</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/i-team/some-fear-a-limousine-shortage-at-the-super-bowl-in-atlanta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5atlanta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, a FOX 5 Atlanta Super Bowl Exclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORY BOOKS 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/sen-cory-booker-of-new-jersey-launches-presidential-campaign-11549022453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Sen. Cory Booker entered the race for the Democratic presidential nomination on Friday, seeking to offer a message of unity in a growing field of Democrats opposing President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI counter-hacking operations raise red flags over privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/31/fbi-counter-hacking-operations-raise-privacy-red-f/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To catch a hacker, sometimes you have to be a hacker. But when it’s the FBI doing the hacking, civil liberties groups get worried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials boosting sales of liquor...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/diageo-toasts-us-millennials-as-it-surpasses-half-year-revenue-and-profit-targets-2019-01-31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The millennial generation has been blamed for the demise of everything from movies to dinner dates to golf. But now the much-slighted demographic group has been credited for something unexpected: saving hard liquor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Force Participation at Trump-Era High...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/susan-jones/labor-force-participation-trump-era-high-632-percent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Congressional Budget Office, in a report released this week, said it expects last year's strong employment growth to carry into 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: VICE to Lay Off 10% of Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/vice-media-to-lay-off-10-percent-of-staff-in-company-restructuring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Having finalized the 2019 budget, our focus shifts to executing our goals and hitting our marks," CEO Nancy Dubuc says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKWATER Founder's New Company Strikes Deal in China. He Says Had No Idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang/erik-prince-had-no-knowledge-of-training-agreement-in-chinas-xinjiang-spokesman-idUSKCN1PQ4FJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former U.S. military contractor Erik Prince had "no knowledge or involvemen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhus Epidemic Worsens in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/investigations/Typhus-Epidemic-Worsens-in-Los-Angeles-505166301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran Los Angeles City Hall official is one of the latest victims of an epidemic of the infectious disease typhus that continues to worsen across LA County. For months, LA County public health officials have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases prompt look at vax exemptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8833041f168c40438a711728f9b857f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VANCOUVER, Wash. (AP) — A measles outbreak near Portland, Oregon, has revived a bitter debate over so-called personal belief exemptions to childhood vaccinations. At least 43 people in Washington and Oregon have fallen ill in recent weeks with the extraordinarily contagious virus. More than a dozen more cases are suspected, and people who were exposed to the disease traveled to Hawaii and Bend, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS owner praises Trump for working for country's 'best interests'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/428012-patriots-owner-praises-trump-for-working-for-countrys-best-interests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft praised President Trump during an interview Friday on “Fox &amp; Friends,” saying he was “working very hard to serve the best interests of the country.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60-foot tunnel found in Texas...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox8live.com/2019/02/01/foot-tunnel-found-texas-running-under-where-border-wall-would-go/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox8live.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wall was described as "pretty stout" and is proving difficult to demolish because of its strong construction and tricky location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 'oldest' woman who 'didn't enjoy single day' in long life dies aged 129...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-oldest-woman-who-didnt-13938303 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Koku Istambulova said she did nothing special to live so long and was laughing with her grandchildren when she died</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandals loom over Bolsonaro after first month in office; 'It smells dirty'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/01/it-smells-dirty-scandals-loom-over-bolsonaro-after-first-month-in-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right Brazilian president plagued by scandal and disaster – not that the bolsonaristas mind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows sleepers can learn language from scratch in depths of slumber...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/31/learn-sleep-study-shows-sleepers-can-learn-language-scratch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People can learn a new language in their sleep, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMS go for Hollywood sequel...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f8fda4d4d2cd4c668feeb2197b0dfa86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Before there was Jared Goff, there was Warren Beatty. Years before Goff or any of today's Rams were born, Beatty had been carried off on his teammates' shoulders to celebrate a Rams title that only Hollywood could dream up. He played quarterback Joe Pendleton in the 1978 Academy Award nominated movie "Heaven Can Wait." At the end, he leads LA to an otherworldly Super Bowl victory over the Steelers. It all happened during a time when the real-life Rams, with Joe Namath, Rosey Grier and the rest of the Fearsome Foursome, embodied everything about Hollywood cool, even if the notion of them winning the Super Bowl felt like something that could only happen in the movies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican magazine denounces sexual abuse of nuns by priests...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vatican-magazine-denounces-sexual-abuse-nuns-priests-101742693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican's women's magazine is denouncing the sexual abuse of nuns by priests — and the resulting "scandal" of religious sisters having abortions or giving birth to children who are then not recognized by their fathers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
With Cash Handouts, India Takes Step Toward Universal Basic Income...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/with-cash-handouts-india-takes-step-toward-universal-basic-income-11549020444</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India unveiled huge handouts for farmers, setting the stage for an election-year spending spree, a possible prelude to implementing a universal basic income as a solution to its poverty problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army simulates attack on gas rigs; Most complex drill in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/army-simulates-attack-on-gas-rigs-in-most-complex-naval-drill-in-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunships fire missiles at cargo freighter acting as enemy vessel in massive exercise meant to prepare for attacks by Hamas, Hezbollah</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male contraceptive gel pioneering trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jan/31/male-contraceptive-gel-couples-trial-manchester-edinburgh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants in Manchester and Edinburgh will rely on the gel as sole contraceptive for a year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forty years since revolution, Iran taunts 'declining' America...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-revolution-anniversary-cleric/forty-years-since-revolution-iran-taunts-declining-america-idUSKCN1PQ4MQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty years after its revolution, Iran has no fear of a "declining" Am...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shorten Work Week to Boost Economy?</title>
      <link>https://www.redpepper.org.uk/less-work-more-play-a-solution-to-britains-economic-woes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.redpepper.org.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of Anxiety Drug Leaves Patients Scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/01/well/mind/anxiety-drug-shortage-buspirone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are no good alternatives to buspirone, so patients who rely on it are struggling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiesto the Wayne Newton of 21st century? </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/entertainment/article/Is-Tiesto-the-Wayne-Newton-of-the-21st-century-13577093.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS - This is the city where Americans go to have big fun doing things that seem absolutely terrible, and on a recent Saturday night, hundreds of them went to see Tiesto. These bacchanalians were no dopes. The best reason to go see Tiesto at one of his three current Las Vegas nightclub residencies is not because you want to hear the planet's second-highest paid DJ spin swollen, vanilla-sweet dance music, but because you seek the classic Las Vegas experience of low-stakes funtimes staged in an environment of expensive theatricality and unblinking grandeur. In this sense, Tiesto is the Wayne Newton of the 21st century. Everyone else is here to have a great night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Universal love'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-cory-booker-president-election-20190201-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cory Booker’s unremitting optimism, wonkish attraction to big ideas and, of course, background as a community organizer have long drawn comparisons to another pioneering African American lawmaker who went on to bigger things : Barack Obama. But can he carry it all the way to the White House?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lagerfeld's 'Bad Cold' Raises Questions About CHANEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/karl-lagerfeld-s-bad-cold-raises-questions-about-chanel#gs.DOOb0I85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karl Lagerfeldâ€™s â€˜Bad Coldâ€™ Raises Questions About Chanel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Spy Plane Spotted Over Colombia...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/latam/201902011072021406-us-spy-plane-colombia-venezuela-coup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has been backing a de facto coup d’etat in Venezuela by urging incumbent President Nicolas Maduro to step down in favour of Juan Guaido, an opposition leader, who proclaimed himself the Latin American country’s interim president over a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Clerk Accused Of Filming Dozens Of Men Using Restroom -- At Police Station...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/31/police-clerk-accused-of-filming-nearly-70-men-using-restroom-at-long-beach-police-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergio Nieto has been charged with 115 misdemeanor counts of invasion of privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy-plagued halftime show...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190201-super-bowl-sets-stage-controversy-plagued-halftime-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Bowl sets stage for controversy-plagued halftime show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hip-hop turns 40 -- and its parents beaming with pride...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190201-hip-hop-turns-40-its-parents-are-beaming-with-pride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hip-hop turns 40 -- and its parents are beaming with pride</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MUSIC?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6654795/David-Bowie-played-Vanity-Fair-star-Johnny-Flynn-upcoming-biopic-Stardust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duncan Jones, David Bowie's son, has poured cold water over the planned biopic about his late father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds charge 19 in Chinese 'birth tourism' scheme in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-crime-birthtourism/u-s-charges-19-in-chinese-birth-tourism-scheme-in-california-idUSKCN1PP37P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nineteen people have been charged in three "birth tourism" schemes tha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House preps emergency plan......</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/30/trump-border-national-emergency-immigration-1138308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress has until Feb. 15 to discuss a border security deal, but the White House is already finalizing its plan B —&amp;nbsp;declaring a national emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sherrod Brown rips Trump's 'phony populism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/potential-2020-contender-sherrod-brown-kicks-listening-tour-n965111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio senator's "Dignity of Work" tour, which launched in his home state Wednesday night, heads to Iowa next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON TAX SHAME IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/amazon-storm-over-tax-bill-13936012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The online giant coughed up less to the state coffers in two-decades than some major UK retailers pay in just one year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bag of puppies rescued after tossed from car...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/life/animals/bag-of-puppies-tossed-out-of-car-near-highway-99-in-spring/285-ca0a2be2-6e2a-4faf-a158-efc16427e45f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A good Samaritan came to the rescue Thursday after seeing someone throw the puppies onto the side of the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Holds DC Press Conference: 'I Will Not Be Silenced'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/roger-stones-live-washington-d-c-press-conference-commercial-free-feed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch now and share the link to spread this message worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Cast to Play David Bowie in Biopic 'STARDUST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/johnny-flynn-play-david-bowie-biopic-stardust-1181578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jena Malone and Marc Maron will also star in the movie from Salon Pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst January Box Office in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-super-bowl-sack-moviegoing-dismal-january-1181275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As February gets underway, the only new movie daring to open opposite the New England Patriots-Los Angeles Rams showdown is Sony's action-thriller 'Miss Bala.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK users happier if leave for month...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/01/31/study-says-quitting-facebook-improves-happiness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook users who quit for a month found themselves happier, and didn't use it as much when they came back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT'S Blacklist: NewsGuard Tries to Cut Off Alternative Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/01/31/financial-blacklisting-newsguard-advises-advertisers-to-avoid-pro-trump-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NewsGuard, the news-filtering browser extension recently partnered with Microsoft and run by neoconservatives, Obama-Clinton alumni, and other assorted Trump haters, has advised advertisers to withdraw their business from websites on its blacklist of "unreliable" news websites — a list that includes Breitbart News, The Drudge Report, and the Daily Mail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manager Claims He Heard Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/01/31/jussie-smolletts-manager-claims-he-heard-assault-maga-country-on-phone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Jussie Smollett is reportedly refusing to turn over his cell phone to police as they continue to probe an alleged attack against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy battle brews over home security cameras; Police want to register...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/01/31/privacy-battle-brews-over-home-security-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police want to register - and even subsidize - connected home security cameras. That’s just the start of the ethical challenges ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC patrolling plastic-straw cop leaves eateries rattled...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/01/30/on-patrol-with-washingtons-plastic-straw-cop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the nation’s capital, as of this month, plastic drinking straws are out. Straws made from eco-friendly materials are in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal Cold Smashes Records...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-01-30-cold-polar-vortex-midwest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extreme cold in the Midwest killed at least 10 people, left thousands without power, shut down schools and government offices and halted mail delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisons Quietly Build Databases Of Inmate Voice Prints...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/30/prison-voice-prints-databases-securus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The voice-print technology allows authorities to mine call databases and cross-reference the voices of individuals prisoners have spoken with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biochemist Sells 'Gene-Editing Kit' for the Masses...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/01/29/east-bay-biochemist-sells-gene-editing-kit-for-the-masses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An East Bay entrepreneur wants to put the power of gene-editing in everyone's hands through his company's "Genetic Design Kits."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Actor arrived home with rope around neck...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/31/jussie-smollett-arrived-home-with-rope-around-neck-after-attack-cops/?_ga=2.16488309.217970341.1548988443-124232095.1548706750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video from a surveillance camera at Smollett’s apartment building showing him arrive home with a rope around his neck is part of a larger effort to obtain as much footage as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM:  TAX RICH AT 90%</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rep-ilhan-omar-supports-taxing-wealthiest-americans-90-135004259.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Through Her Eyes” is a new weekly half-hour show hosted by humanitarian and women’s rights activist Zainab Salbi that aims to explore a hot button news issue through the lens of a female newsmaker. Weeks after Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., made headlines by calling for a top marginal income</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ: I Acknowledge My Privilege in Being Born 'Cisgendered'... </title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-i-acknowledge-my-privilege-being-born-cisgende</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘That is a privilege I have no matter how poor my family was when I was born’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra died after left in cold...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2019/01/30/zebra-dies-in-carroll-county-after-being-left-out-in-the-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARROLL COUNTY, Ind. – A zebra died due to the extreme cold in Carroll County. Sherriff Tobe Leazenby told WLFI one of two zebras on the Pittsburg property died as a result of the cold. Leazenby said investigators checked the scene, and the property met standards for outside animals, making shelter, food and water available. Investigators said it appeared the zebra got stuck in the fence and couldn't get free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid thaw to follow polar blast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96fb8799f33c43338dc56ba51d77b3b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — In Illinois, temperatures could rise by 80 degrees within days. In Michigan, melting snow and rain and a 17-mile ice jam could lead to flooding. Across the Midwest, the sudden warmth was sure to bring more broken roads and busted water mains. The polar vortex that brought many cities to a standstill was expected to end with a rapid thaw that experts say could be unprecedented. But the sudden swing from long johns to light jackets and short sleeves could create problems of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botches words, suffers face spasms, confuses Dems, GOP...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/nancy-pelosi-botches-words-suffers-face-spasms-confuses-dems-gop-while-vowing-no-border-wall-funding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s wrong with Nancy Pelosi? The House Speaker spoke to reporters today for only about 21 minutes, but there were plenty of strange moments as she botched words, suffered face spasms and brain freezes as she attacked President Trump’s proposed border wall and his leadership during the recent partial government shutdown. ﻿ Lamenting the recent …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sets up loudspeakers to spread ideological message...</title>
      <link>http://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1137676.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.globaltimes.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doorbells have eyes: Police want to register private cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/01/31/doorbells-have-eyes-privacy-battle-brewing-over-home-security-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police want to register — and even subsidize — connected home security cameras. That’s just the start of the ethical challenges ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Pair use dating app to meet for van sex, arrested after high-speed chase...</title>
      <link>https://www.battlecreekenquirer.com/story/news/local/2019/01/31/dating-app-hook-up-pennfield-township-arrest-police-chase/2733745002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.battlecreekenquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deputies said the couple had connectedÂ on a social media dating site,Â met in person for the first time and had sex in a van.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-16 fighter jets to patrol sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/f-16-fighter-jets-will-patrol-the-sky-above-super-bowl-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jets will be flying over Atlanta, protecting a 30-mile restricted flight zone around the stadium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive using fingerprint implants evades capture for 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/31/drug-trafficker-evades-capture-15-years-fingerprint-implants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drug trafficker who cut and burned skin to insert implants arrested near Madrid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE 'THE ENABLER'</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/01/apples-hypocritical-defense-data-privacy/581680/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company enables the surveillance that supposedly offends its values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare half-male, half-female cardinal spotted in PA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2019/01/half-male-half-female-cardinal-pennsylvania/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What causes this phenomenon?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barely-transparent transparency data report gets more opaque...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2019/01/31/amazon-government-data-demands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon posted its bi-annual report Thursday detailing the number of government data demands it receives. The numbers themselves are unremarkable, neither spiking nor falling in the second-half of last year compared to the first-half. The number of subpoenas, search warrants and other court orders t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Don Jr. did NOT call father ahead of Tower meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/31/politics/senate-investigators-blocked-phone-calls-not-father-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate investigators have obtained new information showing Donald Trump Jr.'s mysterious phone calls ahead of the 2016 Trump Tower meeting were not with his father, three sources with knowledge of the matter told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would cost Bezos $101B, Gates $74B, Buffett $64B, MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/31/how-much-bezos-gates-buffet-could-pay-under-bernie-sanders-tax-plan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders' new "For the 99.8% Act" would raise estate taxes up to 77 percent for those leaving over $1 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court: San Fran Health Warning On Soda Ads Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/01/31/sf-soda-ad-warning-labels-blocked-9th-circuit-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court on Thursday blocked a San Francisco law requiring health warnings on advertisements for soda and other sugary drinks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient Economy Fuels Best January Stocks in 30 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/resilient-u-s-economy-fuels-january-stock-market-recovery-11548939600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks and smaller companies helped lift U.S. stocks to their best January in 30 years, a sign investors are favoring sectors tied to the U.S. economy as trade tensions cloud global growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In packed churches and secret masses, Papal visit brings Gulf Catholics hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-emirates-worship/in-packed-churches-and-secret-masses-papal-visit-brings-gulf-catholics-hope-idUSKCN1PP2UJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Dubai's overflowing churches and Riyadh's secretive masses, Catholi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce, Jay-Z offer lifetime concert tix for fans who go vegan...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-beyonce-idUSKCN1PP2P8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music superstars Beyonce and Jay-Z are offering fans a chance to win free ticket...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami plastic surgery center promised beauty at discount. 8 women died...</title>
      <link>https://www.naplesnews.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2019/01/30/fla-plastic-surgery-clinics-cut-prices-boost-ads-and-eight-women-died/2467780002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naplesnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm bank freaks after woman uses DNA test, finds donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/woman-finds-sperm-donor-after-using-dna-test-raising-questions-about-donor-anonymity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sperm bank is threatening to sue an Oregon woman who contacted her daughter's biological father after using an at-home DNA test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something mysterious thwarting drivers in small town? Fobs don't unlock. Cars won't start. Blaring alarms can't be quieted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/carstairs-westview-co-op-grocery-car-key-fob-1.4999558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key fobs that suddenly won't unlock vehicles. Cars that won't start. Alarms that go off for no reason. Something mysterious is thwarting drivers outside a grocery store in the small Alberta town of Carstairs — and it's sparking all kinds of theories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON BEATS STREET...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/31/amazon-earnings-q4-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon beats on earnings and revenue, but gives light guidance -- stock seesaws after hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Cuban To Run In Republican Primary?</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/bensmith/howard-schultz-2020-election-republican-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Cuban isn’t ruling it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Stern Ex-Sidekick Arrested for Drug Possession...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/people-news/artie-lange-jail-rehab-1203124809/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Artie Lange was held in the Essex County Correctional Facility in Newark, N.J., on Wednesday night allegedly in an effort to help him sober up before being relocated to a long-term treatme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign sues ex-aide over tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/war-trump-campaign-sues-ex-aide-author-of-tell-all-team-of-vipers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump presidential campaign has officially sued a former White House staffer and author of a nasty West Wing tell-all, claiming the ex-aide violated several confidentiality agreements to "diss the president and key aides."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign journalists freed...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-france/venezuela-frees-journalists-for-french-spanish-media-idUSKCN1PO2FJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela freed on Thursday two French, two Colombian and one Spanish journalist...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad blood between Cook, Zuckerberg spills over...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-vs-apple-tech-s-biggest-cold-war-heats-will-n965236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal animosity is at the heart of it: “There was Ali-Frazier. Now there’s nerd vs. nerd.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker spoke to baby, hurled obscenities at couple using NEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nest-camera-hacked-hacker-spoke-to-baby-hurled-obscenities-at-couple-using-nest-camera-dad-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hacker accessed Illinois family's Nest security cameras, father says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams to star in Super Bowl ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/politics/stacey-abrams-set-make-super-bowl-debut/jqKMteRwmj0Fs3IqwcNOXI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacey Abrams recorded a 30-second TV ad to be seen in Georgia during the Super Bowl. The ad is on behalf of her voting rights group, Fair Fight Action. Abrams, who lost a race for governor to Republican Brian Kemp, appears in the ad with Natalie Crawford, a Republican official from Habersham County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWTIME Sets Roger Ailes Series for Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/showtime-homeland-final-season-wont-premiere-until-fall-roger-ailes-limited-series-set-for-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TCA 2019: Production begins next week on Claire Danes drama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN plays awful high-pitch sound to boot loiterers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/on-air/as-seen-on/7-Eleven-Plays-Piercing-High-Pitch-Sound-Targeting-Homeless_New-York-505143632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Portland convenience store installed a high-pitch sound generator to clear out homeless loiterers. Yes, the problem apparently is that bad. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/weird/' target='_blank'&gt;More offbeat stories here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;KGW's Mike Benner reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK EARNINGS BLOWOUT DESPITE PRIVACY BREACHES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/31/people-say-they-care-about-facebooks-privacy-scandals-but-they-dont.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's announcement that monthly users took off in Europe and Asia shows the company may not ultimately pay a substantial business cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked man bites dog, then bites an FBI agent....</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article225331040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia man stripped naked, attacked and bit his own dog multiple times, then chomped down on the neck of the off-duty FBI agent who was chasing him, report Prince William County Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-kennel owners allegedly had threesome with 'Demon' doberman...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/local/crime/article_2c64dd8e-24cb-11e9-8d20-4fca3b9c0d37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Patterson and his wife had the front toenails of a male dog removed so they could more easily engaged in sex acts with the animal, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran restaurant bans MAGA hats...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/san-francisco-area-restaurant-bans-make-america-great-hats-compares-to-white-hoods-and-swastikas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;An award-winning cookbook author and California restaurant owner says anyone wearing a red &amp;quot;Make America Great Again&amp;quot; baseball cap will be refused service at his restaurant.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
