<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Fox that bit 6 people at Capitol had rabies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fox-caught-on-capitol-grounds-and-euthanized-tests-positive-for-rabies/ar-AAVW9ow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 May Have Been Killed Illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/soul-crushing-barbarity-uncovered-in-d-c-110-dead-babies-five-who-may-have-been-killed-illegally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Handy and the other rescuers have the courage of their convictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: INTERCEPT Parent Company Laying Off Staffers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-intercept-s-parent-company-first-look-lays-off-nearly-20-staffers/ar-AAVVQxE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>META Exploring Virtual Currency: 'Zuck Bucks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meta-exploring-non-blockchain-based-virtual-currency-report/ar-AAVWidU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas chartering buses of illegal immigrants to DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox7austin.com/news/greg-abbott-texas-border-security-charter-buses-illegal-immigrants-dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox7austin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This comes after the CDC announced last week that it is ending a policy that limited asylum at the U.S.-Mexico border to prevent the spread of COVID-19, also known as Title 42.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible moment single tank takes on entire convoy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10692495/Incredible-moment-single-Ukrainian-tank-takes-entire-Russian-convoy-near-Kyiv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to brilliant positioning, the tank was able to fire several rounds at the invaders' convoy, threading the gap between other structures from a concealed location behind a house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRUCK BY TRAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.northjersey.com/story/news/essex/montclair/2022/04/06/eric-boehlert-killed-train-montclair-nj/9485476002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.northjersey.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boehlert, 57, was a veteran writer and media analyst, a founding editor of Salon magazine, and a frequent television and radio guest discussing politics and the press on CNN and CNBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Cremation Units Covering Up Civilian Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/mariupol-city-council-accuses-russian-forces-of-bringing-in-mobile-cremation-units-to-cover-up-civilian-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anchor Alisyn Camerota asked Black “what about Mariupol” after he gave an updated assessment of the state of play of the Russian military in Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants handed CELL PHONES so ICE track them...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10690597/Ex-Trump-officials-urge-Abbott-declare-border-invasion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans want Texas to declare an 'invasion' at the southern border to allow state troopers and National Guard members to turn back migrants as the country braces for Title 42 to end next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fled to Switzerland fearing White House retaliation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10689445/Whistleblower-handed-Hunter-Bidens-laptop-congressmen-fled-Switzerland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whistleblower Jack Maxey gave DailyMail.com a copy of the hard drive from Hunter Biden's  abandoned laptop in the spring of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Eric Boehlert killed in bike accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5063434/eric-boehlert-journalist-dead-bike-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOURNALIST and well-known media critic Eric Boehlert has died after being involved in a bicycle accident as fellow writers pay tribute to the author. Mr. Boehlert tragically passed away on Monday n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami crypto craze on full display at bitcoin conference...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cryptocurrency-technology-business-blockchain-lifestyle-e0b51430d7b3c4853cd4618984b7d484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of cryptocurrency enthusiasts are gathering in Miami as the city builds its reputation as one of the key locations to develop the blockchain technology despite its underdog status. Dozens of companies are using the Bitcoin 2022 conference running Wednesday through Saturday as a venue to network, pitch ideas and share announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion group claims it took 115 fetuses from waste truck...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/04/06/1091228924/anti-abortion-fetuses-waste-truck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., police originally said it found five fetal remains in one of the group member's apartments. Progressive Anti-Abortion Uprising now says there were 115 fetuses in total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NY judge not complying with vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kathy-hochul-covid-health-business-new-york-bf753e18c2841f1ca646270b38a10616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A judge on New York’s highest court has been referred to a disciplinary commission and could be kicked off the bench for failing to comply with a rule requiring proof of vaccination against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon: Russia has fully withdrawn from Kyiv, Chernihiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pentagon-russia-has-fully-withdrawn-from-kyiv-chernihiv/ar-AAVVVFH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARLAND INFECTED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/06/attorney-general-merrick-garland-tests-positive-for-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Garland attended an event with FBI Director Christopher Wray hours before the positive result. He was at a D.C. dinner with hundreds of VIPs on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Warns AMAZON: 'Here We Come' After Union Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-warns-amazon-e2-80-98here-we-come-e2-80-99-after-new-york-union-vote/ar-AAVVLmP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Gridiron Dinner, Covid outbreak among DC A-list guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/after-gridiron-dinner-a-covid-outbreak-among-washington-a-list-guests/ar-AAVVSko</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed to shrink balance sheet by $95 billion a month...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/06/fed-minutes-march-2022-meetings-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve on Wednesday released minutes from its March 15-16 policy meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon researched how to talk to '4,590 alien civilizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5062151/us-government-talk-aliens-first-contact-4590-space-civilizations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON researched the best way to contact aliens and communicate with a possible 4,590 extraterrestrial civilizations, according to secret US files. The Defense Intelligence Agency (DIA) docu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manure 'hot commodity' amid fertilizer shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/manure-is-hot-commodity-as-americans-face-fertilizer-shortage-amid-ukraine-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts joins liberals to criticize 'shadow docket'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/06/politics/supreme-court-shadow-docket-john-roberts-epa-water/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 5-4 Supreme Court reinstated a Trump-era rule Wednesday that restricts the authority of states to reject federal permits under the Clean Water Act in another ruling putting the court's emergency docket in the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma lawmakers vote to ban abortion, imprison doctors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/05/oklahoma-lawmakers-vote-to-ban-abortion-imprison-doctors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors who perform abortions under other circumstances can face a $100,000 fine in addition to a long prison sentence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind energy company kills 150 eagles, pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-billings-eagles-birds-a5538efc2c386c661194fe64904cffe2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILLINGS, Mont. (AP) — A wind energy company was sentenced to probation and ordered to pay more than $8 million in fines and restitution after at least 150 eagles were killed over the past decade at its wind farms in eight states, federal prosecutors said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Embassy Guard Charged With Passing Secrets Onto Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-61015772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ballantyne Smith, 57, is charged with nine offences under the Official Secrets Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Libraries More Popular Than Ever Before...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/libraries-more-popular/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report on over 17,000 U.S. libraries found that library collections are bigger and more digital than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEE NYC:  60% say would be better off somewhere else...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/nearly-60-of-nyc-voters-say-their-family-would-be-better-off-somewhere-else/3633542/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 60% of New York City registered voters agree with the idea that their family would have a better future if they left the city permanently, according to a new poll published Wednesday. The survey from political consultants Fontas Advisors and polling firm Core Decision Analytics adds to a growing body of evidence that New Yorkers are preoccupied with rising…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random violence soars; Girl laughs while breaking hip of senior...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/minor-arrested-as-main-aggressor-in-senseless-attack-on-76-year-old-nyc-woman-source/3633565/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video showed the attackers laughing and smirking as the 76-year-old woman was violently thrown to the ground, breaking her hip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innocent grandma killed in crossfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/surveillance-video-shows-shootout-that-killed-61-year-old-grandmother-in-bronx/3632983/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New surveillance video shows the shootout that left a 61-year-old Bronx grandmother killed as she was caught in the crossfire on her way home from work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's plan to build empire stretching from Vladivostok to Portugal...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-wants-build-pro-russia-26646057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World leaders are calling for President Vladimir Putin to be tried for war crimes but experts are concerned these horrors could continue as the despot pushes forward with a grander plan to build a sprawling empire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Government Faces Crisis After Right-Wing Lawmaker Quits...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-703365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett and Lapid to meet over coalition crisis, Netanyahu congratulates Silman's decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sets fire to gay bar with patrons inside...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/arsonist-poured-gasoline-inside-lgbtq-bar-in-brooklyn-and-set-it-on-fire-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Brooklyn bar will remain closed as police investigate the shocking arson that occurred with patrons inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Good morning to our new overlord!': Woke TWITTER employees vent their fears over Musk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10691887/Employees-reveal-concerns-Elon-Musks-vow-make-significant-changes-Twitter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter employees are voicing their concerns after Elon Musk was named a company board member and majority shareholder. Musk has admitted his investment in the company was not passive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE warns AirPods security flaw could leak private info to strangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5063589/apple-warning-huge-airpods-security-flaw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USED Apple AirPods have a major security flaw, according to a new report. Some used AirPods reportedly stay linked to the previous owner’s iCloud account despite a factory reset, Business Ins…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts Joins Criticism of Supreme Court 'Shadow Docket' Orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/roberts-joins-criticism-of-supreme-court-shadow-docket-orders-1.1748534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts for the first time joined the U.S. Supreme Court’s liberal wing in blasting the conservative majority’s handling of the stream of emergency requests that critics have dubbed the “shadow docket.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Monkey Queen Makes Through Mating Season With Reign Intact...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/06/japans-monkey-queen-made-it-through-mating-season-with-her-reign-intact/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reign of Japan’s monkey queen has just begun. Last year, Yakei, a 9-year-old female Japanese macaque, fought several other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLEGE BASKETBALL CHAMPIONSHIP PULLS MORE VIEWERS THAN OSCARS, GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/march-madness-kansas-jayhawks-mens-basketball-entertainment-sports-arts-and-entertainment-d057c12d27a8cfb1aba49ad6cac3f2a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Kansas' comeback victory over North Carolina to win the NCAA basketball championship was the most-viewed men's title game on cable television. The Jayhawks' 72-69 win averaged 18.1 million viewers on TBS, TNT and truTV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous leaks million state emails...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5063545/anonymous-leaks-a-million-russian-state-emails/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANONYMOUS claims to have leaked over 900,000 Russian state network emails in a major attack. The email addresses are associated with Russia’s largest media corporation that’s been accused of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA SANCTIONS PUTIN DAUGHTERS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5063018/putins-secret-daughters-sanctions-tyrant-dads-war-crimes-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s secret daughters will be hit with sanctions in wake of their tyrant father’s horrific war crimes in Ukraine. Dr Maria Vorontsova, 36, a geneticist, and Dr Katerina Tikh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the beats: Drill rap insiders claim more to music than violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-drill-rap-production-nyc-industry-20220402-fh2bu6ux6fghvhh3cihwfugjyy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicole Racine runs a one stop shop for drill rap hopefuls, grooming them for stardom — they can have headshots taken, she helps them upload their music and videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Overload: Viewers Overwhelmed by Too Many Choices...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/streaming-users-overload-choices-1235125685/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even so, more than 90 percent of people in a Nielsen survey say they'll keep or increase the amount of SVOD services they use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barack lightens up gloomy White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/and-now-here-e2-80-99s-your-host-e2-80-94-barack-obama/ar-AAVTQtp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama and Romney are back, and show how politics have changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/06/politics/barack-obama-mitt-romney-washington/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year 2012 called and wants its politics back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER looks to create travel 'superapp' by adding planes, trains, rental cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/06/uber-chases-superapp-by-adding-planes-trains-and-rental-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco-headquartered firm announced Wednesday that it is adding trains, buses, planes and car rentals to its U.K. app this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Most Americans Can't Name All 4 Of Their Grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/family-tree-name-grandparents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Familiar with your family tree? There’s a good chance you’re not. More than half of Americans can't name of all four of their grandparents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO Scours Skies for Incursions Amid Rising Tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/nato-scours-the-skies-for-incursions-amid-rising-russia-tensions/ar-AAVUrHR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA player Kanter out to corner UN rights chief on China...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220406-nba-player-kanter-out-to-corner-un-rights-chief-on-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-time NBA player Enes Kanter Freedom, whose advocacy on Xinjiang and Tibet has ruffled feathers, hopes to bend UN human rights chief Michelle Bachelet's ear on Thursday about her forthcoming Chin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen to Warn of 'Enormous Economic Repercussions' From Ukraine Invasion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/05/yellen-to-warn-of-enormous-economic-repercussions-from-ukraine-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet L. Yellen plans on Wednesday to warn of major consequences for the global economy as a result</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failure to take down Kyiv was defeat for the ages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-kyiv-europe-dc559574ce9f6683668fa221af2d5340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Kyiv was a Russian defeat for the ages. The fight started poorly for the invaders and went downhill from there. When President Vladimir Putin launched his war on Feb. 24 after months of buildup on Ukraine's borders, he sent hundreds of helicopter-borne commandos — the best of the best of Russia's “spetsnaz” special forces soldiers — to assault and seize a lightly defended airfield on Kyiv's doorstep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wing Azov Battalion emerges as controversial defender of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Right-wing-Azov-Battalion-emerges-as-a-17060658.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine - Inside a warehouse, in a bustling section of this capital, the incessant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Picasso being cancelled?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220406-is-picasso-being-cancelled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pablo Picasso's track-record with women certainly would not make him a feminist pin-up today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-oligarch says Vlad sees war with West already underway...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ex-oligarch-says-putin-sees-war-with-the-west-already-underway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Oligarch Says Putin Sees War With the West Already Underway</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems on defense over gas prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-find-themselves-on-the-defensive-over-gas-prices/ar-AAVTxPN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts infections jump 27%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/massachusetts-coronavirus-cases-jump-by-27-hospitalizations-rise/ar-AAVTEgC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports record Covid cases amid lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/chinas-daily-covid-cases-surge-past-20-000-amid-lockdowns-101649214832715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current outbreak has already surpassed number of infections found in the early days of the pandemic, before testing was easily available, and encompasses a much broader swath of the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: France votes as tight Le Pen-Macron duel looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220406-france-votes-as-tight-le-pen-macron-duel-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France votes Sunday in the first round of presidential elections at which Emmanuel Macron is bidding for a second term in the face of a strengthening challenge from resurgent far-right leader Marine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE first big bank to forecast recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/05/business/recession-inflation-economy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN PUPPET SAYS TROOPS MEAN PEACE...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/04/05/russia-claims-slaughter-in-bucha-was-staged-and-a-fake-attack-16409009/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its foreign minister accused Ukraine and the West of fabricating and spreading a false narrative.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
