<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Aging America: Old will outnumber children first time in HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6426745/Old-people-outnumber-children-time-countrys-history.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By 2030 all baby boomers will be older than age 65, the US Census Bureau has revealed. One in every 5 Americans will be retirement age and deaths will 'rise substantially' in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bertolucci dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/nov/26/bernardo-bertolucci-last-tango-in-paris-director-dies-aged-77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politically pioneering Italian director of The Conformist and Last Tango in Paris, who went on to win the best director Oscar for The Last Emperor, dies from cancer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Crowd at border pepper-sprayed under Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/sdut-border-patrol-rock-throwing-san-ysidro-2013nov25-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of about 100 people attempting to cross the border illegally Sunday threw rocks and bottles at Border Patrol agents, who used a pepperball launcher to force the crowd back into Mexico, federal officials said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The undergrad who uncovers hidden data collection that tech giants want to keep secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/tech/apps-social/article/2174875/jane-wong-explains-why-she-uncovers-hidden-app-features-tech-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UMass-Dartmouth undergrad wants to understand what tech companies are doing with user data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep sea base would be first A.I. COLONY...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/2174738/beijing-plans-ai-atlantis-south-china-sea-without-human-sight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Urged by President Xi Jinping to dare to do something that has never been done before, scientists say challenges could give China huge technology lead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAR GAS FIRED...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/sd-me-border-closer-20181125-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.-Mexico border at the San Ysidro Port of Entry was closed in both directions Sunday after hundreds of migrants rushed the area, prompting federal authorities to launch tear gas in an effort to get the group to disperse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Taxes With Bitcoin? Ohio Says Sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pay-taxes-with-bitcoin-ohio-says-sure-1543161720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio appears set to become the first state to accept bitcoin for tax bills, a show of support for a technology that has garnered lots of hype but failed to gain traction as a form of payment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potentially 'Catastrophic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/Gas-Leak-Shuts-Down-Delaware-Memorial-Bridge-Amid-Thanksgiving-Travel-Rush-501208801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leak of a flammable chemical from a plant next to the Delaware Memorial Bridge forced a shut down of the dual-span suspension bridge on Sunday creating a traffic nightmare during the travel rush home from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clamping Down On 'Misgendering', 'Deadnaming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.refinery29.com/en-gb/2018/11/217696/twitter-new-trans-protection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refinery29.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has updated its terms of service to offer greater protection from online abuse to trans people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Bans Feminist For Writing 'Men Aren't Women'...</title>
      <link>http://thefederalist.com/2018/11/25/twitter-permanently-bans-feminist-writing-men-arent-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Becomes NFL's All-Time Leading Passer...</title>
      <link>https://patriotswire.usatoday.com/2018/11/25/new-england-patriots-tom-brady-peyton-manning-passing-yards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patriotswire.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady fittingly set the all-time passing yards record against the New York Jets in Week 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Prosecutors NOT filing financial charges against Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/25/manhattan-da-wont-be-filing-financial-charges-against-harvey-weinstein/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weinstein, however, still faces predatory assault, rape and other charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Tactic to Catch Fugitive Official: Hold His American Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/china-s-tactic-to-catch-a-fugitive-official-hold-his-two-american-children/18019586/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — When Victor and Cynthia Liu landed with their mother on a tropical Chinese island in June to visit an ailing grandfather, they thought they would soon be on a plane back to their East Coast lives — he to start his sophomore year at Georgetown University, and she to work at the consulting firm McKinsey &amp; Co. in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Big Dipper' satellites to rival to US-run GPS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/china-s-big-dipper-satellites-challenge-the-dominance-of-gps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Is Building a $9 Billion Rival to the American-Run GPS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: 145 whales found dead on beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12166302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DoC found half of the whales already dead and euthanised the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic nuns denounce 'culture of silence, secrecy' surrounding church abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/catholic-church-nuns-sex-abuse-pope-francis-international-union-superiors-general-a8650566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal officer faces trial after romantic involvement with terror suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Federal-agent-faces-trial-in-Houston-after-13416307.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;The email from a federal agent in Dubai about her jet-set affair with a suspected Middle Eastern terrorist could have been torn from a supermarket paperback. “I can’t stop thinking about…you. I haven’t slept for days,” Leatrice Malika De Bruhl-Daniels wrote, according to federal court documents. “I’m deeply attracted to you and I can’t think about you like that. Don’t worry, I will still fight for your visa situation as much as I can.” As U.S. officials continued to investigate the Syrian businessman who’d thrown the federal agent a lavish birthday bash and helped treat her to a Greek vacation, she reportedly texted him, “I don’t want to think u hv lied to me since I put my neck out there for u.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,200+ flights canceled!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/todayinthesky/2018/11/25/snow-flights-canceled-storm-snarls-post-thanksgiving-sunday/2107525002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline passengers faced delays and cancellations, one of the busiest travel days of the year as throngs of flyers made their way home from Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: BIBI PROSECUTOR RECOMMENDS INDICTMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Report-Netanyahus-prosecutor-recommends-indictment-in-two-cases-572785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cases include Case 1000 (The illegal gift affair) and Case 2000 (The Yediot Ahronot affair).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAFFIC HELL: Chemical leak closes Delaware Memorial Bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/news/crime/2018/11/25/gas-leak-closes-delaware-memorial-bridge-both-directions/2109773002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports of a chemical plant's chemical leak at the base of the Delaware Memorial Bridge has shut down all bridge traffic SundayÂ evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants clash with authorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/border-closed-after-groups-of-migrants-stormed-us-border-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities clashed with migrants Sunday after a group estimated to number in the hundreds stormed a US port of entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech toilets to track your every movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/high-tech-toilets-could-soon-141544754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bathroom is arguably the last bastion of privacy, but soon a new high-tech lavatory could be tracking your every movement. Researchers at the European Space Agency (ESA) and MIT have teamed up with sanitation specialists to create the ‘FitLoo’ which screens human waste for early signs of disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honduran Says 20,000 Will March Through Vehicle Lanes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/invasion-honduran-migrant-says-20000-will-march-through-vehicle-lanes-at-border-says-applying-for-asylum-is-waste-of-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital ad duopoly under threat as pressure mounts on FACEBOOKGOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/24/digital-ad-duopoly-threat-pressure-mounts-facebook-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook and Google's duopoly in the digital advertising market could be under threat, after a number of leading British brands said they were reviewing their relationships with the companies amid mounting pressure to cut ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine says Russia seizes three of its ships in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-ships/ukraine-says-russia-seizes-three-of-its-ships-in-black-sea-idUSKCN1NU0YK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian navy said Russian special forces had seized three of its ships in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero dog saves family from gas leak...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/news/2018/11/23/german-shepherd-smells-gas-saves-longneck-familys-life/2081365002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greta, a 5-year-old German shepherd smelled propane and woke up her owners, potentially saving their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV cases could explode as TINDER users having 'riskier sex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/744539/HIV-symptoms-cases-heterosexual-sex-Tinder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocks water route...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/25/europe/russia-ukraine-kerch-strait-intl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian authorities closed off the Kerch Strait Sunday amid a confrontation with Ukrainian naval vessels, Russian state news agencies and the Ukrainian military said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Police face-off with tribe in missionary killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/police-face-off-with-tribe-in-missionary-killing--10966798</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT BLAIR, India: Indian officers had a nervous long-distance face-off with the tribe who killed an American missionary, in their latest bid to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour Party will oppose...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-labour/britains-opposition-labour-party-will-oppose-brexit-deal-corbyn-idUSKCN1NU0KF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's main opposition Labour Party will oppose the government's Br...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret emails by Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6426219/Parliament-seizes-Facebook-internal-papers-Mark-Zuckerbergs-refusal-answer-questions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parliament has exerted its legal powers to get hold of private Facebook documents following Mark Zuckerberg's repeated refusal to answer MP's questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants march toward border in show of force...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/migrants-march-toward-us-border-show-force-191030971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico (AP) — Several hundred Central American migrants have marched toward the international border crossing between Tijuana and California to pressure the U.S to hear their asylum claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unprecedented move'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/24/mps-seize-cache-facebook-internal-papers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents alleged to contain revelations on data and privacy controls that led to Cambridge Analytica scandal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Opens Fire on Ukrainian Vessels... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/russia-fires-at-ukraine-ships-in-black-sea-11563775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crew member is injured after a vessel was hit by the strikes, the Ukrainian navy says, after a day of rising tension off Crimea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to probe Trump money ties to Russia, Saudis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrats-probe-trump-money-ties-russia-saudis-lawmaker-154712755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats intend to probe US President Donald Trump's financial ties to determine whether they are the "hidden hand" driving US foreign policy on Russia and Saudi Arabia, the incoming chairman of the House Intelligence Committee said Sunday. Adam Schiff, currently the ranking Democrat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Now Home to 'World's Biggest' Weed Store... </title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-25/vegas-is-now-home-to-the-world-s-biggest-weed-store-of-course-it-is</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papadopoulos jailed...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-judge-orders-former-trump-campaign-adviser-papadopoulos-160100736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. federal judge on Sunday denied a motion by George Papadopoulos, a former aide for Donald Trump's 2016 presidential campaign, seeking to postpone his sentence pending a separate case he hoped would lead to his conviction being overturned. Papadopoulos will report to jail on Monday to start</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman injured in fall while trying to scale border fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/skbaer/woman-injured-climbing-us-mexico-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26-year-old Guatemalan woman fell and landed on pieces of rebar that pierced her body near the San Ysidro Port of Entry. Her young children were not injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Called Cops on Striking Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/amazon-asked-police-in-spain-to-intervene-warehouse-strike-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Amazon workers across Europe went on strike on Black Friday in protest over working conditions at Amazon warehouses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's New Government Says No Deal With USA on Asylum Seekers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-24/u-s-gets-incoming-mexican-govt-s-backing-on-asylum-plan-wapo-jovqz81n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blair calls for new referendum...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6426445/Tony-Blair-says-Mays-deal-hated-Leavers-Remainers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Labour PM Tony Blair questioned 'literally why are we doing this' when the terms of Theresa May's Brexit was 'painful and pointless'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Saudi prince says CIA cannot be trusted on Khashoggi conclusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/senior-saudi-prince-says-cia-cannot-trusted-khashoggi-125500659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prince, a former Saudi intelligence chief who has also served as ambassador to the United States, said the agency's conclusion that Iraq possessed chemical weapons before the U.S. invasion in 2003 showed it could be unreliable. This is my answer to their assessment of who is guilty and who</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tries to bribe ICE agent to deport his wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article222096380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Oswaldo Burgos, 48, pleaded guilty in federal court in Oregon to trying to bribe an Immigration and Customs Enforcement agent $3,000 to deport his then-wife, whom he was divorcing, and her daughter, whom he had previously sponsored to enter the United States from El Salvador.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hears APPLE antitrust dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-apple/how-much-for-that-app-us-top-court-hears-apple-antitrust-dispute-idUSKCN1NU0JV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When iPhone users want to edit blemishes out of their selfies, identify stars an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALVATION ARMY Bell Ringers Wearing Confederate Flag, 'Aryan' Patches Removed From WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/11/24/salvation-army-bell-ringers-with-aryan-patches-at-nwi-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walmart spokesperson said the store asked the bell ringers to leave as soon as the issue was brought to their attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of missing revised down...</title>
      <link>https://af.reuters.com/article/commoditiesNews/idAFL2N1Y0023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;af.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Corrects spelling of Sierra Nevada in paragraph 5)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday travelers scramble home ahead of Midwest blizzard...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/snowstorm-with-blizzard-conditions-to-blast-i-80-corridor-of-central-us-into-monday/70006709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c34fbd4905ae491ea67a5d597a832187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A fast-moving winter storm was expected to blanket much of the central Midwest with snow on Sunday at the end of the Thanksgiving weekend, grounding hundreds of flights and forcing the closure of part of a major highway on one of the busiest travel days of the year. "It's going to be messy," said Todd Kluber, a meteorologist for the National Weather Service who is based in suburban Chicago. With much of the central plains and Great Lakes region under blizzard or winter storms warnings, nearly 500 flights headed to or from the U.S. had been canceled as of 11 a.m. Sunday, according to the flight-tracking website FlightAware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERSHOWITZ: Mueller's final report 'going to be devastating' for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/mueller-report-devastating-president-frequent-trump-defender/story?id=59393855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alan Dershowitz said the report will have a strong political impact, but is unlikely to result in criminal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK: I AM GOING TO MARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/elon-musk-mars-space-x-14c01761-d045-4da0-924b-322fb6a109ce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Does that sound like an escape hatch for rich people?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN LOOMS IN UK PARLIAMENT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1384dc86bcd418a9eeddd81fdb27f78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — After months of hesitation, stop-and-start negotiations and resignations, Britain and the European Union on Sunday finally sealed an agreement governing the U.K.'s departure from the bloc next year. So much for the easy part. British Prime Minister Theresa May must now sell the deal to her divided Parliament — a huge task considering the intense opposition from pro-Brexit and pro-EU lawmakers alike — to ensure Britain can leave with a minimum of upheaval on March 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Waiters brawl...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-tijuana-waiters-brawl-with-migrants-over-dine-and-dash-fears-attack-each-other-with-tables-chairs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The caravan of Central American migrants have been stymied in their attempt to cross into America, and are now wreaking havoc on Tijuana, Mexico. Video tweeted by Christian Camara shows a reported clash between waiters at a taco restaurant and migrants. Waiters at a taco restaurant in #Tijuana attack a group of #caravan migrants with …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERSHOWITZ: Mueller's final report 'going to be devastating' for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/alan-dershowitz-muellers-final-report-is-going-to-be-devastating-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard Law School professor emeritus Alan Dershowitz predicted on Sunday that special counsel Robert Mueller's final report for the federal Russia investigation will be calamitous for President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTER BURN:  Generators, COORS, canned food. How 'mountain boys' surviving in Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221980400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small group of Paradise residents have remained in town after the Camp Fire destroyed much of the Northern California town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Parliament obtains internal FACEBOOK docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/24/us/six4three-facebook-uk-parliament/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British Parliament has obtained a set of internal Facebook documents the company has fought for months to stop from being made public, according to Facebook and a lawyer involved in a suit against the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday travelers scramble home ahead of Midwest blizzard...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/25/winter-storm-packing-strong-winds-snow-threatens-holiday-travel/2107471002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major airport hubs, including Chicago, face possible travel delays from snow, blizzard-like conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30,000 Indian-American Sikhs entered rucking industry in 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/sikh-indian-americans-becoming-truckers-mintu-pandher-laramie-wyoming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian-Americans who practice the Sikh faith may well be a big part of the solution to a shortage of truck drivers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside kids-only rehab that treats video games like cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/bbcthree/article/d80d46eb-253d-4b99-ba60-caca6858d757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash for realtor after using half-naked models to promote home...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Houston-Realtor-faced-backlash-after-using-13416353.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Realtor, Kristin Gyldenege, said she booked six showings the day after posting pictures of the models in the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Man killed in AL mall shooting 'likely did not fire' shots that injured 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/birmingham/2018/11/man-killed-in-alabama-mall-shooting-likely-did-not-fire-the-rounds-that-injured-2-others-police-said.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We regret that our initial media release was not totally accurate, but new evidence indicates that it was not," a Hoover police spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Rally Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/2018/11/24/mssen-runoff-what-know-trump-rally-biloxi-ms-cindy-hyde-smith/2106551002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox &amp; Friends will broadcast from a Biloxi restaurant on Tuesday morning after Trump rallies for Cindy Hyde-Smith at the Coast Coliseum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memos to Nobody: Inside a neglected fed agency...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edd1f5eaca37478abb79ed5f9eedb0b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mark Robbins gets to work at 8:15 each morning and unlocks the door to his office suite. He switches on the lights and the TV news, brews a pot of coffee and pulls out the first files of the day to review. For the next eight hours or so, he reads through federal workplace disputes, analyzes the cases, marks them with notes and logs his legal opinions. When he's finished, he slips the files into a cardboard box and carries them into an empty room where they will sit and wait. For nobody. He's at 1,520 files and counting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi's Grip on Power to Be Tested This Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pelosis-grip-on-power-to-be-tested-this-week-1543147201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi’s hold on her caucus faces its first major test this week, when House Democrats cast initial votes for their leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime San Fran journalist missing in Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Longtime-San-Francisco-journalist-Ray-Taliaferro-13418925.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A longtime Bay Area journalist and radio host last seen near a pizza parlor in Kentucky has been missing for two weeks, according to media reports. Raphael "Ray" Taliaferro, who was a journalist and news anchor for San Francisco's KGO-AM radio and KRON-TV, was last seen near a pizza parlor called "Mellow Mushroom" in Paducah, Kentucky, on Nov. 10, according to media reports. A missing person's flier posted by the Paducah Police Department stated he may have been experiencing "disorientation and signs of dementia," according to a KRON 4 report. Sheriff Ted Holder of the Massac County Sheriff's Office in Illinois told The Chronicle that Taliaferro's wife reported him missing around 9:30 a.m. in Massac County on Nov. 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Big Tech in Big Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/irwin-m-stelzer/facebook-apple-amazon-netflix-and-google-may-get-government-regulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FAANGs (Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix, and Alphabet) have real problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead sea lions washing up on Puget Sound shores -- with bullet holes...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/along-west-seattle-beaches-slain-california-sea-lions-an-unwelcome-sight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, 13 dead California sea lions have been reported, with six confirmed to have been shot, according to Seal Sitters, a volunteer group that responds to reports of stranded or dead marine mammals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS staffers 'furious' Charlie Rose investigation still ongoing...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/24/cbs-staffers-want-answers-after-year-long-charlie-rose-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News staffers are furious that an investigation into sexual harassment at the network is still ongoing, a year after Charlie Rose’s firing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult Leader Plans Sex-Robot Brothel -- With a Twist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/california-cult-leader-uniclone-unicron-plans-sex-robot-brothelwith-a-twist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it happens, the bionic bordello would require that customers obtain consent from the robots. Is that even possible?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to Judge Every Resident Based on Behavior by End of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-21/beijing-to-judge-every-resident-based-on-behavior-by-end-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Plans to Monitor Moods, Movements, and Kids' Home Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/google-reveals-plans-to-monitor-our-moods-our-movements-and-our-childrens-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you think our privacy is compromised now, just wait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions flare after Ukraine claims Russia ship rammed tugboat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9e44a0c2dce40aebfc117e1490c51b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A Russian coast guard vessel rammed a Ukrainian navy tugboat, resulting in damage to the ship's engines and hull, the Ukrainian navy said Sunday The incident took place Sunday as two Ukrainian navy artillery boats and a tugboat were transiting from Odessa on the Black Sea to Mariupol in the Sea of Azov, via the Kerch Strait, a narrow passage between Crimea and the Russian mainland. "Russian coast guard vessels (...) carried out openly aggressive actions against Ukrainian navy ships" during the transit, the Ukrainian navy statement said. It said a Russian coast guard ship damaged the tugboat's engine, hull, side railing and a lifeboat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman rescuing cat gets stuck in tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article222150020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in North Highlands got stuck in a tree and had to be rescued by Sacramento Metro Fire personnel after trying to rescue a cat that was in the tree, according to a tweet from Metro Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas woman dead after trying to get cheap nose job in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/news/2018/11/24/dallas-woman-dead-after-botched-nose-job-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dallas woman who ended up comatose and on life support after a botched nose job in Mexico has died, according to a family member.Laura Avila died...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN LOOMS IN UK PARLIAMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-46334649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than 18 months of negotiations, European leaders agree a deal for the UK to leave the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU BACKS BREXIT DEAL</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7822575/brexit-summit-live-brussels-second-referendum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU leaders have FINALLY given the green light to Theresa May’s Brexit deal this morning at a historic summit in Brussels – and say it now can’t be changed. European Council Presid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUFFING:  Stocks post worst Thanksgiving week decline since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/23/stock-markets-dow-set-for-losses-as-trading-resumes-for-half-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Friday as some of the most popular technology shares were under pressure once again, while a steep drop in oil prices also weighed on equities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-owned broadcaster says it faces intimidation from Poland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6aacb5672cf491e8a2deb55b608bc69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A U.S.-owned broadcaster said it was the target of attempted intimidation by Polish authorities, describing how security agents appeared at the home of a cameraman who went undercover to film neo-Nazis and told him he must appear for questioning on suspicion of propagating fascism. TVN, owned by Discovery, broadcast undercover footage in January that showed members of a Polish neo-Nazi group celebrating Adolf Hitler's birthday in a forest in 2017. It said that on Friday evening, agents with Poland's Internal Security Agency visited the home of the cameraman who had gone undercover, Piotr Wacowski, and gave him the summons to appear in the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan rejects legalizing same-sex unions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a34cf44ef92949d8b31d84090f64c6ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Voters in Taiwan passed a referendum asking that marriage be restricted to one man and one woman, a setback to LGBT couples hoping their island will be the first place in Asia to let same-sex couples share child custody and insurance benefits. The vote on Saturday, organized by Christian groups that make up about 5 percent of Taiwan's population and advocates of the traditional Chinese family structure, goes against a May 2017 Constitutional Court ruling. Justices told legislators then to make same-sex marriage legal within two years, a first for Asia where religion and conservative governments normally keep the bans in place.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
