<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Farmers Call for Help With Debt at 1980s Levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/americas-farmers-call-help-debts-climb-1980s-levels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US figure skater accused of deliberately slashing rival at world championships...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/21/us-figure-skater-accused-deliberately-slashing-rival-world-championships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American figure skater has been accused of colliding into a 16-year-old Korean rival in the final warm-up session ahead of the opening of the World Figure Skating Championships in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden advisers debate Stacey Abrams as out-of-the-gate VP choice...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2020-presidential-election-joe-biden-stacey-abrams-vp-54472f8f-5bb2-4d1f-bc7c-0544a09ebba5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They want to show the former V.P. "isn't just another old white guy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New populist star emerges from Dutch local elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/602a05ea46894b2a859fa9c6595a9da7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Netherlands has woken up to a new star of right-wing populism, as the party of a Latin-quoting, philosophy-reading lawmaker surged past anti-Islam firebrand Geert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Military to be deployed for next round of Yellow Vest protests...</title>
      <link>http://en.rfi.fr/france/20190320-military-be-deployed-saturdays-french-yellow-vests-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.rfi.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is to deploy its military anti-terror force as reinforcement during Act 19 of Saturday Yellow Vest protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastest-shrinking cities in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2019/03/21/population-decline-us-cities-losing-most-residents/39199277/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a fifth of all states reported a population decline in the last two years. In many metro areas, it has been a long-term trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in migrants at sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/With-more-focus-on-the-southern-border-US-13705397.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO - The Trump administration's focus on the southern border has closed some gaps in immigration enforcement but expanded a challenging problem, law enforcement officials here said Wednesday: undocumented immigrants sneaking into California by sea.  The migrants enter in various ways, including on personal watercraft and small, open-top motorboats known as pangas that often arrive under cover of darkness, said Jeremy Thompson, Customs and Border Protection's director of marine operations in San Diego.  On Sunday, the 87-foot Coast Guard patrol boat USCGC Petrel stopped a vessel with 12 migrants from Mexico aboard near California's southern maritime border. On Tuesday, a Customs and Border Protection team on a high-speed coastal interceptor vessel stopped another group, disabling a boat with gunfire after it failed to stop, and detaining eight more migrants, Thompson said.  Chief Patrol Agent Rodney Scott, who oversees CBP operations in San Diego, said that he expects smugglers to adjust their tactics as U.S. officials alter theirs, and he believes that the United States is taking away most of the "low-risk ways" to get into the country.  "We've been busy out here," Scott said. "Once the rhetoric started with the wall, it definitely picked up in the maritime."  The intercepts are carried out by both the Coast Guard and CBP, which has an Air and Marine Operations branch. They coordinate plans through a Joint Harbor Operations Center at Coast Guard Air Station San Diego, where personnel scan computer screens that display images from dozens of cameras, watching the coastline for watercraft that look out of place.  Across Southern California, 1,022 migrants were intercepted at sea in the fiscal year ending Sept. 30, Coast Guard officials have said. That was up from 213...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots enable BEES and FISH to talk to each other...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2019-03-robots-enable-bees-fish.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through an imaginative experiment, researchers were able to get two extremely different animal species located far apart to interact with each other and reach a shared decision with the help of robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Millennials care more about date's politics than good sex...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/20/millennials-care-more-about-dates-politics-than-good-sex-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody’s sleeping with the enemy these days. “If I see somebody who’s like, ‘I’m moderate or conservative,’ I keep swiping,” Bronx resident Nadine Anglesey tells The Post. The 33-year-old art…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest Accused Of Groping Woman During Last Rites...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/catholic-priest-accused-groping-texas-woman-last-rites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman reported Rev. Gerold Langsch first anointed her chest with holy water, then began to apply lotion, massaging a breast, pinching a nipple and asking "Does that feel good?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Inside Unlikely Rise...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/longform/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-profile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez represents a vision of the Democratic Party's future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to Impose Sweeping Gun Ban After Mosque Killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-zealand-to-ban-military-style-semiautomatic-weapons-and-assault-rifles-11553134883 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern said she would ban all military-style semiautomatic weapons and assault rifles in the wake of the Christchurch mosque massacre that left 50 people dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Ancient Societies Hit Million People, Vengeful Gods Appeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/65039-punishing-gods-rise-with-complex-societies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belief in a punishing, moralizing god follows the rise of complex societies, new research shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternal shell: Sacred turtle embalmed in Hanoi...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/eternal-shell--sacred-turtle-embalmed-in-hanoi-11366274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sacred giant turtle that died in Hanoi's storied Hoan Kiem lake has been given a new lease on life by city authorities who have embalmed the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Reform Causing Freakouts in Rich New York Area Towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/trump-tax-reform-causing-freakouts-in-rich-new-york-area-towns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Tax Reform Hits Home in Wealthy New York Suburbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canned air and water-spraying drones: Smog remedies...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-03-canned-air-water-spraying-drones-smog.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As millions of people in Asia choke under polluted skies, authorities have turned to water-dispersing drones and outdoor air purifiers to improve air quality, while companies have tried to cash in by selling everything from canned air to lung-purifying teas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary Birth: Twin Inside Twin...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/03/20/news/a-twin-inside-a-twin-in-colombia-an-extraordinary-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON pressuring brands: Lower prices or no advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/20/amazon-aggressively-suspending-ads-of-unprofitable-products-as-focus-on-the-bottom-line-grows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has been more aggressively enforcing its policy of suspending ads if the product being promoted doesn't make money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telecoms start blocking websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-19/after-blocking-zerohedge-and-others-nz-telcos-demand-big-tech-censorship-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts hundreds of drilling projects over 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/mar/20/judge-halts-drilling-climate-change-trump-administration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rebuke of the Trump administration’s ‘energy-first’ agenda, a judge rules greenhouse gas emissions must be considered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Red flag' plan to stop Trump: 1M more Florida voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2019/03/20/gillums-red-flag-plan-to-stop-trump-1m-new-florida-voters-927053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Tallahassee mayor said increased voter registration is crucial to the Democratic Party’s ability to survive and thrive in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT LEVEL OF CENSORSHIP IS HERE: THE BANNING OF URLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/the-final-level-of-censorship-is-here-the-banning-of-urls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Blocking Zero Hedge And Others, NZ Telcos Demand Big-Tech Censorship Surge To</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU hits GOOGLE with $1.7 billion fine for blocking ad rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90322678/google-hit-with-another-eu-antitrust-fine-the-grand-total-now-comes-to-e8-2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EU just gave the search giant another multibillion-euro fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kale now one of  most pesticide-contaminated vegetables...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/20/kale-is-now-one-of-the-most-pesticide-contaminated-vegetables.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kale joins the "Dirty Dozen" list this year. The list of fruits and vegetables with the most pesticide contamination also includes strawberries, spinach, nectarines, apples, grapes, peaches, cherries, pears, tomatoes, celery and potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth forecast cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fed-rate-hikes-none-in-2019-federal-reserve-projects-no-rate-hikes-slower-growth-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central bank stands pat on interest rates and signals there may be no more hikes in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 Migrants Apprehended in Five Minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/03/20/400-migrants-apprehended-within-five-minutes-in-el-paso-sector/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents apprehended two large groups of Central American migrants after they illegally crossed the border from Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carter gets new title: Oldest living former president...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/jimmy-carter-gets-new-title-oldest-living-former-president/68TFzP9SMDjrVuqcUt3PkK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 94 years, 172 days the 39th president passes George H.W. Bush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol says detention centers are full; Starts releasing...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/nation/article_b47a4ead-d1f4-541b-9167-c80121d65c04.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol released 50 recently apprehended migrants here Tuesday, the first of several hundred border-crossers who officials say will soon be freed because there is no room to hold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BATTLES GHOST OF MCCAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9cfac2db09c4aa884e9f17e5fcdf346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Casting aside rare censure from Republican lawmakers, President Donald Trump aimed new blasts of invective at the late John McCain Wednesday, even claiming credit for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Jury Finds ROUNDUP Causes Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-jury-finds-roundup-weed-killer-caused-cancer/story?id=61809259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial's second phase started on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>32 dogs trapped in 'hoarding' house saved from freezing waters... </title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/03/20/dogs-saved-freezing-waters-after-hoarding-house-gets-flooded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flooding hit much of the Midwest this week, particularly in Nebraska and Iowa, and morning temperatures in the area plunged into the low 30s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe Midwest flooding could last all spring...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/03/20/midwest-flooding-nebraska-iowa-missouri-could-last-all-spring/3220970002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flooding willÂ carry onÂ in waves and varying degrees of severity over the central United States, including a large part of the Mississippi River watershed, through the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPT. SULLY: Industry Too Cozy With Regulators...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/capt-sully-sullenberger-where-boeing-and-the-faa-went-wrong-in-this-ugly-saga-2019-03-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘Miracle on the Hudson’ pilot says the Boeing 737 Max controversy is ‘unprecedented’ and an ‘ugly saga.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anaesthetic wipes bad memories, phobias from minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/anaesthetic-drug-wipe-memories-ptsd-phobia-mental-health-a8831761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition detects you -- in places never been...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/with-facial-recognition-shoplifting-may-get-you-banned-in-places-youve-never-been/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are hundreds of stores using facial recognition -- none that have any rules or standards to prevent abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George W. Bush celebrates first hole-in-one...</title>
      <link>https://golfweek.com/2019/03/20/ace-alert-president-george-w-bush-joins-hole-in-one-club-at-trinity-forest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;golfweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President George W. Bush served as leader of the free world from 2001-09, but he didn’t have an ace prior to Wednesday’s round at Trinity Forest Golf Club in Dallas. Bush shared a photo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies Learn to Stop Fearing Trump Tweet Wrath...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/20/us/politics/trump-twitter-businesses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years into President Trump’s term, many businesses appear to be increasingly prioritizing their balance sheets over political backlash caused by his efforts to compel them to build and hire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first nationwide DNA database sparks human right fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/rwanda-dna-database-human-rights-privacy-a8832051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant sunfish washes up on beach; 'Thought was shipwreck'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2019/mar/20/giant-sunfish-washes-up-on-australian-beach-i-thought-it-was-a-shipwreck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rare creature found at the mouth of Murray River in South Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies after intense 5-hour sex session...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/columbian-woman-32-dies-after-14164649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 32-year-old woman, known as 'La Fiera' suffered a cardiac arrest after the marathon romping session</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin youth army to teach million to use machine guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1102985/russia-new-vladimir-putin-youth-army-yunarmia-anna-kuznetsova-viktor-bondarev-olga-vasiliy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of Russian orphans as young as eight are to be drafted into Vladimir Putin’s youth army and taught how to use machine guns and throw hand grenades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: JETBLUE pilots raped airline workers during layover...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/20/jetblue-pilots-drugged-raped-three-female-crew-members-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of JetBlue pilots raped two female airline workers during a layover in Puerto Rico — and left one of the victims with an STD, a new Brooklyn lawsuit charges. The heinous incident occur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu to visit White House as Israeli election nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/trump-to-host-netanyahu-at-white-house-next-week-2-weeks-before-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With PM in Washington to address AIPAC, administration says leaders will discuss 'shared interests and actions in the Middle East'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARCH MADNESS: For 7'6 Star, There's No Ceiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/college-basketball/2019/03/20/tacko-fall-ucf-height-nba-march-madness-ncaa-tournament</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world is about to find out there's much more to Tacko Fall than his height.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$8.5B In Bets? Explosion As Legal Gambling Extends Outside Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jayginsbach/2019/03/19/sports-betting-explodes-during-march-madness-aga-estimates-8-5-billion-bet-on-ncaa-tournament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;March Madness is the biggest betting event in sports along with the Super Bowl. The American Gaming Association expects American's will wager near $8.5 Billion on the NCAA Tournament - through brackets, bookies, sportsbooks and online - as legal sports betting continues to grow across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Michigan ice shards pile mesmerizes...</title>
      <link>https://expo.mlive.com/life-and-culture/g66l-2019/03/0fcc2e84077663/gorgeous-ice-shards-are-piling-up-along-lake-michigan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;expo.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is what the ice shards look like in South Haven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first VR gym opening...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/technology/article/worlds-first-virtual-reality-gym-vr-black-box-13701230.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like electric scooters and vapes, virtual reality is a technological innovation that is incredibly easy to make fun of.  I associate VR - an interactive experience that transports the user to an artificial world - with gamers, the porn industry and people who ride Boost Boards in the bike lane. This is why, when I noticed Black Box VR pop up on Market Street, across from the headquarters of Twitter and Uber, it felt like the punchline to a joke only a San Franciscan could make.  Black Box is the world's first VR gym. Founded in 2016 by Ryan DeLuca and Preston Lewis, the company plans to transform - ok, "disrupt" - the boutique fitness industry by fusing two things Americans love: trendy fitness and video games. I don't like either of these things, so I decided to try it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI joining criminal investigation into BOEING... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/fbi-joining-criminal-investigation-into-certification-of-boeing-737-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal grand jury investigation, based in Washington, D.C., is looking into the certification process that approved the safety of the new Boeing plane, two of which have crashed since October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to strengthen ties with nations tired of U.S. 'bullying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-politics-new-year/irans-zarif-will-strengthen-ties-with-nations-tired-of-u-s-bullying-idUSKCN1R12IC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will expand its ties with nations equally tired of "bullying" by ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy Ready to 'Burn Boats' with Laser on Destroyer...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2019/03/20/navy-ready-burn-boats-2021-laser-installation-destroyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON, D.C. — In the next two years, the Navy wants to deploy a laser aboard a guided-missile destroyer as the service learns to integrate directed energy weapon systems on warships, the Navy’s director of surface warfare said on Wednesday. “We are going to burn the boats if you will and move forward with this …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal bites off ICE agent's finger...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/20/illegal-immigrant-bites-ice-agent-finger-sanctuary-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photo is gruesome</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous figures seek secrecy in Epstein suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/20/jeffrey-epstein-related-lawsuit-1229908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The duo said they could face embarrassment if the court makes public records from the suit, which accused a longtime Epstein friend of engaging in sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins poisoned by algae have Alzheimer's-like brain disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article228126094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne Sides With President... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/kellyanne-conway-defends-trump-amid-feud-with-her-husband-you-think-he-should-just-take-that-sitting-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUMORS SWEEP DC</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/370551cfc5334f3ba617c7e2bf77261a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her family wanted a puppy, so Alicia Barnett dreamed they would find one that was smart, steady and a bit mysterious. She hoped their new addition could share a personality — and a name — with the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police chase ends in suspect breakdancing...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/video-suspect-breakdances-at-end-of-chp-chase/5207236/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A slow-speed chase through the San Fernando Valley ended with the suspect breakdancing as officers held him at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Kraft Rejects Plea Deal; Moves To Suppress Video...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/robert-kraft-video-jupiter-florida-prostitution-case-rejects-plea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots owner Robert Kraft rejected a plea offer that would have allowed him to avoid prostitution charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Essay 'Editors' Reveal How Rich Kids Cheat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/another-college-cheating-scandal-how-personal-essay-editors-game-the-system-for-rich-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I’ve edited anywhere from 200 to 225 essays,’ one tutor confesses. ‘I would say about 50 percent were entirely rewritten.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood power elite hosting Kamala fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/entertainment/article228178259.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Goes Up, Up, Up....</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/20/oil-market-us-china-trade-talks-supply-cuts-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. crude inventories fall by 9.6 million barrels, compared with analysts' expectations for an increase of 309,000 barrels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big rig hauling 5,500 gallons of printer ink overturns...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/traffic/breaking-massive-printer-ink-spill-shuts-down-285-south/5ArFTMKMGPhn1djKyiZl1H/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tractor-trailer hauling 5,500 gallons of printer ink overturned Wednesday on the Westside Perimet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver abducts schoolchildren, sets bus ablaze...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-driver-bus-full-children-sets-fire-124524295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A bus driver in northern Italy abducted 51 children and their chaperones Wednesday, ordering the children's hands to be bound and threatening them with death during the drive, before setting the vehicle on fire when he was stopped by a Carabinieri blockade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Investigative FOIA Requests Jump 669% Since Obama Left...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/media-foia-requests-to-epa-spiked-after-trump-election-data-reveal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Freedom of Information Act requests the Environmental Protection Agency received from mainstream outlets such as the New York Times and Washington Post spiked immediately after Republican President Donald Trump took office, according to a Free Beacon analysis of FOIA requests by the media from 2013 to the present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels turn social media into tools for extortion, threats and violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/2019/02/27/mexican-drug-cartels-use-social-media-for-extortion-threats-violence-facebook-whatsapp-youtube/2280756002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fringe Dems To Make Debate Stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/unlikely-democrats-find-new-formula-for-making-the-2020-debate-stage-memes-pleas-and-charities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates are finding that the donor threshold for qualifying is easier to meet than initially expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions watched her kids on YOUTUBE. Off-screen, she was beating and starving them, police say... </title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/star-fantastic-adventures-youtube-kids-allegedly-abused-and-forced-to-perform-for-millions-of-fans-by-mom-machelle-hackney</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘perfect family’ site had 700,800 followers. But if the adopted kids didn’t perform, they told police they were tortured by their ‘momager.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbug cases linked to weight-loss surgeries in Tijuana prompt fresh warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/health/sd-no-pseudomonas-update-20190319-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC officials said 25 cases have been detected among U.S. citizens who crossed the border into Mexico, with most patients having had the surgery performed by the same physician at Grand View Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More than one reality exists...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/65029-dueling-reality-photons.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New experiments addressed a decades-old theoretical question in physics, demonstrating that two realities can exist at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER testing more extreme 'shadowban' technique...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/03/19/journalist-accuses-twitter-of-testing-more-extreme-shadowban-technique-on-his-account/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter admitted on Monday to "removing" a post from Federalist co-founder Sean Davis, but the journalist claims the platform actually shadowbanned, or hidden from other users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China clones 'Sherlock Holmes' police dog to cut training times...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-clones-sherlock-holmes-police-dog-cut-training-024526821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in southwest China's Yunnan province have cloned what they called the "Sherlock Holmes of police dogs" in a program they hope will help cut training times and costs for police dogs, state media reported on Wednesday. The dog, named Kunxun, was cloned from a police sniffer dog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wants Penalties For 'Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/19/andrew-yang-misinformation/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We must introduce both a means to investigate and punish'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with fatal stabbing thought victim was werewolf...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/man-charged-with-fatal-stabbing-in-alexandria-thought-victim-was-a-werewolf-attorneys-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense attorneys say a man accused of brutally stabbing a man to death in Alexandria last July&amp;nbsp;did so because he thought the victim was a werewolf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Sanders Tied with Biden; Beto Gets Post-Announcement Bump...</title>
      <link>http://emersonpolling.com/2019/03/19/national-poll-sanders-tied-with-biden-beto-gets-post-announcement-bump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;emersonpolling.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE:  SKYNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lrX6ktLg8WQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch Sky News live. Our top stories are: Instagram is failing to remove graphic self-harm images and videos, Theresa May will write to Brussels to ask for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD sued over allegedly profiting from photos of slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/03/20/harvard-university-sued-descendants-slaves-over-photos-renty/3213537002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A direct descendant of a slave featured in photos owned by Harvard is seeking an unspecified amount of damages from the university. She's also demanding Harvard give her family the images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang secretly filmed 1,600 hotel guests with spy cameras and live-streamed footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8680942/gang-secretly-filmed-1600-hotel-guests-in-their-rooms-with-hidden-cameras-and-live-streamed-footage-to-online-pervs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERVERTS have secretly filmed about 1,600 guests in hotel rooms throughout South Korea – and charged voyeurs to view the illicit content while it’s live-streamed online. The covert filming was carr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach holds emergency spring break meeting: 'We need to make lot less fun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article228090319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88-year-old enters race!</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/mike-gravel-2020-rock/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Income Can Curb the Racism...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/03/andrew-yang-universal-income-white-nationalist-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I do think economic insecurity can fuel a mindset of scarcity,” Yang told Observer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW THE LAYOFFS?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/disney-bob-iger-memo-a-historic-day-for-our-company-fox-deal-close-1202578863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortly after the Disney’s $71.3 billion acquisition of Fox assets officially closed at 12:02 AM ET Tuesday, the deal’s architect, Disney CEO Bob Iger, sent an internal memo to the incu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Scf8nIJCvs4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DiCaprio. Pitt. Robbie. Experience a version of 1969 that could only happen #OnceUponATimeInHollywood - the 9th film by Quentin Tarantino. https://www.OnceUp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super-smeller' develops swab test for Parkinson's...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/mar/20/super-smeller-helps-develop-swab-test-for-parkinsons-disease </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Distinctive musky odour of people with Parkinson’s could lead to earlier diagnosis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making jokes at university gets you reported to bias response team...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/making-jokes-at-portland-state-gets-you-reported-to-its-bias-response-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jokes about schizophrenia, Native Americans land lecturers, students in campus database</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE: 'YOU. ARE. NUTS.'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-blasts-george-conway-husband-top-white-house-aide-kellyanne-n984771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spouse of Kellyanne Conway, a top adviser to the president, is the focus of a two-day attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY-FOX deal complete: Iger big swing could change media industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-disney-fox-iger-20190319-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney Co. officially acquires the 21st Century Fox assets, including the legendary movie and television studio, cable channels including FX and National Geographic,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority Think Jordan 'GOAT' -- Not LeBron...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/sports/2019/03/survey-shows-majority-of-americans-think-jordan-is-the-goat-not-lebron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Business Insider' teamed up with SurveyMonkey Audience to answer the question, "Who is the greatest basketball player of all time?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Goes to '60s in 'ONCE UPON A TIME IN HOLLYOOD'...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/once-upon-time-hollywood-trailer-poster-tarantino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out the preview now!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
