<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Candidate TV ad: I'll vote against Pelosi!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/democratic-house-candidate-kathy-manning-airs-tv-ad-saying-she-wont-back-pelosi-for-speaker/2018/08/14/ed829a20-a004-11e8-93e3-24d1703d2a7a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year of Republican attack ads against Pelosi, the N.C. lawyer became the latest candidate to announce that she will not support Democrats’ longtime House leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directors tell Musk to stop tweeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/business/dealbook/tesla-board-musk-tweets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla’s board of directors has hired multiple outside law firms, and a number of board members and Tesla employees have urged Mr. Musk to stop posting on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Kobach wins gov nomination after rival concedes...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/politics-government/article216702595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kansas Secretary of State Kris Kobach will advance to face Democrat Laura Kelly and independent candidate Greg Orman in the general election for Kansas governor in November. Gov. Jeff Colyer conceded Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on TESLA; Hit with another fraud suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/tesla-hit-with-new-lawsuit-alleging-elon-musk-manipulated-stock-price-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla is facing another class-action lawsuit accusing CEO Elon Musk of manipulating the company's stock price. A complaint filed on Monday alleges that some investors purchased Tesla stock "at artificially inflated prices and suffered significant losses and damages."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep space gamma ray bursts have mysterious time-reversing effect...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6060269/Gamma-ray-bursts-deep-space-mysterious-time-reversing-effect.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research headed up by the College of Charleston in South Carolina has studied mysterious bursts of high-energy that appear to defy time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEARL JAM Poster Praises Dem, Depicts Dead Trump...</title>
      <link>http://newstalkkgvo.com/missoula-pearl-jam-poster-praises-jon-tester-features-dead-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newstalkkgvo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A poster promoting the band Pearl Jam's August 13 concert in Missoula is being described as reprehensible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President, McConnell Reshape Courts With Little Fanfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/with-little-fanfare-trump-and-mcconnell-reshape-the-nations-circuit-courts/2018/08/14/10610028-9fcd-11e8-93e3-24d1703d2a7a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican-led Senate has installed 24 appellate court judges since January 2017 and is poised to confirm two more this week, a record for a president’s first two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ Newspapers Plan 'Coordinated' Editorials -- But Will They Listen?</title>
      <link>https://www.poynter.org/news/200-newspapers-will-write-pro-journalism-editorials-will-they-also-listen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poynter.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asexual' Hot Identity in Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/california/2018/08/14/asexual-is-new-sexual-identity-in-bay-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new sexual identity has surfaced in the Bay Area, known as "asexual," among those who do not have sexual attraction to other people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town mulls 'eau de lion poo' to scare invading deer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dutch-mull-eau-lion-dung-scare-off-pesky-173044546.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch seaside town overrun by fallow deer is mulling plans to diffuse the smell of lion manure to keep them at bay and stop them invading streets and parks. Situated in the North Sea dunes just west of Amsterdam, Zandvoort has over the past decade been invaded by thousands of the boisterous bucks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver tests positive -- for every possible drug in test by cops...</title>
      <link>http://www.euronews.com/2018/08/14/spanish-driver-tests-positive-on-all-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police stopped a car in northeastern Spain after its driver proved positive for all drugs in the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tears down Jesus posters, replaces with Xi images...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7015374/china-rips-down-jesus-posters-replaced-president-xi-jinping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has taken extreme measures to wipe out all traces of Christianity in the country, by tearing down posters of Jesus and replacing them with images of President Xi Jinping. The country’s ruling…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor describes plunging 160 FEET...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7016476/genoa-bridge-collapse-italy-footballer-survivor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Italian footballer has revealed how he fell 160 feet when he was driving over the doomed bridge in Genoa which collapsed today killing at least 35. The Ponte Morandi road on the A10 motorway in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST BLACK SPEAKER? CLYBURN CHAMPIONS 'TRANSFORMING' PARTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article216593000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If he became speaker of the House, U.S. Rep. Jim Clyburn of South Carolina says he would be a “transitional” leader who would “transform” Democrats. A movement is growing for Clyburn to run for the job if Democrats win the majority in the U.S. House and Nancy Pelosi steps aside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles first in US to install subway body scanners...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/la-become-first-us-install-161917486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles' subway will become the first mass transit system in the U.S. to install body scanners that screen passengers for weapons and explosives, officials said Tuesday. The deployment of the portable scanners, which project waves to do full-body screenings of passengers walking through a station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez claims have fact-checkers working overtime...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/14/ocasio-cortez-claims-have-fact-checkers-working-overtime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York congressional candidate Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has excited the liberal base with her media blitz touting Medicare-for-all, the elimination of ICE and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-day weeks in full effect for Colorado school district...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/education/four-day-school-weeks-in-full-effect-for-school-district-27j/73-583765384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elementary schoolers and kindergartners had one more day of summer break due to the district's new four-day week schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret conditions, no tunnel for El Chapo trial...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/el-chapo-wont-be-tunneling-to-court-during-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman will stand trial in Brooklyn, a judge ruled Tuesday. Defense attorneys for the drug kingpin had tried to convince Brooklyn federal Judge Brian Cogan that he sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Madam: 'Leading questions' made me feel sick...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/kristin-davis-talks-about-russia-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman known as the &amp;quot;Manhattan Madam&amp;quot; for once running a high-end prostitution ring in New York City says she was bullied by Robert Mueller&amp;#39;s team when she was forced to testify in front of a grand jury in connection with the Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  NEW YORK Magazine Owner Explores Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-magazine-owner-explores-possible-sale-1534264090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publisher of New York magazine, Vulture and The Cut is reviewing strategic options including a possible sale, the latest media outlet to consider consolidation in a tough marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile asks Vatican for information on cases...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180814200458-kr4kc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILE-ABUSE/VATICAN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Chile asks Vatican for information on sex abuse cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says Turkey will boycott US electronics...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180814101313-nzpia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-CURRENCY/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Erdogan says Turkey will boycott US electronics, lira steadies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA chief: Domestic surveillance program 'makes awful lot of sense'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tsa-administrator-david-pekoske-says-quiet-skies-domestic-surveillance-program-makes-an-awful-lot-of-sense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Quiet Skies" program has been criticized for tracking American citizens not suspected of any crimes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1,000 victims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/301822e3d7a04b0b88a1c40738c4a513/Report-identifies-more-than-1,000-victims-of-priest-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — More than 1,000 children — and possibly many more — were molested by hundreds of Roman Catholic priests in six Pennsylvania dioceses, while seni</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS SITE HIT WITH ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.newswars.com/infowars-com-site-goes-down-amid-big-tech-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comes as social media giants try to silence political speech ahead of midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER founders sue for billions claiming company 'robbed' them of stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/barry-dillers-iac-sued-by-tinder-founders-2-billion-1134767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CEO Sean Rad alleges that Tinder's parent companies intentionally undervalued the popular dating app to deny early employees billions in stock options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulated financial information...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/tinder-founders-sue-iac-claiming-company-robbed-them-of-stock-options.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plaintiffs in the case filed in New York State Supreme Court in Manhattan include Tinder's founders Sean Rad, Justin Mateen and Jonathan Badeen, as well as three current senior executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK REVIEW: 'A new peak in disgrace'...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/books/2018/08/14/omarosa-memoir-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the 'Fire and Fury' sequel you never wanted: the 2018 tell-all in its purest, saddest form</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranians Impersonating Americans On TWITTER...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/13/iranians-fake-american-twitter/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'But after all we are not American'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK threatens media:  'Work with us or die'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7014408/facebook-threatens-press-saying-work-with-us-or-end-up-in-a-hospice/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK has been accused of threatening media firms into working with them by saying their businesses would end up “in a hospice” if they didn’t. Campbell Brown, Facebook’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's laser cannon;  Kremlin's plans to 'wipe out satellites'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1003268/russia-news-military-laser-cannon-vladimir-putin-us-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US has branded Russia’s plans to build a laser cannon capable of wiping out international satellites as EVIL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER Founders Seek Billions Against Parent Company, Allege Sex Harassment Cover-Up...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/breaking-tinder-founders-seek-billions-against-parent-company-allege-sexual-harassment-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Palestinian Congressional Candidate Gets Physical With Jewish Journalist at Political Event...</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/palestinian-congressional-candidate-assaults-jewish-journalist-at-political-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She claims Trump knew in advance that WIKILEAKS was publishing Hillary emails...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6060473/Omarosa-claims-Trump-knew-advance-Wikileaks-publishing-Hillary-Clintons-emails.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omarosa Manigault Newman claimed in a new interview that President Trump 'absolutely' knew about hacked Hillary Clinton emails in advance of publication in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodeo bull escapes stockyards, runs loose in Oklahoma City...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rodeo-bull-escapes-stockyards-runs-loose-oklahoma-city-185148310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A rodeo bull broke free from the Oklahoma City Stockyards late Monday, charging through city streets and chasing people, including one person who jumped into a river to escape the animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian cops drop 'masculinity' requirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazilian-cops-drop-masculinity-requirement-175952287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sao Paulo (AFP) - Police candidates in southern Brazil are now free to get in touch with their softer side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7011626/genoa-bridge-collapse-italy-motorway-morandi-latest-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT LEAST 35 people – including a baby – died today after a major tourist motorway bridge collapsed during a “violent” lightning storm in Italy. Firefighters say cars and tru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Now Spying on American Soil...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chinese-police-are-spying-on-uighurson-american-soil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is compiling a global registry of its ethnic minorities who have fled persecution, threatening to detain the families of those who don’t comply. The message: Nowhere is safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  'Mega-Round' Investors Shower Start-Ups With Millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/technology/venture-capital-mega-round.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start-ups raising $100 million or more from investors used to be a rarity. Now, this scale of fund raising is commonplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unlikely Activists Who Took On Silicon Valley -- and Won...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/magazine/facebook-google-privacy-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook and Google made billions mining personal data, and fought off anyone who threatened to stop them. Then came a challenge in their own backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300+ 'Predator Priests' Named In PA Grand Jury Report...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/pennsylvania-diocese-sex-abuse-grand-jury-report-released/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-awaited state grand jury report into sexual abuse in six Pennsylvania dioceses, including Pittsburgh and Greensburg, has finally been released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Injuries Reported Following Studio City Explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/LAFD-Responding-to-Studio-City-Explosion-490836201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Fire Department responded Tuesday morning to a reported explosion in a Studio City neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radioactive sheep shed light on secret nuke test...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/radioactive-sheep-shed-light-on-secret-nuclear-weapons-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly discovered data from radioactive sheep provides strong evidence that a mysterious “double flash” detected almost 39 years ago near a remote island group was a nuclear explosion. Ever since th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Hops Fence at LA Zoo, Spanks Hippo...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/08/13/hippo-spanking-video-los-angeles-zoo-lapd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He might have done it for the 'Gram, but now a man who crossed a barricade guarding a hippopotamus enclosure at the Los Angeles Zoo is looking at potential trespassing charges after he was filmed spanking one of the animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100K Cello Found in LA Bush...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/california/100K-Cello-Found-in-Bush-Downtown-490763911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $100,000 cello was found in a bush downtown after it was reported stolen for a few days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein now accused of sex trafficking......</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/14/harvey-weinstein-accused-of-being-a-sex-trafficker-in-new-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit was filed by aspiring British actress Kadian Noble claiming that the “Shakespeare In Love” producer violated federal laws against sex trafficking when he lured her to his Ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of child who died in 'exorcism' expected resurrection...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6057933/Family-child-died-ritualistic-exorcism-expected-resurrected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little boy's father Siraj Ibn Wahhaj, along with one of his wives Jany Leveille, two sisters and a brother-in-law are accused of training children at the camp to use firearms 'to commit school shootings.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Silent...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/14/dnc-keith-ellison-domestic-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total silence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS:  Sleep deprivation fuels loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/14/sleep-deprivation-fuels-loneliness-tired-people-socially-repellent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sleep deprivation is fuelling the loneliness epidemic because overly-tired people are less sociable, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT WON'T MOUNT DEFENSE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/manafort-attorneys-opt-skip-defense-proceed-closing-arguments/story?id=57168855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for Paul Manafort, the former Trump campaign chairman who is on trial for financial crimes, will not present a defense of their client, ABC News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting too little sleep may 'age' heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/getting-too-little-sleep-may-age-heart-154503547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Prolonged periods of insufficient sleep have negative effects on multiple body systems including the cardiovascular system," lead study author Quanhe Yang told Reuters Health in an email. "Studies have shown significant relationships between sleep duration and heart disease risk factors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Humans less likely to turn off robot when it begs to stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/nation-now/2018/08/14/when-robot-begs-mercy-humans-more-likely-listen-study/984952002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans were less likely to turn off a robot when it begged them to stop an experiment, according to a study from researchers in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade War Rattling China Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/world/asia/china-trade-war-trump-xi-jinping-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While President Xi Jinping remains firmly in charge, friction with the Trump administration and troubles at home have dented his political dominance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Ticks Up Amid Supply Risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-ticks-up-amid-supply-risks-1534245421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices rose as expectations of weaker Iranian output offset signs of rising global supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside ROLLS-ROYCE $325,000 SUV...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/13/photos-cullinan-is-rolls-royces-first-suv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The front seat has a center console that doubles as a bar, complete with glassware and a small refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First MUSTANG owner kept car. Now worth $350,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/money/cars/ford/2018/08/14/first-ford-mustang-worth/956784002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third-grade teacher who was the first person to buy a Ford Mustang has brought it to the Dream Cruise in suburban Detroit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/30-dead-genoa-bridge-collapse-deputy-pm-143548232--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (Reuters) - About 30 people were killed on Tuesday by the collapse of a motorway bridge in the Italian port city of Genoa, AGI news agency reported, quoting Italy's Deputy Prime Minister Matteo Salvini. "Around 30 people are dead and many others are seriously injured," Salvini told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRAZY RICH ASIANS' Poised to Beat Mark Wahlberg at Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-crazy-rich-asians-preps-26m-debut-1134632 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon M. Chu's rom-com — the first Hollywood studio movie to feature an all-Westernized Asian cast in 25 years — is opening midweek.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison Accuser Refuses To Release Video As Another Allegation Emerges...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/archives/2018/08/14/ellison-accuser-refuses-release-video-another-allegation-emerges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Explosive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 50%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_aug14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGLY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e90365d3ea744dd790bfd874b65a5fc4/Trump-lashes-out-at-Omarosa,-calls-her-'that-dog'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump escalated his messy clash with former aide Omarosa Manigault Newman on Tuesday, referring to the longtime colleague, who had been the top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars plunge as highway bridge collapses in Italy; Dozens feared dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/011a01863fcd4ba194e7871d1c536a03/Cars-plunge-as-highway-bridge-collapses-in-Italy;-11-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A bridge on a main highway linking Italy with France collapsed Tuesday in the Italian port city of Genoa during a sudden, violent storm, sending vehicles plunging 90</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery craft filmed over NCarolina lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article216602815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video gaining traction on YouTube suggests a “huge UFO” was recently spotted over Lake Norman north of Charlotte. The footage was recorded May 29 but has recently gained attention on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW DRAMA...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6059211/He-said-Hes-embarrassed-Audio-Trump-spokeswoman-saying-thought-n-word-tape-exists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recording doesn't establish that an 'n-word' tape exists. It does show Trump spokeswoman Katrina Pierson telling colleagues she thinks it's true and musing about how to 'spin it.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AND MORE OMAROSA TAPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-audio-omarosa-trump-campaign-aides-apparently-discussing-fallout-of-n-word/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House aide Omarosa claims to have heard tape of President Trump using the N-word during his time on "The Apprentice"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian town rocked by 800 quakes daily...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/14/kilauea-volcano-hawaii-earthquakes-tourism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents say constant tremors from the nearby Kilauea eruption have turned the village of Volcano into a ‘ghost town’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Toxic 'red tide' killing Florida wildlife, menacing tourism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/13/florida-gulf-coast-red-tide-toxic-algae-bloom-killing-florida-wildlife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year 267 tons of marine life, including thousands of small fish and 72 Goliath groupers, have washed up along 150 miles of the Gulf Coast from the unrelenting bloom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dozens dead' after motorway bridge collapses during violent storm in Italy...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/14/huge-motorway-bridge-collapses-onto-houses-italy-trapping-people-7837360/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images show the bridge - which sits above an industrial site - with a large centre piece missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK NOW DELETING ALTERNATIVE LEFT-WING MEDIA PAGES TOO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/the-purge-facebook-now-deleting-alternative-left-wing-media-pages-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NATO-backed @DFRLab is currently assisting FB's purge. This is deeply disturbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THAT DOG'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/president-trump-calls-omarosa-dog-lowlife/story?id=57164350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump fired off a nasty tweet at his former aide Omarosa Maigault Newman Tuesday, calling her a "lowlife" and a "dog." "When you give a crazed, crying lowlife a break, and give her a job at the White House, I guess it just didn’t work out. Good work by General Kelly for quickly firing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satanist' burns down historic 250-year-old wooden church...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/satanist-teenager-burns-down-historic-13079705 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schoolboy Ignat Sharapov, 15, has been arrested as experts say it will cost more than £1million to repair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years after UFO encounter, man breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/magnolia/2018/08/13/alien-abduction-45-years-after-ufo-encounter-mississippi-man-breaks-his-silence/922706002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moss Point man hopes to set record straight on his alien abduction experience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THAT 'DOG'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/1029329583672307712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“When you give a crazed, crying lowlife a break, and give her a job at the White House, I guess it just didn’t work out. Good work by General Kelly for quickly firing that dog!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The media's blatant hypocrisy -- even about media-bashing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/the-blatant-media-hypocrisy-even-about-media-bashing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the age of self-congratulatory media. “Democracy dies in darkness” goes the ridiculous tagline on The Washington Post’s front page. Reporters openly call themselves heroes and firefighte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal shelter accused of freezing cats to euthanize them...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2018/08/14/southern-indiana-animal-shelter-accused-of-freezing-cats-to-euthanize-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPENCER COUNTY, Ind. – A southern Indiana animal shelter is under investigation after an employee said she was told to freeze cats alive to euthanize them.  Bridget Woodson, a former employee at the Spencer County Animal Shelter, said her boss instructed her twice to put cats in a freezer, reports WEVV. Woodson said she took the animals to a veterinarian to be humanely euthanized instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To fend off NETFLIX, theaters try 3-screen immersion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fend-off-netflix-movie-theaters-094828458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Sit at the back of the movie theater, and it's possible to see the appeal of ScreenX, the latest attempt to drag film lovers off the sofa and away from Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott iPhones!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-calls-boycott-iphones-targets-103554633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey’s president escalated tensions with the US on Tuesday after calling for a boycott of American electronics, amid reports that diplomatic talks have stalled over the issue of a detained US pastor. Showing no signs of backing down in a standoff with President Donald Trump, Recep Tayyip Erdogan suggested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What the hell are you doing?'</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180814/what-the-hell-are-you-doing-swedish-politicians-react-to-car-burnings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish politicians were quick to react after a spate of car fires in the greater Gothenburg region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy theories more rampant than ever?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/14/conspiracy-theories-misconceptions-rampant-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans’ beliefs about politics are as inaccurate and bizarre as ever. Is there a way to fix that?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts see hope after fresh spate of Latin American corruption scandals...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180814-experts-see-hope-after-fresh-spate-latin-american-corruption-scandals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From laboratory in far west, China's surveillance state spreads quietly...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-monitoring-insight/from-laboratory-in-far-west-chinas-surveillance-state-spreads-quietly-idUSKBN1KZ0R3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filip Liu, a 31-year-old software developer from Beijing, was traveling in the far western Chinese region of Xinjiang when he was pulled to one side by police as he got off a bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vienna dethrones Melbourne as world's most liveable city...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/vienna-tops-melbourne-as-worlds-most-liveable-city-economist-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vienna has dislodged Melbourne for the first time at the top of the Economist Intelligence Unit's Global Liveability Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture army base...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/taliban-capture-northern-afghan-base--kill-at-least-14-soldiers-10616380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAZAR-I-SHARIF, Afghanistan:  Taliban fighters overran a northern Afghan army base, officials said on Tuesday (Aug 14), killing at least 14 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-dressed plane passenger tied up after going berserk on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/plane-passenger-left-just-bra-13079273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane crew tied her legs together and her hands behind her back, before sitting her on the floor of the plane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blue wave' to be tested in key Midwestern primaries...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/midwest/ct-midwestern-primaries-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are fighting to beat back Republican gains across the Midwest as the 2018 primary season roars through Wisconsin and Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Cryptocurrency Market Plumbs New Depths...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cryptocurrency-market-plumbs-new-depths-in-2018-1534241274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broad selloff in digital currencies has pushed the value of the entire market below $200 billion for the first time this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In speech that Beijing tried to stop, Hong Kong independence advocate lashes out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/pro-independence-hong-kong-politician-andy-chan-discusses-china-atfcc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A politician who advocates independence for Hong Kong lashed out at China in a speech to foreign journalists that the central and local governments wanted stopped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOME DEPOT Crushes Earnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/home-depot-earnings-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Depot reaped the benefits of a warmer start to the summer, following a rocky spring season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada rematch pits rural voters against booming Las Vegas...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/401644-nevada-rematch-pits-rural-voters-against-a-booming-las-vegas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside a bustling mall on a recent Saturday, volunteers working for the Nevada Democratic Party pester attendees at a job fair hosted by the Latin Chamber of Commerce to register to vote. Steven Horsford is working the crowd, smiling and laughing with the volunteers he recognizes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Burning: Migrant Gangs Unleash Coordinated Fire-Bomb Rampage Across Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-13/sweden-burning-migrant-gangs-unleash-coordinated-fire-bomb-rampage-across-multiple</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror probe after driver ploughs into pedestrians outside UK Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7009654/parliament-westminster-crash-incident-latest-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVERAL pedestrians and cyclists have been injured this morning after a car “driving at 50mph” ploughed into barriers outside the Houses of Parliament. A man, in his 20s, has been arres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than munchies: Eating pot 'elevated' dining...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/aug/13/more-than-munchies-how-eating-pot-went-from-crude-to-elevated-dining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannabis is becoming a cooking ingredient in its own right, as chefs create elaborate cannabis tasting menus at private dinners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of global crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/aug/13/turkish-lira-record-low-ripples-through-global-currency-markets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peso and rand become knock-on casualties of Turkey’s currency slide after lira falls 8% against the dollar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Struck by Car After Beating Man to Death on Highway in Road Rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/crime/article216610405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two men killed Sunday after a road rage car crash on Interstate 5 in Natomas have been identified by the Sacramento County Coroner’s Office. Witnesses saw an Oroville man chase another man with a bat, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 dogs, cats saved by police in daring wildfire rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.mynbc5.com/article/caught-on-video-60-dogs-cats-saved-by-police-in-daring-wildfire-rescue/22716685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mynbc5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saved! 60 dogs, cats rescued as California wildfire threatened an animal shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan refugees find safe haven in Scotland, along with gray weather, weird food...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article215843715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tie to the oil industry was the seed for a small but growing outpost of Venezuelans who are settling in Scotland after fleeing chaos and crime back home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than Half Foreign Refugees on Food Stamps...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/13/more-than-half-of-foreign-refugees-are-on-taxpayer-funded-food-stamps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of the annual inflow of foreign refugees arriving in the U.S. are on food stamps, analysis of a government report reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry passengers punch conductor...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/furious-straphanger-beats-up-subway-conductor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A viral video shows a subway conductor getting pummeled by an angry man and woman at a Brooklyn station this weekend. Jacob Credell was working on a southbound A train just before 5 a.m. on Saturda…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Loses Mars Rover in Dust Storm...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/13/nasa-opportunity-rover-still-lost-mars-dust-storm-engulfed-red-planet-begins-settle-7831488/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plucky exploration 'droid was battered in a super-powerful maelstrom and is now feared to be lying dead on the surface of the Red Planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of California detainees are Indians crossing through Mexico... </title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-indian-immigrants-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian nationals make up about 40% of those held at ICE's detention facility in the Imperial Valley, officials say, and of 680 migrants detained at a federal prison in Victorville, 380 are Indian. Asylum seekers say they're fleeing an increase in persecution under a Hindu nationalist government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Brightest ever' Perseids meteor shower stuns stargazers...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6054643/Brightest-Perseids-Meteor-Shower-revealed-stunning-new-photos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stargazers around the world will be able to see the Perseids for the last time tonight. The annual event will be visible in Central America, Asia, much of Africa, and parts of South America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD TUES:  Trump aggressive use of nondisclosure agreements, even in govt... </title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-nondisclosure-agreements-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's bitter fight with a former top White House aide has highlighted his aggressive and unconventional use of nondisclosure agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Island with Flourishing 'Third Gender'...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/travel/story/20180813-guna-yala-the-islands-where-women-make-the-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the small indigenous territory of Guna Yala off Panama’s eastern coast, a flourishing ‘third gender’ community is defying stereotypes – and venerating women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neglected Horse Suing!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-horse-was-neglected-by-its-owner-Now-the-horse-13153158.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESTACADA, Ore. - Justice is an 8-year-old American quarter horse who used to be named Shadow. And when he was named Shadow, he suffered. At a veterinarian's exam last year, he was 300 pounds underweight, his black coat lice-ridden, his skin scabbed and his genitals so frostbitten that they might still require amputation. The horse had been left outside and underfed by his previous owner, who last summer pleaded guilty to criminal neglect. And now Justice, who today resides with other rescued equines on a quiet wooded farm within view of Oregon's Cascade mountains, is suing his former owner for negligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging process REVERSED in human cells for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1002867/science-news-Ageing-process-REVERSED-human-cells-University-of-Exeter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have successfully reversed the process of ageing in cells for the first time in a move which could help beat the likes of Alzheimer’s and dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significant rise in mosquito 'disease danger days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/significant-rise-in-mosquito-disease-danger-days-in-u-s-report-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many cities in the U.S. are facing an increasing number of days indicating a heightened risk for disease transmission, according to new research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Wild Subway Attacks Stun NYC...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/13/a-train-subway-attack-new-york-city-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It happened shortly after 4:30 a.m. Saturday at the Grant Avenue station in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONGEST WAR:  Taliban blindsides U.S. forces with surprise Afghan offensive...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/13/taliban-surprise-offensive-afghanistan-catches-us-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban is on the verge of dramatically expanding its control over southern and eastern Afghanistan in a surprise offensive that has caught Afghan and American forces off guard and thrown a vexing new wrench into the Trump administration’s strategy for ending the nearly 17-year-old war there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-olds hack mock version of Florida's election site in minutes...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-reg-kid-election-hack-20180813-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They haven’t even made it to high school yet, but they managed to hack into a mock version of Florida’s election website and change the results in a matter of minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry passengers punch train conductor...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-conductor-assaulted-by-angry-passengers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is looking for a man and woman who assaulted a subway conductor in the face after getting angry with him for announcing the train was going express.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW A TARGET?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/401637-signs-grow-that-mueller-is-zeroing-in-on-roger-stone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller appears to be narrowing his focus on Roger Stone in his investigation into Russian interference in the election, prompting widespread speculation that the longtime adviser to President Trump is likely a target in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Woos Partners for China Expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-woos-partners-for-potential-china-expansion-1534071600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Google’s search engine remains blocked in China, the company is courting allies there by providing tools and support to a growing number of app developers, manufacturers and advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-girlfriend speaks out...</title>
      <link>https://thinkprogress.org/keith-ellison-ex-girlfriend-karen-monahan-speaks-out-b4e8c3bf7095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thinkprogress.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I know who I am. I know what I was going to go through."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
GOOGLE tracks movements, like it or not...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/828aefab64d4411bac257a07c1af0ecb/AP-Exclusive:-Google-tracks-your-movements,-like-it-or-not</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Google wants to know where you go so badly that it records your movements even when you explicitly tell it not to.        An Associated Press investiga</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
