<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT PLAYS SILVER</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/nils-pratley-on-finance/2021/feb/01/reddits-flash-mob-wont-be-able-to-work-the-gamestop-magic-on-silver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will be a great deal harder to push up the price of the metal, which is already at an eight-year high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMESTOP stock craze about populist uprising against Wall St.  But it's more complicated than that...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/savingandinvesting/the-gamestop-stock-craze-is-about-a-populist-uprising-against-wall-street-but-it-e2-80-99s-more-complicated-than-that/ar-BB1diiAb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rebels storming Wall Street aren’t all small fry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CABLE NEWS RATINGS FALL BACK TO EARTH IN FIRST POST-TRUMP WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/vip/cnn-primetime-ratings-fall-post-trump-1234897869/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While January 2021 will go down in the ratings record books for CNN, the last week of the month may offer a portent of what the post-Trump era will be like for the network. In the first week of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House reviewing whether Trump should continue receiving intel briefings...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/536785-white-house-reviewing-whether-trump-should-continue-receiving-intel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is conducting a review to determine whether former President Trump should continue receiving intelligence briefings now that he has left office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to fly first mission to space with all-civilian crew...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/space/spacex-announces-first-mission-space-all-civilian-crew-n1256390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four-person expedition is expected to launch into orbit sometime in the fourth quarter of this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Despite claims of bias, conservatives thrive on social media...</title>
      <link>https://thefulcrum.us/big-picture/social-media-bias</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefulcrum.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media has become a punching bag for conservatives, who claim Facebook and Twitter have been silencing them. But in reality, the political right thrives on such platforms, a new report found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid spread of UK corona variant in Southern California sparks alarm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rapid-spread-u-k-coronavirus-193235139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Diego County has California's largest cluster of known cases of B.1.1.7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man Kills Married Couple, Then Self Following Snow Disposal Argument...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/02/01/man-kills-married-couple-then-self-following-snow-disposal-argument-luzerne-county-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials said the gunfire occurred just before 9 a.m. Monday in Plains Township.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 CHIEFS out with virus...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/01/chiefs-demarcus-robinson-daniel-kilgore-go-on-covid-19-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 issues that have pockmarked the NFL season have popped up just before Super Bowl 2021. The Kansas City Chiefs placed wide receiver Demarcus Robinson and center Daniel Kilgore on the CO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California town will pay you to visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Santa-Maria-hotel-deal-stimulus-money-100-free-15914850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Our destination is less crowded than other California destinations, and offers more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children's author arrested for torturing, starving her kids...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/jennifer-wolfthal-children-abused/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The writer and her husband are accused of abuse so horrific that one of the three children they adopted in 2014 remains in the hospital in serious condition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt mulls ending quarantine exemptions for vaccinated returnees...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/coronavirus-in-israel-govt-extends-lockdown-skies-remain-closed-657391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov’t to weigh extending lockdown again or reopening economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal switch hints at larger problems...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/536811-trump-legal-switch-hints-at-larger-problems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump abruptly changed his legal team over the weekend, underscoring his difficulties in putting together a strong defense just a week before his impeachment trial is to begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to fly first mission to space with all-civilian crew...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/01/spacex-to-fly-first-mission-to-space-with-an-all-civilian-crew-later-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX announced on Monday that it will launch four private individuals on a Crew Dragon capsule into orbit around the Earth for the Inspiration4 mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems look to make Marjorie Taylor Greene face of GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/536817-democrats-look-to-make-marjorie-taylor-greene-the-face-of-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats seizing on a string of controversies surrounding Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) hope to make her the face of the GOP in the 2022 midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Finalizing GAMESTOP Stock Movie...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/netflix-gamestop-stock-movie-screenwriter-mark-boal-noah-centineo-scott-galloway-makeready-1234684568/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: As Wall Street developments unfold in real time in the David V Goliath battle between hedge funds and social media-fueled day traders that sent shares of GameStop soaring 135% on a singl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstar Cities in Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/superstar-cities-are-in-trouble/ar-BB1dhzqv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The past year has offered a glimpse of the nowhere-everywhere future of work, and it isn’t optimistic for big cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Forced To Shovel Way To Surface After Blizzard Buries Tahoe Cabin...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/01/29/tahoe-city-family-stuck-in-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's an incredible sea of white in Tahoe City. The Heller family went to bed in their cabin, but they woke up in a snow cave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALDS Tests 'McPlant' Burger...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/2021/02/01/mcdonalds-quietly-rolls-out-mcplant-burger-test-markets/4344091001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald’s Corp. has quietly begun selling the McPlant burger in Denmark and Sweden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 38% of nursing home workers accept dose...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/only-38-nursing-home-workers-195942843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first national-level figures show just 38% of nursing home staff members accepted the vaccine in early weeks, the CDC reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mob' that closed DODGER site sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/mob-that-temporarily-closed-dodger-stadium-vaccination-site-sparks-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a group of protesters managed to disrupt operations at Dodger Stadium’s mass COVID-19 vaccination site Saturday, some Los Angeles officials expressed fury at the demonstrators while calling f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The View From the Republican Rebels...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/political-commentary/trump-impeachment-republicans-cheney-1121628/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re done with Trump and want their party back, but the pro-impeachment Republicans are still looking for the best way forward</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of Moscow's 12 million residents have had Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9211297/Half-Moscows-12million-residents-Covid-19-mayor-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with news outlet Rossiya-1, Mayor of Moscow Sergei Sobyanin said the number was based on city hall 'analysis and research'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers debate bill to rout out radical Islam in France...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-emmanuel-macron-secularism-france-bills-d3146e80f369006ed6f5a0d8fe2bc1b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French lawmakers debated a bill on Monday they hope will uproot radical Islam in the country, beliefs that authorities maintain are creeping into public services, associations, some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Arizona so bad?</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-health/2021/02/01/why-arizona-is-worst-nationwide-us-rate-new-coronavirus-cases/4281247001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of January, Arizona has had the highest rate of new COVID-19 cases in the U.S. Here are seven contributing reasons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US murder rate increase in 2020 has 'no modern precedent'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/01/americas-murder-rate-increase-in-2020-has-no-modern-precedent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murder rates saw a “historic” increase in 2020 compared to 2019, with more than 1,200 additional killings year-over-year in a sample of 34 American cities, according to a study released…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon law to decriminalize all drugs goes into effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/02/01/oregon-decriminalizes-all-drugs-offers-treatment-instead-jail-time/4311046001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive legislation that decriminalizes all drugs in Oregon looks to give addicts an opportunity for a different life through rehab and treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUSTIN DIAMOND DEAD AT 44...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/01/dustin-diamond-saved-by-the-bell-star-dead-44-stage-4-cancer-screech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Saved by the Bell" star Dustin Diamond dead at 44.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hunters' getting shots early by gaming system...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/01/us/vaccine-hunters-covid-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Vaccine hunters" stalk a pharmacy or vaccination site for leftovers. Spurred by reports of doses being dumped and feeling antsy for the country's vaccine rollout to pick up the pace, they want to prevent waste -- by getting their shot early.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry accepts damages from MAIL over 'baseless' article...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-55888361</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two articles claiming he snubbed the Royal Marines were "false and defamatory", the duke's lawyer says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Promises Most Innovative. Cinematic Super Bowl In Broadcast History...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/02/01/super-bowl-lv-coverage-innovative-technology-cameras-angles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The millions of viewers tuning in to Super Bowl LV to enjoy an unparalleled viewing experience, filled with a wide array of innovative technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELON JOINS CLUBHOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/elon-musk-makes-characteristically-wild-debut-on-a-buzzy-social-app-clubhouse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Office Supply Hits Record High With Skyscrapers Empty...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/manhattan-office-supply-hits-record-high-with-skyscrapers-empty/ar-BB1dhLfT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a record amount of office space available in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of sleep, overstressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9210573/A-Americans-walk-zombie-like-daze-stress-lack-sleep.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that almost a third of Americans suffer from concussion-like symptoms, largely due to stress and a lack of sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions surround ASTRAZENECA vaccine use for elderly...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/questions-surround-astrazeneca-vaccine-elderly-163648380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subject of a sometimes acrimonious row between the EU and Britain, the AstraZeneca Covid-19 vaccine has also fuelled debate over its effectiveness among the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI:  Pharmacist who destroyed 500 vaccine doses believes Earth is flat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wisconsin-pharmacist-who-destroyed-more-than-500-vaccine-doses-believes-earth-is-flat-fbi-says/ar-BB1dhvnD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Brandenburg, the Wisconsin pharmacist who is charged with destroying nearly 600 doses of the Moderna vaccine, also believes the Earth is flat and that the sky is not real, according to court records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Imagines Last Day of Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/how-it-ends-follows-l-a-s-overcomplicated-class-on-the-last-day-of-human-existence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How It Ends won me over as soon as Nick Kroll’s character referred to a stockpile of marijuana as “the medicine.” This was the ridiculous phrase that dodgy doctors and paranoid weed-store proprietors had to use in those goofy years when we all pretended that all marijuana use in the city was strictly medicinal, before […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TO OVERTAKE US ECONOMY IN 5 YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/01/new-chart-shows-china-gdp-could-overtake-us-sooner-as-covid-took-its-toll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic may have affected the U.S. economy more than the Chinese economy, analysts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMESTOP FADES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/01/gamestop-shares-reddit-trader-frenzy-continues-into-february.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop shares were lower on Monday as the Reddit-fueled frenetic trading extended into February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA authorized to fine passengers who refuse to wear masks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/tsa/536734-tsa-authorized-to-fine-passengers-who-refuse-to-wear-mask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) has been authorized to fine passengers who fail to comply with the new mask requirements on public transportation systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Has Hardest Week...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/01/30/dallas-county-ends-deadliest-week-covid-19-1407-new-cases-20-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas County ended this week with 183 deaths to COVID-19, which is the most in one week since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan lashes out at Turkey's LGBT movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.rudaw.net/english/middleeast/turkey/01022021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rudaw.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Biohacker' vows to live to 180 years using cryogenics!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/millionaire-biohacker-vows-live-180-23422804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Asprey, the self-proclaimed founder of "biohacking", appeared on ITV's This Morning today (February 1) to explain some cheap and easy ways to supposedly help you live longer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On iPhones, FACEBOOK and APPLE begin war of pop-up messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/on-iphones-facebook-and-apple-begin-a-war-of-pop-up-messages/ar-BB1dhUkt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has been going to battle with Apple a new App Store policy that requires apps to ask for permission to track their users across the web. Facebook think prompts Apple plans to implement are misleading and will counter them with its own prompt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chilling trend: Longer, deadlier pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-variants-pandemic-longer-contagious-deadly-88cdee57-a640-484e-860f-2cec9f950a94.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mutated versions of the coronavirus could prolong the pandemic for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire smoke may carry 'mind-bending' amounts of fungi and bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wildfire-smoke-may-carry-mind-140018077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are analyzing what microbes exist in the smoke and dust produced during wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Prosecutors Urge Navalny Jail Term as Protests Swell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-prosecutors-urge-navalny-jail-term-as-protests-swell/ar-BB1dhhle?ebsb=3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian prosecutors demanded opposition leader Alexey Navalny’s imprisonment, a day after police detained record numbers of protesters against President Vladimir Putin for a second straight weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage Of Police Pepper-Spraying 9-Year-Old Sparks Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jemimamcevoy/2021/02/01/footage-of-rochester-police-restraining-pepper-spraying-9-year-old-girl-sparks-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is not something that any of us should want to justify, can justify,” said Mayor Lovely Warren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Rise of the BARSTOOL conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/964006/rise-barstool-conservatives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Portnoy is the future of the conservative movement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA, China, UAE Probes Race to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/02/nasa-perseverance-china-eae-mars-probe-arrive-february/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’ll be a “Wright’s brothers” moment for NASA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fighter jet conducts dangerous 'low pass' of U.S. ship in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/1/russian-fighter-jet-conducts-dangerous-low-pass-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian fighter jet on Sunday buzzed past an American warship operating in the Black Sea, officials said, describing the incident as a dangerous, unjustified “low pass.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Amount of Trash Washing up on Malibu Beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.smdp.com/residents-report-unprecedented-amount-of-trash-washing-up-on-malibu-beaches/201449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smdp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Monica News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Bennett Reveals Alzheimer's Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/tony-bennett-reveals-alzheimers-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Bennett on Monday revealed that he has been diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Top NY Health Officials Have Quit as Cuomo Scorns Expertise...</title>
      <link>https://www.capitalgazette.com/coronavirus/ct-nw-nyt-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-health-experts-20210201-rxfqtmwdrjcrdfsuksanzelfc4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as the pandemic rages and New York struggles to vaccinate a large population, Gov. Andrew Cuomo has all but declared war on his own public health bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDANCE Most Disturbing: Boy Who Traps His Family in Hole...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sundances-most-disturbing-thriller-is-about-a-boy-who-traps-his-family-in-a-hole </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vaxxers Won't Stop Harassing Nurse They're Convinced Is Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/anti-vaxxers-wont-stop-harassing-tiffany-dover-nurse-theyre-convinced-is-dead-after-covid-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiffany Dover fainted after getting the COVID vaccine on TV. Then the insanity started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They stormed Capitol to overturn results of election they didn't vote in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/01/us/capitol-rioters-non-voters-invs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were there to "stop the steal" and to keep the president they revered in office, yet records show that some of the rioters who stormed the US Capitol did not vote in the very election they were protesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As The Don raked in cash denying his loss, little went to actual legal fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.wionews.com/world/as-trump-raked-in-cash-denying-his-loss-little-went-to-actual-legal-fight-360674</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wionews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump and the Republican Party entered this year having stockpiled more than $175 million from fundraising in November and December based on his false claims of voter fraud, spending only a tiny fraction on lawyers and bills for his effort to overturn the presidential election, according to new campaign finance reports filed Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Thought He Was Living in 'Matrix' -- and Killed His Parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/he-thought-he-was-living-in-the-matrix-and-killed-his-parents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Premiering at Sundance, the new doc “A Glitch in the Matrix” examines whether we are living in a simulation controlled by an advanced society, or if it’s all in people’s heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case of the Serial Sperm Donor...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/01/the-case-of-the-serial-sperm-donor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2015, Vanessa van Ewijk, a carpenter in the Netherlands, decided that she wanted to have a child. She was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Nation: Third Of Adults Walking Around In Concussion-Like Daze...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/zombie-nation-third-have-concussion-symptoms-stress-lack-of-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a third of people are walking around with the same symptoms as concussion due to stress and lack of sleep, suggests a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl security officers prep for triple threat of pandemic, politics, crowds...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210201095922-3nu8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOOTBALL-NFL-SUPERBOWL/SECURITY (PIX):Super Bowl security officers prep for triple threat of pandemic, politics and hometown crowds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skepticism lurks in town famous for syphilis study...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-sexually-transmitted-diseases-coronavirus-pandemic-syphilis-us-news-eae3315d2dfecd6443b56a2dc7bcb887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUSKEGEE, Ala. (AP) — Lucenia Dunn spent the early days of the coronavirus pandemic encouraging people to wear masks and keep a safe distance from each other in Tuskegee, a mostly Black city where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collapseologists warning humanity business-as-usual will make Earth uninhabitable...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/op-ed-collapseologists-warning-humanity-110002191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of scientists, writers and academics from 30 countries are demanding that we acknowledge that widespread social collapse is "a credible scenario this century."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splendid isolation: Family outsails COVID nightmare on the sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210201101455-f9iex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNGARY-SAILING/FAMILY (PIX, TV):Splendid isolation: Hungarian family outsails COVID nightmare on the sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Rachel Wood, Other Women Acuse Marilyn Manson of Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/02/he-horrifically-abused-me-for-years-evan-rachel-wood-and-other-women-make-allegations-of-abuse-against-marilyn-manson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manson’s representatives, who were not immediately available for comment, have “categorically denied” similar accusations in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Says He Wired Up Monkey's Brain to Play Video Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/elon-musk-says-he-wired-up-a-monkey-s-brain-to-play-video-games/ar-BB1dh4El </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBErs charged with illegal street-racing conspiracy in SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/youtubers-charged-with-illegal-street-racing-conspiracy-in-southern-california/article_63f729f5-3a05-5581-85e9-f35efabe2594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Rushdan Abdallah's videos on YouTube have been viewed by millions and offer an up-close glimpse of car culture in Southern California: getting caught in the middle of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients simultaneously infected with two variants in 'new pathway'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/brazil-patients-simultaneously-infected-two-23411192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mixture of two different strains of the virus in one host could be "another evolutionary pathway for the virus" leading to even more contagious variants in future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA dirty little secret: Profit doesn't come from selling cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/31/investing/tesla-profitability/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla posted its first full year of net income in 2020 -- but not because of sales to its customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea lions dying from mysterious cancer. The culprits? Herpes and DDT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sea-lions-dying-mysterious-cancer-140011203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found that sea lions exposed to DDT and other chemicals in the ocean are more likely to die from a herpes-induced cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LIGHTS OFF:  Amsterdam officials to vote on plans for 'erotic center' away from city in bid to clean up sex-and-drugs reputation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9207675/Amsterdam-officials-reveal-plans-erotic-centre-away-city-centre.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the new plans she has put forward, Amsterdam Mayor Femke Halsema is hoping to turn the focus away from sex and drugs and make the inner city more livable for locals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGETS SILVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/31/silver-futures-jump-7percent-as-reddit-traders-try-their-squeeze-play-with-the-metal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Futures contracts tied to silver were surging higher on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAN. WAS WORST MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EtGd42qWMAA-NQE?format=jpg&amp;name=large</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIRES TWO DEFENSE LAWYERS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republican-party-future-balance-trump-175159539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former US president Donald Trump announced Sunday he had picked two lawyers to head his defense team days before his historic second impeachment trial, as Republicans braced for a battle over the future of their party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LOSES IMPEACHMENT TEAM</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Legal-team-exits-as-Trump-fixates-on-false-claims-15912903.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The implosion of former president Donald Trump's legal team comes as Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT seeks to fill void if GOOGLE exits Australia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/microsoft-seeks-fill-void-google-020046084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has a "Plan B available" if Google follows through on threats to leave Australia over plans to compel digital giants to pay news organisations for content, local media reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Protesters shut DODGERS Stadium vax site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-vax-mob-closed-dodger-235818591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protest left several city leaders infuriated, with some questioning why police didn't do more to move the demonstrators out of the way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
