<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Naftali Bennett...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/lapid-i-dont-know-if-well-form-a-government-or-not-before-mandate-expires-669478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yamina leader Naftali Bennett informed Lapid of his decision on Friday * They agreed that Bennett would serve first as prime minister until September 2023</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba rolls out homegrown vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-bets-on-biotech-prowess-as-it-rolls-out-homegrown-covid-19-vaccine/ar-AAKuiTM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soberana, or sovereign, is how Cuba baptized its top COVID-19 vaccine, which just completed the last phase of clinical trials. Other shots are called Abdala, named after a poem by independence hero José Martí, and Mambisa, the word for 19th Century insurrectionists in the fight against Spanish rule. The names reveal a lot about the island's political and economic strategy to focus on a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Hat Shop Selling Nazi-Style Jewish Stars Proclaiming 'Not Vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/tennessee-hat-shop-blasted-selling-nazi-style-jewish-stars-proclaiming-not-vaccinated-1596081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The store's Instagram account contains conspiracy theories about COVID-19, facemasks and vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. warship fails to intercept test missile target...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210529153819-bgkup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DEFENSE/MISSILES (PIX):U.S. fails to intercept test missile target</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arms Race in America: Gun Buying Spiked During Pandemic. It's Still Up...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/29/an-arms-race-in-america-gun-buying-spiked-during-the-pandemic-its-still-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — It was another week with another horrific mass shooting. In cities across the country, gun homicides were climbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In SKorea 'healing forest,' stressed compete for ultimate chill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-south-korea-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98healing-forest-e2-80-99-the-pandemic-stressed-compete-for-the-ultimate-chill/ar-AAKvF3u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winner is the best at putting daily pressures aside. It’s an event for our time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC SPIRAL: Washington Square Park 'drug den' horrifies Greenwich Village...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/29/washington-square-park-drug-den-horrifies-greenwich-village/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawless, drug-infested Washington Square Park is horrifying even famously free-spirited Greenwich Village residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'QUIET PLACE' Biggest Pandemic-Era Debut With $57M...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/box-office/a-quiet-place-2-box-office-debut-1234984558/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A Quiet Place II” is set to make a loud debut at the domestic box office this Memorial Day weekend. The sequel to 2018’s “A Quiet Place” is projected to bring in $47 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining Czar McNally on Nearly Dying, Graydon Carter, Woody Allen, Restaurant Empire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news/keith-mcnally-nearly-dying-graydon-035722767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benjamin Norman/The New York Times via ReduxKeith McNally, the famed 69-year-old restaurateur of such hotspots as Balthazar, Pastis, the Minetta Tavern, and Café Luxembourg, is planning his return to New York City next month, having recovered from a life-imperiling battle with COVID in his native England. In a candid interview with The Daily Beast, he says that the pandemic almost broke his restaurant empire, but that plans are advancing to build branches of the Minetta Tavern in Washington, D.C., and Pastis in Miami. “After divorce, a stroke, and COVID destroying 75 percent of the finances of my restaurants, it’s crucial I make money,” McNally told The Daily Beast.The Bars Where Warhol Made Merry: New York’s Coolest Art HangoutsIn recent months, his Instagram account has become a controversy vector, with McNally attracting criticism for attacking the decision of a publisher not to publish Woody Allen’s memoir; defending Ghislaine Maxwell as “currently innocent”; for saying a fashion buyer looked “like a hooker”; for highlighting a chef was Chinese and mentioning their accent (later criticized by writer Faith Xue); and for claiming creative director Marcus Teo had left McNally’s now-shuttered venue Lucky Strike without paying (which Teo denied via a receipt), which McNally later said was a joke.Eater NY has said McNally’s Instagram account “has taken a wrong turn into yikes.” He also recently started an online war with Graydon Carter (former editor in chief of Vanity Fair, and Air Mail founder), who booked a table for 12 at Morandi, McNally’s Greenwich Village restaurant, then didn’t show. McNally said “this fancy fucker” would never be allowed in one of his restaurants again. (Carter later apologized, said he would make a donation to the wait staff’s tip pool, and called McNally “deranged.”) In the interview below, McNally intimates Carter’s ban may not be permanent after all—and yes, there is a response from Carter to that.McNally, who suffered a stroke in 2017 that left him paralyzed on the right side, also doubles down on supporting Allen, and expands on why he feels so strongly about making such provocative statements on Instagram, as well as speaking about how close he came to death, how COVID left his empire close to ruin, his standout celebrity memories (which feature Prince, George Clooney, and Bill Cosby), his drive to create restaurants, and his new relationship. It has been a wild ride since McNally opened his first restaurant, the legendary and much-loved Odeon, in 1980 with his first wife Lynn Wagenknecht and brother Brian McNally.McNally asked to conduct this interview by email, so we began there.Why did you want to do this interview by email?I prefer interviews by email because since my stroke I sound as if I’m talking underwater.How ill were you with coronavirus? I read you were “gasping for air” at the Chelsea and Westminster Hospital in London?I “gasped for air” only when asked by the hospital doctor, “Do you want to be revived if your heart stops?”Did you make arrangements imagining you may die?After the doctor told me I had a 50 percent chance of dying, I’m ashamed to say I didn’t think of my family, only my unfinished book.Did the experience make you confront your mortality?Like I confront all urgent matters, I put it on a back-burner.How has it compared, if at all, with having your stroke?Having a stroke was nothing compared to being tested with a fucking nasal swab for COVID.Why choose to be in London rather than stay in New York City?Initially because of the theater and my younger kids’ education, but these days—after divorce, a stroke, and COVID destroying 75 percent of the finances of my restaurants—it’s crucial I make money. I’m returning to NYC on June 25, and planning to live there full-time starting in September.How are you feeling now?Like always, hoping things get better, but knowing they won’t do.What are you working on?My memoir. (I hate the word “memoir.” It sounds like I’m speaking from a very high horse.) I’m two-thirds finished. Most of my day consists of putting off writing about a past which, for the most part, makes me cringe. I’m also building another Minetta Tavern in Washington, D.C.Your restaurant Lucky Strike closed in the pandemic. How was that for you?I never think twice about restaurants I’ve closed.How has the pandemic affected your business? You said you were losing $5k a day.COVID cost me a fortune. It cost others their lives, so I consider myself lucky.Are you confident that NYC restaurants are back and healthy?I was shocked by the response to reopening Balthazar. The first night was like V-E Day. Customers were dancing in the aisles and strangers kissed. And customers have suddenly gone crazy with their tips. I think Balthazar’s reopening symbolized to New Yorkers the re-emergence of the city. I feel very confident about the return of NYC more generally.Did the city, Governor Cuomo, and Mayor De Blasio behave responsibly when it came to the hospitality industry—its shutdown and return to life?In general, I think Cuomo did the right thing for New York, De Blasio less so, but it was an impossible situation for both of them.What are your plans when you get back?In September, I begin building the D.C. Minetta Tavern, and with my co-designer, Ian McPheely, I’m designing a Pastis in Miami with my Pastis partner, Stephen Starr. Like many restaurateurs, I lost a ton of money during COVID. These commercial ventures are a consequence of me being almost broke.The Graydon Carter feud: what do you have to say about his response to you?His response was bullshit. Graydon (Get) Carter knows he was a no-show without calling three times before. Look, there are more important things than no-shows at a Manhattan restaurant, but the fucker’s an editor. His whole life revolves around reshaping events to conform to his narrative.Will you lift your ban on him, or is it total and forever?Unless Graydon kisses my feet, the ban’s forever. Or at least one week.In an email to The Daily Beast, Carter wrote in response: “It’s fiction, and I’m just not going to engage.”Madonna was another difficult customer, you have said. Who have been your favorite and least favorite celebrities at your restaurants?My least favorite customer was Bill Cosby, even before I discovered he was an accused rapist. My three favorites are Tom Stoppard, Woody Allen, and Mike Nichols. For the first six months after my stroke, Tom Stoppard would send me mini-reviews of plays he'd seen in London. I’ll never forget this.What’s the wildest celebrity shenanigans in any of your restaurants that you witnessed?The wildest night at one of my places was in 1988 at my club on 14th Street, Nell’s, when Prince gave a spontaneous two-hour performance for free. It was sensational. My unsuspecting customers went bonkers!Which celebrities have surprised you the most, for good or bad?For good: George Clooney left a $2,000 tip at Balthazar once on a $75 cheque.For bad: One time at Nell’s I got a call from Bill Cosby’s assistant announcing that the famous comedian was coming to Nell’s alone the following Sunday. Cosby wanted no special treatment, the assistant told me. He wanted to be treated like everybody else.The following Sunday, Cosby arrived alone, stood at the bar, ordered a drink or two, watched his favorite jazz band, and left without incident. He received cordial treatment, but nothing more. Three days later I received an angry letter from Cosby complaining about the service. He claimed it was so unfriendly he would never return. I never found Cosby funny before the incident, but after it, I disliked him as much I do all vain, egotistical men who drug women in order to sexually assault them.Balthazar, Odeon, and the many others: what is their magic?It’s not for me to say. I only build restaurants that I want to go to. Sometimes they work, sometimes they don’t.Is there immense pressure when creating new venues to have those as legendary templates to live up to?I would like to say that after my stroke, I feel no pressure opening something as superficial as a restaurant. But the opposite is true.Was it fun having Pastis feature in Sex and the City (when Carrie went there with Aleksandr Petrovsky)?Kind of. The director actually asked me to be in it. I said no, which I now regret.What do you think of the vibe and folks who flock to the Meatpacking District now compared to, say, the days of Florent?I like the Whitney (Museum) and the High Line. I loathe most of the other stuff.Do you deliberately court controversy on Instagram? Why post what you did about Woody Allen, Ghislaine Maxwell, and the fashion buyer you said resembled a hooker? Do you stand by, or regret these and the other posts?I hate cancel culture and political correctness. I’m a Democrat, but dislike liberals who hurl abuse at Trump supporters, or jump onto the bandwagon of the latest fashionable cause. I support the #MeToo movement, but I loathe people who are blind to its minor flaws. It was a disgrace that Senator Al Franken was forced to resign (in January 2018, over sexual misconduct claims) without receiving due process. But it was far more disgraceful how many liberals were gung-ho about his resignation. I’m not intentionally controversial, but it's hard to turn a blind eye when I see so much hypocrisy on Instagram.1. WOODY ALLEN:Woody Allen has never been charged with a crime. The Child Sexual Abuse Clinic of Yale–New Haven Hospital made a thorough investigation in 1992 and came to the conclusion that Allen had NOT sexually abused Dylan, and one possibility they raised was that Dylan may have been “coached” by her mother. In my opinion, only one person in the world knows for certain whether or not Allen abused Dylan. And I believe him. (Editor’s note: the recent documentary series, Allen v. Farrow, criticized the credibility of the clinic’s evidence-gathering, particularly in how it questioned Dylan Farrow.) What I detest about today’s cancel culture is that it’s nigh on impossible to support #MeToo and also support Woody Allen. 2. GHISLAINE MAXWELL:As I’ve said ad nauseam on Instagram: I don’t support Maxwell. I support her right to due process. I strongly believe that the more vile the accusation, the more important it becomes that the accuser receives due process. As a result of writing this on Instagram, I was accused of being a sex trafficker, a rapist, a pedophile, and worse. I was not defending Maxwell (as the muckraking Airmail maliciously suggested), I was defending Maxwell's right to due process.3. MARCUS TEO:A harmless joke that I regret. I deleted the post and apologized to Marcus who, according to my staff, is the most decent man imaginable. (He’s since been to Balthazar.)4. FAITH XUE:Faith took umbrage at a restaurant kitchen story I wrote on Instagram in which I imitated the Chinese chef's accent. I would have done the same if the chef had been French. Does this mean we have to remake Schindler's List with non-German accents? It’s fucking preposterous!5. THE FASHION BUYER:After remarking that a fashion buyer on Instagram was posing like a hooker, I instantly apologized to hookers everywhere for the disservice I did to them.Did you/do you know Ghislaine Maxwell, Jeffrey Epstein, and Prince Andrew? What are your thoughts on them?No! I never met one of them, ever! Graydon Carter’s Airmail tried to smear my character by intimating that I’d met Maxwell. I absolutely have not met her.Ghislaine should be tried, and if found guilty, forced to change her name to something easier to spell, before serving a hefty prison sentence. My guess is that Epstein was a dangerous, malignant creep. Prince Andrew should definitely be extradited and tried by an American court. The reason why this won’t happen is the reason why I’m an avid anti-royalist.You seem very ready to come to the defense of people with damaged public reputations? What motivates that? Loyalty to friends, or something else?Not in 25 years have I defended anyone I’m friends with. But in the end, a reputation is the only thing we have. Unless we want mob rule, it’s paramount we don’t accuse someone of anything unless we have incontrovertible evidence.Are you intending to be more cautious on Instagram and social media, or continue to be as outspoken as you care to be?Because I believe a democratic society is characterized by free and open discussion of ideas I won’t be any more cautious than I am already. Freedom is the right to tell people what they don’t want to hear. Either George Orwell or Gina Lollobrigida said this. I’m not sure which.What was growing up in Bethnal Green, East London like, and what kind of boy were you?I grew up in a rough neighborhood in the 1950s where you had to be tough, or have a tough older brother, to survive. I had two, so life was cushy. Until they left to live abroad, that is, when I got the crap beaten out of me.What were your early ambitions?To have sex with Diana Dors.You worked as a stage manager in a strip club. What were your other jobs and life before the restaurants happened? Was owning restaurants always your ambition, or something else?I never had ambitions of being in the catering trade. In fact, I never ate in a restaurant until I was 17. At 19, I hitchhiked alone to Kathmandu, which I write quite a lot about in my very unfinished memoir. After returning from India in 1972, I worked days at Smithfield meat market in London and studied English literature at night school afterward.You set up Odeon with Lynn and Brian in 1980. What is your relationship with Brian like now (you once said you didn’t get along with your brothers growing up), and with Lynn?Lynn’s my best friend. Brian and I get along like brothers, meaning we hate each other half the time and get along great the other half. It seems to me that it’s far more natural for families to not get along than the reverse. But most people pretend the opposite is true.People go on about the famous folks in your restaurants, yet you don’t seem to be a starstruck kind of guy.I am starstruck, I just hide it well. But I’m a lot closer to my staff than the customers. I’m far more in awe of my chef who creates a dish than a customer who simply eats it. How can I not be?Did you drink a lot or take drugs?I drink wine with dinner, but seldom more than 2 glasses. Despite owning a fashionable nightclub, Nell’s, where everybody took drugs, I never took a single one because I have a fear of letting go. But Nell’s made the most money of all my places, so maybe I should not let myself go more often.You have said you were served divorce papers when recovering from your stroke (from Alina, your second wife).I was shocked out of fucking hell when, a year after my stroke, Alina had a lawyer’s emissary storm into my bedroom and toss divorce papers at me. But now, three years later, I can see the funny side of it.What is your personal life like right now?I’m lucky enough these days to be in love with a beautiful, intelligent woman who adores me without having to take ecstasy. She’s half-Palestinian, half-Austrian. Isn’t everybody?What is your dream NYC night out when you return?My dream night in NYC is staying at home, away from the madding crowd, watching a film with one of my children, or Tamimah, my girlfriend. By the way, Thomas Hardy (author of Far from the Madding Crowd) is one of my favorite novelists, although he always referred to himself as a poet, not a novelist.What about the future? Is retirement an option, or not?I’m lucky if I get up in the morning. The rest is a bonus.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mothers criticize BLM activists for profiting off their dead sons...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/29/mothers-criticize-blm-activists-for-profiting-off-their-dead-sons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLM’s Los Angeles chapter raised $5,000 for her son’s funeral, but Lisa Simpson claimed she never received any of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe Rattled By Multiple Quakes; 'Big One' Coming?</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/05/28/several-earthquakes-shake-lake-tahoe-with-a-big-one-overdue-is-it-coming-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple earthquakes rattled the Lake Tahoe region on Friday, the latest in a sequence that began in late April. Many in the area are now wondering what's next?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viral TIKTOK video brought chaos to Huntington Beach. Officials fear just beginning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/viral-tiktok-video-brought-chaos-120033246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police and elected officials worry the pandemonium that occurred in the city highlights the power of social media, which can disseminate information far and wide, causing events to get out of hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since nose doesn't know pot now legal, K-9s retire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/va-state-wire-police-marijuana-marijuana-legalization-253af1ba6e541060085108e027b367c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Asking dogs to follow their noses won't work anymore in states that have legalized marijuana. As Virginia prepares to legalize adult possession of up to an ounce of marijuana on July 1, drug-sniffing police dogs from around the state are being forced into early retirement, following a trend in other states where legalization has led to K-9s being put out to pasture earlier than planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA releases stunning new pic of Milky Way 'downtown'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-science-5ccca40b88d9096c78fdea2a212ada8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA has released a stunning new picture of our galaxy’s violent, super-energized “downtown.” It's a composite of 370 observations over the past two decades by the orbiting Chandra X-ray Observatory, depicting billions of stars and countless black holes in the center, or heart, of the Milky Way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even in face of surging grocery prices, retail beef and pork prices cause sticker shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/even-in-the-face-of-surging-grocery-prices-retail-beef-and-pork-prices-cause-sticker-shock/ar-AAKvANC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beef and pork prices hover at near record high due to labor shortages, high grain and energy costs and just plain old demand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warships 'swarmed by 100 UFOs' over month period...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/nine-navy-warships-were-swarmed-24203067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Investigative filmmaker Jeremy Corbell, who has released various authentic UFO videos seen by US Navy vessels, claimed anti-drone technology was completely ineffective</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Hamptons Booms, World of Luxury Problems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/29/as-the-hamptons-booms-a-new-world-of-luxury-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was 4 p.m. last Friday and a 30-something New Yorker who’d just flown into the East Hampton airport was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam detects highly contagious new virus variant as infections surge...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/556076-vietnam-identifies-new-highly-transmissible-variant-of-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vietnam has detected a new, highly transmissible variant of the coronavirus, the Vietnamese Health Ministry announced Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Prosecutors Zero In On Trump's Real-Life Wayne Manor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prosecutors-zero-trump-real-life-004618943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyAs two separate investigations into the Trump Organization heat up, a series of subpoenas issued by the New York attorney general and the Manhattan district attorney shows how prosecutors are probing one particular land deal.The subpoenas, which have not been publicly released until now, have been issued during the past 18 months to three towns just north of New York City.Investigators asked for a trove of documents related to Donald Trump’s failed attempts to develop a luxury golf course on a 212-acre, forested estate that spans across those three towns and includes several mansions. The requested documents and subsequent court filings show that investigators are examining whether the Trump Organization inflated the value of the property for a charitable tax write-off.The Daily Beast has learned the state Attorney General’s Office issued a round of subpoenas in November 2019. Investigators demanded copies of “zoning, property planning, or other building and construction permissions” sought by Trump’s firm for the property, Seven Springs LLC. At question is the dense forest that surrounds a towering, 60-room, century-old, sandstone chateau that includes three pools, carriage houses, and is imposing enough to justify its own forecourt and fountain.Think: Bruce Wayne. (There’s even a massive suspected bat population on the grounds of the estate.)When locals fought Trump’s building plans, Trump decided to give away his land rights to a conservation group—allowing him to take a hefty $21.1 million tax deduction in 2015, according to a filing made by investigators last August.But the pivotal question remains: Was the gifted land really worth that much if nothing was built on it?The towns of Bedford, New Castle, and North Castle handed over dozens of documents, according to records The Daily Beast obtained.At that time in late 2019, the AG’s office had already issued a subpoena seeking records and communications to see if the Trump Organization and its officers committed bank fraud—again, essentially a case concerning lying about asset values. Nearly a year later, the team would acknowledge in court filings that it hadn’t yet “reached a determination” whether it had found “violations of any applicable laws.”Meanwhile, Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance Jr. was busy trying to get then-President Trump’s tax returns in order to examine his “hush money” payments to the porn star Stormy Daniels. As that investigation expanded into a criminal probe of Trump’s property valuations in cities across the country, that office also sent subpoenas for the Seven Springs conservation deal to the same three towns in December 2020.Except this time, investigators demanded a much larger collection of records. They asked for items like planning board meeting minutes, which would help show whether Trump ever really stood a chance at building on the land, and they sought records dating back more than 15 years in some cases—items that one clerk said should have been destroyed.Another town clerk said that, as recently as two months ago, DA investigators were still picking up boxes of documents and loading them onto a truck.The Daily Beast received a copy of the DA’s more recent subpoenas to Bedford, New Castle, and North Castle, as well as the documents they turned over.Those subpoenas, tied to a 2018 case called “Investigation into the Business and Affairs of John Doe,” demanded copies of a dozen different types of records, as well as “appraisals, engineering reports, and environmental impact statements.”Where those two separate probes overlap, their efforts have now merged.Ever since news of a grand jury broke, Trump reacted in his standard, bitter fury. He publicly denounced the New York investigations as politically motivated, and he claimed they were trying to harm his potential 2024 presidential run.In the past few days, lawyers and other advisers close to the twice-impeached former president have personally reassured Trump they do not believe New York prosecutors will ever actually indict him, according to two people familiar with the situation.“I told him that he has nothing to worry about,” one of these advisers said.Still, Trump’s attorneys have already discussed possible legal maneuvers in the event that the ex-president is eventually indicted as a result of these probes. According to a person with direct knowledge of the conversations, Trump’s lawyers would argue, for instance, that the investigation was tainted due to New York Attorney General Letitia James’ openly “partisan” rhetoric about Trump’s alleged criminality and her remarks about Trump being an “illegitimate” president.Former Manhattan Assistant District Attorney Alissa Marque Heydari, who now runs the academic Institute for Innovation in Prosecution, sounded more hopeful.“Using the grand jury to focus on the acts of the most powerful will help restore trust in the criminal justice system,” she said. “Too often, those tools are brought to bear on the last powerful in our society. But the investigations of the AG and DA buck this norm.”But one source of Trump’s palpable anger with the New York investigations isn’t the possible legal peril; it’s the ballooning financial cost to him and his business empire.The ex-president has recently complained repeatedly about how he feels the investigators could drag this out for years, and that the hefty legal bills are becoming “such a pain in the ass,” one of these sources recounted.Indeed, a motion delivered by Trump’s lawyers earlier this month alleged that a lawsuit filed against him by the NAACP over the Jan. 6 Capitol riot was “frivolous,” and stated that the Democratic plaintiffs and their lawyers “should be ordered to pay President Trump’s fees and costs.”Last week, the AG’s office confirmed that its civil case had recently become a criminal one. James later revealed that two of her prosecutors have been deputized to work alongside the Manhattan DA’s team. And on Tuesday, The Washington Post reported that the DA has already convened a grand jury to make the historic decision of whether or not to indict Trump and others involved.“It’s relatively rare to partner up to this extent on an investigation together,” said Tess Cohen, a criminal defense lawyer who presented cases before grand juries for years when she was at the Special Narcotics Prosecutor's Office in New York City.Given the circumstances, Cohen said it’s likely that both prosecution teams are now presenting to the same grand jury, which is an even rarer development that could indicate a few things. Either one investigation team has access to a key cooperating witness that the other side needs, or the unprecedented act of targeting a former president is such a political minefield that bringing two government offices together strengthens their case.Neither office would confirm the existence of a sitting grand jury, as such proceedings are secret by state law, nor would they provide comment for this story.Another reason to team up might be differences in jurisdiction, said Dan Feldman, a law professor at John Jay College of Criminal Justice who worked at the AG’s office for six years until 2005. Feldman, who as a state legislator also wrote New York's mob-busting anti-racketeering law, said the AG’s office also has greater ability to use that against the many entities and players in the Trump world on this deal.“Because the AG has the organized crime task force, they are particularly well-equipped to pursue an Organized Crime Control Act indictment because they have the expertise, the background, and statewide jurisdiction,” he said.The attorney general has the ability to prosecute crimes that occurred outside of Manhattan. Although the Trump Organization and its Seven Springs LLC subsidiary are based in New York City, the property being appraised is in Westchester County and any meddling in that deal may have occurred outside the city.Trump’s second son, Eric Trump, hired the real estate firm Cushman &amp; Wakefield in June 2015 to appraise the property, according to material gathered by the AG’s office. That firm determined that the property was worth $56.5 million as of Dec. 1, 2015, just days before Trump gave away development rights on a huge chunk of that land.When Trump did sign the agreement, he turned over rights to the North American Land Trust. The conservation easement, as it’s called, bestows power on this nonprofit to protect the 158 acres of red oaks, sugar maples, and huckleberry bushes. An environmental assessment in the document says “it is likely that the Conservation Area provides critical habitat for some of the rarest bat species of the region,” like the little brown bat.One person involved in that conservation deal told The Daily Beast they were questioned by the AG’s office more than two years ago about the land’s value and how it was appraised. The person said they had not spoken to investigators since or been brought before any current grand jury as a witness. The AG’s office would not confirm their account.Another person who was ordered to turn over documents was Charles Martabano, the land-use attorney who represented Seven Springs and tried to develop the property. State investigators used a subpoena to obtain hundreds of pages of emails, although he successfully kept many of them from prosecutors by declaring them subject to attorney-client privilege.“From his point of view, there is absolutely, positively nothing inappropriate here,” said Martabano’s attorney, George J. Calcagnini.One town clerk, who turned over documents to investigators, lambasted the investigation as a waste of time and said the town shouldn’t have kept the documents long enough to turn over to investigators.“They're not going to find what they're looking for,” she said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hollywood 'Jesus' Went Full Q...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-jesus-jim-caviezel-went-000054592.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyJim Caviezel, best known for playing Jesus in Mel Gibson’s The Passion of the Christ and his starring role in CBS’ Person of Interest, made people do a double take when he appeared at a right-wing conference in April to promote his forthcoming anti-child trafficking movie.It wasn’t entirely shocking that Caviezel was at the Health and Freedom Conference, which was attended by former President Donald Trump’s usual posse, including the conspiracy theory-loving trio of MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, attorney Lin Wood, and former Trump lawyer Sidney “release the Kraken” Powell. The actor has proudly been one of few outspoken conservative Christians in Hollywood, counting Steve Bannon as a good friend and often closing out interviews by reciting one of Ronald Reagan’s speeches.But while talking about his new movie Sound of Freedom, Caviezel went on a wild tangent about a QAnon conspiracy theory called “adrenochroming.” The event’s 4,500-strong crowd had a decent showing of raised hands when asked if they were familiar with the term. Essentially, it’s an insane theory rooted in anti-Semitism (and the Pixar film Monsters, Inc.) that liberal elites and members of Hollywood are secretly killing children in order to harvest adrenochrome from their blood for psychedelic experiences, satanic rituals, and even to extend their lifespan. How QAnon Became Obsessed With ‘Adrenochrome,’ an Imaginary Drug Hollywood Is ‘Harvesting’ from KidsHere’s how Caviezel explained it. “I’ll just simplify it,” he began. “When you are scared, you produce adrenaline. You’re an athlete, you get in the fourth quarter, you have adrenaline that comes out. If a child knows he’s going to die, his body will secrete this adrenaline. They have a lot of terms that they use that [Tim Ballard] takes me through, but it’s the worst horror I’ve ever seen. The screaming alone, even if I’d never, ever, ever, ever saw it, it’s beyond.”“These people that do it,” he paused, seeming to hold back tears. “There’ll be no mercy for them.”The crowd burst into applause.So how did Caviezel wind up getting sucked into one of the more fringe conspiracy theories of QAnon? Normally, it’d be easy to track a person’s fall down the rabbit hole of QAnon, starting with their social media behavior, which often involves sharing questionable posts from questionable profiles on Facebook and Twitter.However, Caviezel doesn’t have a very active presence online, apart from his Instagram account that he started in September 2020. Describing the page as his only social media account, he has a sprinkling of posts that include some behind-the-scenes moments at work and photos of scripture. There did seem to be a convincingly real Twitter account belonging to Caviezel that went inactive right when he started his Instagram, which posted about his upcoming projects, praise for Mel Gibson, support of Donald Trump, and dozens of tweets about being pro-life.But it seems that Caviezel could have been brought into the QAnon fold through working on his new movie Sound of Freedom, which is based on the life story of Tim Ballard, who runs the controversial anti-child sex trafficking organization Operation Underground Railroad (OUR). Ballard handpicked Caviezel to play him in the movie, explaining that he was moved by his performances in The Passion of the Christ and The Count of Monte Cristo.Caviezel did not respond to The Daily Beast’s requests for comment.Ballard claims his decade in the U.S. government included a stint as a CIA agent and as an undercover agent with Homeland Security; he was later tapped by Trump to be a council member of the Public-Private Partnership Advisory Council to End Human Trafficking. He spouts off unverified statistics about child trafficking, some of which were repeated by Trump while he was in office.Ballard’s group OUR frequently finds itself entangled with QAnon conspiracy theorists, sometimes by Ballard’s own doing. Last summer, when a since-debunked claim that online furniture retailer Wayfair was secretly promoting the sale of children through its site, Ballard seemed to give credence to the claim, reportedly talking about it at a QAnon-heavy conference and on social media.“With or without Wayfair, child trafficking is real and happening,” he said in a video message. “This is not a small thing or a conspiracy theory, this is the fastest growing criminal enterprise in the world. The children need us.” Ballard did not return The Daily Beast’s requests for comment.That last phrase is a familiar rallying cry for QAnoners, who are often lured into the web of deep state rumors and promises of armed uprisings by claims of a global child sex trafficking ring filled with billionaires, powerful politicians, and members of Hollywood.The slogans #savethechildren and #saveourchildren have become so associated with the QAnon community that when Trump incited a mob to storm the Capitol on January 6th, several insurrectionists carried signs with variations of the phrases, including “Protect the Children'' and "The Children Cry Out for Justice.” In an attempt to stop the spread of disinformation, Facebook has tried to redirect users from the hashtags, instead providing links to reputable groups that work to stop child sexual exploitation. OUR is not among the organizations listed.So it’s no surprise that when Ballard was mentioned several times by Caviezel during his address to the ultra-right-wing conference, the crowd erupted into cheers and applause, already familiar with his work. And when Caviezel suggested that he learned about “adrenochroming” from Ballard, the concept was not new to them.When video of Caviezel’s remarks posted to YouTube, the comments were flooded with talk of “save the children,” declarations of how the “evil Satanic cult will be defeated by the Lord,” and how many believe that “this is common in the dark backrooms of the elite.”Sound of Freedom seems to have leaned into its QAnon fanbase, using both #freethechildren and #savethechildren in its promotional marketing, with fans responding in kind. At a screening for the movie, Caviezel was photographed with former heavyweight boxer David Niño Rodriguez, who has turned into a vocal QAnon supporter and, as of May, still believes a “Trump revival is coming.”Last May, he was on a podcast talking about pizzagate and adrenochrome, saying “they traumatize the kid until you fucking can’t pull out any more adrenaline and then they kill him.”“They drink that shit up,” he added. “It’s a fucking fact bro, everyone knows it. I’m confident to say, ‘Yeah it’s happening.’ All the most powerful people in the world are doing it, you got to remember the elite control shit and they only bring in like minds. So, I don’t have names, I just know this.” Timothy Ballard, Jim Caviezel and director Alejandro Gomez Monteverde on the set of Sound of Freedom Instagram Caviezel also claims that Hollywood doesn’t want a film about the evils of child trafficking, resulting in Sound of Freedom’s delayed release, even though many films’ release dates were pushed due to the ongoing pandemic.“Obviously you understand the content of this, once the world sees this film, once they see the ships that they transport the children in, all that stuff…,” he told the conference. “There’s no other film like this. Our industry can’t make this film right now because a lot of people who are involved in this all over the world, many of these people are very famous.”“So, in the fourth quarter, that’s when we hope [the movie will come out],” he added. “We are going to need your prayers.”Caviezel has long believed he’s up against the forces of Hollywood given his religious beliefs, even claiming that taking the role of Jesus in 2004’s The Passion of the Christ made him a pariah in the industry. Yet he managed to land roles throughout the years, including on CBS’ primetime crime drama Person of Interest in 2011, playing the character of John Reese alongside Michael Emerson and Taraji P. Henson.His time on the show and his connection to QAnon was explored at length in the popular podcast QAnon Anonymous earlier this month, as hosts Julian Feeld, Travis View, and Jack Rockatanksy devoted a whole episode to Caviezel, with featured guest Dave Anthony.Feeld spoke with three anonymous people who worked on Person of Interest with Caviezel who described numerous instances of bizarre behavior from the actor, with the men later summing him up toward the end of the 80-minute episode as “perfect for QAnon!”They said he was “profoundly consumed by a jumble of bizarre religious, military and nationalistic fixations,” initially refusing to participate in an episode where he had to rescue a same-sex couple because it went against his morals. “All of them told me they felt Caviezel was homophobic and believed members of the LGBTQ community were going to hell,” the sources claimed.Another claim was that Caviezel would often make snap judgements of what someone’s ethnicity and race was based on their skin color or appearance, then mimic the language he believed they spoke. He allegedly bowed to an Asian executive and attempted to speak in Chinese to him, later waving off concern because he had adopted two Chinese children.The sources claimed that he would talk in a “blaccent” when around Black crew members and later refused to let his character have a romantic relationship on screen with his Black female co-star because “people shouldn’t have interracial relationships.”He allegedly had an “obsession with identifying Jewish people that was accompanied by a pretty clear hatred for Islam,” and the source said he once walked up to a demonstration where people were planning to burn the Quran in Washington, D.C, and allegedly said, “I know Islam, Islam is evil all the men want Sharia [law].”The sources also mention how Sound of Freedom director Alejandro Monteverde is also a devout Catholic and, like Caviezel, anti-abortion. Caviezel has been very vocal about his pro-life stance, saying in 2010 that he regards it as the “greatest moral defect of the western world.” Discussing how Attila the Hun “raised the bar to another level” when he began killing women and children during wars, he said “abortion goes much further.” Bill O'Reilly and actor Jim Caviezel attend the 30th Annual Great Sports Legends Dinner. Bryan Bedder/Getty “When the mother herself kills her son she goes against her own nature, against her own instinct,” he said. “People talk about ‘choice,’ but when a woman does that, when she destroys the life of her unborn child, then we have arrived at the limit. The level cannot go higher regarding evil.”Speaking to a church congregation in 2014, he spoke about abortion at length, telling the crowd, “Some of you had abortions. Some men and women are adulterers. Some have committed murder. Some of you didn’t have the abortion but you paid for it, so you have contributed to this. Many people are a part of this great sin in this country.”QAnon expert Jack Bratich, an associate professor of journalism and media studies at Rutgers, explained to The Daily Beast how it can often be a slippery slope into QAnon for those who believe they are trying to protect the unborn and vulnerable children when their belief is rooted in religion, because they are sometimes already predisposed to believe that those who think otherwise are evil.“In 2020, when you started seeing that kind of Save the Children hashtag, almost more prominent than QAnon, it was kind of a gateway. You would have these protests for Save the Children and a lot of people would want to ‘save the children,’ right? So, they would show up to these protests or watch a video, and then the more extreme components of QAnon would enter, like adrenochrome and a satanic pedophile ring at the highest levels of government in Hollywood.”“They’re not just predisposed to save children or even save fetuses, but they think there’s a vast enemy that’s out to destroy children. If they already have that kind of framework, that people who are pro-choice are actually evil, that it’s not just a policy matter that they’re actually evil, then it’s a pretty easy slide to go there when it comes to child trafficking and cannibalism.”A recent poll found that roughly one quarter of Republicans believe in some form of the QAnon conspiracy, while QAnon is now as popular in the U.S. as some major religions.Currently, Sound of Freedom does not have an official release date. Its Instagram account has not posted since last September. It appears some of the movie’s producers are still working to get it distributed on a larger scale, hosting small word-of-mouth screenings around the country, most recently in Houston. Ballard appeared to announce a firmer premiere date in April, claiming it would be coming out in the fall of 2021, but the post has since been taken down.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
