<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FBI raids Detroit city hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2021/08/25/detroit-city-hall-raids-fbi-statement/5589949001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Detroit Special Agent in Charge Timothy Waters issued statement after raid on Detroit city hall as well as several homes of city council members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA app backtracks Roger Stone ban after 'censorship' accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/08/25/jason-millers-right-wing-gettr-site-backtracks-on-roger-stone-ban-after-accused-of-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Gettr claims to have reversed the ban, a war of words is still raging over in TrumpWorld</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 citizens remain?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/25/politics/blinken-americans-afghanistan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Antony Blinken said Wednesday that there are approximately 1,500 people who may be Americans left in Afghanistan, adding that when evacuation operations began, there was a population of as many as 6,000 American citizens in the country who wanted to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative hoaxers face $5M fine for election robocalls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-elections-election-2020-260f8df2ed47fa17bf3e88d0a49e64f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Two conservative hoaxers face a record $5.1 million fine for allegedly making illegal robocalls to wireless phones without the owners' consent in the 2020 election. The Federal Communications Commission said Tuesday that the proposed fine for Jacob Wohl, Jack Burkman and Burkman's lobbying firm would be the largest ever for violating the Telephone Consumer Protection Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected jail inmates given drug that 'can cause serious harm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ivermeticin-inmates-covid-19-arkansas-fda-warnings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FDA warns that the anti-parasite drug ivermectin shouldn't be used for COVID-19 and can be harmful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo bans woman who said she had 'affair' with chimpanzee...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/belgian-zoo-banned-woman-said-023651564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Antwerp Zoo said that the interactions between the woman and Chita the chimpanzee resulted in the chimp being ostracized by other primates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy assassin seeks parole -- with no opposition from prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/sirhan-sirhan-convicted-of-robert-f-kennedy-assassination-seeks-parole-with-no-opposition-from-prosecutors/ar-AANJS2S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now 77, the convicted killer of RFK is seeking release on grounds that he is no longer a threat, and that the stature of his victim should not be a consideration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,100 citizens remain?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/afghanistan-news-taliban-refugees-08-25-21/h_15b040da4bb2c75f448fb648b1717867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one week after the Taliban takeover of Kabul, the situation at the capital's airport has become increasingly desperate as thousands still wait to depart the country. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Known Software Can Trigger Revocation of Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/08/25/atlas-citizenship-denaturalization-homeland-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as ATLAS, the software mines various federal databases for derogatory information. It runs autonomously on Amazon servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NY gov. adds 12,000 deaths to tally...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/ny-nursing-home-deaths-kathy-hochul-andrew-cuomo-delta-variant/10974447/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York now reports nearly 55,400 people have died of COVID-19 in New York based on death certificate data submitted to the CDC, up from about 43,400 that Gov. Cuomo had reported to the public as of Monday, his last day in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBIPALANTIR glitch allowed unauthorized access to private data...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/25/fbi-palantir-glitch-allowed-unauthorized-access-to-private-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A computer glitch in a software program, Palantir, used by the FBI allowed some unauthorized employees to access private data for more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 'could be cancelled' as UK food shortage crisis grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/15960414/co-op-boss-warns-food-shortages-worst-ever-seen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUPERMARKET bosses have warned that shortages could hit Christmas food supplies. Richard Walker, Iceland’s chief executive, has said that a lack of lorry drivers is threatening deliveries. Ga…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Barron Trump's new $35k-a-year school dubbed 'The Asylum'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3538365/barron-trumps-new-school-sex-harassment-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER President Donald Trump’s youngest son, Barron, has been enrolled in a swanky private school in West Palm Beach, Florida. Oxbridge Academy, where Barron is now a student, was founded by Willi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Branch Poses Biggest Immediate Terror Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/isis-branch-poses-biggest-immediate-terror-threat-to-evacuation-in-kabul/ar-AANJWRl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The United States has been battling the Taliban and their militant partners in Afghanistan, Al Qaeda and the Haqqani network, for 20 years. But the biggest immediate threat to both the Americans and the Taliban as the United States escalates its evacuation at the Kabul airport before an Aug. 31 withdrawal deadline is a common rival that is lesser known: Islamic State Khorasan, or ISIS-K, the terrorist group’s affiliate in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOWOUT:  MSNBC PAYS MADDOW $30M YEAR; WEEKDAY SHOW TO END IN '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-massive-msnbc-deal-paying-rachel-maddow-to-work-less</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBCUniversal will give Maddow $30 million annually while ending her show next year and giving their top star a more flexible schedule than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H'WOOD MOBILIZED...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/gavin-newsom-recall-hollywood-democrats-help-1235002709/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the California governor aims to fend off an ouster in the Sept. 14 election, his advisers have quietly called on Reed Hastings, Steven Spielberg and other left-leaning moguls to contribute big money and to mobilize Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willis Tower in Chicago skyscraper most struck by lightning...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/the-5-us-skyscrapers-that-get-struck-by-lightning-most-often/990352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say lightning never strikes the same place twice, but that's far from true. Some might guess One World Trade Center, the tallest building in the U.S., is hit most -- but it actually ranks second.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country Now Comes Before Profit For Tech Giants in Xi's China...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/country-now-comes-profit-tech-002735895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China’s biggest companies are starting to make a habit out of giving away their earnings.In the latest example, Pinduoduo Inc., an e-commerce company known for giving big discounts to customers when they buy produce together, said it will donate all of its first net profit since going public to support the country’s farmers and agricultural areas. The company will keep giving away earnings at least until the donations reach 10 billion yuan ($1.5 billion).“Improving agriculture has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops must get shot ASAP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-4cf7451267919302de4a7b591508e80c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Military troops must immediately begin to get the COVID-19 vaccine, Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin said in a memo Wednesday, ordering service leaders to “impose ambitious timelines for implementation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Witches Trying to Hex Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k789qv/these-witches-are-trying-to-hex-the-taliban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the fall of Kabul, practitioners began to gather online to fight against the Taliban with a mix of direct aid and magick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apathetic voters could hand California to Elder...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/25/california-governor-recall-gavin-newsom-larry-elder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gavin Newsom remains popular but Democrats appear far less likely than Republicans to vote in the election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: ONLYFANS Drops Planned Porn Ban...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/onlyfans-drops-porn-ban-sexually-explicit-policy-1235048705/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OnlyFans dropped plans to ban pornography from its service, less than a week after the U.K. content-creator subscription site had announced the change citing the need to comply with policies of ban…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Drinking 8 Glasses Of Water Daily Key To Healthy Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drinking-more-water-heart-failure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drinking eight glasses of water a day is an age-old recommendation which doctors say keeps your entire body healthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Newsom could lose job to Republican in recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-california-e2-80-99s-gavin-newsom-could-lose-his-job-to-a-republican-in-a-recall/ar-AANIUPw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what you need to know to follow the special election to recall California Governor Gavin Newsom, why his job is threatened and who is running to replacement should he lose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For NFL teams with unvaccinated QBs, this could be long, complicated season...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/For-NFL-teams-with-unvaccinated-quarterbacks-16410338.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots gathered for practice Tuesday in Foxborough, Mass., without...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban shows off 'special forces' in propaganda blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210825-taliban-shows-off-special-forces-in-propaganda-blitz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban shows off 'special forces' in propaganda blitz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more ICU beds in Arkansas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/569293-no-more-icu-beds-in-arkansas-for-covid-19-patients-governor-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arkansas Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R) on Tuesday revealed that his state has run out of intensive care unit (ICU) beds to treat COVID-19 patients amid a surge of new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After takeover, concerns mount over U.S. counterterrorism ability...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825113009-xmjll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-COUNTERTERRORISM (PIX):After Taliban takeover, concerns mount over U.S. counterterrorism ability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam to pay recovered COVID patients to help in hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825091730-ytc07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIETNAM (PIX):Vietnam to pay recovered COVID-19 patients to help in hospitals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital detox: Can taking break from tech improve well-being?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825035945-ws30l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic fuels tech fatigue, researchers cast doubt on the benefits of a 'digital detox'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias hidden in mortgage-approval algorithms?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-technology-business-race-and-ethnicity-mortgages-2d3d40d5751f933a88c1e17063657586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new four-bedroom house in Charlotte, North Carolina, was Crystal Marie and Eskias McDaniels’ personal American dream, the reason they had moved there from pricey Los Angeles. A lush, long lawn, 2,700 square feet of living space, gleaming kitchen, and a neighborhood pool and playground for their son, Nazret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Cities Pitch Wall Street-Style Sign-On Bonuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/desperate-us-cities-pitch-wall-street-style-sign-on-bonuses/ar-AANJ0eS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The labor constraints jeopardize essential services such as trash pick-up, and exacerbate shortages in demanding jobs like 911 dispatchers that predated the Covid-19 crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Drought Crushing Ranchers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/25/the-worst-thing-i-can-ever-remember-how-drought-is-crushing-ranchers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOWNER, N.D. — Darrell Rice stood in a field of corn he’d planted in early June, to be harvested in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIRVANA Sued by Baby From Album Artwork for Child Pornography...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/nirvana-sued-by-baby-from-nevermind-album-artwork-for-child-pornography/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spencer Elden is suing the band for child sexual exploitation, saying he was unable to consent to having his image used for the iconic 1991 album</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pain compliance': Video shows trooper pummeling Black man...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-louisiana-monroe-ronald-greene-6c56ef6f5f3bc413d150737bf705e944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONROE, La. (AP) — Graphic body camera video kept secret for more than two years shows a Louisiana State Police trooper pummeling a Black motorist 18 times with a flashlight — an attack the trooper defended as “pain compliance.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student athletes wear ANKLE MONITORS so they can be alerted if another player tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9924171/Washington-State-high-schools-faces-controversy-asking-students-wear-COVID-ankle-monitors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents have deemed Eatonville High School's decision to implement COVID-19 trackers as 'intrusive and overreaching,' as school say they are 'proximity monitors' not trackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly $5 TRILLION spending plans win key House vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-democrats-advance-bidens-almost-204659880.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Joe Biden's plans to spend nearly $5 trillion to change the world's largest economy advanced in the House of Representatives on Tuesday, after Democratic leaders reached an agreement with centrist lawmakers to end a dispute threatening the bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil detains two travelers for perching atop iconic Christ statue...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-detains-two-french-travelers-002624464.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian authorities have detained two French men for watching the sun rise over Rio de Janeiro from the top of the iconic Christ the Redeemer statue while the monument was closed, one of the travelers told AFP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury, disgust that thousands will be left behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/fury-disgust-cia-pentagon-congress-thousands-afghans-will-be-left-n1277552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evacuations are likely to slow greatly by Friday to give U.S. troops time to withdraw. That's not enough time to evacuate all the Afghans who helped the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two House members make unauthorized trip to Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/two-congress-members-make-unauthorized-trip-to-kabul-amid-evacuation-efforts/ar-AANHPju?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps. Seth Moulton (D-Mass.) and Peter Meijer (R-Mich.), who both served in Iraq before being elected to Congress, returned home via a U.S. military flight used for evacuating U.S. citizens, allies and vulnerable Afghans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Attorney General's own agency produces report clearing him of bribery...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/08/24/texas-ag-ken-paxtons-own-agency-produces-report-clearing-him-bribery-abuse-of-office-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton’s office released a report Tuesday claiming to clear him of allegations that he repeatedly misused his power to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST US TROOPS START TO LEAVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/afghanistan-news-taliban-refugees-08-24-21/h_c4ad841c86a6d6123a9d5615bb97588d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one week after the Taliban takeover of Kabul, the situation at the capital's airport has become increasingly desperate as thousands still wait to depart the country. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's causing worst die-off of manatees? Starvation from Florida ecosystem collapse...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-08-worst-die-off-manatees-starvation-florida.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manatee deaths reported in the past half-century include nearly 5,000 from boat strikes, water structures and red tides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes DOUBLES among American youth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824220833-ug1b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HEALTH/DIABETES-YOUTH (PIX):Diabetes surges among American youth, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia gov. deploys National Guard medical staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/governor-deploys-national-guard-troops-hospitals-across-state/577SPPRU45HQTA7X3D7HBKRS5E/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The members of the Georgia National Guard are being deployed to hospitals across the state to assist hospital staff as emergency rooms near capacity because of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO SHOWS PARIS POLICE CHECKING BAR CODES...</title>
      <link>https://vm.tiktok.com/ZMRjpFGfV/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;vm.tiktok.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XposeTheCxntz (@xposethecxntz) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Police in Paris patrolling coffee shops scanning COVID passports 🤯 #woketok #STAYWOKE #covidvaccinesideeffects #spikeprotein #covidpassport #fypシ | Paris police scanning covid passports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahamas hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.travelandleisure.com/travel-news/cdc-adds-bahamas-level-4-travel-warning-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.travelandleisure.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention raised six more destinations to its highest warning level on Monday, including popular vacation hotspot the Bahamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SOAR MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/23/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks were marginally higher Tuesday following a broad-based rally on the first fully approved Covid-19 vaccine and ahead of the Fed summit this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices hit new record highs...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/569233-new-home-sales-tick-higher-as-prices-hit-new-record-highs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New home sales ticked higher in July while prices climbed to another record high, according to data released Tuesday by the Census Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAFD captain attacks city's vaccination requirement, prompting internal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lafd-captain-attacks-citys-vaccination-120021975.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles fire captain, Cristian Granucci, recorded a video of himself criticizing the city's COVID-19 vaccination requirement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Suppliers Having Trouble Keeping Shelves Stocked...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-food-suppliers-having-trouble-183524384.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some of the largest U.S. food distributors are reporting difficulties in fulfilling orders as a lack of workers weighs on the supply chain. Sysco Corp., North America’s largest wholesale food distributor, is turning away customers in some areas where demand is exceeding capacity. The company also said prices for key goods such as chicken, pork and paper products for takeout packaging are climbing amid tight supplies. In particular, production has slowed for high-demand, labor-inte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $3.5 TRILLION budget after deal with moderates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/house-passes-budget-blueprint-0a1258e07b1a8b9aeddb69980093c838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Striking a deal with moderates, House Democratic leaders muscled President Joe Biden’s multitrillion-dollar budget blueprint over a key hurdle Tuesday, ending a risky standoff and putting the party’s domestic infrastructure agenda back on track.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 leaders can't sway Biden to delay Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-afghanistan-g-7-summit-13631be5beba847935719ec4d8a4d5ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States clashed with some of its closest allies Tuesday over President Joe Biden’s insistence on sticking to an Aug. 31 Afghanistan withdrawal date that will shut down a frantic international evacuation effort from Taliban rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As chaos unfolds, White House projects calm: 'Gaslighting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/24/biden-afghanistan-evacuation-chaos-506753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t think the president’s rhetoric matches the conditions on the ground,” one former State Department official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA cancels annual meeting due to concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-texas-coronavirus-pandemic-b340c4bec89088fa69032c0ea84963f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The National Rifle Association announced Tuesday it has canceled its annual meeting, which had been set to be held next month in Houston, due to concerns over COVID-19. The NRA’s meeting had been set for Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passed out man found with 300 ballots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-95b6935d64ab60da519e2296d46df99a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORRANCE, Calif. (AP) — California authorities are investigating why a man found passed out in a car had more than 300 unopened mail-in ballots for the gubernatorial recall election. The man was arrested Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Early Test Case' for China-Led World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-early-test-case-for-a-china-led-world/ar-AANFZIY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing’s policies now that the Taliban is in charge will provide clues as to how it views global leadership.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
