<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wolf-colonized island gives new insights into predator and prey relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/wolf-population-moose-research-predator-prey-isle-royale-rcna24485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan's Isle Royale has been the perfect fishbowl for wolf research. A new study from the island shows wolves may actually help the animals they prey on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky says he'll meet Blinken, Austin in Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/zelensky-blinken-austin-kyiv-ukraine-meeting-74bb88da-9d98-4123-a8c9-013da4dc4d3e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They will be the highest ranking U.S. officials to visit Ukraine since the start of Russia's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Special Forces in Ukraine?</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-23/russia-investigates-media-report-on-presence-of-british-sas-special-forces-in-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE BRACES</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220423-france-braces-for-le-pen-macron-showdown </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push to ascend to House speaker relies on ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-covid-health-kevin-mccarthy-donald-trump-d60b2af63d5023584cc06b86b3b54e54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAKERSFIELD, Calif. (AP) — The next speaker of the U.S. House could very well hail from California — not Nancy Pelosi’s slice of the Golden State, but the other California, Donald Trump’s California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Washington TIKTOKer is getting people to reveal their salaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-washington-tiktoker-is-getting-people-to-reveal-their-salaries/ar-AAWwaTO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime spikes in Manhattan's trendy neighborhoods...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/23/nyc-crime-spikes-in-manhattans-east-and-west-villages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major crimes are surging in both the East and West villages, turning Manhattan’s once iconic arts and culture hubs into cesspools of rampant property thieves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In election misinformation fight, '2020 changed everything'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-voting-rights-technology-business-social-media-f5ba340c7a98f6f058fb3afac74a26bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Beth Bowers grew up in the 1960s and 1970s with parents who marched in protests, wrote letters to members of Congress and voted in elections big and small. Her father, a World War II veteran, and her mother, an educational counselor, did not use social media sites in their lifetimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow preparing to deploy devastating 'Satan 2' nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18349839/russia-deploy-satan-2-nuclear-missiles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA is preparing to deploy its devastating intercontinental ballistic missile, dubbed ‘Satan 2’, by this autumn, the country’s military has claimed. Dmitry Rogozin, head of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI tool accurately predicts tumur regrowth in cancer patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2022/apr/23/cancer-ai-tool-predicts-tumour-regrowth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Tool predicts how likely tumours are to grow back in cancer patients after they have undergone treatment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys forced to ride dogs and motorbikes in sickening 'Torture Island' circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkeys-forced-ride-dogs-twisted-26778718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: DISTRESSING CONTENT: Monkeys are being forced to participate in sickening stunts, including swimming races, at a tourist resort in Vietnam while animals are paraded in front of crowds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers met with him on election schemes...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lawmakers-meadows-election-aide-testifies-4a83238e-36d2-421a-8d79-bf451e5b29f0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former White House chief of staff was allegedly warned that there could be violence on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robberies of mail carriers rise dramatically with no signs of abating...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/-need-protection-mail-carriers-sound-alarm-surge-robberies-rcna25147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between 2018 and 2021, robberies of letter carriers more than tripled, and robberies involving a gun more than quadrupled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: The intoxication of power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/kevin-mccarthy-and-the-intoxication-of-power/ar-AAWweBH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1-million milestone: Orange County median home price hits seven figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/dollar1-million-milestone-orange-county-median-home-price-hits-seven-figures/ar-AAWvPm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy scrambles to contain fallout from leaked tape on Trump and Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gop-rep-kevin-mccarthy-scrambles-090049697.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republican leader Kevin McCarthy, Calif., and GOP allies are scrambling to contain the damage from new leaked audio recordings around Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election chief threatened by Republican leader seeking illegal access to voting equipment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-local-election-chief-threatened-154811452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Republican Party leader in North Carolina threatened to get a county elections director fired or have her pay cut unless she helped him gain illegal access to voting equipment, the state elections board told Reuters. The party official, William Keith Senter, sought evidence to support false conspiracy theories alleging the 2020 election was rigged against former U.S. President Donald Trump. Senter, chair of the Surry County Republican Party, told elections director Michella Huff that he would ensure she lost her job if she refused his demand to access the county's vote tabulators, the North Carolina State Board of Elections said in written responses to questions from Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poop pill could be secret to crushing it at gym?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/23/poop-pill-could-be-the-secret-to-crushing-it-at-the-gym/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Created by looking at the eco-systems of high-performing athletes, a new probiotic pill may be the key to handling certain diseases and lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Le Pen Territory, Anger at Distant President...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/23/in-le-pen-territory-as-france-votes-anger-at-a-distant-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. RÉMY-SUR-AVRE, France — Eternal France, its villages gathered around church spires, its fields etched in a bright patchwork of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel closes crossing to Gaza workers after new rocket attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20220423-israel-closes-crossing-to-gazans-in-response-to-new-rocket-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel said it will close its only crossing from the Gaza Strip for workers on Sunday in response to overnight rocket fire, stopping short of conducting retaliatory strikes in an apparent bid to ease…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's censors scrub viral Shanghai lockdown video from online platforms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220423-china-s-censors-scrub-viral-shanghai-lockdown-video-from-online-platforms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A viral video showing the impact of the prolonged coronavirus lockdown on Shanghai's residents has been taken down by China's internet censors Saturday, triggering an online backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discreetly, Young in Japan Chip Away at Taboo on Tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/23/discreetly-the-young-in-japan-chip-away-at-a-taboo-on-tattoos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — Ayaka Kizu, a web designer in Tokyo, stood by her office desk one recent day, peeling Band-Aids off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time to Head for Lifeboats': Dem Fatalism Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/its-time-to-head-for-the-lifeboats-democratic-fatalism-intensifies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The collective mood of Democratic insiders has darkened appreciably in recent weeks. Pollsters and prognosticators are forecasting increasingly dire results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl, 4, dies after forced to drink whiskey by her grandmother...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/girl-4-dies-being-forced-010200669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana woman who wanted to teach her 4-year-old granddaughter a lesson about drinking forced her to drink half a bottle of whiskey, police in Baton Rouge said. The girl, China Record, died Thursday of acute alcohol poisoning. Investigators said that her grandmother, 53-year-old Roxanne Record, forced her to finish a bottle of whiskey while the girl’s mother, 29-year-old Kadjah Record, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman formerly held at Fort Worth prison could be 1st to receive gender-affirming surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.fltimes.com/news/nation/woman-formerly-held-at-fort-worth-prison-could-be-1st-to-receive-gender-affirming-surgery/article_b6f270a7-737a-589b-a492-3d29c89ba0aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas — A judge has ordered the Bureau of Prisons to schedule gender-affirmation surgery for a transgender woman who has experienced repeated delays in receiving treatment, including when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Florida's rapid-fire smackdown of DISNEY even legal? Experts raise questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/is-florida-s-rapid-fire-smackdown-of-disney-even-legal-experts-raise-questions/article_66e1494a-1bd0-5309-ae9d-bb265d290b57.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — In four days, the proposals went from drafts to law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot rats to search for survivors at disaster sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5184115/robot-rats-may-soon-be-unleashed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBOT rats may soon be unleashed to search for survivors at disaster sites as researchers continue to develop the technology. It comes as scientists have unveiled a mechanic critter named SQuRo (sm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women who jog enjoy more intense orgasms...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/5184035/women-jog-more-intense-orgasms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOMEN who jog enjoy more intense orgasms —   and the further they go  the better the climax. Experts say running strengthens pelvic muscles involved in the big O and helps improve blood flow to vit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sets self on fire in front of Supreme Court building...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/us-news/northeast/man-sets-himself-on-fire-in-front-of-supreme-court-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsnationnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police responded to a man setting himself on fire in front of the Supreme Court building Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon compares Bill Gates to pregnant man emoji...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10745545/Elon-Musk-likens-Bill-Gates-controversial-pregnant-man-emoji-scathing-tweet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk dissed Bill Gates' gut on Twitter today, posting a photo of the Microsoft mogul alongside Apple's controversial pregnant man emoji 'in case you need to kill a boner.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows had been warned of violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-steve-bannon-donald-trump-mark-meadows-congress-1c77eda3332af497c866bab774d26fad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former White House official told the House committee investigating the Capitol riot that President Donald Trump's chief of staff, Mark Meadows, had been advised of intelligence reports showing the potential for violence, according to just-released transcripts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight over vaccine column could kill one of the oldest alt-weeklies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-fight-over-a-vaccine-column-could-kill-one-of-the-oldest-alt-weeklies/ar-AAWv9mB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene 'can't remember' if she urged martial law...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/greene-says-she-can-t-remember-if-she-urged-trump-to-impose-martial-law/ar-AAWu0Ml?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small towns see biggest boom of new pandemic-era residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2667070?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bend, Oregon, is in the middle of nowhere — 2 1/2 hours from Eugene over a mountain pass that can be treacherous even in springtime. And that’s what people like about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service rush to remove Pence from besieged Capitol becomes 'coup' focus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/secret-service-rush-to-evacuate-pence-from-besieged-capitol-becomes-coup-focus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence's pivotal decision to refuse Secret Service agents trying to evacuate him from the Capitol as threatening rioters charged into the building is taking center stage as the select Jan. 6 committee prepares to address the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan claims massive subscriber boost due to controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/joe-rogan-spotify-subscribers-1235134232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The podcaster says his recent headlines gained him 2 million new Spotify listeners, though sources counter that his subscriber growth has been consistent.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
