<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of new fires in Brazil as Amazon outrage grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hundreds-fires-brazil-amazon-outrage-grows-141009002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of new fires are raging in the Amazon rainforest in northern Brazil, official data showed Saturday, amid growing international pressure on President Jair Bolsonaro to put out the worst blazes in years. Official figures show 78,383 forest fires were recorded in Brazil so far this year, the highest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haley-Pence rivalry heats up as GOP weighs post-Trump future...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/24/haley-pence-rivalry-post-trump-1474377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews with top Republicans reveal they're watching each other warily ahead of a potential 2024 showdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST CRIME IN SPACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7390353/NASA-investigates-claims-astronaut-accessed-spouses-bank-account-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decorated astronaut Anne McClain (far left and far right) is accused of accessing estranged wife Summer Worden's (in black) bank account as part of a campaign to gain custody of her son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIARRITZ BRACED!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7389913/Trump-opens-G7-slap-leaders-calling-friends-part.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump threw shade at some of America's closest partners on Friday evening, mere hours before he'd see them in Biarritz at the Group of Seven summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: APPLE Contractors Listening to 1000 Siri Customer Recordings a Day...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201908241076625393-each-apple-contractor-listening-1000-siri-customer-recordings-day/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contractors hired by Apple reportedly listened to more than 1,000 Siri recordings per shift containing private information of the company’s customers, before Apple suspended the internal project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Dems regret not voting in '16 -- sure to cast ballot in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Some-Pa-Democrats-regret-not-voting-in-2016-14375503.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA - The Rev. Alyn E. Waller, a senior pastor at Enon Tabernacle Baptist Church in Philadelphia, believes African American voters in his city hold the key to the White House.  After backing a Democrat for president since 1988, Pennsylvania swung behind Donald Trump in 2016, helping to propel him to the presidency with a dramatic turnout of supportive white voters while the turnout of black Democratic voters in urban areas fell.  Hillary Clinton easily won the vote in Philadelphia, but the drop-off from prior elections left her unable to offset white Republican votes coming from more rural and conservative parts of the state.  It was a moment not lost on Trump. During a rally in Pennsylvania in December 2018, he praised black Americans for staying at home. "They didn't come out to vote for Hillary," he said. "They didn't come out. And that was a big - so thank you to the African American community." He also has often lauded his rural supporters for their high turnout.  Overall, turnout of black voters fell from nearly 67 percent in 2012 - during the reelection of the nation's first African American president - to less than 60 percent in 2016 while the white percentage rose incrementally, according to a Pew Research study.  In Pennsylvania, exit polls showed, the percentage of the vote cast by African Americans, who overwhelmingly sided with Clinton, dropped from 13 percent in 2012 to 10 percent in 2016. White voters, who went dramatically for Trump, rose from 78 percent to 81 percent of the electorate.  Interviews with black and white voters in the state show that a different dynamic may already by in play - on both sides.  Arresting the slide in black turnout and cutting into Republican advantages among white and rural voters is seen by Democrats as key to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town devastated by wildfire savors high school football win...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/223ca2c17b694a1f9a416f14dc46e1c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARADISE, Calif. (AP) — It's hard to recognize Paradise. It is heaps of melted metal. It is scorched pine trees. It is a place where things used to be, before a fire destroyed nearly 19,000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global disputes set to jolt summit in French resort...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190824110110-tsz6t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Global disputes set to jolt G7 summit in French resort</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters beat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/24/hong-kong-fresh-rallies-as-protesters-target-airport-transport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teargas thrown at masked protesters angry over lamp posts equipped with sensors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Farmers Union condemns: 'Making things worse'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/trade/458641-national-farmers-union-condemns-new-tariffs-trump-is-making-things-worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Farmers Union (NFU) on Friday hammered President Trump over his escalating trade war with China, saying he is “making things worse.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Crime in Space? Astronaut Accessed Estranged Spouse Bank Account From ISS...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/201908241076627686-first-crime-in-space-astronaut-reportedly-accessed-her-estranged-spouses-bank-account-from-iss/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The astronaut's spouse, ex-Air Force intelligence officer Summer Worden, filed a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission claiming that NASA astronaut Anne McClain had committed identity theft, even though she saw no indication that her funds had been spent or moved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Rips Up Agenda for G-7 in Fit of Climate Fury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-opposes-macron-threat-block-164247790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. Emmanuel Macron has gone off script.It took the French president less than 24 hours to wrong foot his closest partners and toss a curve ball into the buildup to the Group of Seven summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hong Kong police fire tear gas as clashes return to city streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-police-fire-tear-gas-clashes-return-094621442.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong riot police on Saturday fired tear gas and baton-charged protesters who retaliated with a barrage of stones, bottles and bamboo poles, as a standoff in a working-class district descended into violence. The city has been gripped by three months of street protests that started against a proposed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Flame Throwing Unsettles Base...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-amazon-flame-throwing-unsettles-120000674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As Europeans threaten to block access to Brazilian exports over President Jair Bolsonaro’s environmental policies, some of the agribusiness players loyal to the former Army captain are starting to fret about the consequences of his rhetoric.French President Emmanuel Macron issued the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian capsule carrying robot fails space station docking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a39432b400664260be02058443ad2f0f </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A Russian space capsule carrying a humanoid robot has failed to dock as planned with the International Space Station. A statement from the Russian space agency Roscosmos said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift says Trump 'gaslighting American public'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/aug/23/taylor-swift-trump-thinks-his-presidency-autocracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: songwriter discusses her political awakening in a Guardian interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate: Michigan city should be as white 'as possible'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ba35f94a280648dfb1cf7e7af9712689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARYSVILLE, Mich. (AP) — A city council candidate in Michigan said Friday she has no plans to end her campaign after shocking a public forum when she said she wants to keep her community white "as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew scared to return to USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9788445/prince-andrew-never-return-to-us-jeffrey-epstein-lawsuits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew is “frustrated” because he fears he will not be able to return to the US due to the Jeffrey Epstein scandal, reports claim. The Duke of York is reportedly worried he may be drawn into…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bans pro-Trump news outlet from buying ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/epoch-times-begins-hiding-its-connection-huge-pro-trump-ad-n1045416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By hiding its multimillion-dollar dark money ad spend, the organization bypassed Facebook's political advertising transparency rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-9 found dead in Long Beach officer's hot patrol car...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/k-9-found-dead-in-long-beach-officers-hot-patrol-car/ar-AAGePD9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 40 wild burros slaughtered in the Southern California desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/more-than-wild-burros-slaughtered-in-the-southern-california-desert/article_146cb0db-762f-5432-895d-75b0c168a5e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — More than 40 wild burros have been found shot and killed along the Interstate 15 near the California-Nevada border, federal officials said on Friday, and they’ve offered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills realtor busted for breaking into celebrity homes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/23/beverly-hills-realtor-busted-for-breaking-into-celebrity-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Beverly Hills real estate agent and another man are accused of burglarizing the homes of celebrities, including Usher and Adam Lambert, often during open houses in tony Los Angeles neighborhoods,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another bizarre painting found in ranch...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/23/another-bizarre-painting-found-in-jeffrey-epsteins-new-mexico-ranch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein didn’t limit his tacky art collection to his Upper East Side townhouse — his multimillion-dollar New Mexico ranch was home to a “creepy” painting depicting a young girl wearing a we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Franken Seeks Return to Public Eye...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/al-franken-seeks-paid-speaking-184613301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Al Franken is ready to make his comeback.After resigning from the U.S. Senate at the beginning of 2018 due to sexual-harassment allegations, the comedian is working with Hollywood firm United Talent Agency to make paid public speeches. The agency sent an email this week pitching Franken</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domingo to return to the stage amid harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eaee868d9e7e467ca9f9a29d7c7e289c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Placido Domingo returns to the stage at the Salzburg Festival this weekend to perform for the first time since multiple women accused the opera legend of sexual harassment in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dem field: Narrowing but unwieldy, unpredictable...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7465d05d4904f9fb8455aa770ecc6a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The Democratic presidential field is shrinking but not quickly enough to ward off the prospect of a long, bruising fight for the nomination. Three candidates dropped out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -623</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf9913be052d442e9df282cf222039d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average plunged more than 600 points Friday after the latest escalation in the trade war between the U.S. and China rattled investors. The broad sell-off sent the S&amp;P 500...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic team facing big test... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae2070e1b65d4573bb916932fe675ef3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing a trade war against China that has shaken the global economy, President Donald Trump gathered his most trusted economic aides in the Oval Office. The assembled brain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi says public doesn't support impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/347a9835cb994b16915df056f39ab4d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi still isn't ready to launch impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump. Pelosi told House Democrats on a conference call Friday, "The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work on more replacement wall starts in AZ, NM...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/316aebde39764098922d8df48942c989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA TERESA, N.M. (AP) — Work crews in Arizona and New Mexico forged ahead Friday with construction of taller border fencing funded through a national emergency declaration by President Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axelrod warns Supreme Court vacancy fight would 'tear country apart'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/rbg-scare-david-axelrod-warns-supreme-court-vacancy-fight-could-tear-this-country-apart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That didn't take long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA LAUNCHES ANOTHER ONE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9788393/north-korea-launch-ballistic-missile-over-sea-of-japan-us-military-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea has test fired a ballistic missile over the Sea of Japan, US and Japanese officials have said. The latest test comes just a week after two missiles were launched into the same area and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global worry over Amazon fires escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/aug/23/amazon-fires-global-leaders-urged-divert-brazil-suicide-path</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say international pressure may be only way to sway Bolsonaro government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg Undergoes MORE Cancer Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/08/23/753699013/justice-ruth-bader-ginsburg-underwent-another-round-of-cancer-treatment-this-sum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 86-year-old justice just wrapped up weeks of treatment after a new cancerous tumor was found on her pancreas. Doctors say there's no evidence of cancer elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malignant...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/ruth-bader-ginsburg-underwent-treatment-tumor-pancreas-supreme-court-says-n1045891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 86-year-old justice missed oral arguments in January for the first time in her years on the court recuperating from a previous cancer scare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reshaped American Politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/david-koch-billionaire-conservative-activist-philanthropist-dies-79-n1045696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He and his brother, Charles Koch, helped to build a massive conservative network of donors to support libertarian-leaning economic policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hits soybeans, autos and other products in key swing states...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/escalation-in-us-china-trade-war-threatens-global-economy-poses-trump-reelection-risk-2019-08-23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American cars, soybeans and oil largely produced in key swing states have been targeted for additional import tariffs by China, marking the latest volley in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY TO RUMBLE</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/23/rising-tariffs-tanking-stocks-inside-trumps-trade-battle-with-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday “ordered” US companies to find “an alternative to China” for doing business after the country slapped more retaliatory tariffs on US imports, sending the stock market into…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Newspaper cost-cutting persists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhregister.com/news/article/As-Gannett-GateHouse-merge-newspaper-14374389.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) - Just a week after announcing its $1.4 billion acquisition of Gannett , GateHouse Media was again laying off journalists and other workers at its newspapers, possibly foreshadowing the future awaiting employees of what will become the largest U.S. newspaper company.  GateHouse and Gannett say the merger will allow GateHouse to accelerate its newspapers' move to digital while paying down huge sums GateHouse borrowed in order to fund the acquisition. But it's unclear exactly how it will make that happen.  Last week, more than two dozen newsroom employees and other workers were reportedly laid off at 10 newspapers, from Providence, Rhode Island, to Brockton, Massachusetts, to Oklahoma City. The Associated Press confirmed several of these layoffs with the affected employees, others in their newsrooms or union representatives. GateHouse did not announce the workforce reductions, and neither the company nor its owner, New Media, had any comment for this story.  Gannett also declined to comment, but pointed to previous public statements by New Media CEO Mike Reed in which he said the merged company would "not only preserve but actually enhance quality journalism."  The latest layoffs may not be directly related to the merger. GateHouse also reportedly laid off dozens of employees in May and this winter. Its earnings reports show that revenue is declining when the impact of acquisitions is stripped out.  Further newsroom cuts show that "GateHouse doesn't have a vision for growing revenue, only cutting costs," charged Andrew Pantazi, a reporter at the Florida Times-Union, a GateHouse paper in Jacksonville, Florida, and the head of a union chapter there. "Eventually they'll run out of costs to cut."  Many in the newsrooms and the communities that depend on those newspapers are mourning the changes wrought by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Sinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-dollar-sinks-as-trump-tweets-stoke-intervention-fears-2019-08-23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s latest Twitter attack on Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, accompanied with more complaints about the U.S. dollar, is stoking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Highest-Paid Actresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/maddieberg/2019/08/23/highest-paid-actresses-scarlett-johansson/#6d5037834b4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ten highest-paid actresses together earned $314.6 million—69% more than last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Exposure Confirmed At DISNEYLAND...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/08/23/measles-disneyland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female teenager visiting from New Zealand was infectious with the measles virus when she visited Disneyland and Disney California Adventure Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypersonic airliner: LA to Tokyo in under two hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/hypersonic-airliner-would-take-you-new-york-tokyo-under-two-ncna1042776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 300-passenger Stratofly MR3 would hit speeds of up to 5,400 miles an hour. Just don't expect to book a flight anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious pointy skulls shed new light on ancient rituals...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/mysterious-pointy-lengthened-skulls-discovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery of mystery pointy and lengthened skulls in Croatia is shedding new light on the region’s strange ancient rituals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA driver appears FAST ASLEEP as car zips along at 70 mph...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/video-appears-to-show-tesla-driver-asleep-at-the-wheel-on-i-5/5488646/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is not what you want to see while driving on the freeway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romance scam 'one of largest in US history'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/23/us/nigeria-romance-scam-arrests/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US prosecutors charged 80 people -- mostly Nigerians -- in the widespread conspiracy that defrauded $6 million from businesses and vulnerable elderly women. Seventeen people have been arrested so far mostly in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful Catholic Group Facing Allegations of Insurance Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/emaoconnor/knights-of-columbus-insurance-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knights of Columbus is being accused of inflating its numbers to appear more profitable to insurance companies — and some of its members say they’re paying the price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Franken Seeks Return to Public Eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-23/al-franken-seeks-paid-speaking-gigs-in-return-to-the-public-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Venomous Brown Recluse Found Inside Woman's Ear...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/08/23/doctors-find-spider-in-womans-ear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Susie Torres thought she had water in her left ear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severed cat head at Graydon Carter's home amid Epstein reporting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/23/vanity-fairs-graydon-carter-found-severed-cat-head-outside-home-amid-jeffrey-epstein-reporting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vanity Fair editor-in-chief Graydon Carter made a disturbing discovery on his front lawn — the severed head of a cat — just after he assigned a reporter to dig into Jeffrey Epstein’s alleged sexual…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to train against AI avatars...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/23/armys-close-combat-units-to-train-against-ai-avata/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army officials say an augmented reality training system created by Microsoft will be ready for prime time by 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite dangers, MO docs can OK marijuana for pregnant women...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/business/health-care/article234009157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg visits hospital for tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7387385/Ruth-Bader-Ginsburg-86-visits-hospital-tests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 86, was seen leaving the Howard Laboratory at the Memorial Sloan Kettering Hospital on the Upper East Side on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS XI ENEMY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/23/bad-sign-for-trade-talks-trump-calls-china-president-xi-enemy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My only question is, who is our bigger enemy, Jay Powell or Chairman Xi?" Trump wrote amid a series of tweets that rattled markets Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Deep Fake must be stopped before we no longer know what's real...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/opinion/jordan-peterson-deep-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can tell you from personal experience how disturbing it is to discover a website devoted to making fake audio clips of you — for comic or malevolent purposes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top publishers sue AUDIBLE for copyright infringement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2078e81c5ca42a9bcde6aeea678b129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some of the country's top publishers are suing Audible, citing copyright infringement as they ask a federal judge to enjoin the audiobook producer-distributor's planned use of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines Considering Flying U.S. F-35Bs Off of Japan Warships...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2019/08/23/marines-considering-flying-u-s-f-35bs-off-of-japans-largest-warships</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON – Officials in Tokyo have requested Marines deploy F-35B fighters aboard Japan’s largest warships, a U.S. defense official confirmed to USNI News on Friday. The service is now studying the feasibility of deploying short take-off vertical landing (STOVL) fighters from JS Izumo (DDH-183) and JS Kaga (DDH-184), Japan’s 24,000-ton big deck amphibious. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian President Abbas: Millions Of Fighters Will Take Over Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/pa-president-abbas-millions-of-fighters-will-take-over-jerusalem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PA President Mahmoud Abbas threatened this week that "million of fighters" would swarm Jerusalem and topple the Jewish state's capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS:  Trump 'Orders' American Businesses to Find Alternative to China...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190823155042-k15dh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA-TRUMP (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Trump presses U.S. companies to close China operations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -400</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/23/us-stocks-wall-street-monitors-speech-from-fed-chair-jerome-powell.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped after Donald Trump ordered that U.S. companies find alternatives to their operations in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair doesn't commit to deep interest rate cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Fed-Chair-Powell-vows-to-sustain-the-expansion-14373128.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON HOLE, Wyo. - Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said Friday that the trade war is a "complex, turbulent" situation and he vowed the central bank will "act as appropriate to sustain the expansion," suggesting another interest rate cut may be coming but not the large decline President Donald Trump has urged.  "Our economy is in a favorable place," Powell said, according to prepared remarks, but he added that there are "significant risks," especially from trade policy uncertainty.  Twice during his speech here at the Kansas City Fed's annual monetary policy symposium, Powell reiterated that the Fed's overriding goal is to ensure the economy continues to grow and the central bank would do what was necessary to make that happen.  "Our challenge now is to do what monetary policy can do to sustain the expansion so that the benefits of the strong jobs market extend to more of those still left behind," Powell said.  Trump has lashed out at the Fed almost daily, calling on Powell to lower interest rates a full percentage point from just shy of 2.25% now down to 1.25%, the type of action that is typically done when the economy is in a recession or dangerous situation.  "Now the Fed can show their stuff!," Trump tweeted shortly before Powell's speech Friday morning.  In his remarks, Powell repeatedly characterized the U.S. economy as in a good place with low unemployment, solid growth and strong consumer spending, painting a picture of an economy that could possibly use a small boost but does not need massive aid.  "The U.S. economy has continued to perform well overall, driven by consumer spending," Powell said. "It will be appropriate at times for us to tilt policy one way or the other because of prominent risks."  Wall Street investors now predict a 96% chance the Fed will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves, Tsujihara and Art of Hollywood Self-Sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/les-moonves-kevin-tsujihara-art-hollywood-sabotage-1233956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before the #MeToo era, there was a long tradition of Tinseltown executives destroying their own careers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEFFEN YACHT SNAPS BECOME TOP STATUS IN MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-david-geffens-yacht-photos-became-a-status-thing-hollywood-1233154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A voyage on Rising Sun is summer’s "most coveted" vacation for A-listers with Oprah Winfrey, Chris Rock, Steven Spielberg, Leonardo DiCaprio and even Jeff Bezos popping up on the mogul’s Instagram feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDMA, Or Ecstasy, Shows Promise As PTSD Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/mdma-or-ecstasy-shows-promise-as-a-ptsd-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MDMA, the psychoactive ingredient in the club drug known as molly or ecstasy, is being tested in combination with therapy as a treatment for severe trauma.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
