<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Sowell warns USA may not resist siren song of socialism: 'I wouldn't bet on it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/5/thomas-sowell-warns-us-may-not-resist-siren-song-o/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Sowell, a living legend in the field of economics, says he fears the U.S. may eventually succumb to the siren song of socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ailes biopic flops...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/divide-conquer-debut-ratings-second-smallest-audience-ae-calendar-year-1202569958/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divide &amp; Conquer: The Story of Roger Ailes notched 228K viewers in its debut on A&amp;E Sunday night – the cable net’s second smallest primetime audience of 2019 to date. That includes 52…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Oversight Committee, White House in standoff...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/house-oversight-committee-white-house-standoff-viewing-security/story?id=61455537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's White House and the oversight committee are in a standoff over viewing security documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN decorates restaurant to honor Chinese Communist hero...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-kfc-chinese-restaurant-lei-feng-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast food chain Kentucky Fried Chicken (KFC) launched a restaurant themed to honor Communist hero Lei Feng, ahead of the soldier's remembrance day Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More $100 bills in circulation than $1 bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-100-dollar-bill-mysteriously-popular-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago, the number of $100 bills lagged well behind $1 and $20 notes. But the tally has doubled since the end of the financial crisis; by 2017 the C-note had eclipsed the $1 to become the most widely distributed U.S. currency. Output is still climbing, and experts are perplexed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 'oldest' tattooing kit made from bones of dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-03-05/worlds-oldest-tattoo-kit-human-bones-tonga-archaeology/10872926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests tools thought to have been destroyed by the Canberra firestorm of 2003 were fashioned from the remains of ancient Tongan tattooists' ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Zucker refused to meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/national-association-of-black-journalists-calls-out-cnn-over-lack-of-diversity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organization also says CNN boss Jeff Zucker refused to meet with a NABJ delegation to discuss the issue when asked about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: NKorea rebuilding long-range rocket site...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/north-korea/north-korea-rebuilding-long-range-rocket-site-photos-show-n979721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos taken just 2 days after the Trump-Kim Hanoi summit show rebuilding at the Sohae Satellite Launching Station, North Korea's operational space launch facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit Card Debt Record $870 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-credit-card-debt-closed-2018-at-a-record-870-billion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Credit Card Debt Closed 2018 at a Record $870 Billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet lion mauls owner to death in back yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47454610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big cat was one of two held illegally by Michal Prasek, causing concern among local residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to seek 10 years of tax returns in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/05/democrats-plan-to-demand-trumps-tax-returns-in-about-two-weeks-1205449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s returns are unlikely to be released anytime soon, even once Democrats make their request. The administration is promising a fight in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Beats Fallon for First Time in Key Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/05/business/media/colbert-fallon-ratings-nielsen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS late-night host, who has led in total viewers for more than a year, beats his NBC rival for the first time in viewers 18 to 49 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Think Solved Mystery of Green Icebergs...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/news/scientists-may-soon-solve-century-old-mystery-of-green-icebergs-1777172/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most icebergs appear white or blue when floating in seawater, but since the early 1900s explorers and sailors have reported seeing peculiar green icebergs in certain parts of Antarctica. The strange green icebergs …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance broker subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/05/politics/trump-organization-aon-insurance-broker-subpoena-new-york/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Department of Financial Services has opened an inquiry into the Trump Organization's insurance practices, sending a subpoena Monday to the company's longtime insurance broker, according to a person familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33109: America's richest zip code not in NY or CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/bloomberg-analysis-this-is-americas-richest-zip-code.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the country's wealthiest zip code had an average annual income of $2.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black journalist group places CNN on 'special monitoring list'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/432714-black-journalists-group-places-cnn-on-special-monitoring-list-citing-lack-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Association of Black Journalists (NABJ) said Tuesday that it would place CNN on a "special media monitoring list," citing a lack of black representation among the network's leadership ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG: NO</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/michael-bloomberg-will-not-run-for-president-in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg will not run for president in 2020, the billionaire businessman said in a statement posted online on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Goes Easy on NCAA Convicts, Citing Widespread Corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-05/ex-adidas-official-two-others-sentenced-in-ncaa-bribery-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blood everywhere': Cruise ship rocked by extreme wind...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/05/blood-everywhere-cruise-ship-rocked-by-extreme-wind-gust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Norwegian Cruise Line is blaming a strong, sudden gust of wind for tilting the Norwegian Escape on Sunday night, an incident reportedly responsible for injuring multiple passengers. “Just befor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company offers to build 234 miles of border wall for $1.4 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/company-offers-to-build-234-miles-of-border-wall-for-1-4-billion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. company is offering to build 234 miles of President Trump's border wall for just $1.4 billion, a fraction of the $8 billion the Trump administration is hoping to use for that project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron declaration of love awkward scoop for Italy state TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190305-macron-italy-interview-rai-salvini</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aimed at healing a vicious spat between France and Italy, French President Emmanuel Macron’s interview on Italian television has shed light on the battle waged by Italy's ruling populist parties for control of the country’s state broadcaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intensity of Far-Left Protests Up...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/tennessee-gop-says-intensity-of-far-left-protests-has-increased/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican members of the Tennessee legislature say they are concerned about the increased willingness for physical confrontation exhibited by protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Saves Family From Carbon Monoxide Poisoning...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/cat-saves-florida-family-carbon-monoxide-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Central Florida couple is crediting Bella for saving their lives. Bella is not their daughter or their dog, she is their cat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suits and ties optional, GOLDMAN hedges dress code...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-world-work-goldman-sachs/suits-and-ties-now-optional-goldman-sachs-hedges-dress-code-idUSKCN1QM283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs Group Inc said on Tuesday that it is relaxing the dress code for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT: Agree 100% with keeping U.S. troops in Syria...</title>
      <link>chttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/trump-says-he-agrees-100-percent-keeping-u-s-troops-n979466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The End Of Recycling...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/03/china-has-stopped-accepting-our-trash/584131/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are consuming more and more stuff. Now that other countries won’t take our papers and plastics, they’re ending up in the trash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Median 1-BR Rent In San Fran Soars To $3,700 A Month...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/median-1-bedroom-rent-sf-3690-month-zumper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already known for outrageously high rents, the monthly rent in San Francisco has just hit a whole new level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau climate rally interrupted by melee, protester heckles...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/5021524/justin-trudeau-climate-rally-interrupted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Trudeau was speaking about Jane Philpott's resignation from cabinet. Then the heckling started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE PORN BLOCKED IN UK</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8565486/porn-uk-ban-unlock-card/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WATCHING free porn in Britain is about to get a lot trickier thanks to new rules that aim to protect children from online smut. As early as next month, porn sites will be required to get proof of I…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FDA Set to Approve Ketamine Nasal Spray for Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/03/04/700014137/fda-expected-to-approve-esketamine-nasal-spray-for-depression</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration is expected to approve a new type of drug for depression. It is esketamine, a chemical cousin of the anesthetic and party drug ketamine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff Hires Ex-Prosecutor to Lead Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/adam-schiff-hires-a-former-prosecutor-to-lead-the-trump-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the House Intelligence Committee is conducting an aggressive inquiry into the Trump campaign’s ties to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian couples flogged in front of crowd for having sex outside marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/six-young-couples-flogged-front-14090286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of men cheered and filmed the Sharia law punishment before one of the women was pictured limping away in tears in Aceh, Indonesia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media, comedy replace news as Maduro's grip on media blacks out turmoil in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/4/nicolas-maduro-media-control-censors-news-venezuel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news that Venezuelan residents watch and read depends on the whims of a regime that would rather not have them ponder whether they truly live in the democratic workers’ paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's saddest elephant' dies after 43 YEARS locked up in solitary confinement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8567026/worlds-saddest-elephant-dies-after-43-years-locked-up-in-solitary-confinement-at-spanish-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s saddest elephant has died after 43 YEARS locked up in solitary confinement at a Spanish zoo. Cordoba Zoo said that keepers awoke to “sad news of the death of our beloved elephant …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  Rio Carnival reveler dressed as Michael Jackson stuns crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8564032/rio-carnival-paedo-michael-jackson-costume/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RIO carnival reveller shocked crowds when he turned up at the spectacular parade in this Michael Jackson outfit. The Sae Clemente samba school performer attracted some strange looks as he cavorte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guy Trump Called 'Fat Jerry' Is Chairman Nadler Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-and-nadler-have-warred-for-years-but-the-stakes-have-never-been-higher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressman who stood his ground against the developer in New York is up against the president in Washington now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spacecraft Beresheet takes first selfie in space... </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Israeli-spacecraft-Beresheet-takes-first-selfie-in-space-582512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The selfie shows the Southern Hemisphere, and Australia can clearly be seen in the background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHT FRIGHT: 'Drop everything, evacuate immediately. Plane will explode'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6772417/Passengers-scramble-safety-flight-China-LA-forced-make-emergency-landing.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cabin on the plane from Beijing to Los Angeles was full of 'screams and panic' over a suspected fire in the baggage hold on the Air China Boeing 777.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Boss Talks League Growing Mental Health Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/sports/nba/2019/03/01/adam-silver-sloan-nba-unhappy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it’s a generational issue.’’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen asked about pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lawyer-for-cohen-approached-trump-attorneys-about-pardon-11551753372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Michael Cohen, Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer, raised the possibility of a pardon with attorneys for the president after federal agents raided Mr. Cohen’s properties in April, according to people familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influence of centrists fading fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/The-influence-of-centrist-Democrats-is-fading-13663777.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To state the obvious, the policy agenda of the Democratic Party has moved to the left. Ideas that used to be on the fringe - Medicare-for-all, guaranteed jobs and the Green New Deal, all financed by very progressive taxation - are now much more widely accepted by Democrats. Two possible theories explain this evolution: the old one from the center-left and the new one from the "leftier" left. The center left was/is essentially friendly, and largely deferential, to markets. Left to their own devices, financial markets will efficiently allocate excess savings to their most productive uses - so over-regulation is dangerous. Same with globalization. Taxes should be progressive, but not too much so or you'll dampen private investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke, a sheriff in Appalachian coal country struggles to provide law and order...</title>
      <link>https://www.officer.com/command-hq/news/21070781/kentucky-sheriff-struggles-to-provide-law-and-order-as-county-struggles-with-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.officer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With only one other paid law enforcement officer on staff now to help Martin County Sheriff John Kirk monitor a 231-square-mile area day and night, the department is stretched to its limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of dead West Point cadet retrieve his sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/parents-dead-west-point-cadet-retrieve-his-sperm-n979316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Military Academy Cadet Peter Zhu was declared brain dead Wednesday, four days after the California resident was involved in a skiing accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama tornado survivors reckon with 'Armageddon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.inforum.com/news/science-and-nature/981769-Alabama-tornado-survivors-reckon-with-Armageddon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inforum.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A couple and their grandson survive deadly tornadoes by sheltering under a mattress as their house disintegrated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CAPTAIN MARVEL' review: Mundane, unimaginative, bland; Lack of elan in every dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/captain-marvel-review-1192277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brie Larson stars as the titular hero in the Marvel adaptation, also featuring Samuel L. Jackson, Jude Law, Gemma Chan and Annette Bening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely to seek 10 years of tax returns in coming weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/House-Democrats-likely-to-seek-10-years-of-13663805.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Congressional Democrats are likely to request 10 years of President Donald Trump's tax returns in coming weeks, tailoring their inquiry in a way they hope will survive a court battle, according to according to lawmakers and others involved in the discussions. The exact parameters of the request are still in flux, including whether to seek tax returns related to Trump's many business enterprises in addition to his personal returns. But Democrats led by House Ways and Means Committee Chairman Richard Neal, D-Mass., along with congressional lawyers, are in the advanced stages of preparing the request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHANEL brings out stars to honor Lagerfeld final collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/chanel-brings-out-stars-honour-lagerfelds-final-collection-doc-1e83up4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN focus group rejects Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/432611-cnn-focus-group-rejects-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CNN focus group comprised of Democratic voters has rejected former Vice President Joe Biden as their presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities investigating swastikas scrawled in blood near Holocaust museum...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/04/blood-swastikas-la-brea-public-restroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating what they say may be a possible hate crime at a public restroom Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron first season in LA has become disaster...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/26137383/lebron-first-season-los-angeles-become-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lakers are on the verge of missing the playoffs in LeBron James' first season in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Hold Clues to Rise and Fall of Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8563177/sealed-maya-ritual-cave-untouched-for-1000-years-was-opening-to-the-underworld-and-is-filled-with-spooky-relics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ANCIENT ‘untouched’ Maya ritual cave has accidentally been discovered by archaeologists in Mexico who were actually searching for a sacred well. The cave is thought to have been seal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales of safe rooms, nuclear bunkers rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/luxury/dont-panic-sales-safe-rooms-nuclear-bunkers-rising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the daily news cycle leaves you wanting to batten down the hatches and wait for it all to blow over, you&amp;rsquo;re far from alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE patronage of Trump hotel rose sharply after merger announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/T-Mobile-patronage-of-Trump-s-DC-hotel-rose-13663614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - T-Mobile's patronage of President Donald Trump's hotel here increased sharply after last April's announcement of its merger with Sprint, with executives since spending about $195,000 at the property, the company told congressional Democrats in a letter last month. Before news of the megadeal between rival companies broke on April 29, 2018, the company said, only two top officials from T-Mobile had ever stayed at the Trump International Hotel Washington, with one overnight stay each in August 2017. But the day after the merger's announcement, nine of T-Mobile's top executives were schedule to check in, The Washington Post reported in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maya ritual cave 'untouched' for 1,000 years stuns archaeologists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/culture/2019/03/maya-ritual-balamku-cave-stuns-archaeologists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exploration of Balamku (Cave of the Jaguar God) reveals ancient religious practices—and may hold clues to the rise and fall of the Maya empire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: BUGATTI unveils most expensive new car ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/bugatti-unveils-the-most-expensive-new-car-ever-built.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only one version has been made and is already sold to a mystery owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Where pay most, least taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/2019/03/05/taxes-2019-where-income-sales-and-property-tax-highest-us/39124869/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the checkout counter to the 1040 form due every April, what Americans end up paying in taxes depends largely on where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dressed up, ready for fun: New Orleans celebrates Mardi Gras...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7761daf5827b44d5a08ce994637c8820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — The streets of New Orleans will be filled Tuesday with excited kids catching beads from atop ladders, revelers in fancy costumes walking through the French Quarter and Mardi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Who Couldn't Beat Climate Debate Now Seek to Join It...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/republicans-couldn-apos-t-beat-090000456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s just not worth the fight anymore,” Shimkus said in an interview when asked about his changing stance on climate change. Shimkus is among a number of Republicans who -- after years of sowing doubt about climate change or ignoring it altogether -- are scrambling to confront the science they once</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Trump White House lawyer calls Mueller 'hero'; Probe no witch hunt...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-white-house-lawyer-calls-mueller-american-hero/story?id=61455661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Congressional investigations into the White House, Ty Cobb said, "It's never gonna be over."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths from alcohol, drugs, suicide hit new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/03/05/suicide-alcohol-drug-deaths-centers-disease-control-well-being-trust/3033124002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths from alcohol, drugs and suicideÂ in 2017 hitÂ theÂ highest level since federal data collection started in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This man fasts 17 to 24 hours a day. It's changed his life...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/2019/03/04/weight-loss-approach-uses-intermittent-fasting-app-inspiration/2978617002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life Fasting Tracker app from LifeOmic helps users practice intermittent fasting, which advocates say helps with weight loss and increased wellness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Weighs Ending Phone Surveillance Program Exposed by Snowden...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nsa-weighs-ending-phone-surveillance-program-exposed-by-snowden-11551752806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency is considering ending a once-secret surveillance program that annually collects hundreds of millions of telephone call records, including those belonging to Americans, because it lacks operational value, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRODIGY lead singer found dead in home...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8561534/prodigy-keith-flint-suicide-marriage-split-home-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRODIGY star Keith Flint killed himself days after putting his beloved home up for sale — following a devastating split from his wife. The rave legend, 49, died at the Essex farmhouse he shared wit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron blasts Brexit as cause of Europe's biggest crisis since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6771177/Emmanuel-Macron-calls-Brexit-irresponsible-lie.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his most ferocious attack on Brexit to date, the French President said Britain's withdrawal was peddled by 'anger mongers and fake news' and 'offers nothing'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Calls for Online Jihad...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-supporters-around-the-world-rally-for-steep-escalation-in-online-jihad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jihadists urged to hit sites including Reddit, LinkedIn, Pinterest, Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Vine, and Snapchat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OPENS OBSTRUCTION PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1c319d8e4c943a482d03195d069e92a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats launched a sweeping new probe of President Donald Trump on Monday, an aggressive investigation that threatens to shadow the president through the 2020 election season...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of autosexual: People attracted to selves...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/shortcuts/2019/mar/04/age-of-the-autosexual-the-people-sexually-attracted-to-themselves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you turned on when you look in the mirror, and enjoy nothing more than a steamy night at home alone? You could be an autosexual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed keeps GDP growth view at 0.3%...</title>
      <link>https://www.streetinsider.com/Fed/Atlanta+Fed+leaves+U.S.+first+quarter+GDP+growth+view+at+0.3+percent/15211588.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.streetinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - The U.S. economy is growing at a 0.3 percent annualized rate in the first quarter, based on data on domestic construction spending in December released on Monday, the Atlanta Federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors announce second person 'cured' of HIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/03/04/second-person-effectively-cured-of-hiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time, doctors appear to have put HIV into “sustained remission” with a stem cell transplant — effectively curing the recipient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT's latest dog-like robot can do backflips on command...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/MIT-s-latest-dog-like-robot-can-do-backflips-on-13661951.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They can already open doors, traverse steep flights of stairs, run at high speed and unload your dishwasher. Now, for the first time ever, a four-legged robot has performed a physical feat that evades all but the most athletic among us: a backflip. The acrobatics arrive courtesy of Massachusetts Institute of Technology, where researchers have unveiled a springy, 20-pound robot that's also capable of walking either right-side up or upside down. The vaguely canine-like machine - dubbed "Mini Cheetah" - is also able to trot over uneven terrain about twice as fast as an average person's walking speed, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Patient Gives Hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-aids-cure/london-hiv-patient-becomes-worlds-second-aids-cure-hope-idUSKCN1QL2C0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An HIV-positive man in Britain has become the second known adult worldwide to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic freeze envelops lower 48...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/04/historic-cold-envelops-most-of-the-lower-48/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When this freakish cold spell is done, several hundred new record low maximum and record low temperatures will have fallen. In the last seven days alone, cold records are outpacing warm by about fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal crossings set to surge; 70,000 detained last month...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/After-cold-busy-month-at-border-illegal-13661974.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas - In a dusty lot along the U.S.-Mexico border fence, a single Border Patrol agent was stuck with few options and falling temperatures. A group of 64 parents and children had waded through a shallow bend in the Rio Grande to turn themselves in to the agent on the U.S. side. He radioed for a van driver, but there were none available. By 2 a.m., the temperature was 44 degrees. The agent handed out plastic space blankets. The group would have to wait. Mothers and fathers swaddled their families in the silvery, crinkling sheets and clustered with them on the ground, shushing the children. They shivered in the cold wind, and the sound of crying carried on, like a broken alarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on Trudeau as second minister resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190305-canada-trudeau-minister-philpott-resigns-snc-lavalin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a serious blow to Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, a second member of his Cabinet resigned on Monday, saying she had lost confidence in how the government had dealt with an escalating political scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Republicans make 'socialism' the bogeyman of 2020, as Democrats bristle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/03/04/trump-gop-make-socialism-bogeyman-2020-democrats-bristle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democrats bristle, but Republicans have successfully framed the 2020 election as a struggle against socialism - an ideology that not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fountain of youth? Scientists switch-off gene to DOUBLE lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/763449/immortality-science-genetics-roundworm-university-east-anglia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone post may violate gag?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6770935/Mueller-tells-judge-Framed-Roger-Stone-Instagram-pic-violate-gag-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new introduction to a re-issue of Stone's 2017 book, he writes: 'Mr. Mueller may frame me for some bogus charge in order to silence me or induce me to testify against the president.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Cameras Spot Shoplifters BEFORE Steal?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/the-ai-cameras-that-can-spot-shoplifters-even-before-they-steal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AI Cameras That Can Spot Shoplifters Even Before They Steal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMPLOYEES UNCOVER ONGOING CENSORED SEARCH WORK...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/03/04/google-ongoing-project-dragonfly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of employees said Google made hundreds of changes to smartphone apps for the controversial project, thought to be defunct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude 'Mona Lisa' may be by Leonardo, say experts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nude-mona-lisa-may-leonardo-experts-183816399.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nude drawing that bears a striking resemblance to the "Mona Lisa" was done in Leonardo da Vinci's studio and may be the work of the master himself, a French museum said Monday. Experts at the Louvre in Paris, where the world's biggest collection of Leonardo's work is held, have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers posing as immigration officials target victims for money and personal info...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/scammers-posing-law-enforcement-immigration-officials-steal-personal/story?id=61457495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scammers posing as immigration officials have targeted and attempted to extort victims for personal information and money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNT ME OUT</title>
      <link>http://westchester.news12.com/story/40067049/im-not-running-hillary-clinton-rules-out-2020-bid-for-first-time-on-camera-in-exclusive-interview-with-news-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;westchester.news12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton ruled out a 2020 presidential run for the first time on camera in an exclusive interview with News 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Teen spiked stepdad's drinks with cattle tranquilizer...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/wisconsin-tranquilizer-teen-872954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 4--A Wisconsin teenager accused of injecting cattle tranquilizer in his stepfather’s energy drinks thought his actions were “funny” and would not harm the victim, according to police who arrest</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
