<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Venom from sea snails could hold key to future painkillers...</title>
      <link>https://www.scotsman.com/health/scottish-scientists-say-venom-from-sea-snails-could-hold-key-to-future-painkillers-3633219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scotsman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlocking the secrets of the deadly venom produced by a poisonous sea snail could hold the key to developing better, less addictive painkillers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKROCK President Says 'Entitled Generation' Now Learning About Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/blackrock-kapito-says-scarcity-inflation-230000585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. President Rob Kapito warned that inflation is having dramatic effects on the economy, with an entire generation now learning what it means to suffer from shortages.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: U.S. Doubts Russian Pullback; Lavrov in ChinaUkraine Update: Kyiv Seeks Cease-Fire Deal in Russia TalksHome Prices Suggest Housing Bubble Brewing in U.S., Dallas Fed SaysThe Fed Has Made a U.S. Recession InevitableWorld’s Longest Passenger Flight Plans to Avoid Russ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No curfew in Miami's South Beach for last spring break weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/miami-beach-not-planning-spring-break-curfew-this-weekend-mayor/2724375/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Beach isn’t planning to have a curfew this coming weekend after rowdy spring break crowds and violence led officials to impose one this past weekend. Mayor Dan Gelber made the announcement during a virtual conference call Tuesday morning with Miami Beach’s Chamber of Commerce. “It won’t happen this weekend unless there’s some metric or something happens that changes our…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: You Eat Credit Card Worth Of Plastic Every Week, And It's Altering Your Gut...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/microplastics-food-gut-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent review suggests people consume about five grams of plastic particles per week — the equivalent of the weight of a credit card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliens 'abducting humans and living on Earth before invasion', prof claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/aliens-abducting-humans-living-earth-26590249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr David Jacobs has written a number of books on alien abductions, interviewing supposed subjects about their experiences, and he claims to have formed a sinister conclusion from their testimony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Some 'Super-Immune' to Covid?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/never-had-covid-you-may-hold-key-to-beating-the-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never Had Covid? You MayÂ Hold KeyÂ To Beating the Virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political battle lines form on Clarence Thomas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/600248-political-battle-lines-form-on-clarence-thomas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The simmering debate over Justice Clarence Thomas’s judicial ethics is shaping up as a midterm election issue, with lawmakers on both sides setting up their positions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill would fine socials for terrorist accounts...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/house-legislation-targets-social-media-platforms-that-allow-terrorist-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new piece of House legislation would mandate that social media platforms remove terrorist organizations and their supporters or face a $50,000 fine for every infraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECHO OF ERASED NIXON TAPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-7-hour-gap-in-Trump-s-calls-evokes-a-missing-17038428.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was chatter about a magazine and whether anybody read it, about a letter to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials bracing for unprecedented strains at Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-officials-bracing-for-unprecedented-strains-at-mexico-border-if-pandemic-restrictions-lifted/ar-AAVDUsm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK AND FEAR</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220330-in-israel-shock-and-fear-after-attack-in-central-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I was supposed to go to study today, but now I'm going to a funeral," laments Shlomo Alperin, 23, still in shock from witnessing the most violent attack in years in greater Tel Aviv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>META Fraud Suit Over Inflated Ad Metrics Gains Ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/meta-small-advertisers-win-class-action-status-in-fraud-suit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Small Advertisers Win Class-Action Status in Fraud Suit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating avocado twice week cuts risk of heart disease by fifth...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/eating-avocado-twice-week-cuts-082522674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No links were found between eating avocado and the risk of stroke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive flamingo seen on Texas coast 17 years after escaping Kansas zoo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/flamingo-escaped-kansas-zoo-2005-164816414.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of two flamingos that escaped from a Kansas zoo during a storm 17 years ago has been spotted on the coast of Texas, wildlife officials said. The Coastal Fisheries division of Texas Parks and Wildlife confirmed Tuesday to The Associated Press that the African flamingo — known as No. 492 because of the number on its leg band — was captured on video shot March 10 by an environmental activist near Port Lavaca, Texas, at Rhodes Point in Cox Bay. While the other flamingo was never seen again, No. 492 has been spotted several times in Wisconsin, Louisiana and Texas, sometimes with other wild flamingos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland to end oil imports; Germany warns on gas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-germany-0205525f2107f57e31b41d02e5a91e6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Poland announced steps Wednesday to end all Russian oil imports by the end of 2022, as Germany issued a warning over natural gas supplies and called on consumers to conserve energy in a sign of escalating economic tensions in Europe over Russia’s war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry, academy torn on how to handle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-industry-e2-80-94-and-the-academy-e2-80-94-are-torn-on-how-to-handle-will-smith-e2-80-99s-oscars-slap/ar-AAVDUsl </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid creeps closer to Biden as restrictions fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/covid-creeps-closer-to-biden-as-restrictions-fall/ar-AAVDckW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New wave of terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-702703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security forces conduct widespread arrest raid, map home of Bnei Brak killer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military wants AI to replace human decision-making in battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-military-wants-AI-to-replace-human-17035719.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a suicide bomber attacked Kabul International Airport in August last year, the death...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine strikes in Russia for first time...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/29/ukraine-missile-may-have-hit-military-camp-inside-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian forces may have struck back for the first time inside Russia with an artillery strike Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bolsters security as violence worsens...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/30/israel-bolsters-security-amid-deadliest-wave-of-terrorist-attacks-in-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BNEI BRAK, Israel — Israel security forces bolstered their presence across the country and the occupied territories early Wednesday, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin pledge to scale back in Ukraine draws skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-roman-abramovich-kyiv-europe-ef9c28c44f94b34262fe6b7c296d58a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russia's pledge to scale back some military operations in Ukraine drew skepticism, a bitter reality check in a rare moment of optimism five weeks into what has devolved into a bloody war of attrition .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith would face little more than slap if charged...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oscars-chris-rock-jada-pinkett-smith-entertainment-los-angeles-f2c8b77d6bc16dada3eb1d33b32b1908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Will Smith’s slap seen ’round the world at the Oscars was clearly a crime, legal experts say, but the chances of prosecution are slim and even if convicted he’d likely face little more than a slap of his own — on the wrist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Palestinian gunman kills 5 in Tel Aviv shootings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/islamic-state-group-israel-arrests-west-bank-tel-aviv-79e263b125e731302d4a89d1c483d423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli forces operating in the West Bank on Wednesday arrested five Palestinians allegedly involved in a deadly shooting attack in central Israel, where a Palestinian gunman on a motorcycle used an assault rifle to kill five people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California group votes to limit reparations to slave descendants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-legislature-a57cb7d1c8926c804b2cb384246e15c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California’s first-in-the-nation task force on reparations has decided to limit state compensation to the descendants of free and enslaved Black people who were in the U.S. in the 19th century, narrowly rejecting a proposal to include all Black people regardless of lineage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Of-Its-Kind Nasal Spray Could Be Available By Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nasal-spray-prevents-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their study discovered a small molecule that people can spray into their noses which prevents COVID from infecting human cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negotiators told not to eat or drink at talks amid poison concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-to-negotiators-don-t-eat-or-drink-at-russia-talks-amid-poison-concern/ar-AAVCM5Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON RECALLS 'BURNER PHONES'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-burner-phones-john-bolton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House records show a gap of over 7 hours in Trump's communication on January 6, and the former president said he's never heard of the phrase "burner phones."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused of harassing Tim Cook with pleas for sex...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-california-san-jose-apple-inc-7c9f8594a5f546fa7d69635662338562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — A woman accused of harassing Apple CEO Tim Cook with pleas for sex and other crude suggestions before showing up at his Silicon Valley home in a threatening manner last October agreed to stay away from him for the next three years under an agreement approved Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Tells J&amp;J Recipients To Get 2 mRNA Shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/if-you-got-j-26j-vaccine-consider-two-mrna-booster-shots-cdc-data-suggest/ar-AAVDrIO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA APPROVES 4TH JAB; 5TH COMING?</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/fda-approves-2nd-covid-19-vaccine-booster-for-those-50-and-older</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. regulators are allowing people 50 and older to get another booster dose of the Pfizer or Moderna COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army leader led child porn ring, risked US security...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2022/03/29/civilian-army-leader-led-child-porn-ring-risked-us-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Frodsham was a top civilian commander at a U.S. air base in Afghanistan when Army commanders ordered him home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Buying Drones, Armored Vehicles With Covid Funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkp8zg/police-are-buying-drones-and-armored-vehicles-with-covid-relief-funds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has encouraged more spending on police tech, despite local activists’ calls to fund life-sustaining food and housing programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/9. Record on triggering while trying to fix inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/29/federal-reserve-recession-inflation-rates-00021119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Fed begins a new round of rate increases to combat the worst inflation in 40 years, the central bank is once again sparking concern that it's doing too little too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cawthorn orgy comment sparks Republican frustration...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/600181-mccarthy-to-speak-to-cawthorn-after-orgy-comment-sparks-gop-frustration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) pledged to speak to Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS:  Le Pen closing gap on Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220329-french-far-right-leader-le-pen-closing-gap-on-macron-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran French far-right leader Marine Le Pen is closing the gap on President Emmanuel Macron ahead of a possible election duel between the two of them next month, two new polls show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not a Ceasefire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-29-22/h_724c88dcb604926363ebcdde88d7e21b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shelling has intensified around the suburbs of Kyiv, and Ukraine's deputy defense minister said Russian forces are attempting to establish a "corridor" around the Ukrainian capital to block supply routes. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US troops in Poland training Ukrainians...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/29/politics/us-troops-poland-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US troops in Poland have been providing Ukrainians with some instruction on how to use the weapons the West has been shipping into Ukraine, sources familiar with the matter tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intentional fire sparks renewed concerns at abandoned New Orleans skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/new-orleans-plaza-towers-intentional-fire/39124441#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent fire sparks renewed concerns at abandoned New Orleans skyscraper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ town sues woman, 82, for 'burdensome' public records requests...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/news/2022/03/nj-town-sues-woman-82-for-voluminous-and-burdensome-public-records-requests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elouise McDaniel, of Irvington, said she has a “legal right” to know the information she has requested from the town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Warren cheers Biden billionaires' tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/29/sen-elizabeth-warren-lauds-biden-billionaires-tax-calls-for-even-more-ceo-pay-changes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren praised the Biden administration's renewed effort to introduce a new tax on the country's wealthiest households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gervais mocks meltdown with alopecia joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/ricky-gervais-oscars-will-smith-1235121518/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British comedian posted a clip from his U.K. version of 'The Office' poking fun of the Will Smith-Chris Rock drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 3 Think He Should Be Charged With Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/poll-will-smith-charged-chris-rock-oscars-slap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new StudyFinds.com poll shows that two in three Americans think Will Smith should be actually be charged for slapping Chris Rock at the Oscars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor survives assassination attempt after he overslept...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukraine-mayor-survives-rocket-assassination-26580942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian cruise missile struck the Mykolaiv Regional State Administration building, leaving several missing and feared dead, but missed Vitaliy Kim, as he was at home asleep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Aerial Bombing Intensifies!</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2022-03-29/russia-begins-retreat-from-kyiv-in-major-strategy-shift-u-s-general</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with surprising opposition and bogged down supply lines, Russian President Vladimir Putin is repositioning his forces in an attempt to gain a more effective position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN 'WITHDRAWS' TROOPS FROM KYIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5001140/putin-withdrawing-troops-kyiv-losing-ukraine-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has said it is to “drastically reduce” forces near the Ukrainian capital Kyiv as its invasion continues to falter. The announcement was made by the Deputy Defence Minister Alexander Fomin an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual defense of war? Patriarch trying...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/spiritual-defense-war-ukraine-putins-090057639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriarch Kirill, a close ally of Vladimir Putin, has lent a spiritual justification for the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-President Asks Putin to Release Dirt on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-asks-putin-to-release-dirt-on-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump called on Russian President Vladimir Putin to release dirt on President Joe Biden amid Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly contagious Omicron subvariant now dominant in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/29/health/ba-2-dominant-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The highly contagious Omicron subvariant BA.2 is now the dominant strain of Covid-19 in the United States, causing an estimated 54.9% of all new Covid-19 infections last week, according to new data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen shrugs off health issues, attends Philip service...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/queen-elizabeth-ii-covid-entertainment-health-europe-06dd230e64e4cf7418149a428c4ffe1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II walked into Westminster Abbey through a side door Tuesday, making good on her wish to attend a service of thanksgiving for her beloved husband Prince Philip. The monarch entered the church on the arm of her second son, Prince Andrew, then separated from him to walk to her seat alone, easing concerns about her health that had raised questions about whether she would attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers still confident, but outlook not as rosy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prices-consumer-confidence-f284d6bbaff12f04ffc872143f659406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SILVER SPRING, Md. (AP) — U.S. consumer confidence bounced back in March and remains high, though consumers' short-term outlook is not quite as rosy. The Conference Board, a business research group, said Tuesday that its consumer confidence index — which takes into account consumers’ assessment of current conditions and their outlook for the future — rose to 107.2 in March from 105.7 in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'TOP GUN: MAVERICK' Trailer Teases Return of Val Kilmer's Iceman...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/top-gun-2-trailer-iceman-val-kilmer-tom-cruise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And he's got a job for his old pal Maverick</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL will require every team to have minority assistant coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/nfl-will-require-every-team-to-have-minority-coach-in-key-offensive-role/ar-AAVAgIN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Your Toilet Paper Is On...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/the-battle-for-your-toilet-paper-is-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Private Jets Take to Skies, Creating Gridlock on Ground...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/29/more-private-jets-take-to-the-skies-creating-gridlock-on-the-ground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Mike Pellitteri started flying his private plane in 2013, it was easy to find a spot to park it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG probe says evidence suggests Trump Org misstated asset values over decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/29/ny-ag-probe-suggests-trump-business-misstated-asset-values-for-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has criticized the probe of his Trump Organization by New York Attorney General Letitia James as politically motivated.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
