<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Deer Carcasses Left On Cars Outside YMCA...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/dead-deer-left-on-cars-of-somali-ymca-patrons-in-st-cloud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Cloud police are investigating a disturbing find on the hoods of two cars Wednesday night. Someone put deer carcasses on two cars parked at the St. Cloud YMCA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Survives CA Bar Massacre -- Loses Home In Wildfire Next Day...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/borderline-bar-shooting-woolsey-fire-destroys-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From bullets to flames, a woman survived two unthinkable tragedies less than 24 hours apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraplegic airline passenger forced to urinate in bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2018/11/16/paraplegic-flyer-forced-urinate-bottle-airline-investigates/2023540002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paraplegic athlete Darren Belling claims he was forced to urinate in a bottle on aÂ flyDubai flight because he couldn't access the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol deaths soar for middle-aged, women...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/11/16/alcohol-deaths-emergency-room-increase-middle-aged-women-addiction-opioids/1593347002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From 2007 to 2017, the numberÂ of deaths attributable to alcohol increased 35 percent. The death rate rose 24 percent. Deaths among women rose 67 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Foster kids forced to drink semen not sex assault, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2018/11/15/senon-louis-ramirez-conviction-overturned-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adams County District Attorney Dave Young on Thursday urged the Colorado legislature to update the state’s laws after a court overturned a man’s conviction in a graphic child sexual assault case on grounds that his actions did not constitute the crime of which he was found guilty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Says He Has Answered Mueller Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-says-he-has-answered-questions-from-mueller-1542392074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said he has answered a set of questions provided by special counsel Robert Mueller, but hadn’t yet submitted them to investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCARE:  91,000 pounds of raw turkey recalled amid salmonella outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/salmonella-outbreak-91000-pounds-jennie-o-raw-turkey-recalled-today-2018-11-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jennie-O-Turkey recall is the first tied to an outbreak the U.S. Department of Agriculture says is widespread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage crews sick of being treated like trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/torpy-large-atlanta-garbage-crews-sick-being-treated-like-trash/FJ6ff0bMIdLORMXoDhL32M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AJC columnist Bill Torpy on the low pay and high on-the-job death rate of Atlanta's sanitation workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Trump Asking, Is Pence Loyal?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/16/us/politics/mike-pence-trump-administration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has repeated the question so many times that he has alarmed some of his advisers. But Mr. Trump has not openly suggested dropping Mr. Pence from the ticket in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Air in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-chokes-toxic-air-wildfires-rage-170430103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools and tourist attractions across the San Francisco Bay Area were shut Friday as smoke from California's deadliest ever wildfire a three hour drive away produced air quality levels worse than in polluted megacities in South Asia. The closures came as the number of people missing from the giant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA INFERNO TOLL RISES TO 66...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/officials-order-evacuations-camp-fire-threatens-8000-acres/story?id=59065896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Camp Fire is now the most destructive and deadliest in California's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimmel Begs Michelle O to 'Save Us'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/16/jimmy-kimmel-begs-michelle-obama-to-save-us-from-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC late-night host Jimmy Kimmel begged former First Lady Michelle Obama to "save" the United States from the Trump presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACOSTA GETS A PASS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ffb3a155f454a0893dc2d9db18c81d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge ordered the Trump administration on Friday to immediately return the White House press credentials of CNN reporter Jim Acosta, saying Acosta suffered "irreparable harm" from the decision to bar him. U.S. District Court Judge Timothy Kelly, an appointee of President Donald Trump, announced his decision following a hearing. The judge said Acosta's credentials would be returned immediately and reactivated to allow him access to the White House. CNN had asked the judge to force the White House to return the credentials that give Acosta, CNN's chief White House correspondent, access to the White House complex for press briefings and other events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Trump aide tell-all due to hit shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/16/trump-white-house-cliff-sims-book-996198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former top White House aide Cliff Sims is modeling his book on George Stephanopoulos’ tell-all memoir &amp;quot;All Too Human.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University mandates 'all students' take 'diversity and inclusion' courses...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11530</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You can’t map out social change."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FL RECOUNT BY HAND...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/797e56eb5f694a0787cbebfcf9370797</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — A hand recount began Friday in Florida's acrimonious U.S. Senate contest after an initial review by ballot-counting machines showed Republican Gov. Rick Scott and Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson separated by fewer than 13,000 votes out of more than 8 million cast. Under state law, a hand review is required when the victory margin is 0.25 percentage points or less. A state website's unofficial results show Scott ahead of Nelson by 0.15 percentage points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Brexit referendum 'more likely than ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7756229/second-brexit-referendum-more-likely-than-ever-as-fresh-poll-shows-voters-want-another-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SECOND referendum on Brexit is now “more likely than ever” as Theresa May’s political future remains on the brink, Tom Watson has said. Labour’s deputy leader said yet ano…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP JUDGE SIDES WITH CNN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/media/cnn-trump-lawsuit-hearing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal judge Timothy J. Kelly sided with CNN on Friday, ordering the White House to reinstate chief White House correspondent Jim Acosta's press pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers Can Track Thanksgiving Turkey's 'Life Story'; Personal Details Including Where Came From...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/thanksgiving-turkey-tracker-consumer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just a week to go until Thanksgiving, it's time to buy your turkey. But this year, you can also read about your turkey's story with a tracker code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  WINTER STORM BLAST NORTHEAST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — The first snowfall of the season lingered Friday in the Northeast as thousands of exhausted commuters pointed their fingers at politicians and meteorologists for leaving them creeping along highways or stuck in mass transit hubs because of a storm that left seven dead as it moved through the Midwest and South. Some students in West Orange, New Jersey, were forced to sleep at their schools after their buses turned back, while others were taken to a diner to eat because snow-covered roads were clogged with traffic Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE MEDIA MESS</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6398199/Federal-judge-restores-CNNs-Jim-Acostas-White-House-press-pass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge handed CNN a major victory, ruling the Trump White House must restore the press credentials it stripped from the network's chief White House correspondent last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ accidents in NJ...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-gov-don-t-blame-me-for-the-mess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers were stranded for hours, mass transit was a mess and stranded students were forced to spend the night at their school. &amp;nbsp;New Jersey&amp;#39;s first snowstorm of the season was a disaster and the state&amp;#39;s response left them seething.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Israel set for early elections after cabinet breaks up, source says...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/israel-set-for-early-elections-after-cabinet-breaks-up-source-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elections to be brought forward from November 2019 after talks among coalition fail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban ranching: Socialist commune's response to crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/urban-ranching-socialist-communes-response-venezuelas-crisis-145527022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Corina Pons CARACAS (Reuters) - A socialist commune has drawn the ire of its neighbors in a wealthy area of Caracas with an unusual response to the hyperinflation and food shortages afflicting Venezuela: turning its backyard into an urban cattle pasture. The leaders of the Apacuana commune, devotees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 536 AD was worst year to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6397621/Why-536-AD-worst-year-alive.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers claim the awful year was likely caused by a cataclysmic volcanic eruption in Iceland and it kick-started a century of economic misery, disease, death and suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramer says CEOs telling him off record economy has quickly cooled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/cramer-says-ceos-are-telling-him-off-the-record-the-economy-has-cooled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Cramer outlines what he's hearing from chief executives about the state of the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband: Republican Party has become 'personality cult' under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/george-conway-republican-party-become-personality-cult-trump-130234835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — George T. Conway III, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, said the Republican Party has become “a personality cult” under President Trump and that he would “move to Australia” rather than vote for the president again. “I don’t feel comfortable being a Republican anymore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Cheney Aide in Mueller's Sights as Probe Expands...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/top-cheney-aide-in-muellers-sights-as-probe-expands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller’s investigators have examined an array of operatives with ties to Saudi Arabia, Israel, and the UAE—including John Hannah, Dick Cheney’s former national security adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 5, does 4,105 press-ups -- non-stop!?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/boy-5-gets-new-mercedes-for-doing-4105-press-ups-non-stop-8146111/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ramzan Kadyrov, a close lieutenant to Vladimir Putin, gave Rakhim Kurayev the keys to the luxury car as a reward for the boy’s 2 hours 25 minutes achievement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake generation too scared to cause a scene!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6396997/Snowflakes-SCARED-cause-scene-Half-16-24-year-olds-wouldnt-complain-bad-service.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three-quarters of Brits have delayed complaining or put it off entirely, study finds, and only 46% of young people would complain about bad service in a restaurant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini ice age could be on way...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/a-mini-ice-age-could-be-on-the-way-and-its-going-to-get-very-very-cold-8146529/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nasa fears that temperatures are about to plunge to grim lows which will leave the whole of humanity shivering and miserable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary advisers battle over whether she'll run...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/416981-hillary-advisers-battle-over-whether-shell-run-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Clinton’s former spokesperson, Philippe Reines blasted Mark Penn’s assessment of her chances of running, suggesting that Penn is out of the loop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new Egypt capital being built, what becomes of Cairo?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/with-new-egypt-capital-being-built-what-becomes-of-cairo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cairo is a city of 20 million people, a metropolis combining charm and squalor and a place where architectural treasures compete with overcrowded, impoverished neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China ups cash rewards for citizens who report porn...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/china-ups-cash-rewards-citizens-report-porn-123139031--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is raising the cash rewards paid to citizens for reporting pornographic and "illegal" publications to authorities, government regulators said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury hotel built in former pit mine to open in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/gravity-defying-hotel-gives-new-mean-to-sleeping-with-fishes-1528524/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18-story Intercontinental Shanghai Wonderland Hotel has been built into the side of a huge hole in the ground left by a former pit mine. Sixteen of its floors are below ground level, looking ou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller probe to go on, Whitaker tells Graham...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/72660937c96d4db6aec8826e14abde2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker has told Republican Sen. Lindsey Graham in a meeting that special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation will proceed, according to a person familiar with the meeting. The meeting with Graham and Whitaker Thursday comes as a bipartisan group of senators is pushing legislation to protect Mueller's job. The senators are concerned about Whitaker's past criticism of the Mueller probe, which is looking at Russian interference in the 2016 election and ties to President Donald Trump's campaign. Trump appointed Whitaker acting attorney general last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruling expected in CNN credentials case... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/judge-announce-ruling-cnn-reporters-credential-case-055213240--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge is expected to announce Friday whether he will order the Trump administration to return the White House press credentials of CNN reporter Jim Acosta. U.S. District Court Judge Timothy Kelly, an appointee of President Donald Trump, has set a hearing for Friday morning to announce his decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian woman gets jail after exposing philandering boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/indonesian-woman-gets-jail-after-exposing-philandering-boss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOMBOK, INDONESIA (AFP) - An Indonesian woman who exposed her cheating boss has been slapped with a six-month jail term for her trouble.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu battles to save weakened ruling coalition...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/netanyahu-battles-save-weakened-ruling-coalition-doc-1aw1101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy-Paste Error Reveals Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-16/copy-paste-error-reveals-assange-already-facing-us-indictment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK can now tell who live with based on pictures, captions...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90269076/facebook-can-now-tell-who-you-live-with-based-on-your-pictures-and-captions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t want to tell Facebook who your family is composed of? Doesn’t matter–Facebook will find out anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abrams push for new Georgia Gov. vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7985be43fa4c4422bfece25cb0204307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Stacey Abrams' campaign and legal team is preparing an unprecedented legal challenge in the unresolved Georgia governor's race that could leave the state's Supreme Court deciding whether to force another round of voting. The Democrat's longshot strategy relies on a statute that's never been used in such a high-stakes contest. It is being discussed as Georgia elections officials appear to be on the cusp of certifying Republican Brian Kemp as the winner of a bitterly fought campaign that's been marred by charges of electoral malfeasance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGMENT DAY FOR MAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7754150/theresa-may-future-balance-michael-gove-decides-resignation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REBEL Tories have enough support to topple Theresa May, they claimed today. Brexiteer shop steward Steve Baker told the hardline European Research Group that at least 48 MPs have called for a vote …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT CHAOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/11/16/brexit-deal-latest-news-theresa-may-faces-battle-save-premiership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty Tory MPs have publicly said they have submitted letters of no confidence in Theresa May as the Prime Minister fights to keep her job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No confidence vote 'likely'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/16/no-confidence-vote-against-theresa-may-is-now-looking-likely-8146609/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government whips have been told to cancel engagements today and return to London with a source saying a no confidence vote in the Prime Minister is now 'likely'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home DNA tests doom anonymity for sperm, egg donors...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-11-home-dna-doom-anonymity-sperm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Ryan Kramer had to do was to swab his cheek and embark on nine days of geneological research to identify his biological father, a man who thought he would remain anonymous when he donated his sperm and never took a DNA test himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare white lion to be auctioned off 'and shot by trophy hunters'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fury-over-rare-white-lion-13599126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majestic beast, named Mufasa, is at the heart of a legal battle in South Africa as campaigners desperately bid to save his life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first oral sex robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7753384/first-oral-sex-robot-autoblow-ai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first oral sex robot — named Autoblow A.I. — has been created. US developers taught it the actions after studying 108 hours of video porn. They say the device for men, yet to be patente…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut bacterium fountain of youth? </title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/space/go-for-launch/la-sci-sn-gut-bacteria-aging-20181115-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move over Bifidobacterium and Lactobacillus. There’s a new health-promoting gut bacterium in town, and it appears to maintain — and even restore — health as we age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA INFERNO TOLL RISES TO 63</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-cool-weather-aids-fight-north-california-fire-154905743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAGALIA, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on wildfires in California (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600+ MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/us/california-fires/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of rescue personnel dressed in white overalls are sifting through smoldering rubble and mangled cars, searching for human remains in California's deadliest wildfire. At least 63 people were killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Reality Is Cooling, Not Warming'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/15/boston-weather-snow-snowiest-decade-northeast-storms-weatherbell-trends-beyond-the-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How this November snowstorm could impact the rest of our winter snowfall totals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-necked man and Joker lookalike are upping the 'Florida Man' mugshot game...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article221698600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mugshots out of Florida took off on social media this week. One showed an Escambia County man, Charles McDowell, with a large neck, who was arrested on multiple charges. Another showed a heavily tattooed “Joker” lookalike, Lawrence Sullivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to make original movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/apple-enters-multiyear-agreement-with-a24-to-make-original-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The multi-year deal involves the New York-based film and TV studio producing multiple films for Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC area hit with biggest November snowfall in 29 years...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2018/11/more-snow-than-expected-thursday-meteorologists-explain/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday had far messier weather than people seemed to expect. And many thought forecasters dropped the (snow)ball. But they didn’t. Here’s what happened and how meteorologists are often faced with a “lose-lose” situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut bacterium fountain of youth? </title>
      <link>ttps://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/space/go-for-launch/la-sci-sn-gut-bacteria-aging-20181115-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKEBOOK DELETES 1.6 BILLION ACCOUNTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/11/15/facebook-transparency-report-fake-account-removal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been less than a day since the New York Times published a brutal report about the state of affairs at Facebook, including a deep look at the company's fail...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey develops AUTISM symptoms in world first as it's given antidepressants...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/742743/autism-study-research-monkey-autism-prozac-fluoxetine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela ID card [manufactured in China] can track, punish citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/venezuela-id-card-tracks-citizens-like-china-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela is rolling out a new, smart-card ID manufactured by China's ZTE Corp that will help the government track, reward, and punish citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blots Out Sun, Cools Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/california-air-is-so-bad-it-s-blotting-out-the-sun-cooling-land#gs.8x6QLlU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Air Is So Bad Itâ€™s Blotting Out the Sun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly assertive Melania puts first back in First Lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/newly-assertive-melania-trump-puts-first-back-first-lady-doc-1av5vz1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Suicide rates increasing among American workers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/416953-cdc-suicide-rates-increasing-among-american-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suicide rate among Americans of working age increased 34 percent from 2000 to 2016, according to a report released Thursday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed camera will catch drivers on phones from over half mile away...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/15/this-speed-camera-will-catch-drivers-on-their-phones-from-over-half-a-mile-away-8143422/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's probably time you stopped using your phone behind the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuees set up camp in WALMART parking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/751ea83a0e454bb8a7dcf0e2e5229dc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — Fire refugee Anna Goodnight sat on an overturned shopping cart Thursday in a Walmart parking lot as she ate scrambled eggs and tater tots while her husband drank a Budweiser. The couple was trying to put a good face on a weeklong ordeal that left them uncertain of the fate of their home and now had them camping next to the store with hundreds of others forced to flee from a deadly Northern California wildfire . But William Goodnight finally lost it and began to cry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Cut to Be Eroded Next Year by Inflation Switch...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-tax-cut-to-be-eroded-next-year-by-inflation-switch-1542302217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS announced the tax code’s parameters for 2019, implementing a new method for making inflation adjustments that will result in higher tax payments over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke spreading from California fires sparks health concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0082d079001472b8e9c223dc384ac88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke masks. Eye drops. No outdoor exercise. This is how Californians are trying to cope with wildfires choking the state, but experts say an increase in serious health problems may be almost inevitable for vulnerable residents as the disasters become more commonplace. Research suggests children, the elderly and those with existing health problems are most at risk. Short-term exposure to wildfire smoke can worsen existing asthma and lung disease, leading to emergency room treatment or hospitalization, studies have shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US PREPARING TO PROSECUTE ASSANGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-is-optimistic-it-will-prosecute-assange-1542323142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is preparing to prosecute WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange and is increasingly optimistic it will be able to get him into a U.S. courtroom, according to people in Washington familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY ON BRINK; MINISTERS QUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7752634/stubborn-theresa-may-geoffrey-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May vowed to dig in like cricket legend Geoff Boycott as she found herself on a sticky wicket. Two key ministers were among seven to quit over her Brexit agreement. But the PM pledged to ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUP!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6392287/Its-Jeremy-Corbyn-persuaded-Cabinet-Brexit-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister used a press conference in Downing Street to double down on her determination to press ahead with her controversial pact with the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER STORM BLAST NORTHEAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/destructive-ice-storm-major-snow-event-to-pummel-northeastern-us-through-weeks-end/70006623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gridlock Across NYC...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-11-14-winter-storm-avery-impacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what we know so far about the impacts from this winter storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port Authority Bus Terminal closed after overcrowding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/15/port-authority-bus-terminal-closed-due-to-snowstorm-overcrowding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Port Authority Bus Terminal is so crowded with commuters waiting for buses amid a massive winter storm that the agency is blocking any more people from entering, officials said. Officials close…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  Meditation works well as traditional therapy for vets with PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/759bf5a933db41c6bb2be1263aec6165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meditation worked as well as traditional therapy for military veterans with post-traumatic stress disorder in a small experiment sponsored by the Department of Defense. One method preferred by the Department of Veterans Affairs is exposure therapy, but it doesn't work for everyone and many can't handle what it requires: purposely recalling traumatic events and confronting emotions. Meditation could be a better choice for some, the researchers said. The experiment tested meditation against exposure therapy, which involves working with a therapist and gradually letting go of fears triggered by painful memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA  RECOUNT BY HAND</title>
      <link>http://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/11/15/florida-orders-first-ever-statewide-hand-recounts-as-legal-fights-continue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unprecedented statewide hand recount is now under way in the Sunshine State, further extending a high-stakes, partisan battle over every last vote in Florida's crucial U.S. Senate race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hockney Painting Sells for $90M, Living Artist Record...</title>
      <link>http://www.artnews.com/2018/11/15/david-hockneys-famed-pool-scene-sells-90-3-m-christies-new-record-work-living-artist-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.artnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orcas share personality traits with humans...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-killer-whales-personality-traits-humans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killer whales display personality traits similar to those of humans and chimpanzees, such as playfulness, cheerfulness and affection, according to new research published by the American Psychological Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Special Counsel allowed to proceed in troll farm case...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/judge-rules-mueller-proceed-case-russian-firm-linked/story?id=59224515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. District Judge ruled on Thursday that special counsel Robert Mueller’s case against Concord Management and Consulting can proceed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke masks safe? Handouts end in Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221709795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire stations are ending free distribution of N95 respirator masks in the Sacramento region after the county raised safety concerns, though smoke from the Camp Fire continues to create unhealthy air conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  Meditation works well as traditional therapy for vets with PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/local/allegheny/14298638-74/meditation-helps-veteans-with-ptsd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meditation worked as well as traditional therapy for military veterans with post-traumatic stress disorder in a small experiment sponsored by the Department of Defense. One method preferred by the Department of Veterans Affairs is exposure therapy, but it doesn't work for everyone and many can't handle what it requires: purposely ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military stratospheric balloons that never come down...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612417/darpa-is-testing-stratospheric-balloons-that-ride-the-wind-so-they-never-have-to-come-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sensor that can spot the wind direction from miles away will let DARPA’s surveillance balloons hover at the very edge of space in one spot indefinitely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lame duck agenda: No middle class tax cut?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/white-house-mcconnell-omit-promised-tax-cut-from-recap-of-lame-duck-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump told Senate Republican leaders on Thursday that his top lame-duck priorities include passing a spending bill with border security funds and approving new prison reform legislation — but middle-class tax cuts appear to have fallen from the agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY ON BRINK; MINISTERS QUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7744103/dominic-raab-resigns-theresa-may-brexit-deal-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEFIANT Theresa May tonight insisted she WON’T quit and stuck to her Brexit plan – as her leadership hung by a thread. The PM vowed to fight “with every fibre of my being” h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-door fight with veteran lawmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/15/ocasio-cortez-climate-change-976915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freshman star pushes for select committee on climate amid opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great whites circle below stranded spearfishermen in terrifying footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/animals/sharks-circle-below-stranded-fishermen-in-terrifying-footage/news-story/f54763057f4455d40b7f0d0f4a601f85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the two Australian men who became stranded in the middle of the ocean when they drifted away from their boat while they were in the water has shared the story of their terrifying ordeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge postpones decision over Acosta press pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/media/cnn-lawsuit-decision-postponed/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for CNN and the Trump administration are awaiting an initial ruling on the network's federal lawsuit over press access to the White House. And they're going to have to wait a little while longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC tells SPACEX can deploy up to 11,943 satellites...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2018/11/spacex-gets-fcc-approval-for-7500-more-broadband-satellites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial launch of 4,425 satellites to be followed by 7,518 closer to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She could be replaced 'in weeks'...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/uk-pm-may-could-replaced-weeks-rather-months-141402198--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) - A leadership challenge to British Prime Minister Theresa May could be completed in weeks, eurosceptic lawmaker Jacob Rees-Mogg said on Thursday. "I think it can be done quite quickly. I think the parliamentary processes can be sped up," he told reporters, adding "not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Tests New 'High Tech Weapon'...</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/northkorea/2018/11/16/0401000000AEN20181116000453315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong-un has inspected a test of a newly developed high-tech weapon, the North's state media reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum refuses to concede -- gains just 1 vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/os-ne-florida-vote-recount-deadline-20181115-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Gillum refused to concede and urged vote counting to continue even as his margin behind Ron DeSantis was slimmed by just one vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival blasts 'undertone of racism in caucus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/marcia-fudge-speaker_us_5bed9033e4b03af89267a979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fudge, a congresswoman from Ohio, suggests African-Americans in Congress are getting a raw deal from Pelosi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'firmly rejects' diplomatic request to visit internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/china-will-firmly-reject-diplomatic-request-to-visit-uighur-camps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will “firmly reject” a request from a group of western diplomats seeking to visit a region reportedly suffering under widespread repression, a top diplomat said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Algorithm flips another seat for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.centralmaine.com/2018/11/15/final-ranked-choice-vote-count-slated-for-noon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centralmaine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine Corps veteran wins 50.5 percent of the vote versus 49.5 for incumbent Republican Rep. Bruce Poliquin after the elections results are run through the ranked-choice tabulation software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi taunts rebels...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pelosi-taunts-critics-support-elected-speaker/story?id=59222261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi taunted critics Thursday, saying she still has support to be elected speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned to use altered forms to fix mail ballots...</title>
      <link>https://www.naplesnews.com/story/news/politics/2018/11/15/florida-recount-democrats-launch-plan-altered-state-form-fix-ballots/2009178002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naplesnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Democrats launched plan to give voters altered forms to fix absentee ballots after state deadline in hopes a judge would allow them to count.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT:  Bernie rolls out 'Stop WALMART Act'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bernie-sanders-rolls-out-stop-walmart-act-that-would-block-stock-buybacks-until-retailer-raises-pay-2018-11-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After his Stop BEZOS Act helped push Amazon to raise pay for its workers, Sen. Bernie Sanders launches a similar effort Thursday that targets Walmart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First lady Melania Trump speaks about civility and good online habits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/specials/live-video-1?adkey=bn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to employees: 'AMAZON will fail' -- our job to delay...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/bezos-tells-employees-one-day-amazon-will-fail-and-to-stay-hungry.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At an all-hands meeting, Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos was asked what he's learned from the failures of big retailers. Bezos told employees that "Amazon is not too big to fail," and that the company must stay hungry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate confesses to 90 deaths!</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article221716090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas prosecutor says a man convicted in three California murders but long suspected in dozens of deaths now claims he was involved in about 90 killings nationwide _ about a third of which investigators have corroborated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate accused of killing alleged child molester; Said God 'told me to do it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article221659165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate with schizophrenia at Tarrant County jail charged with killing a notoriously accused child molester said he hears voices, “God and his mother” spoke to him before the killing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach misses election recount deadline after machines stop working...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/palm-beach-likely-to-miss-recount-deadline-after-machines-stop-working-supervisor-sends-technical-manager-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's already farcical recount was dealt yet another blow Thursday when Palm Beach County failed to meet a 3 p.m. deadline, with the election supervisor blaming faulty equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  'Tremendous Respect for George Soros'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-crisis-pr-denial-1203029724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg claimed during a press call Thursday that he wasn’t aware of the company’s relationship with Defenders, a Washington D.C.-based consulting and PR company that was doing…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK says getting better at removing 'hate speech'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e3dbb9561734b4da9b4d3a9ec5c509a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Facebook says it's making progress on deleting hate speech, graphic violence and other violations of its rules and detecting problems before users see them. The company released its second report Thursday detailing how it enforces community standards on hate, nudity and other posts. Compared with its May report, Facebook says it has doubled the amount of hate speech it detects proactively, before users report violations. The new report covers April to September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative outlet files brief in support of White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/416954-conservative-outlet-one-america-news-files-brief-in-support-of-white-house-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of conservative outlet One America News Network (OANN) said Thursday that the organization will file an amicus brief in support of the White House as it faces a lawsuit from CNN over the revocation of reporter Jim Acosta's press pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY SCHUMER HOSPITALIZED...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/15/amy-schumer-hospitalized-for-pregnancy-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details emerging</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
