<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'HARDBALL' Matthews Fumes: How Could They Let Trump off Hook?</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-matthews-livid-over-mueller-how-could-they-let-trump-hook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We were told for weeks by experts you cannot deal with an obstruction of justice charge or investigation without getting to motive’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Media Predict Trump Family Leaving White House in HANDCUFFS...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-flashback-dems-media-predict-mueller-probe-results-impeachme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘My impression is after all of this is said and done that some people end up in jail’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Man, the myth, the legend...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/who-robert-mueller-man-behind-report-trump-n974296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telling a lie was the "worst sin" that could be committed in his household growing up, the former FBI director once recalled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> MUELLER TEAM FINISHED</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/meet-mueller-s-team-best-prosecutors-business-or-angry-democrats-n976226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has trashed them, but some experts say the group has an impressive track record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA READY FOR COMEBACK...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/23/how-madonna-is-using-younger-stars-to-cling-to-relevancy/?_ga=2.260900111.364405462.1553375123-1659663997.1548819272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You don’t real­ly hear people talk about her that much anymore, whereas everyone wants to know if Ariana Grande has crossed the street.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN TO LEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-23/wikileaks-raising-1-million-leaked-copy-mueller-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Horror Rules as 'US' Brings in $29 Million Opening...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/03/23/modern-horror-rules-as-jordan-peeles-us-brings-in-29-million-opening-eyes-60-70-mil-weekend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s all about “Us” this weekend. Jordan Peele’s follow up to “Get Out” scored a huge $29 million Friday including $7.4 mil from Thursday previews. By Sunday nig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baristas beware: Robot that makes gourmet cups of coffee has arrived...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Baristas-beware-A-robot-that-makes-gourmet-cups-13708775.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the food industry, it seems, the robot revolution is well underway, with machines mastering skilled tasks that have always been performed by people.  In Boston, robots have replaced chefs and are creating complex bowls of food for customers. In Prague, machines are displacing bartenders and servers using an app. In Denver, they're taking orders at a fast food drive through.  Robots are even making the perfect loaf of bread these days, taking charge of an art that has remained in human hands for thousands of years.  Now comes Briggo, a company that has created a fully automated, robotic brewing machine that that can push out 100 cups of coffee in a single hour -- equaling the output of three to four baristas, according to the company.  Using a blend of Latin American beans, the machine -- known as a "coffee haus" -- creates customized cups of gourmet coffee that can be ordered via an app, giving customers control over ingredients, espresso shots, flavorings and temperature without any human interaction. The company says no other business in the world has applied as much technology to "specialty coffee."  Removing the human element from ordering a cup of coffee is one of the company's primary selling points.  "No more lines, no more counter confusion, no more misspelled names," Briggo's website says, flicking at human failings.  Briggo said all eight of its machines are owned by the company, but they've recently begun offering a licensed business model to prospective operators. The company didn't reveal how much that business model costs, but noted that rent and revenue-sharing arrangements are typical when a machine is placed in a public location, such as an airport.  Kevin Nater, Briggo's president and chief executive, said the machine would thrive in locations in which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once site of Sanders' last stand, California now pivotal...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-bernie-sanders-california-20190323-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, California was the last stand for Bernie Sanders' insurgent presidential bid. Now, California is an early primary state and Sanders is a front-runner. By holding three major rallies in California this weekend, Sanders is signaling he intends to compete hard in the Golden State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN LOOMS OVER REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435429-showdown-looms-over-mueller-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr said he could inform lawmakers of the probe's general findings as soon as this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kraft speaks out first time since prostitution bust: 'I am truly sorry'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/23/robert-kraft-speaks-out-for-first-time-since-prostitution-bust-i-am-truly-sorry/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;” I know I have hurt and disappointed my family, my close friends, my co-workers, our fans and many others who rightfully hold me to a higher standard.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC ON EDGE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/washington-edge-muellers-findings-trump-141350716.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Attorney General Bill Barr was expected to hand Congress as early as Saturday the key findings of the Russian meddling probe with Washington anxious to learn if President Donald Trump is implicated in serious wrongdoing. Chronic tweeter Trump, who headed out from his Florida residence early for a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of flu season has not been this bad in last 2 decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/03/23/flu-season-nears-finish-line-but-medical-visits-remain-high-april/3254871002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC says the percentageÂ of medical visitsÂ for flu-like symptoms for the week remains stubbornly high, signaling elevated flu activity through April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Brexit Rally Draws 1 Million Protesters Demanding New Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/put-it-to-the-people-march-brexit-second-referendum-london-a8836756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship off Norway issues mayday; Evacuation of 1,300 passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e77902e765f142dca749301f665f86cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Police say a cruise ship with engine problems has sent a mayday call off Norway's western coast and is making plans to evacuate its 1,300 passengers and crew. Norwegian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutorial Focus Moves to New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-mueller-report-lands-prosecutorial-focus-moves-to-new-york/ar-BBV83Qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of thousands join referendum protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-47678763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters demand another EU referendum as MPs struggle to agree a way out of the Brexit impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy group sues for release...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435422-privacy-group-sues-doj-for-public-release-of-mueller-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Electronic Privacy Information Center (EPIC) filed a lawsuit on Friday to obtain special counsel Robert Mueller’s final report on his investigation into possible obstruction of justice by President Trump and possible coordination bet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full disclosure battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mueller-probe-apos-end-kicks-080000229.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I intend to consult with Deputy Attorney General Rosenstein and Special Counsel Mueller to determine what other information from the report can be released to Congress and the public consistent with the law, including the Special Counsel regulations, and the Department’s long-standing practices and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Family against billionaire': Battle over Zuckerberg's Hawaiian estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/23/mark-zuckerberg-hawaii-estate-land-parcels-auction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parcels near Facebook CEO’s property auctioned off amid lengthy fight over Native Hawaiian land rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugged orangutan found in airline luggage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/23/drugged-orangutan-found-in-russians-airline-luggage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police at Indonesian airport also found two live geckos and five lizards in suitcase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayday? Pressure builds on PM to quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-betting/mayday-pressure-builds-on-pm-theresa-may-to-announce-plans-to-quit-idUSKCN1R40DN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May was under pressure on Saturday to set out plans for h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLIC STILL IN DARK</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/83d570e5100640f7bf8245045e7c6aee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller closed his long and contentious Russia investigation with no new charges, ending the probe that has cast a dark shadow over Donald Trump's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable viewers digest through Hannity, Maddow...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/301bd7169962433e92430fe9b98aa468</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For Sean Hannity, the "witch hunt" was finally over. Rachel Maddow considered it the start of something. The diametrically opposed opinion hosts, who vie for the distinction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As 'caliphate' ends where is leader Baghdadi?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/baghdadi-ghost-world-jihads-low-profile-boss-145547891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most wanted man who has so far eluded capture, Islamic State group chief Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has seen his "caliphate" crumble and its last shred of territory in Syria evaporate on Saturday. After declaring himself caliph in 2014, Baghdadi held sway over seven million people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian Singer Banned After Claiming Lack Of Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/clevelandbanner/article/62ca9512d1514a6d9e85e66ec496d292/egyptian-singer-banned-after-claiming-lack-free-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — An Egyptian singer has been banned from performing in her home country after suggesting that it does not respect free speech.A video clip circulated online shows Sherine Abdel-Wahab, during a performance in Bahrain, saying: "Here I can say whatever I want. In Egypt, anyone who talks gets imprisoned."Egypt's Musicians Union responded late Friday by barring the singer, popularly known by her first name, from performing. It also summoned her for questioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron to miss playoffs first time since '05...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lakers-james-officially-nba-postseason-picture-055826368--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary superstar LeBron James will miss the NBA playoffs for the first time since 2005 as the Los Angeles Lakers were officially eliminated with a 111-106 loss to the Brooklyn Nets. The four-time league MVP also had his eight-year run to the NBA finals snapped on Friday night as the loss takes the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Investigations Loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-report-concludes-but-other-investigations-loom-11553289647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conclusion of special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia investigation leaves in its wake about a dozen other probes into President Trump and his associates by an array of federal, state and congressional investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concern Grows for U.S. Citizens Detained in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/concern-grows-for-u-s-citizens-detained-in-venezuela-11553302782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department is demanding that a dozen U.S. citizens and permanent residents being held in detention in Venezuela be granted access to proper nutrition and medical care, and be afforded fair judicial treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:   Mueller Must Remain Silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/03/ken-starr-muellers-report-shouldnt-go-congress/585577/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unusual situation facing Robert Mueller does not somehow work a repeal of well-established traditions of confidentiality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UFO community still believes -- and science is starting to listen...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/ufo-sightings-believers-mufon-unidentified-flying-objects-outer-space-20190322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last two years, scientists, politicians, and professionals have increasingly been willing to touch the taboo subject of UFOs and perhaps lend a little credence to those who still believe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streisand says Michael Jackson accusers were 'thrilled to be there' and his 'sexual needs were his sexual needs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-barbra-streisand-michael-jackson-accusers-thrilled-sexual-needs-20190323-7z3b2dqgbzh7jfs4yyhqhdfjyi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barbra Streisand is under fire for comments she made about two men accusing Michael Jackson of sexually assaulting them as children.The legendary singer and actress said that Wade Robson and James Safechuck — whose allegations against the late King of Pop resurfaced in the recent documentary “Leaving Neverland" — “were thrilled to be there” and that what allegedly happened to them “didn’t kill them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>675 DAYS OF INVESTIGATION</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/435383-muellers-investigation-ends-but-the-political-circus-will-continue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats need to face the reality that the only chance they have to beat Trump is at the ballot box.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kraft spa tapes may be released to public...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/22/robert-krafts-sexual-and-graphic-spa-tapes-may-be-released-to-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kraft’s powerful legal team is “surprised and disappointed” that prosecutors have denied their request to stop the “sexual and graphic” videos from inside the Asian spa going public. Kraft’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:   Don't expect hysteria to end...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/22/mueller-wraps-up-but-dont-expect-the-hysteria-to-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Bob Mueller has handed in his report, marking the effective end of the three-year Trump-Russia investigation. Hallelujah! This means that Mueller firmly expects to file no more crim…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemalan with no legs tries to sneak cross Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/legless-man-rescued-by-border-patrol-agents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border patrol agents had to rescue a double amputee from an island in the middle of the Rio Grande River this week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
