<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_t25xAp270o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May has named 7 June as the day she will step aside as Conservative leader, drawing her turbulent three-year premiership to a close. May says it has ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANCE ARMSTRONG: It wasn't legal but I wouldn't change a thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/may/24/lance-armstrong-it-wasnt-legal-but-i-wouldnt-change-a-thing </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeach Bolsonaro? Just Five Months In, Talk Has Already Begun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeach-bolsonaro-just-five-months-090001196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Propelled to the presidency by a vociferous army of online ideologues, including his sons, Bolsonaro’s government comprises an uneasy mix of radicals, pragmatists and economic liberals. In his five months in office, Bolsonaro has done little to rein in the extremist fringe, even when they target Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY CALLS IT A DAY... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9144415/theresa-may-resigns-brexit-tory-leadership-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEARFUL Theresa May today finally admitted her time was up and quit as Prime Minister insisting: “I’ve done my best”. The PM was forced to resign after she failed to deliver Brexi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPERM COUNTS DECLINE; PLASTICS TO BLAME?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/24/toxic-america-sperm-counts-plastics-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study that tested both men and dogs added to concerns that chemicals in the environment are damaging the quality and quantity of sperm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS, VOICE CRACKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/theresa-resignation-live-pm-holds-16192866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After almost three years of gridlock, Theresa May has named her resignation date and plunged the nation into a chaotic Tory leadership race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1131491/theresa-may-resigns-next-prime-minister-Tory-leader-boris-johnson-dominic-raab-andrea-lead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA MAY has tearfully announced she will stand down as Prime Minister and Conservative leader in two week’s time on June 7 following significant pressure for her to quit - but who will replace her in the top job? Here are all the runners and riders for the top position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'VE DONE MY BEST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7066101/PM-summons-inner-circle-Downing-Street-gets-ready-quit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM announced her departure in an emotional statement on the steps of Downing Street after meeting Tory backbench chief Sir Graham Brady and giving the news to her staff behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/uk-politics-48394091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest reaction as Mrs May announces she will step down as party leader on 7 June</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastinating genius: Did da Vinci have attention disorder?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190523224436-nov8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-DAVINCI/ (PIX):Procrastinating genius: did da Vinci have attention disorder?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to Testify IN PRIVATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/05/23/nadler-mueller-wants-to-testify-in-private/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday's broadcast of MSNBC's "Rachel Maddow Show," House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler (D-NY) stated that Special Counsel Robert Mueller | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES DEATH PENALTY?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-23/assange-faces-death-penalty-doj-files-espionage-act-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM DEBATES START IN MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/23/bill-de-blasio-and-michael-bennet-2020-democrats-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20 podiums allotted for the first Democratic presidential debates are quickly filling up, and the decision about who gets on stage could soon become much more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN: NO SURRENDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-commander/iran-says-it-will-not-surrender-even-if-it-is-bombed-idUSKCN1ST13X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will not surrender to U.S. pressure and will not abandon its goals even if ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused 'sex cult' leader had trouble having sex, trial witness says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-cult-leader-erectile-dysfunction-20190523-oepapt2slncxnlb2aag7qzgfx4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The charismatic leader of a controversial “sex cult” had trouble having sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: 'Villainous' Trump wants us to impeach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/pelosi-trump-wants-be-impeached-n1009236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House speaker's message to Democrats came as vocal support for impeachment rose among lawmakers in the caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-security Ebola burials spark dismay, anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190524-high-security-ebola-burials-spark-dismay-anger-dr-congo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-security Ebola burials spark dismay, anger in DR Congo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORK 9-HOUR WEEK TO SAVE PLANET?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/780956/britain-nine-hour-week-work-greenhouse-gas-emissions-united-nations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago slips in population but still third-largest in USA... </title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-census-chicago-metro-population-towns-05172019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago remains the third-largest U.S. city, though fourth-place Houston continued to close the gap, new census data show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do swarms of tiny temblors rattling West Coast warn of catastrophic quake?</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article230765154.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>185K Released in 5 Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/22/dhs-releases-7-9k-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-8-days-185k-released-in-5-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's DHS has released about 7,900 border crossers and illegal aliens into the U.S. in the past eight days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Movie Boxoffice Lagging Well Behind Previous Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/05/23/endgame-did-not-save-a-box-office-still-10-behind-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With "Avengers: Endgame" running out of steam, this year's box office still lags ten percent behind 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOONEY ISIS FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/05/23/george-clooney-worried-for-kids-safety-as-amal-works-on-isis-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have real security issues on a daily basis,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE MONDE director summoned by French intelligence service...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/le-monde-director-summoned-french-intelligence-211346945.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The managing director of the newspaper Le Monde, Louis Dreyfus, said Thursday he has been summoned for questioning by France's domestic intelligence agency, following a similar order against one of the daily's senior reporters. Dreyfus told AFP he and Ariane Chemin -- who broke the story of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Taliban' Lindh released as Afghan war still boils...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/american-taliban-lindh-released-afghan-war-still-boils-191325947.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Walker Lindh, the US Muslim convert who came to be known as the "American Taliban" after being captured while fighting in Afghanistan in 2001, was released Thursday after serving 17 years in a federal prison. The US Bureau of Prisons confirmed his early morning release from the federal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Booms...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-largest-cities-shrinking-040101410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fort Worth, Texas, is now the 13th most populous U.S. city, surpassing both San Francisco and Columbus, Ohio, according to newly released population estimates from the Census Bureau. Fort Worth grew by 19,552 residents during the twelve-month period ending in July 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ce08485cee37470db8983b8bd06c40a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — She's calling for an "intervention" to save the nation from him. He says she's "crazy." The enmity between President Donald Trump and House Speaker Nancy Pelosi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILLEGALS FLOOD CITIES FAR FROM BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c7aec8b18ae4cb3a8ed0a624c641eb9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A surge of asylum-seeking families has been straining cities along the southern U.S. border for months, but now the issue is flowing into cities far from Mexico, where immigrants are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-help guru filmed using N-word repeatedly...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/janebradley/tony-robbins-filmed-using-racial-slurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows the self-help guru using the n-word repeatedly and describing how he responded to a skeptical participant by getting “in her face” and kissing her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel agencies ordered to cooperate with 2016 campaign 'spying' probe...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/445347-trump-orders-intel-agencies-to-cooperate-with-barr-probe-into-spying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has ordered U.S. intelligence officials to cooperate with Attorney General William Barr's investigation into surveillance of members of his 2016 campaign, the White House said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Investigate the investigators' escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9e926bfccb5947d5a5f8eb260cb0a7e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump directed the U.S. intelligence community on Thursday to "quickly and fully cooperate" with Attorney General William Barr's investigation of the origins of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper plate Kurt Cobain ate pizza off of sells for $22,000...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox46charlotte.com/news/unusual/a-paper-plate-that-kurt-cobain-ate-pizza-off-of-just-sold-for-22000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox46charlotte.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California-based auction house Julien&amp;rsquo;s Auctions, which specializes in celebrity memorabilia, just sold an old paper plate that Kurt Cobain ate pizza off of and wrote a set list on for a staggering $22,000.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarium mystified by birth of baby anacondas in all-female exhibit...</title>
      <link>https://whdh.com/news/new-england-aquarium-mystified-by-birth-of-baby-anacondas-in-all-female-exhibit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whdh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (WHDH) - Two green baby anacondas were recently born in an all-female exhibit at the New England Aquarium in Boston, making them “biological celebrities”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots conduct daily health inspections of schoolchildren...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2204279-robots-conduct-daily-health-inspections-of-schoolchildren-in-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of preschools in China are using robots to give students heath checks. Each morning they examine pupils looking for signs of contagious diseases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Letters Underscore Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/American-Taliban-John-Walker-Lindh-Prison-Letters-ISIS-Terrorism-510286491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prison letters from the Northern California man who became known as the 'American Taliban' after his capture by U.S. forces in the 2001 invasion of Afghanistan underscore concerns among authorities that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials fighting measles outbreaks threaten rare air travel ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Officials-fighting-US-measles-outbreaks-threaten-13884328.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in five states have warned people believed to be infected with measles and planning to travel that a federal regulation could prevent them from boarding planes.  All eight individuals agreed to cancel their flights after learning the government could place them on the "do not board list" managed by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, said Martin Cetron, director of the agency's Division of Global Migration and Quarantine, which tracks disease outbreaks.  "The deterrent effect is huge," even in cases like these where the government's authority was not invoked, Cetron said. The agency had been contacted about the individuals by health officials from New York, California, Illinois, Texas and Washington state, CDC officials said.  Officials are often reluctant to talk about the government's travel ban authority "because it is a politically charged and politically visible request," said Lawrence Gostin, a professor of global health policy at Georgetown University.  The step is less restrictive than other public health measures like isolation or quarantine, but it "is seen as a government using its power over the people and the states, which is kind of toxic in America right now," said Gostin. "There is nothing unethical or wrong about it. It's just plain common sense that if you have an actively infectious individual, they should not get on an airplane."  Health officials emphasize that vaccination is the best and most effective way to protect against measles and that the majority of people with infectious, communicable diseases, like measles, listen to doctors' advice to not travel.  But for those who insist on traveling, federal authorities can use the list, which is managed by the CDC.  Officials in Rockland County, New York, and New York City, at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-13 gangster guilty of killing man for wearing Peyton Manning jersey...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/23/ms-13-gangster-convicted-of-killing-man-for-wearing-peyton-manning-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MS-13 gangster was found guilty on Thursday of conspiring to kill a man for wearing a No. 18 Peyton Manning jersey. Jose Suarez, also known as “Chompira,” was convicted on murder, racketeering a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: GOVT DECLARES WAR ON JOURNALISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/edward-snowden-doj-declared-war-on-journalism-by-charging-julian-assange-with-espionage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edward Snowden said the Justice Department declared "war" on journalism after accusing WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange of violating the Espionage Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record store bans Morrissey over political views...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/worlds-oldest-record-store-bans-morrissey-sales-because-he-has-a-different-opinion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diversity of thought? Not here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Trump faked being disabled to get out of Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445220-buttigieg-trump-faked-being-disabled-to-get-out-of-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Pete Buttigieg on Thursday hammered President Trump for in the past saying he had bone spurs to avoid being drafted into the Vietnam War, saying he faked the disability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jimmy Pitaro silenced screams of 'left-wing' ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/23/how-jimmy-pitaro-silenced-the-screams-of-left-wing-espn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nadir of ESPN’s failure with politics came in September 2017, when Jemele Hill, lucratively paid and newly minted co-host of a network family jewel, the 6 p.m. “SportsCenter,” respo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowner confused after break-in: Intruders steal nothing, clean house, leave origami roses...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/man-says-someone-broke-into-his-home-cleaned-it/27574128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Massachusetts homeowner came home last week to find that someone had broken into his residence, but after a quick search of the home, he realized nothing was missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge questions whether House can sue over border wall funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/judge-questions-whether-house-can-sue-border-wall-funding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge was skeptical whether the House can sue over the Trump plan to fund border wall projects with defense funds. And if federal courts should intervene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE TESTS FIRST AMENDMENT LIMITS</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Assange-charged-with-violating-Espionage-Act-13882846.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Federal prosecutors on Thursday accused WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange of violating the Espionage Act, bringing against him a new, 18-count indictment alleging that he unlawfully obtained and disclosed national defense information.  The new charges dramatically raise the stakes of the case both for Assange and the news media, raising questions about the limits of the First Amendment and protections for publishers of classified information.  Prosecutors say Assange worked with a former Army intelligence analyst to obtain and disseminate classified information - conduct of which many traditional reporters might also be accused. Prosecutors, though, sought to distinguish the anti-secrecy advocate from a traditional reporter.  "Julian Assange is no journalist," said John Demers, the Justice Department's Assistant Attorney General for National Security. He said Assange engaged in "explicit solicitation of classified information."  Assange was previously indicted by a U.S. grand jury over his interactions in 2010 with Chelsea Manning, the former Army intelligence analyst who shared hundreds of thousands of classified war logs and diplomatic papers with WikiLeaks. If convicted, Assange would face a maximum of five years in prison under that conspiracy charge. The new charges carry with them a maximum possible sentence of 170 years in prison.  The new charges against Assange carry potential consequences not just for him but for others who publish classified information, and they could lead to a change in the delicate balance in U.S. law between press freedom and government secrecy. They also raises fresh questions about whether the British courts will view the new charges as justified and worthy of extradition.  Prosecutors say in the new indictment that Assange and WikiLeaks "repeatedly encouraged sources with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds stuck in Mt. Everest 'traffic jam' near summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/mount-everest-deaths-traffic-jam-climbers-nepal-china-himalayas-a8927291.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKEBOOK: 3,000,000,000+ accounts removed -- in 6 months!</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d276ebdec5224398b9d70a6424bdee7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Facebook removed more than 3 billion fake accounts from October to March, twice as many as the previous six months, the company said Thursday. Nearly all of them were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi questions President fitness to stay. He calls her 'crazy, mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ce08485cee37470db8983b8bd06c40a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi openly questioned President Donald Trump's fitness to remain in office Thursday, suggesting a staff or family "intervention" for the good of the nation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MORNING AFTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/live-intense-thunderstorms-erupt-over-oklahoma-as-new-round-of-severe-weather-unfolds/70008345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA City Bars Mosque Members From Praying, Told They Need Permit...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/05/22/vacaville-mosque-permit-prayer-sessions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of a Vacaville mosque have been told they can’t pray in their own building during the holiest time of the year in Islam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigid Offices Killing Women's Productivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/05/warm-offices-women-productivity/589966/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As their goosebumps have long suggested, women perform better on tests of cognitive function at toastier room temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA readies for busiest summer travel season ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Summer-air-travel-13881788.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memorial Day weekend traditionally marks the beginning of the peak summer travel season as vacationers take to the skies in large numbers. And this year, according to new forecasts, those numbers are likely to be larger than ever before.  What's more, the crowded skies could be complicated this summer by safety and labor issues that weren't a factor in last year's peak season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK fake account removal doubles to 3 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Facebook-removes-3B-fake-accounts-but-how-many-13881859.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) - Facebook removed more than 3 billion fake accounts from October to March, twice as many as the previous six months, the company said Thursday.  Nearly all of them were caught before they had a chance to become "active" users of the social network.  In a new report, Facebook said it saw a "steep increase" in the creation of abusive, fake accounts. While most of these fake accounts were blocked "within minutes" of their creation, the company said this increase of "automated attacks" by bad actors meant not only that it caught more of the fake accounts, but that more of them slipped through the cracks.  As a result, the company estimates that 5% of its 2.4 billion monthly active users are fake accounts, or about 119 million. This is up from an estimated 3% to 4% in the previous six-month report.  The increase shows the challenges Facebook faces in removing accounts created by computers to spread spam, fake news and other objectionable material. Even as Facebook's detection tools get better, so do the efforts by the creators of these fake accounts.  The new numbers come as the company grapples with challenge after challenge, ranging from fake news to Facebook's role in elections interference, hate speech and incitement to violence in the U.S., Myanmar, India and elsewhere.  Facebook also said Thursday that it removed more than 7 million posts, photos and other material because it violated its rules against hate speech.  Facebook employs thousands of people to review posts, photos, comments and videos for violations. Some things are also detected without humans, using artificial intelligence. Both humans and AI make mistakes and Facebook has been accused of political bias as well as ham-fisted removals of posts discussing - rather than promoting -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSANGE 'ESPIONAGE' CHARGES</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/23/doj-accuses-assange-of-violating-espionage-act-1342653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department has hit WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange with Espionage Act charges, significantly escalating a legal fight against the high-profile activist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE COULD TEST FIRST AMENDMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/23/us/politics/assange-indicted-espionage-act-first-amendment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange faces 17 new counts in a superseding indictment over his role in publishing classified documents in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doomed May could cling on for weeks -- and quit after Trump visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9135337/theresa-may-set-to-quit-andrea-leadsom-brexit-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May is set to cling on to power a few more days but will have to name the date of her departure tomorrow, it is believed. The PM is under pressure to resign immediately after scrapping the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds announce $16B farm aid to offset war losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-aid/trump-administration-announces-16-billion-farm-aid-plan-to-offset-trade-war-losses-idUSKCN1ST1F6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Thursday unveiled a $16 billion farm aid package to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jersey Shore Beachgoers Warned Of 'Clinging' Jellyfish Carrying Paralysis Toxins...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/22/jellyfish-toxins-jersey-shore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we approach Memorial Day weekend, wildlife officials are warning anyone headed to the Jersey Shore of toxic invasive jellyfish lurking in the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA first-of-kind test manages drones in cities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c371a6501b8146fba5fd00cedf6040ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — NASA has launched the final stage of a four-year effort to develop a national traffic management system for drones, testing them in cities for the first time beyond the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deepfake' AI turns Mona Lisa into 'real person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/05/23/deepfake-ai-can-turn-mona-lisa-convincing-real-person/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI can now turn the Mona Lisa into a real life person with just one picture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Engineer Accidentally Trips On LSD -- For 9 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/05/21/1960s-rock-music-san-francisco-lsd-buchla-100-synthesizer-grateful-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, an urban legend circulated online and in documentaries purporting how part of a groundbreaking musical instrument -- versions which are stored at a Bay Area university and other institutions -- was dipped in a psychedelic drug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad Agency Fires Back at NRA With $50 Million Counterclaim...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nra-legal-fight-ackerman-mcqueen-ad-agency-fires-back-with-dollar50-million-counterclaim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The firm blames the NRA for a coup against Oliver North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of Smollett records...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-met-jussie-smollett-sealed-court-records-20190523-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge ordered the case file in the aborted prosecution of “Empire” actor Jussie Smollett unsealed Thursday in a victory for the news media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Barack Obama Jealous of Michelle's Book Success...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/report-obama-wants-his-memoir-to-beat-michelles-book-sales-privately-points-out-she-used-a-ghostwriter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama wants to beat the book sales of his wife Michelle's bestselling memoir and even dings her for using a ghostwriter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police raid on reporter erupts into 1st Amendment debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c28cd852d95443c8a827ff30914b611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A battle between the press and police is playing out in politically liberal San Francisco after police raided a freelance reporter's home and office seeking to uncover the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH COLD WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks/wall-street-slides-on-fears-of-likely-us-china-tech-cold-war-idUSKCN1ST1AZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock indexes fell more than 1% on Thursday, as investors sold off technolo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATASTROPHIC DAMAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7061433/Tornado-strikes-Jefferson-City-Missouri-causing-catastrophic-damage-state-capital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A catastrophic tornado has ripped through Missouri's capital, according to the National Weather Service. The 'violent tornado' was confirmed in Jefferson City around 11.43pm Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Geoffrey Rush Awarded $1.9 Million in #MeToo Defamation Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-48379980</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar-winner Geoffrey Rush is awarded A$2.9M over allegations printed in an Australian newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSTER TORNADO STRIKES MISSOURI...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-05-23-jefferson-city-missouri-tornado</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The capital city of Missouri was one of several areas hit by a tornadoes late Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fascist symbols and rhetoric on rise in Italian EU vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/46b367873afe41c9bc040ed603ad6742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A banner emblazoned with the words "Honor to Mussolini," unfurled just steps from the Milan piazza where the fascist dictator's body was hung upside down after his 1945 execution....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says family needs to stage 'an intervention'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pelosi-trump-cover-lead-impeachment/story?id=63227637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Pelosi appears emboldened by Thursday's fracas with President Trump, capitalizing on the the showdown to move past her party’s divisions regarding impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-05-23/us-iran-conflict-intensifies-amid-talk-of-troop-deployment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Geoffrey Rush Awarded $1.9 Million in #MeToo Defamation Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/geoffrey-rush-awarded-1-9-million-in-metoo-defamation-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar winner is awarded the largest ever defamation payout to a single person in Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's youth will witness demise of America and Israel, Supreme leader warns... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9139202/irans-america-israel-ayatollah-khamenei-trump-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN’S youth will witness the demise of American and Israeli civilisation, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei vowed. The leader’s comments come a day after a senior Revolutionary Guards commander bragged Donal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grindr killer 'had sex with Britain's worst paedo' in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/grindr-killer-stephen-port-had-14323579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Stephen Port had a relationship with Richard Huckle while both were serving time at HMP Belmarsh in south east London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young people blame 'climate change' for their small savings!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-to-get-young-people-to-save-for-the-future-when-they-think-the-planet-is-doomed-2019-05-23 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many young people today think civilization may not exist when they’re of retirement age. Here are ways to get them to invest for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MORNING AFTER</title>
      <link>https://www.kmov.com/news/extensive-damage-reported-in-jefferson-city-tornado/article_3e570d70-7d20-11e9-9ea3-17562169e9ac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kmov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “violent tornado” touched down in Jefferson City, Missouri, causing heavy damage, according to the National Weather Service, but there were no immediate reports of fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST DAY OF MAY?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7061901/Mays-day-power-meets-final-executioner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May is trying to maintain dignity as the sun sets on her time in power - with a resignation announcement seen as inevitable after she meets Tory 1922 committee chief Graham Brady tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot dog pulls 3-ton plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/a-robot-dog-just-pulled-a-3-ton-plane-and-were-not-scared-at-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seriously. We should stop kicking the robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says trade talks can't continue unless US addresses its wrong actions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/23/china-says-trade-talks-cant-continue-unless-us-addresses-its-wrong-actions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Ministry of Commerce spokesperson does not single out any U.S. action, but it's been a tense couple of weeks for the trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record store bans Morrissey over political views...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/record-store-bans-morrissey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spillers Records, which is described as the world&amp;#39;s oldest record store, has banned albums by the artist Morrissey over his political views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military bases making people sick?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/23/chemical-colorado-springs-military-communities-pfcs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Colorado Springs, businesses are suing the military for perfluorinated compounds, which some are calling ‘Agent Orange 2.0’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE STOCK JITS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/23/stock-market-trade-war-concerns-weigh-on-market-sentiment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell sharply on Thursday as U.S.-China trade worries persisted with more companies suspending business with Chinese telecom giant Huawei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers ditch iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/23/a-growing-number-of-chinese-consumers-are-switching-from-apples-iphone-hong-kong-paper-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Huawei is winning over more and more Apple fans in China as the escalated trade tensions stoked "nationalist sentiment," according to South China Morning Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four More Women Have Accused Tony Robbins Of Sexual Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/katiejmbaker/four-more-women-accuse-tony-robbins-of-sexual-misconduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The self-help guru is accused of groping followers at his events, exposing himself to women assistants, and sexually harassing fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>102-year-old woman suspected of killing 92-year-old neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48379650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 102-year-old is thought to have battered and strangled her 92-year-old female neighbour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOW DUMPS ON ARIZONA...</title>
      <link>https://www.azfamily.com/news/ap_cnn/storm-brings-more-snow-and-rain-as-unusual-may-weather/article_632724c4-7ccf-11e9-a4b4-ab22a8767dc9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azfamily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This May has been somewhat of an anomaly for Arizona with late-season snowstorms hitting the Flagstaff area and multiple days of lower than average temperatures in Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wallendas plan highwire walk over Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bc373f40dae943948e999d510007c2b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For his next trick, daredevil Nik Wallenda plans to cross New York's Times Square — without his feet touching the ground. ABC announced Thursday that Wallenda and his sister...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimpanzees spotted cracking open tortoises for meat...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chimpanzees-spotted-cracking-open-tortoises-meat-130452951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Scientists say they have observed wild chimpanzees tucking into an unusual snack: tortoises, whose hard shells they cracked against tree trunks before scooping out the meat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented observations...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-does-a-chimpanzee-eat-a-tortoise-by-smashing-it-li-1834958754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As omnivorous creatures, chimpanzees eat all sorts of things, including fruits, termites, tiny rodents, and even full-grown monkeys. As for chimps eating reptiles, that’s completely unheard of—until now. Unprecedented observations have uncovered a community of chimps in Gabon that regularly consume tortoises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Fired Gun Over Oral Denial...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/anneisha-speed-case-49738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 22--Angry that a male acquaintance refused to perform oral sex on her, a 19-year-old Louisiana woman fired a shot at the man, prompting him to jump from the second-floor balcony of his Baton Roug</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sees biggest slump in tourism for four years...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/us-counts-cost-of-biggest-slump-in-tourism-for-four-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb surgeon went 'all in' on $180 million mansion, then came high-end housing glut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/22/celebrity-surgeon-goes-all-in-on-180-million-bel-air-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-end real estate market is suffering, with a glut of overbuilt and overpriced mansions in many of the country's most affluent ZIP codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq's Christians 'close to extinction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-48333923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK Christian leaders are accused of failing to speak out as an ancient community faces annihilation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Taliban' released from prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/23/american-taliban-john-philip-walker-lindh-released-from-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notorious “American Taliban” John Walker Lindh — who abandoned his country to train with Osama bin Laden — has been released from an Indiana prison. The 38-year-old from Nor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in charge? Power struggles roil DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7f64b7cbdc8a4589a856e4cc1f103bb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A dozen times, Rep. Ayanna Pressley asked the witness for a yes or no answer on housing policy. Not once did Ben Carson, President Donald Trump's housing secretary, give...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Smarter people listen to instrumental music...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/22/smarter-people-listen-to-instrumental-music-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there seems to be an air of pretension among aficionados of jazz and classical music, psychological research is giving them good reason. A new study published in Evolutionary Behavioral Sciences…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Surges...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/buttigieg-surges-voters-begin-suffering-080000503.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infatuated with O’Rourke since his 2018 Senate bid in Texas, Sweat hosted a watch party for his presidential campaign launch at her Davenport, Iowa, home in March. Then she started to hear more about Pete Buttigieg. Sweat’s burgeoning support of Buttigieg and her waning interest in O’Rourke is mirrored</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norman Lear delights with live 'ALL IN THE FAMILY' and 'JEFFERSONS'...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/2019/05/23/live-in-front-of-a-studio-audience-was-a-new-delightful-take-on-nostalgia-ew-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, a TV event for those of us who aren’t into musical theater. Though there was one stand-out song (all…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kailua beach named best in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afb3b02c917449ffb2541cc7a3d0ca6a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAILUA, Hawaii (AP) — In Kailua, the sand is soft and white, the water is clear and calm, and the view is exactly what you would expect from a beach in the Hawaiian Islands. Those are among...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
