<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm Determined UK Students' Grades. Chaos Ensued...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-algorithm-determined-uk-students-grades-chaos-ensued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's A-Levels, the high-stakes exams taken in high school, were canceled due to the pandemic. The alternative only exacerbated existing inequities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest woman in USA celebrates turning 116 with drive-thru birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-8632493/Oldest-woman-200-grandchildren-celebrates-116th-birthday-style.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hester Ford, from Charlotte, North Carolina, blew out 116th candles this weekend. The great grandmother, who has 200 great-grandchildren, is believed to be the oldest person living in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universities drastically reshaped...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/16/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The return to college campuses this month has offered a preview into how the coronavirus pandemic has drastically reshaped the university experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter films own arrest at Proud Boys rally...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/16/michigan-reporter-filmed-arrest-at-proud-boys-rally-in-kalamazoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Jesus — I’m being arrested!” Samuel Robinson suddenly cried, his camera shaking as officers were shown around him. He repeatedly shouted, “I’m media!” bef…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems in conservative S.C. see opportunity for gains...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-conservative-c-see-opportunity-122218359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#39;s been nearly 15 years since a Democrat won a statewide office and 44 years since a Democratic presidential candidate claimed the state. In the U.S. Senate race, Democrat Jaime Harrison has raised more money than GOP incumbent Lindsey Graham for two quarters in a row. A Democrat captured a longtime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama 'uses loopholes to bypass coastal protection laws in Hawaii' to build compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8631723/Planning-loopholes-bypass-coastal-protection-laws-Hawaii-compound-tied-Obama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials and community members confirmed to ProPublica that Obama plans to reside in the compound on Oahu, which was purchased for $8.7 million by his close friend Marty Nesbitt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KODAK loan: Insider trading in new garb?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/512174-the-kodak-loan-insider-trading-in-a-new-garb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DFC loan to Kodak is the first of its kind under the Defense Production Act, and so it is not surprising that it raised a number of new issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden looks to make inroads with evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511809-biden-looks-to-make-inroads-with-evangelical-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden is seeking to make inroads with evangelical voters, a demographic that overwhelmingly sided with President Trump during the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's Been Pacifist for 75 Years. Missile Proposal Challenges That...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/16/japans-been-proudly-pacifist-for-75-years-a-missile-proposal-challenges-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — Shinzo Abe is facing some of the toughest challenges of his record-setting tenure as Japan’s prime minister, with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no balloon drops, what's a convention for?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/08/16/joe-biden-kamala-harris-keys-to-democratic-convention/3368123001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Joe Biden, the to-do list at this week's virtual convention includes spanning a political spectrum from John Kasich to AOC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defund police? Already happening thanks to Covid-19 budget crunch...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/15/defund-the-police-coronavirus-budget-395665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision about how much spending needs to be cut, and from where, will be up to each state’s bank balance and the political makeup of its government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian surfer punches shark to save wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200816-australian-surfer-punches-shark-to-save-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian surfer punches shark to save wife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fire tornado' warning? Weather service issues what could be first...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-tornado-warning-weather-issues-001717718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Fire tornadoes happen, but the issuance of a tornado warning on one is a first.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Cult of Priests Who Hate Pope Francis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-secret-cult-of-priests-still-wont-recognize-pope-francis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest in Sacramento, California, has been excommunicated for not accepting Pope Francis as the real pope. He’s not the only one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA clears saliva test opening door to wider testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/08/15/fda-clears-saliva-test-for-covid-19-opening-door-to-wider-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA granted emergency use authorization for a saliva test for the virus that causes Covid-19, which could improve testing capability in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF CALI ROLLING BLACKOUTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article244996275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington QB Alex Smith cleared to play after horrific injury...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29671320/washington-qb-alex-smith-cleared-football-activity-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Football Team quarterback Alex Smith, who suffered a leg injury in 2018 that nearly cost him his life, will be cleared for football activity and be activated off the physically unable to perform list, a source told ESPN's John Keim on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/south-korea-confirms-279-new-covid-19-cases-most-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telephone service begins between UAE, Israel amid deal...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/middle-east/2020/08/telephone-service-begins-between-uae-israel-amid-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Telephone service between the United Arab Emirates and Israel has begun as the two countries open diplomatic ties. Associated Press journalists in Jerusalem and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's brother dies aged 71...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robert-trump-president-younger-brother-022805753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump&amp;#39;s younger brother, Robert Trump, a businessman known for an even keel that seemed almost incompatible with the family name, died Saturday night after being hospitalized in New York, the president said in a statement. The president visited his brother at a New York City hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered brain bleeds that began after recent fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/robert-s-trump-the-presidents-younger-brother-dies-at-71/ar-BB180r9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered brain bleeds that began after recent fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/15/us/politics/robert-s-trump-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A loyal spokesman for the family, he shunned the spotlight and had “zero sense of entitlement.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney slams administration over death toll... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/No-way-to-spin-that-Romney-says-of-U-S-15486939.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney, R-Utah, offered rare Republican criticism of the Trump administration's coronavirus response Friday, saying the federal government dismissed the virus's threat and failed to protect Americans as infections spiraled out of control.  "Short term, I think it's fair to say we really have not distinguished ourselves in a positive way by how we responded to the crisis when it was upon us," Romney said in a video interview with the Sutherland Institute. "And the proof of the pudding of that is simply that we have 5 percent of the world's population but 25 percent of the world's deaths due to covid-19.  "And there's no way to spin that in a positive light," Romney added.  At least 166,000 people nationwide have died of coronavirus-related complications - about 21 percent of the worldwide death toll. An additional 1,222 U.S. deaths were reported Friday and 1,218 were reported Saturday as of late evening.  Here are some other significant developments:  - The number and rate of infections in children under 17 have increased since March, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said in recently updated guidance, underscoring the risk for young people and their families as schools weigh whether to reopen with in-person instruction. Although the virus is far more prevalent and severe among adults, the true incidence of infection in U.S. children remains unknown because of a lack of widespread testing, according to the agency.  - The Food and Drug Administration granted emergency-use authorization Saturday to a saliva-based coronavirus test, developed by Yale University researchers, that aims to reduce turnaround times in commercial laboratories.  - New York continued to report progress against the virus after experiencing the country's most severe outbreak in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Crisis Ripples Across Nation as Election Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/usps-postal-workers-slowdown-2020-election-2c0d3cf8-38d1-459b-9c21-07e9e637c82b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This isn't a just a potential threat — it is happening before our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia, Anti-Facists Face Off in Tense Stone Mountain Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/protesters-clash-in-stone-mountain/3ZXGYQQJWFB6VAMZSZR74B4DXE/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters clash in Stone Mountain. Far-right militia, leftist groups faced off as police held back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX and UPS warn they cannot deliver votes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/video/ups-fedex-warn-cannot-carry-174229060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the fight over voting by mail grows in the U.S. leading up to November’s presidential election, on Friday private delivery companies UPS and FedEx shot down social media calls that they step in to deliver mail-in ballots from the U.S. Postal Service.        This comes as USPS warned states of potentially &amp;quot;significant&amp;quot; delays.        In a statement exclusively to Reuters, UPS said (quote):        “State ballots must be postmarked to be considered valid and only the USPS has lawful postmarking status. Therefore UPS, FedEx and other private parties cannot technically be involved in shipping ballots.”        While FedEx responded (quote):        &amp;quot;FedEx does accept individual ballots, and we advise that customers planning to return their ballots via FedEx should closely review their state&amp;#39;s guidelines on absentee voting and deadlines for ballots or related election documents.&amp;quot;        All this taking place while President Donald Trump on Thursday said he opposed providing funds for the struggling Postal Service for mail voting, which is expected to surge to 50% as the coronavirus pandemic rages ahead of the Nov. 3 presidential election.        The Postal Service said on Friday it has written to 46 states and the District of Columbia warning there is a significant risk voters will not have enough time to complete and return their ballots.        There are other hurdles that these private companies would face…        While the USPS touches every U.S. mailbox six days a week, other companies visit only when they have a delivery or a pre-arranged pickup.        The other issue is cost...        According to Tammy Patrick, a former Arizona election official and senior advisor to the Democracy Fund foundation, domestic costs would skyrocket, since delivery firms charge significantly more for deliveries than the price of a 55-cent stamp while international costs would be “astronomical.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT VS RIGHT BATTLE IN MICHIGAN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1316052/proud-boys-group-brawl-antifa-protests-kalamazoo-michigan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RALLY organized by far-right group Proud Boys in Kalamazoo, Michigan, escalated into violence when they were met by a peaceful church vigil. The First Congregational Church hosted a gathering of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING BLACKOUTS CALI...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2020-08-15-california-heat-wave-power-outages-rolling-blackouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is sweltering under a late summer heat wave that's led to rolling blackouts and warnings about air quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trigger Oakland Estuary Sewage Spill...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/15/rolling-power-outage-triggers-oakland-estuary-sewage-spill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boaters were being warned Saturday to stay away from the Oakland Estuary after an estimated 50,000 gallons of raw sewage spilled during a power outage Friday night at the East Bay Municipal Utility District wastewater treatment plant in West Oakland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxe Quarantine Lives of Silicon Valley Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/08/luxe-quarantine-lives-of-silicon-valley-elite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis Kalanick is throwing (outdoor) parties, private-jet owners are hopping from safe zone to safe zone, and dinner party hosts are administering 15-minute COVID-19 rapid tests—all business as usual. “Coronavirus is a poor person’s virus,” says one source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Apocalypse: The rich and famous are fleeing in droves...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8631063/Hollywood-Apocalypse-rich-famous-fleeing-droves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAROLINE GRAHAM: The pandemic has made many in Hollywood realise they don't need to live in LA - or anywhere near it - to keep working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney slams administration over death toll... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/15/romney-slams-trump-administration-over-us-coronavirus-death-toll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Sen. Mitt Romney criticized the Trump administration's early response to the coronavirus outbreak, saying they didn't immediately "ring all the alarm bells."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracing Trump's Postal Service obsession  --  from 'loser' to 'scam' to 'rigged election'... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tracing-Trump-s-Postal-Service-obsession-from-15486836.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Soon after taking office in 2017, President Donald Trump seized on the U.S. Postal Service as an emblem of the bloated bureaucracy. "A loser," he repeatedly labeled one of America's most beloved public institutions, according to aides who discussed the matter with him.  Allies coddled Trump by telling him the reason he lost the popular vote to Hillary Clinton in 2016 was widespread mail-in balloting fraud - a conspiracy theory for which there is no evidence - and the president's postal outrage coarsened further.  Then Trump complained to senior White House advisers that Jeff Bezos - a presidential foe in part because he owns The Washington Post, whose news coverage the president thought was unfair and too tough on him - was "getting rich" because Amazon had been "ripping off" the Postal Service with a "sweetheart deal" to ship millions of its packages, one of them recalled. They explained that this was not true and that the Postal Service actually benefited from Amazon's business, the adviser added, but the president railed for months about what he described as a "scam."  And now Trump has fixated again on the Postal Service, this time trying to make it a tool in his reelection campaign by slowing mail service, blocking an emergency infusion of federal funds and challenging the integrity of mail-in balloting. The president acknowledged last week that his opposition is rooted in his desire to restrict how many Americans can vote by mail.  The breathtaking moves by the Trump administration this summer to disrupt a Constitutionally mandated government service during the coronavirus pandemic - under the argument that it will boost operational efficiencies - represent the culmination of Trump's grievance-fueled crusade against the Postal Service that dates to the start of his presidency. Many of his complaints...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters Tear Down George Washington Statue at L.A. City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/08/14/watch-rioters-tear-down-george-washington-statue-at-l-a-city-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters tore down a statue of George Washington near Los Angeles City Hall on Thursday evening, the latest monument to fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Military Posts Video of Air Defense Drills as Warning to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/08/14/chinese-military-posts-video-hong-kong-air-defense-drills-warning-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese military publishes a short video of air defense drills seen as a warning to the U.S. against interfering in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing mailbox in Baltimore latest symbol of turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/politics/bs-md-pol-usps-signs-20200815-dy6sstao7bemliolecgh6gkvvi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More signs of the turmoil at the U.S. Postal Service emerged in Maryland this weekend after at least one of the service’s iconic blue mailboxes was removed from a Baltimore street corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong journalists harassed, arrested and losing press freedoms under new law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-journalists-harassed-arrested-120007846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The raid this week of Apple Daily&amp;#39;s newsroom and leadership changes at broadcaster iCable highlight the shrinking space for independent journalism as Beijing exerts more control over a once freewheeling Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA says President not entitled to extra protection from grand-jury subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-subpoena/manhattan-da-says-trump-not-entitled-to-extra-protection-from-grand-jury-subpoena-idUSKCN25A1Z1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump is not entitled to greater protection from a grand-jury subpoena for his tax returns just because he is president, the Manhattan district attorney said in a court filing on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey will send ballots to all active registered voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2020/08/everybody-gets-a-ballot-murphy-says-nj-to-have-mostly-mail-in-voting-in-november-election-because-of-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Phil Murphy is expected to discuss the issue more Friday afternoon at his latest coronavirus briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Fun Police Should Stand Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-fun-police-should-stand-down/ar-BB17ZH48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorching temps in Southwest shatter records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/15/weather/weekend-heat-record-california-and-texas/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 80 million people are under excessive heat alerts this weekend with records possible in over 10 states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds developing corona strain for human 'challenge' trials...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-developing-coronavirus-strain-human-220417655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US scientists are developing a strain of the coronavirus that could be used to deliberately infect volunteers in so-called &amp;quot;challenge studies,&amp;quot; a government agency said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NEWSWEEK apologizes for op-ed questioning Kamala eligibility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe4e75db0007c1854e98cb6f2d3488c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Newsweek has apologized for an op-ed that questioned Sen. Kamala Harris’ U.S. citizenship and her eligibility to be Joe Biden’s running mate, a false and racist conspiracy theory...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police move in...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cc42ee6ff8cb1c05278a1e2d7f045a2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STONE MOUNTAIN, Ga. (AP) — After several hours of mostly peaceful demonstrations Saturday in an Atlanta suburb that's home to a giant Confederate memorial, large numbers of police moved in to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans brave open sea on tubes, fishing for survival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/025a5e913ae0e6f7537c55cae8e48569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA GUAIRA, Venezuela (AP) — The biggest fear is a fishhook puncturing the inner tube that keeps them afloat far from shore. Then come sharks grabbing their catch and maybe biting their legs. And...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Seethes Over Kamala's Call to 'Lock HIM Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-holds-a-grudge-against-kamala-harris-for-wanting-to-lock-him-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s VP pick caught Trump’s attention during the primary season by saying he should be prosecuted after he leaves office—and now those comments are taking on a new relevance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Took NEWSWEEK Days and Staff Revolt to Apologize for Birtherism Op-Ed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/it-took-newsweek-three-days-and-a-staff-revolt-to-apologize-for-kamala-harris-birtherism-op-ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apology nevertheless fell far short of staffers’ demands that the magazine retract and remove the supposedly erudite exploration of 19th century Supreme Court rulings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Hollywood's Long, Strange History of Movie Nudity...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-hollywoods-long-strange-history-of-movie-nudity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new documentary “Skin: A History of Nudity in the Movies” aspires to be the definitive doc on movie nudity. Here’s why it falls short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia, Anti-Facists Face Off in Tense Stone Mountain Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/far-right-militia-pro-confederacy-groups-anti-facists-face-off-in-tense-stone-mountain-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White supremacists and militia members were met by antifa counter-protestors in the city that’s home to the largest Confederate monument in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Fun Police Should Stand Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/08/containing-the-pandemic-isnt-a-job-for-cops/615298/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social gatherings provoke moral indignation—but bringing in law enforcement will promote injustice, not reduce infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer to speak on why he's switching to Joe...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/vote2020/2020/08/15/Volant-farmer-Rick-Telesz-Democratic-convention-why-switch-to-Biden/stories/202008150023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A registered Democrat who said he’s never voted a straight ticket, Mr. Telesz voted for Barack Obama twice before casting a ballot for Mr. Trump in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shake-up at CDC...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/14/cdc-chief-of-staff-departs-395509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Kyle McGowan and Amanda Campbell have been with the health department since the start of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On eve of convention, Texas Dems hope Biden fares better than Clinton in winning over Sanders fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.northwestgeorgianews.com/associated_press/on-eve-of-national-convention-texas-democrats-hope-biden-fares-better-than-clinton-in-winning/article_128e695e-b43a-533c-9203-a1984ed3ad45.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.northwestgeorgianews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Sarah Hernandez is a Bernie Sanders supporter who's frustrated yet again that Democrats picked another relatively moderate establishment icon — former Vice President Joe Biden, this time around</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDERS CLOSED:  American Passports Useless Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/american-passports-are-useless-now/ar-BB17XtvC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force pilot taking on AI adversary in simulated dogfight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-us-air-force-f-16-pilot-is-going-to-take-on-an-ai-adversary-in-a-simulated-dogfight-and-you-can-watch-it-live/ar-BB17YsOQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Denies Report Birx Has Been Replaced...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-denies-cnn-report-that-birx-has-been-replaced/ar-BB17YGr8?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's assault on Postal Service gives Dems new campaign message... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-assault-on-the-u-s-postal-service-gives-democrats-a-new-campaign-message/ar-BB17Yyrq?li=BBorjTa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE HILL Publishes Campaign Ads Disguised as 'Op-Eds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/the-hill-publishes-campaign-ads-disguised-as-op-eds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hill is known for its high-metabolism national political coverage, wonky Washington D.C. reporting, but also for a sprawling opinion section that often serves as a landing pad for campaign staffer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diocese in Kentucky releases list of priests accused of sexually abusing minors...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/state/kentucky/article244969970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panhandler punched Chinese American woman and called her slur. Will it be considered hate crime?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/a-panhandler-punched-a-chinese-american-woman-and-called-her-a-slur-will-it-be/article_3beb18a4-e390-5626-83f1-92e10a1f39e0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — On July 28, Chinatown resident Jing Chen and her 12-year-old daughter were walking on 13th Street in Center City when they suddenly felt a splash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant apologizes for weighing customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200815-china-restaurant-apologises-for-weighing-customers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China restaurant apologises for weighing customers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin brothels reopen -- but no sex allowed?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200815-berlin-brothels-reopen-after-lockdown-but-no-sex-allowed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlin brothels reopen after lockdown, but no sex allowed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt To Surpass $78 Trillion By 2028...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikepatton/2020/08/14/national-debt-to-surpass-78-trillion-by-2028-what-it-means-for-americans/#416be7af5ddf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Debt has risen over 3,370% since President Jimmy Carter took office. Here's what it means for Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infection rates in children 'steadily increasing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/15/health/us-coronavirus-saturday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts say children make up more than 7% of all coronavirus cases in the US -- while comprising about 22% of the country's population -- and the number and rate of child cases have been "steadily increasing" from March to July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% of tests come back too late to be clinically meaningful...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/15/forty-percent-of-us-covid-19-tests-come-back-too-late-to-be-clinically-meaningful-data-show.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health experts say Covid-19 test results need to be returned within two to three days to be clinically meaningful. A CNBC/Dynata survey of 9,444 Americans in all 50 states shows almost 40% of tests took longer. And there's major variation state by state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service chief admits 'unintended consequences' of his policy overhaul...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/14/postal-service-chief-under-fire-admits-unintended-consequences-of-his-policy-overhaul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worries about the election have only grown this week amid reports USPS is warning states that it cannot guarantee all mail-in ballots will arrive in time to be counted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE faces growing number of companies in open revolt over App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/14/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, Fortnite maker Epic Games performed a high-profile stunt against Apple by blatantly ignoring the App Store's payment policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing state ballots might not be delivered in time to be counted...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/931266/pennsylvania-ballots-might-not-delivered-time-counted-postal-service-warns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Postal Service has warned that in Pennsylvania, some mail-in ballots may not be delivered in time to be counted this November. In a July letter to Pennsylvania State Secretary Kathy Boockvar, USPS general counsel Thomas Marshall described the 'risk that ballots requested near the deadline under state law will not be returned by mail in time to be counted under your laws as we understand them,' NBC News reports. The USPS also described Pennsylvania's current deadlines as 'incongruous with the Postal Service's delivery standards,' per Axios. Voters in the swing state can request a mail-in ballot up to Oct. 27, and they have to be received by 8:00 p.m. on Election Day, according to The Hill. But officials in the state are looking to extend the deadline to receive mail-in ballots three days, with Boockvar raising concern in a court filing that 'voters who apply for mail-in ballots in the last week of the application period and return their completed ballot by mail will, through no fault of their own, likely be disenfranchised,' CNN reports. The warning in Pennsylvania came just after President Trump in an interview cited his desire to prevent universal mail-in voting this November, noting that if the Postal Service doesn't get the funding that Democrats are seeking, 'that means you can't have universal mail-in voting, because they're not equipped to have it.' Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAE Sheikh Mohammed saves the day -- or does he?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/512002-uaes-sheikh-mohammed-saves-the-day-or-does-he</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether Netanyahu or Trump will benefit electorally from the agreement between Israel and the UAE is an open question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O to go to bat for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/512110-michelle-obama-to-go-to-bat-for-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former first lady's address at the Democratic convention is expected to shine a harsh light on President Trump while urging Democrats to get out and vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters stage 'wake-up call' outside home of postmaster general...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/512164-dc-protesters-stage-wake-up-call-outside-home-of-postmaster-general</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters angry with the recent actions of Postmaster General Louis DeJoy staged a demonstration outside his home in Washington, D.C., on Saturday, calling for support for the U.S. Postal Service (USPS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delay of game? College football emerges as virus flashpoint...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/512114-delay-of-game-college-football-emerges-as-coronavirus-flashpoint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This fall’s college football season has become the latest flashpoint in the debate over the United States' handling of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof vest sales soar amid surge in NYC shootings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/15/bulletproof-vest-sales-soar-amid-surge-in-nyc-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With bullets flying over Broadway, New Yorkers are buying up bulletproof vests. Midtown dealer Brad Pedell — who runs 221B Tactical — claims sales of body armor are up 80 percent this year compared…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING BLACKOUTS CALI</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worst-heat-wave-years-causes-144343229.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broiling conditions that began Friday in California may rival the deadly seven-day heat event of July 2006.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump losing ground among retirees in must-win Florida...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-losing-ground-among-retirees-013725294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Farr is a staunch 77-year-old Republican in the sunny southern state of Florida, which lures retirees from all over America -- a powerful political bloc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate committee sought investigation of Bannon, raised concerns about Trump family testimony...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senate-committee-sought-investigation-bannon-024424165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Intelligence Committee believed former Trump confidant Stephen K. Bannon may have lied to Congress, according to a letter obtained by The Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 50 Confederate symbols moved, taken down... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/more-50-confederate-symbols-moved-215600118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months since George Floyd died in Minneapolis while in police custody, protests have rippled across the United States, with hundreds of demonstrators rallying against systemic racism and calling for justice. Among some of the more prominent changes sparked by Floyd&amp;#39;s death is the speedy removal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires burn thousands of acres... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lake-ranch-2-fires-burn-170647237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lake fire near Lake Hughes and the Ranch 2 fire above Azusa have forced widespread evacuations and worsened air quality during an epic heat wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School cancelled in Arizona area after 'sick out'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200815014105-o3yue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ARIZONA-SCHOOLS:School cancelled in Arizona area after 'sick out' over reopening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New outbreaks are the norm' says Spain...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200814194223-80mnx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-GERMANY (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-'New outbreaks are the norm' says Spain as COVID-19 travel curbs pile up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizzerias Battling Shortage Of Cheese, Pepperoni...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/08/14/business-booming-at-local-pizzerias-even-as-cheese-pepperoni-harder-to-come-by/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the shortage, business at pizzerias has actually increased as more people look for easy meals to pick up and eat at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Ignore Stimulus Rift, Sowing Worries on Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stocks-shrug-stimulus-rift-sowing-110000266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- This week’s run-up in U.S. stocks toward their highest levels on record seems an anomaly, considering the political breakdown over a $1 trillion-plus fiscal stimulus package, and it’s spurring concerns from Wall Street to Capitol Hill.Federal Reserve officials and private economists alike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting Against Dollar More Popular Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/betting-against-dollar-more-popular-193921169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Betting against the U.S. dollar was already the top second-half trade for currency and rates investors and its popularity is only growing as the greenback tumbles, according to a Bank of America Corp. survey.A weaker dollar was the favorite trade for 36% of the fund managers surveyed this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Crisis Ripples Across Nation as Election Looms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/15/postal-crisis-ripples-across-nation-as-election-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DARBY, Pa. — Each day, when Nick Casselli, the president of a Philadelphia postal workers union, sits down at his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Colleges Move Classes Online, Families Rebel Against Cost...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/15/as-colleges-move-classes-online-families-rebel-against-the-cost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Southern California’s soaring coronavirus caseload forced Chapman University this month to abruptly abandon plans to reopen its campus and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dodges question on QANON conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c972b0201ba3eab039daecefe44ecc92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Friday twice ignored a question about whether he supports QAnon, a convoluted, right-wing, pro-Trump conspiracy theory. A reporter asked the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of sea lions to be killed in Seattle --  to save fish...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9bad3b5a320fd46ba3476f9e39571bfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — U.S. authorities on Friday gave wildlife managers in Washington, Oregon and Idaho permission to start killing hundreds of sea lions in the Columbia River basin in hopes of helping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian fast food chain bets on automated restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/435b022057351e5957b4c1dba457e9f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia (AP) — A Colombian fast food chain is planning to turn its branches into automated restaurants at a moment when the coronavirus pandemic has slammed the food service industry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delays in every state!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ba8699f4094310f44cb2afac958ed1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. Postal Service is warning states coast to coast that it cannot guarantee all ballots cast by mail for the November election will arrive in time to be counted, even if...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
