<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kim's 'grip on NKorea never stronger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14109473/kim-jong-un-north-korea-covid-meth-starving-dirt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korean defections are now at “virtually zero” with Kim Jong-un’s grip never stronger due to a combination of Covid and crystal meth smuggling, The Sun can reveal. The pandemic has made it alm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurt by Lockdowns, CA Small Businesses Push to Recall Gov...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/19/hurt-by-lockdowns-californias-small-businesses-push-to-recall-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Alexandra and Daniela Del Gaudio had never been to a political rally before, let alone one to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingenuity helicopter phones home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/20/world/mars-ingenuity-helicopter-update-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ingenuity helicopter, sidekick and traveling companion to NASA's Perseverance rover, has checked in with a good report and is "operating as expected," according to the agency. It will be the first helicopter to fly on another planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX attacks Joe's dogs for being dirty...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/539710-newsmax-guest-mocks-bidens-senior-dog-champ-unlike-a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax host Greg Kelly took aim at President Biden’s dog Champ on Friday, mocking his appearance during a segment of his show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New legislation would protect drivers who hit protestors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-legislature-oklahoma-city-oklahoma-legislation-238201499e0d4a960ef49b92f25dbb31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — When massive demonstrations against racial injustice erupted across the nation last summer, protesters used an increasingly common tactic to draw attention to their cause:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern Baptists divided over politics, race, LGBTQ policy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-baptist-southern-baptist-convention-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-1b4bce88b58067f341e6e8eef259307f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divisions over race, politics, gender and LGBTQ issues are roiling America’s largest Protestant denomination, the Southern Baptist Convention, ahead of a meeting of its executive committee next...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Era of Black Holes Is Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/02/black-hole-collisions-gravitational-waves/618095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have discovered a black-hole treasure trove that is changing our view of the cosmos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Navy sailors who disarm mines and bombs, learning never stops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailypress.com/military/dp-nw-navy-eod-20210220-rsijyde335frfpm52mg2ogfcuu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailypress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy's explosive ordnance disposal groups take on an expanded role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden declares major disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/20/biden-declares-major-disaster-in-texas-as-state-struggles-with-fallout-from-power-outages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has approved a major disaster declaration for Texas as the state grapples with widespread power outages and water shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Lives of Cuban Surfers Fighting for Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dangerous-lives-cuban-surfers-fighting-042602294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HandoutOur 1958 Toyota Land Cruiser, a car that borders on modern in Cuba, rolled to a stop on the outskirts of the famed Guantanamo Bay naval base. Cuban military men in fatigues approached the rear door where our group, consisting of myself, my filming partners Seth, Marco, and Tyler, and two Cuban surfers named Frank and Yaya, were packed in like sardines with our legs all jammed in a formation we dubbed “the zipper.” While the guardsmen probed around our vehicle, intently eyeing the stack of surfboards strapped precariously to our roof, I found myself thinking of a line from one of the interviews we’d conducted days earlier with Yaya:“It doesn’t matter if it’s old or new, the mark or the brand, when we have a surfboard in our hands it is a treasure.”Over the first three months we’d spent filming Havana Libre, the meaning of this line took on several forms as we began to slowly evolve our understanding of the complicated context in which Cuban surf exists, and this stop was the manifestation of a reality that we’d often imagined but didn’t entirely comprehend. After all, surfing in Cuba was not exactly… legal. The circumstance that enabled us to embark on creating a film about this diehard and underground surf community was the sudden thawing of a hostile Cold War-era relationship between Cuba and the United States. It was the first time in roughly 60 years. Like many, our interest was sparked by the nostalgic images of tropical antiquity and the opportunity to seemingly step into the past, but what captivated us was the pursuit by a younger generation to escape the time capsule and chase their dreams. Inside Frank Gonzalez’s home in west Havana, the first thing I noticed was the faded green walls peeking from the bedrooms that were papered with wrinkled covers from old surf magazines and stickers of American skateboard brands. It was such a familiar collage from my own childhood, but I soon came to learn how much value every image held. When Yaya says surfboards are treasure, her sentiment goes far beyond the board itself. It extends to every morsel of information from the outside world; every image and opportunity to grow more connected to the broader surfing world beyond the blockade. We first heard her line as a commentary about how much passion they had for surfing, but over time it began to represent every obstacle they have to overcome simply to be able to surf.In one of his interviews, Frank commented, “We try to stay as far away from politics as we can, but eventually it always traps you.”The film we set out to make had very little political ambition, but like everything in Cuba, eventually we too were trapped by it. Political tendrils are embedded in the DNA of every Cuban story, and there is no way to tell an honest anthology of surf culture on the island without including politics to some degree. In essence, the blockade is the foundation of their disposition.There is no surf shop in Cuba. The closest thing to resembling one is Frank’s makeshift workshop where he has a collection of assorted chunks of foam and handmade tools, bartered carbon fiber and scraps of fiberglass from boatyards, and other ingredients to make and repair boards that have taken him years to amass. His craft was developed by dissecting every photograph that found its way into Cuba through the bag of some tourist. He’d analyze what the shape of the board should look like, how people positioned their hands to dive under waves, and how it looked as surfers shifted their balance to carve. Without internet access, each piece was vital for taking the next steps forward.This scarcity in material makes the barrier to entry very high. As Frank says, “If you want to be a Cuban surfer, you have to really want it.” On top of the scarcity of material is an equal scarcity of general knowledge. Your average Cuban most likely doesn’t know that a sport called surfing even exists. When traces of surfing did finally reach Cuba, its timing happened to coincide closely with the fall of the Soviet Union, Cuba’s lifeline at the time, and yielded the country’s biggest economic crisis. The ensuing exodus of tens of thousands of Cubans via shoddily built rafts deepened the conflict between Cuba and the United States and transformed the ocean into a highly policed and dangerous place for Cubans to enter. Handout It is important to understand this history because, while there was no signpost explicitly saying “surfing is illegal,” it is the reason that it has been forced to exist in the shadows. For decades, water activities were prohibited and surfers risked incrimination for fear that they were fleeing to America. And this brings us back to Guantanamo, where we sat with bated breath hoping that the soldier reprimanding us doesn’t notice the blinking red light of a recording GoPro that he’d unknowingly repositioned, framing a perfect portrait of himself. One of the men informed us we’d entered into a high-security zone due to our proximity to the American base, and that several days prior they detained a man who had triggered a series of alarms trying to escape on a windsurfing board. It was in this moment that we sort of realized the gravity of our surroundings, and the reality of what it means to be a surfer in Cuba. Throughout the interrogation, their attention kept resting back on our cargo on the roof, and, despite all our camera gear and computers, we were all hoping for the same thing.“Please don’t take their boards…”After about an hour we were told we could carry on with our voyage. They said they’d be monitoring us and under no circumstances were we allowed to enter the water anywhere along the coast, nor were we allowed to take our cameras out at any point. We pulled off the road just after our stop and after almost a thousand miles of coastal exploration, we could see a river mouth in the distance, opening into the bay with a beautiful peeling wave breaking down the presumably land-mined shores of the base. We took a moment to soak it in, and then hit the road looking for something new. HAVANA LIBRE is world premiering as the opening night virtual film at the upcoming Big Sky Documentary Film Festival in Missoula, Montana, on Feb. 19Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC tax agency subpoenaed in Trump criminal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-investigation-subpoena-excl/exclusive-new-york-city-tax-agency-subpoenaed-in-trump-criminal-probe-idUSKBN2AK037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan District Attorney’s Office has subpoenaed a New York City property tax agency as part of a criminal investigation into Donald Trump’s company, the agency confirmed on Friday, suggesting prosecutors are examining the former president’s efforts to reduce his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSE: Taiwan scrambles air force again after Chinese exercises...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210220140812-2cf3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (PIX):Taiwan scrambles air force again after Chinese exercises in South China Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ERASING 'FORMER GUY'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-biden-cabinet-iran-nuclear-b7838bf96681674211b2b2b3a421385e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Joe Biden walked into the Oval Office for the first time as president a month ago, his pens were ready. Already. Lining a fine wooden box, they bore the presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reports world's first case of human infection with H5N8 bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-birdflu-russia/russia-reports-worlds-first-case-of-human-infection-with-h5n8-bird-flu-idUSKBN2AK0DU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has registered the first case of a strain of bird flu virus named A(H5N8) being passed to humans from birds and has reported the matter to the World Health Organization (WHO), Anna Popova, head of consumer health watchdog Rospotrebnadzor, said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech industry looking to replace smartphone -- all eyes on APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/20/apple-facebook-microsoft-battle-to-replace-smartphone-with-ar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry watchers and participants think that Apple has a good chance to validated and revolutionize augmented reality like it did with smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS 'getting closer' to precious oil reserves as terrorists launch savage attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-getting-closer-precious-oil-23532757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorists have amassed a fighting force and taken on Government forces in the southern African country, leading to brutal massacres and the arrival of foreign mercenaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More men suffering from infertility than ever before...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/20/why-more-men-are-suffering-from-infertility-than-ever-before/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sperm counts in Western countries have dropped by more than 50 percent since the 1970s. At the same time, men’s problems with conceiving are going up: Erectile dysfunction is increasing and testost…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year After Crash, Pandemic Losers Are New Winners...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/a-year-after-covid-crash-pandemic-losers-are-the-new-winners/ar-BB1dQHmV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after Covid-19 reordered world markets, sparking a brutal selloff for many stocks and creating new lockdown darlings, the prospect of vaccine-led reflation is turning the tide for the pandemic’s main laggards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Dangerous Network of Backstreet Castrators, Cutters, Eunuch-Makers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-dangerous-global-network-of-backstreet-castrators-cutters-and-eunuch-makers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast got an unprecedented look at the world of backstreet castrations where people desperate to have genitalia altered or removed undergo risky, illicit operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Russian court, Navalny caged and angry but far from silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-a-Russian-court-Alexei-Navalny-is-caged-and-15965827.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny took time in court this past week to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Will 15 Million Listeners Go Now?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/20/where-will-rush-limbaughs-15-million-listeners-go-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So who now takes the place of Rush Limbaugh as the media ringmaster of the right? The answer, most likely,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford on Wearing Same Ripped Jeans and Allowing Self to 'Be Unproductive'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/20/tom-ford-on-wearing-the-same-ripped-jeans-and-allowing-himself-to-be-unproductive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until last week, Tom Ford — designer, film director and chairman of the Council of Fashion Designers of America —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE fires another lead AI ethics researcher...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-fires-another-lead-ai-023400207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google said Friday it fired a lead artificial intelligence ethics researcher, following controversy last year over the tech giant's dismissal of a Black colleague who was an outspoken diversity advocate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America has sent five rovers to Mars -- when will humans follow?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/america-sent-five-rovers-mars-023628925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its impeccable landing on Thursday, NASA's Perseverance became the fifth rover to reach Mars -- so when can we finally expect the long-held goal of a crewed expedition to materialize?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should the rich pay for the pandemic? Argentina thinks so. Other countries are taking a look...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Should-the-rich-pay-for-the-pandemic-Argentina-15964581.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUENOS AIRES - At his colonial-era estate in central Argentina, Gabriel De Raedemaeker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite security concerns, online voting advances...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/02/17/despite-security-concerns-online-voting-advances</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In nine states, some jurisdictions have allowed voting via computer or app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarcity of niche biotech ingredients slows covid vaccine rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/why-grandparents-can-e2-80-99t-find-vaccines-scarcity-of-niche-biotech-ingredients/ar-BB1dOpBh?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Limited supply of key ingredients called lipids has constrained coronavirus vaccine manufacturing and contributed to the frustratingly slow rollout of shots in the United States and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejoins Paris accord, vows to make up for lost time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9277269/World-leaders-applaud-US-formal-return-Paris-climate-pact.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US' return became official Friday, a month after Biden said America wants back in. Donald Trump announced its withdrawal from the Paris accord in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes lawsuit against CNN thrown out...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/539681-nunes-lawsuit-against-cnn-thrown-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Friday threw out a libel lawsuit filed by Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.) against CNN over coverage saying he was involved an effort to dig up dirt on now-President Biden regarding dealings with Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vaccine-gate' roils Peru: Politicians, families and friends secretly got shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vaccine-gate-roils-peru-politicians-015226078.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seizing on COVID-19 to expand its global influence, China has emerged as a major player in the vaccine sweepstakes — particularly in Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declaring 'America is back,' Biden tries to regain Europe's trust...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/declaring-america-back-biden-tries-195859319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden officially reaffirmed U.S. fealty to the transatlantic alliance at two global conferences Friday, seeking to regain allies' trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as Texas homeowners hit with electricity bills as high as $17,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2371047/texas-homeowners-electricity-bills-high-demand-freeze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS homeowners have been hit with more than brutal winter storms – they are getting accompanying massive electricity bills.  Electricity bills for Texans shot up as high as $17,000 per…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED probing Cruz flight data leak...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/united-probing-cruz-flight-data-leak-470375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of United employees have access to customer flight data, but leaks about individual travelers' flight plans are rare in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX attacks Biden's dogs for being dirty...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/aliciasadowski6/status/1362930155140751363</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of planning caused cold catastrophe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/weather-texas-2a3095311cf760fb9f1a6d2e835e5bc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week’s killer freeze in the U.S. was no surprise. Government and private meteorologists saw it coming, some nearly three weeks in advance. They started sounding warnings two weeks ahead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trip tests durability of scandal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ted-cruz-elections-texas-0e858493599cd3dee8f6bb568ec8a645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Ted Cruz's political career already featured many surprise twists before a jaunt to Mexico this week brought him a new level of notoriety. The Texas senator was once the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside WIKIPEDIA's bias: Socialism whitewashed, communist atrocities buried...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/wikipedia-bias-socialism-pages-whitewashed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big tech is under fire for bias and censorship, but one outlet has escaped much scrutiny: Wikipedia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Underground militant son now San Fran DA, fighting for dad's release from jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9277335/DA-son-seeks-release-father-imprisoned-fatal-81-heist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco District Attorney Chesa Boudin (left) is seeking clemency from New York Gov Andrew Cuomo for his father, David Gilbert, who is serving a 75-year term for the Brink's robbery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE removes Ohio committee video, citing 'misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/public-health-misinformation-coronavirus-pandemic-ohio-bills-fe1a3028ab5dbdc1072e4558e9aec760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Legislative testimony made Wednesday in support of a GOP-backed effort to limit public health orders made by Ohio's governor was removed from YouTube after the service deemed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin opposes Biden's budget chief, imperiling nomination...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/joe-manchin-comes-out-against-neera-tanden-biden-s-omb-n1258387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democrat's opposition is a significant blow to her prospects of confirmation to head the Office of Management and Budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol riot involved wider conspiracy with Oath Keepers; 6 more charged...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/six-more-oath-keepers-charged-in-wider-plot-for-capitol-riot/ar-BB1dQ5CS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six more people with links to the Oath Keepers were charged for their alleged roles in last month’s violent breach of the U.S. Capitol, as prosecutors pursued a wider conspiracy case against the far-right militia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last year showed police aren't always heroes or villains...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-last-year-showed-Americans-that-the-police-15962553.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the middle of former president Donald Trump's impeachment trial, House Speaker Nancy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HOTEL WORKERS TELL ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2021/02/19/trump-hotel-employees-tell-all-what-it-was-really-like-serving-right-wing-elite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four years' worth of stories about VIP visits and grooming protocols, palm-greasing, rotten vegetables, and that time they lost Steve Mnuchin’s coat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible new images of Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/19/world/mars-rover-new-images-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After safely landing on the surface of Mars Thursday, NASA's Perseverance rover has sent back a never-before-seen view: what it looks like to land on Mars. The rover also returned some new color images of its landing site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL asking for 100% increase in TV rights payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/19/nfl-asking-for-100percent-increase-on-tv-rights-disney-pushing-back-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC, CBS and Fox are likely to accept increases closer to 100% than Disney, which already pays a high price tag for its Monday Night Football package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lust To 'Cancel' Should Spark Soul Searching...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/19/americans-lust-to-cancel-one-another-should-spark-soul-searching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the result of our overly politicized culture where many people like to shame and destroy their enemies, but it is undermining the benefits of free and open dialogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER deplatformed founder...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/parler-bans-former-ceo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I know it’s a ban because I know how the architecture works. I can’t log in anymore.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asylum-seekers waiting in Mexico released in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-mexico-coronavirus-pandemic-el-paso-immigration-ca4f1ed0bc6ce8ff72484d8c70b08a02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The U.S. government on Friday released 25 asylum-seekers into the country with notices to appear in court, ending their long waits in Mexico and marking a milestone in unraveling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Achieve Real-Time Communication With Lucid Dreamers in Breakthrough...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4admym/scientists-achieve-real-time-communication-with-lucid-dreamers-in-breakthrough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International scientists have unlocked a new and exciting avenue to explore the world of dreams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food supply nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-facing-food-supply-nightmare-192425383.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Restaurants in Texas are throwing out expired food, grocery stores are closing early amid stock shortages and residents are struggling to find basic necessities as a cold blast continues to upend supply chains.At Tarka Indian Kitchen, a chain with eight locations in Texas, fresh veggies and meat were discarded after the chain was shuttered for days. The same is true for Coolgreens, which sells salads and sandwiches, while Milkshake Concepts had to throw out inventory due to a burst pipe. Similar stories are piling up during a historic cold spell that has knocked out power and snarled roads.At a Whole Foods Market store in the Woodlands, Texas, two women were overheard exchanging tips on where to find a gallon of milk, while another person asked a store employee about buying the entire supply of bottled water.The situation is so dire in Houston, a major city for dining out, some people have running lists of restaurants that are open and have food supplies. Late Thursday, a canvass of restaurants in the area showed several were either out of food, unexpectedly closed or only available for large group orders. People were complaining about difficulties using UberEats and DoorDash as a result.Read More: Texas Water Outages Affect 14.4 Million People: Energy UpdateTarka Chief Executive Officer Tinku Saini said via email that the issues extend beyond expired food. “We’ve transitioned to working through the water challenges -- access to water, low water pressure and boil-water notices in some areas. Then, we are navigating the obstacles with suppliers as they determine the safest way to deliver our products.”The challenges are further limiting residents’ access to food as grocery store shelves remain barren in many areas. Supermarket chains such as Kroger Co. have implemented purchase limits on items such as eggs and milk, while HEB Grocery Co. said the weather is causing “severe disruption in the food supply chain.”Some chains that have managed to remain open have been closing before sunset so shelves can be restocked overnight. Hard-to-find items in the Houston area include beef, bread, deli meats, frozen pizzas and milk. A visit to an HEB store in the city’s northern suburbs on Thursday afternoon found the produce section with little more than a few bags of oranges.Target Corp. closed three stores in Texas and was restocking food and water in stores that are still open. Amazon.com Inc.’s Whole Foods Market chain is working to “reopen all stores in the coming days,” a spokesperson said in an email.Indeed, there’s hope operations may return to normal soon as services come back online and temperatures rise. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas, which manages the state’s grid, said it had returned to normal operations Friday.Related: Gas Stations Still Dark as Texas Emerges From FreezeStill, many restaurants, which have already endured a nightmare year from pandemic-driven shutdowns, face obstacles to reopening. Some companies are trying to adapt in the meantime.Dickey’s Barbecue Pit, which has 142 Texas locations, said it could be a week or two until it is back to normal hours and full menus, though operations are resuming at most of its restaurants. The company has altered its menu and is going directly to its suppliers when possible to pick up food.On Monday, as the lights flickered at its 80-year-old original location in Dallas, staff began giving away food to first responders instead of letting it expire.“With the understanding that our food is no good to anyone if it’s spoiled and these heroes need it most, I encourage anyone who is able to do the same,” Dickey’s CEO Laura Rea Dickey said.(Updates with details of food shortage beginning in third paragraph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Dogs Discovered Near Russian Chemical Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k7a9an/blue-dogs-russia-chemical-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pictures of the stray dogs with vibrant blue fur went viral on Russian social media. But there’s a nice ending to this tail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Bill's 'SILENCE OF THE LAMBS' Home to Open to Overnight Guests...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/02/18/buffalo-bills-home-in-the-silence-of-the-lambs-will-soon-be-open/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are brave enough, you will soon be able to book a stay at Buffalo Bill's home in "The Silence of the Lambs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Will Children's Immune Systems Look Like In Post-Pandemic World?</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/02/18/what-will-our-kids-post-pandemic-immune-systems-be-like/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once we're beyond the pandemic, what happens to our immune systems? Will it affect how often our kids get sick? Dr. Gigi Chawla, head of general pediatrics at Children's Minnesota, answers these Good Questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home intruder killed by armed 12-year-old; Hero saves grandmother...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/19/home-intruder-killed-by-armed-12-year-old-hero-sav/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 12-year old boy who jumped to his grandmother’s defense during a North Carolina home invasion managed to kill one of two intruders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC calls for 'full investigation' into nursing home scandal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/19/aoc-calls-for-full-investigation-in-cuomo-nursing-home-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — NY Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez called for an investigation into Gov. Andrew Cuomo’s mounting nursing home crisis on Friday. “I support our state’s return to co-equa…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
