<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Social media nightmare of cures, claims, snake-oil sales...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/why-novel-coronavirus-became-social-media-nightmare-014917035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest reputational risk Facebook and other social media companies had expected in 2020 was fake news surrounding the US presidential election. Be it foreign or domestic in origin, the misinformation threat seemed familiar, perhaps even manageable. The novel coronavirus, however, has opened up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals turn to snorkel masks... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/hospitals-turn-snorkel-masks-ease-respirator-overload-020738689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As hospitals face an overload of COVID-19 patients struggling to breathe, innovative medical staff are turning to snorkelling masks from sports stores to stop their lungs collapsing. The idea started in Italy, the European country worst-hit by the coronavirus pandemic, with hospitals in other nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-virus measures spark Mideast fears of setback in liberties... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/anti-virus-measures-spark-mideast-fears-setback-liberties-022504291.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armoured vehicles in the streets, hundreds arrested, smartphone surveillance -- sweeping measures to fight the coronavirus have raised concerns in the Middle East over the erosion of already threatened human rights. As the world battles the COVID-19 pandemic, more than three billion people are now living</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMATIC PAY CUT HITS TABS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ami-tabloids-are-on-a-ventilator-after-david-pecker-enforces-brutal-staff-pay-cut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Pecker sent a memo to staff on Saturday, claiming coronavirus was the reason for slashing their pay by 23 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Cuomo Gives Rousing Speech to National Guard...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/news/cuomo-announces-4-more-temporary-hospitals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo said Friday morning that he will ask the federal government for permission to build four more emergency hospitals in New York City to deal with the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  Belarus football league plays on...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/belarus-ploughs-lone-furrow-over-coronavirus-football-league-185531425--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the rest of Europe shuts up shop to combat the new coronavirus, Belarus remains resolutely open for business. The Belarus President Alexander Lukashenko has dismissed the global health crisis as a &amp;quot;psychosis&amp;quot;, and refuses to follow the example of much of the globe by imposing a lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's toll tops 10,000 despite long lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-says-virus-response-fateful-eu-104005657.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus toll in Italy shot past 10,000 on Saturday and showed little sign of slowing despite a 16-day lockdown. Italy now looks certain to extend its economically debilitating -- and emotionally stressful -- business closures and the ban on public gatherings past their April 3 deadline. Italians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico asks residents to stay home for month...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200329005045-flxb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO-TALLY (URGENT):Mexico asks residents to stay home for a month to slow coronavirus as cases rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DEATH TOLL DOUBLES IN TWO DAYS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200329002442-prcmb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 7-Trump drops idea of New York lockdown as U.S. death count crosses 2,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Confirmed Cases' Almost Meaningless Metric...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/confirmed-coronavirus-cases-almost-meaningless-123550415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- It doesn’t matter that the United States surpassed China this week in reported Covid-19 cases because those numbers (83,507 and 81,782 respectively as of March 26) don’t tell us how many people actually became infected in either country. Nor do they tell us how fast the disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope's special blessing: God turns everything to our good...</title>
      <link>https://www.vaticannews.va/en/pope/news/2020-03/pope-francis-urbi-et-orbi-blessing-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vaticannews.va&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis delivers an extraordinary blessing “To the City and to the World” on Friday to pray for an end to the Covid-19 coronavirus pandemic. In ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses Buy Spy Software to Keep Tabs on Remote Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2020/03/27/covid-19-bosses-panic-buy-spy-software-to-keep-tabs-on-remote-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email came from the boss. We’re watching you, it told Axos Financial Inc employees working from home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where Hope Finally Made a Comeback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorker Tries to Recreate 'Italy Magic' By Singing Out Window,  Told to 'Shut The F**k Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020/03/video-quarantined-new-yorker-tries-to-recreate-italy-magic-by-singing-out-window-but-is-told-to-shut-the-fk-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, he tried...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO WARNED WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/604376/andrew-cuomo-new-york-coroanvirus-slams-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Donald Trump pulled back from a plan to quarantine New York, New Jersey and Connecticut on Saturday, hours after NY Governor Andrew Cuomo blasted the plan as “illegal” and a &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Entertainment, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People arrested for violating stay-at-home orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/03/26/breaking-news/kauai-police-launch-checkpoints-to-enforce-lockdown-compliance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Keys closed to visitors... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Florida-Keys-which-welcomes-all-to-come-as-you-15162424.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. - The Overseas Highway into the Florida Keys was blocked off to visitors Friday, an acknowledgment that tourism - the lifeblood of the islands - will have to be temporarily sacrificed as part of the effort to stop the spread of the novel coronavirus.  The move follows a crescendo of actions from local officials, who a week ago ordered tourists to leave and all hotels and short-term rentals to close, and comes as part of a broader attempt across the Sunshine State at a time when spring breakers are usually descending.  Monroe County has had 14 reported cases of coronavirus infection and no deaths, but residents said they've noticed more and more people coming to the Keys recently from Miami-Dade County, which has the most cases in the state, at 744.  "It breaks my heart," said Elizabeth Moscynski, president of the Key Largo Chamber of Commerce. "It's so tough, because we're such a friendly place. Now we have to tell people they can't come down."  Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis announced at a news briefing Friday that he would be expanding restrictions on travelers and tourists entering the state from areas of the country hardest hit by the virus.  He said he was adding Louisiana to an earlier executive order that requires air travelers from New York, New Jersey and Connecticut to self-isolate for two weeks upon arrival. Travelers from nearby Louisiana, which is also experiencing an outbreak, will now be required to isolate as well, including those traveling by car.  Since his earlier order, 3,400 travelers from the New York area have been screened in Florida, and there has been a "dramatic reduction in air traffic," DeSantis said.  The governor also announced a two-week ban on new vacation rentals, though it was not immediately clear how state officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyotes walking streets of San Francisco...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/living-in-sf/article/Coyotes-are-being-seen-on-the-empty-streets-15159105.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While families' cats and dogs are enjoying the upside of spending days with their owners working from home during the coronavirus shutdown, wild coyotes in San Francisco are reportedly also taking advantage of the benefits of a suddenly empty city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While Bay Area shelters in place, construction on mansions and luxury condos continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/media/While-the-Bay-Area-shelters-in-place-1702055.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens If Workers Cutting Up Meat Get Sick?</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/what-happens-if-workers-cutting-up-the-nations-meat-get-sick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As meatpackers rush to meet demand, their employees are starting to get COVID-19. But some workers say they’re going to work ill because they don’t have paid sick days and can be penalized for staying home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it.&amp;#160;He has written about the investigation into Russia&amp;#8217;s election interference, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts, decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea and the impeachment of the president. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post&amp;#8217;s original story breaking the Ken Starr investigation of the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper&amp;#8217;s lead writer on the subsequent impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton.&amp;#160;During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush&amp;#8217;s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama&amp;#8217;s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five&amp;#160;books, most recently&amp;#160;"Impeachment: An American History" (Modern Library, 2018) with Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali and Jeffrey A. Engel. He also wrote&amp;#160;&amp;#8220;Obama: The Call of History&amp;#8221; (New York Times/Callaway, 2017), a finalist for an NAACP Image Award for Outstanding Literary Work;&amp;#160;&amp;#8220;Days of Fire: Bush and Cheney in the White House&amp;#8221; (Doubleday, 2013), which was named one of the five Best Non-Fiction Books of 2013 by The New York Times Book Review; &amp;#8220;The Breach: Inside the Impeachment and Trial of William Jefferson Clinton&amp;#8221; (Scribner, 2000), a New York Times bestseller; and, with Ms. Glasser, &amp;#8220;Kremlin Rising: Vladimir Putin&amp;#8217;s Russia and the End of Revolution&amp;#8221; (Scribner, 2005), named one of the Best Books of 2005 by The Washington Post Book World.&amp;#160;He will publish his sixth book in May 2020, &amp;#8220;The Man Who Ran Washington: The Life and Times of James A. Baker III,&amp;#8221; co-authored with Ms. Glasser and published by Doubleday. Mr. Baker has won all three major awards devoted to White House reporting: the Gerald R. Ford Prize for Distinguished Coverage of the Presidency (twice), the Aldo Beckman Memorial Award (twice) and the Merriman Smith Memorial Award. Mr. Baker is also a political analyst for MSNBC and a regular panelist on PBS&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;Washington Week.&amp;#8221; A native of the Washington area, Mr. Baker attended Oberlin College and worked for The Washington Times for two years before joining The Post in 1988 as a Virginia reporter. Ms. Glasser is now a staff writer for The New Yorker and the two live in Washington with their son Theodore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump&amp;#8217;s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile "What Is Hillary Clinton Afraid Of?" Her hobbies include singing, and she is married with three children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SMITH</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/ben-smith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Smith is the media columnist. He joined The New York Times in 2020 after eight years as founding editor in chief of BuzzFeed News. Before that, he covered politics for Politico, The New York Daily News, The New York Observer and The New York Sun. Email: ben.smith@nytimes.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BACKS OFF 'QUARANTINE'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-considering-enforceable-quarantine-n-y-parts-n-j-connecticut-n1171186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don’t know how that could be legally enforceable,” New York Gov. Cuomo said, adding, “I don’t even like the sound of it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside president's push to reopen country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-trumps-risky-push-to-reopen-the-country-amid-the-coronavirus-crisis/ar-BB11PMHk?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GOOD NEWS FILE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NEWS Poll Shows Biden CRUSHING Trump By 25 Points in Swing Counties...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-news-poll-shows-joe-biden-crushing-trump-by-25-points-in-swing-counties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Fox News poll shows former Vice President Joe Biden leading President Donald Trump by a crushing 25 point margin in counties that were close in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not since Black Plague have Jerusalem's holy alleys fallen so still...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Not-since-the-Black-Plague-have-Jerusalem-s-holy-15162438.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - Adeeb Joudeh, standing in front of the now-locked Church of the Holy Sepulcher in Jerusalem's Old City, had a pretty specific answer when asked when the church last closed to the public like this:  "It was the year 1349, at the time of the Black Plague," he said, holding the key that had shut things down a day earlier and back in the 14th century as well.  They measure time differently here in the oldest section of one of the world's oldest cities, the ancient, dispute-riddled and spiritually dense center of three major religions. Yet it takes an eternity to recall the last time Christians, Jews and Muslims, each claiming various overlapping quarters of the Old City, were kept from their eternal rounds.  But coronavirus, like the medieval pandemic before it, has all but silenced this bustling Holy Land hot spot. The walls built by King Herod, the Crusaders and others (aided by the flashing lights of police cars at the gates) keep out the throngs of tourists and pilgrims who would normally teem through this UNESCO World Heritage site, especially in the weeks before Passover, Easter and Ramadan.  The steep, narrow lanes are empty but for police patrols and the relatively few residents who live in the Old City full time. Worship sites of all kinds are closed, most notably the Church of the Holy Sepulcher, built on the site where Jesus is said to have been buried and resurrected; the Western Wall, the most sacred place of prayer for Jews; and al-Aqsa Mosque, the third-holiest site in Islam.  Here, for the guardians of all that is sacred, the stillness feels like a necessary evil.  "To see the holy church closed is very, very, very sad for me," said Joudeh, one day after getting orders from Israeli health officials to swing the big doors shut indefinitely. "All the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California braces for cruelest month...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-28/how-bad-will-the-next-few-weeks-for-california-as-coronavirus-cases-explode</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two months after California's first confirmed case of the deadly COVID-19, the state is preparing to confront what public health authorities agree that April will be a month that portends a peak in sickness and death. How cruel remains to be seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having more unusual dreams? You may not be alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.largsandmillportnews.com/news/national-news/18339202.unusual-dreams-lockdown-may-not-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.largsandmillportnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Mark Blagrove, who specialises in sleep and dreams, said people may be having more intense or emotional experiences in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S OLDEST MAN CELEBRATES 112TH BIRTHDAY IN ISOLATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-03-28/worlds-oldest-man-bob-weighton-celebrating-his-112th-birthday-in-isolation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL I$ COMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/antoinegara/2020/03/27/billionaire-investor-bill-ackman-explains-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a press release, billionaire investor Bill Ackman explains a wild and crazy month that left his firm up 0.2%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in coronavirus quarantine runs into street naked and bites woman to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/man-coronavirus-quarantine-runs-street-21773158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 35-year-old man is reported to have started tearing his clothes off after a week of self-isolation before running into the street and launching his attack on a sleeping woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK using drones with speakers to force people inside...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/coronavirus-uk-council-deploys-talking-21771362</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neath and Port Talbot Council shared a video of its drone being tested showing how it will bark orders at people who ignore orders to stay inside during the coronavirus crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military in charge of protecting homeland isolated in Cheyenne mountain bunker...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8162937/Coronavirus-drives-army-command-teams-infamous-Cheyenne-mountain-bunker.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military teams that monitor foreign missile and warplane threats to the United States are isolated at a number of military sites, including Cheyenne Mountain in Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots erupt in Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8162773/Chinas-coronavirus-epicentre-Wuhan-lifts-lockdown-travel-restrictions-time-two-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking footage showed a mob overturning a police van on a bridge linking Wuhan, which is the capital of Hubei Province, and neighbouring Jiangxi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 26 FOOT sneeze zone: Social distancing limit at least four times too short?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8162697/Social-distancing-EIGHT-metres-avoid-coronavirus-risk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public are being asked to keep a distance of at least 6ft 6in (2metres) but a new study by the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) suggests the gap should be four times bigger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden Warns Government Surveillance Amid COVID-19 Could Be Long Lasting... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/snowden-warns-government-surveillance-amid-covid-19-could-be-long-lasting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governments could look for reasons to continue tracking people's activity, he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADER OR TRAITOR?  Ackman says accusations he tried to drive down market on CNBC are 'absurd'... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/27/bill-ackman-says-his-cnbc-interview-was-bullish-denies-harming-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The idea that my appearance pushed the market down an additional 4% that day is absurd," Ackman told investors on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rats swarm New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-new-orleans-rats-precautions-streets-empty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With restaurants closed save for take-out service, far less food waste is being discarded in the city's alleyways, driving the local rodent population out into the open to search for scraps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Create Web Portal to Inform on Neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2020/03/28/uk-police-create-web-portal-to-inform-on-lockdown-violations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British police force has set up a website for the public to inform on people suspected of breaking the national lockdown rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan is a national political reporter at Axios. He writes the weekly Axios Sneak Peek newsletter and covers both ends of Pennsylvania Ave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcgis.com/apps/opsdashboard/index.html#/bda7594740fd40299423467b48e9ecf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcgis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/gtconway3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest articles from Larry Elder on Townhall.com featuring conservative political commentary and news on today's trending topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin 'one of most powerful Cabinet members in modern history'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/905240/coronavirus-stimulus-make-mnuchin-most-powerful-cabinet-members-modern-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin will gain some unprecedented power from the coronavirus relief bill he helped write. The House is set to pass a stimulus bill that addresses economic shortfalls caused by the COVID-19 pandemic on Friday (or possibly Saturday). It'll send individual checks to Americans and billions of dollars to institutions and businesses, and with Mnuchin overseeing it all, it'll make him 'one of the most powerful Cabinet members in modern history,' The Washington Post writes. Mnuchin has been at the forefront of congressional negotiations surrounding the stimulus bill since the start, steering it from its trillion-dollar beginnings to a final total more than double that cost. A highlight of the bill is its $1,200 checks for individual Americans. Mnuchin will be responsible for ensuring those checks actually get distributed, and has so far been hopeful â€” perhaps unrealistically so â€” that they'll be out by April. The bill also contains a $500 billion funding program, and Mnuchin will oversee how it's distributed to local and state governments, as well as businesses, the Post notes. He'll undoubtedly face pressure from corporate executives looking for bailouts from that fund, and will have to weigh those pleas alongside the needs of taxpayers. Mnuchin will remain 'under constant scrutiny by Democrats, Republicans, a new inspector general, a new congressional oversight panel, as well as [President] Trump' as these disbursals go on, the Post notes. But he's so far gotten both sides of the aisle and the president onboard with the bill, even as Trump reportedly fielded dozens of calls complaining about what was inside it. Read more at The Washington Post. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Daily presidential tracking polls...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Who Mocked Self-Quarantining On Socials --  Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/2020/03/28/coronavirus-pandemic-21-year-old-tests-positive-online-post-bragging-not-social-distancing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tennessee woman who once mocked self-quarantining and social distancing during the coronavirus [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID...</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.idrudgereport.iDrudgeReportUniversal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;play.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, Android will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allows results in alerts being sent to your phone whenever there is a siren, new banner or a highlighted headline (e.g. colored red.) Review these urgent headlines anytime by tapping on the urgent headlines button (bell with lines under it.) Then to modify which alerts you receive by tapping on the settings (gear) icon. *** SCROLL TO TOP *** Tap on the reload button.  *** COLUMN SWITCHING (phones) *** Tap on the columns icon once to be taken to the top of the first column. Tap again for the top of the second column. Tap for the third column. Tap one more time and you'll be brought to the top. Repeat as desired. A personal response for those who tap on the Notifications Button &gt; Settings Button &gt; Tap "App Support" for comments, bug reports or suggestions for improvement. Posting bugs in the comments may not get the attention they deserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funder Scored 10,000% Return!</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/03/hedge-fund-bill-ackman-profit-coronavirus-market-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Ackman is a vocal advocate for imposing a 30-day nationwide shutdown to combat COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
First known cat infected...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/27/first-known-cat-infected-with-coronavirus-reported-in-belgium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sick pet in Liège tested positive after showing classic symptoms of COVID-19 — including difficulty breathing — a week after its owner first fell sick, health officials told a press…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Soulless and disgusting'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/26/the-rich-are-shaming-themselves-in-a-time-of-coronavirus-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the global economy craters, as the gap between the haves and have-nots is now one of life and death, the one percent is playing to type and doing what they do best: profiteering. Just days after…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW SULLIVAN</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/author/andrew-sullivan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View an archive of articles by Andrew Sullivan for Daily Intelligencer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scared medical workers decry lack of protection...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-medical-workers-decry-abysmal-lack-coronavirus-protection-061827504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medical staff in America's coronavirus hotbed New York are struggling with long hours and a dire need for protective equipment -- and as infections surge, they increasingly fear for their own safety. The same week the United States became the new epicenter of the pandemic -- with about 120,000 confirmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super-spreader' guru puts Indian villages on high alert...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/super-spreader-guru-puts-indian-villages-high-alert-092109976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 15,000 people who may have caught the coronavirus from a 'super-spreader' guru are under strict quarantine in northern India after the Sikh religious leader died of COVID-19. The 70-year-old guru, Baldev Singh, had returned from a trip to Europe's virus epicentre Italy and Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightfall brings nightmares in Rome's hospitals,...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/romes-hospitals-nightfall-brings-nightmares-fear-death-220312050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clad in a white overall, hospital director Antonino Marchese paints a difficult picture. "Other patients have probably been infected and not even realised it and have recovered," says Marchese, a shock of white hair framing a face half covered by a mask. One coronavirus sufferer who recovered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhode Island Police Hunt Down New Yorkers Seeking Refuge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rhode-island-police-hunt-down-211405349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Rhode Island police began stopping cars with New York plates Friday. On Saturday, the National Guard will help them conduct house-to-house searches to find people who traveled from New York and demand 14 days of self-quarantine.“Right now we have a pinpointed risk,” Governor Gina Raimondo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We let ourselves get caught up in things'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-faces-coronavirus-tempest-alone-st-peters-square-193023795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis stood alone in vast Saint Peter's Square Friday to bless Catholics around the world suffering under the coronavirus pandemic, urging people to ease their fears through faith. In a historic first, the Argentine performed the rarely recited "Urbi et Orbi" blessing from the steps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Oklahoma plains, an island of near normality in pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oklahoma-plains-island-near-normality-110140413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On red cobbled Main Street in Guymon, the biggest town in Oklahoma's panhandle, Jesus Ruiz gives "high and tight" hair cuts as a red, white and blue barber's pole turns lazily outside. About half the customers in the barber shop work at the busy pork processing plant in Guymon, a majority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's war with virus is no joke anymore...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnson-war-coronavirus-no-joke-113742710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For Boris Johnson, as for others, it started with a cough and a fever.The British prime minister did what he was told by the most senior medic in the land and took a test. Johnson was in his Downing Street apartment at midnight on Thursday when the result came through: he’d tested positive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic infects Europe with 'germ of division'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/epidemic-infects-europe-germ-division-133819804.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union has faced and survived a series of existential threats over the years but the coronavirus epidemic has exposed old wounds that could yet prove fatal. A debt crisis in Mediterranean countries, a series of refugee influxes and the ongoing saga on Brexit all rattled the European project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last flight to Bangkok: 'If I die, I want to die in my country'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200328115401-ax1sp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SINGAPORE-THAILAND (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Last flight to Bangkok: 'If I die, I want to die in my country'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia tightens quarantine rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200328000343-x7jvf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA:Australia tightens quarantine rules to combat coronavirus, warns of fines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland blocks roads to Helsinki...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200327214859-ttfb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FINLAND (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Finland blocks roads to Helsinki to curb coronavirus spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian diplomats instigated killing of dissident in Istanbul...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200327201312-k2k1h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-IRAN/KILLING (EXCLUSIVE, TV):EXCLUSIVE-Iranian diplomats instigated killing of dissident in Istanbul, Turkish officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLOBUCHAR: Husband Coughing Up Blood...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/03/27/he-was-coughing-up-blood-sen-amy-klobuchar-on-husbands-recovery-from-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"At the beginning I kind of believed him, like, 'Ahh no problem, it's a cold.' I'm sure that's what he thought. You know how guys can be, and that's how he was," she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve's Balance Sheet Tops $5 Trillion for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/federal-balance-sheet-tops-5-210123506.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Federal Reserve’s balance sheet topped $5 trillion for the first time amid the U.S. central bank’s aggressive efforts to cushion debt markets against the coronavirus outbreak through large-scale bond-buying programs.Total assets held by the Fed rose by $586 billion to $5.25 trillion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Survived Spanish Flu, Depression, Holocaust.  They Have Some Advice...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/28/they-survived-the-spanish-flu-the-depression-and-the-holocaust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of us, it is almost impossible to comprehend the ferocity and regularity with which life was upended during</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis Awakens Sleeping Giant: China's Youth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/28/coronavirus-crisis-awakens-a-sleeping-giant-chinas-youth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students have flooded social media to organize donations for Chinese doctors battling the coronavirus epidemic. Workers have marched in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Stress-Bought All the Baby Chickens...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/28/america-stress-bought-all-the-baby-chickens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For chicken hatcheries, the weeks leading up to Easter are always the busiest. Spring is in the air for people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newfound respect for life?</title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/church-in-the-usa/2020/03/new-york-cardinal-hopes-coronavirus-crisis-stirs-newfound-respect-for-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cruxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's Cardinal says he hopes the global pandemic will lead to a renewed appreciation of human life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE APP IPHONE, IPAD...</title>
      <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/official-drudge-report-free/id375614185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.apple.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‎Welcome to the all new version 6 of the one and only official app of the Drudge Report. Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, iOS will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping "Allow" results in alerts being sent to your phone whenever the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRIES HOPE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ebe632a7b354362c22f95aa56d756298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Groundless assurances keep coming from President Donald Trump, a rosy outlier on the science of the coronavirus pandemic. It's been that way since before the virus spread...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires more missiles into sea...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e30f99ca9b3075e11ccf39f6ec536b69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Sunday fired two suspected ballistic missiles into the sea, South Korea said, calling it “very inappropriate” at a time when the world is battling the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus hotspots grow in middle America...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cb56e50250328b923776408386b3a82a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The coronavirus continued its unrelenting spread across the United States with fatalities doubling in two days and authorities saying Saturday that an infant who tested positive had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro makes life-or-death gamble...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b21a296383694c6726d03e027134daf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Even as coronavirus cases mount in Latin America’s largest nation, Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has staked out the most deliberately dismissive position of any major...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers key to keeping nation fed are wary of spread...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/647a445d026527acdc2848a740666d38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Salvador Calzadillas isn't worried about catching the coronavirus when he's picking mandarin oranges in the trees in central California. But he said the mere act of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Fiscal conservatives fully embrace biggest bailout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c295f39bcb742aea238640be1b92735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Republicans who have spent the past decade howling about the danger of ballooning deficits embraced the coronavirus rescue package approved by Congress and signed by President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus pulls federalism debate into 21st Century...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/212b06d9914390f498b6fe684463a3c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A flu pandemic was ravaging the world, killing indiscriminately in almost every country, including more than 600,000 deaths in the United States. The states were in a panic, but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News from The Associated Press, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Lloyd Grove coverage by The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news, politics, culture, technology, health, and more, through its articles, podcasts, videos, and flagship magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutschlands führende Nachrichtenseite. Alles Wichtige aus Politik, Wirtschaft, Sport, Kultur, Wissenschaft, Technik und mehr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://www.pravdareport.com/world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravdareport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rated the #1 political newsletter by political professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times Opinion columnists, editorials and op-eds. Analysis from David Brooks, Maureen Dowd, Charles Blow, Paul Krugman and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite is the top U.S. website covering the intersection of media and politics with original reporting and bi-partisan commentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! brings you the latest celebrity &amp; royal news from the UK &amp; around the world, magazine exclusives, fashion, beauty, lifestyle news, celeb babies, weddings, pregnancies and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC is the world leader in business news and real-time financial market coverage. Find fast, actionable information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking the biggest stories in celebrity and entertainment news. Get exclusive access to the latest stories, photos, and video as only TMZ can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Rutenberg is a writer-at-large for The New York Times and the Sunday magazine. He was previously the media columnist, a White House reporter and a national political correspondent. He was part of the team that won the Pulitzer Prize for Public Service in 2018 for exposing sexual harassment and abuse across industries.&amp;#160;He started at The Times in 2000, as a reporter covering the media industries. Before coming to The Times he had worked as as a staff writer for The New York Observer, The New York Daily News, The New York Post and was editor of The Manhattan Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urns far exceed death toll, raising more questions about Beijing's tally...</title>
      <link>http://shanghaiist.com/2020/03/27/urns-in-wuhan-far-exceed-death-toll-raising-more-questions-about-chinas-tally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;shanghaiist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single mortuary has had 5,000 urns delivered over the past two days, double the city’s reported coronavirus death toll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News stories from Boston, Massachusetts and beyond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
