<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Officer who had heart attack during Capitol riot received threatening voice mail for testifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-officer-who-had-a-heart-attack-during-capitol-riot-received-vulgar-threatening-voice-mail-for-testifying/ar-AAMH4cl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a voice mail left for D.C. police officer Michael Fanone, a man accused Fanone of lying about the events on Jan. 6 and said he wished the rioters killed the officers defending the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in Tracing Alerts Reveals Scale of UK 'Pingdemic'...</title>
      <link>https://businesshala.com/rise-in-covid-tracing-alerts-reveals-scale-of-u-k-s-pingdemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businesshala.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Businesshala) - About 690,000 people in England and Wales were told to isolate by official COVID-19 mobile phone apps in the week ending July 21,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS: USA breaks world record -- and loses...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/us-breaks-world-record-and-loses-042725207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Katie Ledecky-led U.S. relay broke the world record in the 4x200-meter freestyle here on Thursday ... and lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attendees in hospital as COVID cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210729114105-a20t3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Two Games attendees in hospital as Japan COVID-19 cases surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biles makes mental health talk of Games...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-athletes-mental-health-7c7dad85a3ded5d3fce07055f5387d37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Brittney Griner has long been open about her ongoing battle with depression, an ailment that triggered suicidal thoughts when she was younger and last year drove her out of the WNBA bubble because the isolation was too much to handle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yelling, Throwing, Tweeting: Day Coverings Returned to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/yelling-throwing-tweeting-the-day-masks-returned-to-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The lack of basic human decency being exhibited in the House is a stain on our country,” said Rep. Dean Phillips (D-MN).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-headed snake eats two mice at same time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/two-headed-snake-named-ben-24641772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Barczyk said it was rare to see each head of the snake eat a mouse each at the same time. He works at a reptile zoo which also houses two-headed turtles and albino creatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: PEOPLE QUICK TO BELIEVE WORST WHEN STRESSED...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/people-b948131.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stress can make us jump to undesirable conclusions, new research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 8.2 mag largest quake to hit Alaska since 1965...</title>
      <link>https://www.alaskapublic.org/2021/07/28/major-quake-hits-near-alaska-peninsula-triggers-tsunami-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.alaskapublic.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala bad polls trigger Dem worries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/565336-harriss-bad-polls-trigger-democratic-worries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris has some ground to make up in order to be perceived more favorably by the public, a complicating factor for the Biden administration as it maps out its midterm strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL APPROVES 3RD SHOT</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/israeli-health-ministry-panel-recommends-third-covid-shot-for-older-people-1.10049085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDACE OWENS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/show/candace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us weekly as Candace Owens delves into the political and cultural issues of the day with her signature blend of intelligence and humor. CANDACE features celebrity interviews and panel discussions with the world’s most influential thought leaders and cultural mavens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fines for breaching Sydney lockdown doubled; Police given extra powers to shut down businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9837589/Fines-breaching-Sydneys-lockdown-doubled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fines for Covid rule breakers in NSW have doubled and police can shut down businesses and construction sites that under wide-ranging new powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE ROGAN</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/show/4rOoJ6Egrf8K2IrywzwOMk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;open.spotify.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to The Joe Rogan Experience on Spotify. The official podcast of comedian Joe Rogan. Follow The Joe Rogan Clips show page for some of the best moments from the episodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAWKER begs readers to have an 'open mind and heart' in quiet relaunch...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/gawker-quietly-relaunches-asks-readers-for-an-open-mind-and-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picked up at a bankruptcy auction by Bustle Digital Group, Gawker reappeared in a third iteration after Bustle’s headstrong CEO Bryan Goldberg attempted to resuscitate the site twice before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds releasing infected migrants into communities...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/07/28/la-joya-covid-migrants-whataburger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The undocumented migrant family at Whataburger told a police officer that Border Patrol had released them because they had COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong's urban farms sprout gardens in the sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbesindia.com/article/forbes-lifes/hong-kongs-urban-farms-sprout-gardens-in-the-sky/69083/1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbesindia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their heads in the clouds and their hands in the soil, a group of office workers are busy harvesting the fruits of their labour on the roof of a Hong Kong skyscraper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks on. Masks off. Masks on again at White House...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/masks-masks-off-masks-again-150227895.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden made adherence to COVID guidelines a cornerstone of his campaign to defeat Trump. He beat Trump, but beating the pandemic may be harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY sails into new LGBT waters with 'JUNGLE CRUISE' film...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/disney-sails-lgbt-waters-jungle-015845392.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Jungle Cruise," Disney's new nostalgia-soaked adventure film based on a 1950s theme park ride, has an unexpectedly modern twist -- one of its main characters comes out as gay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports highest number of new cases in world...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/covid-delta-variant-surge/?id=79058271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pandemic of the novel coronavirus has now infected more than 195 million people worldwide and killed over 4.1 million of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand rated best place to survive global societal collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/28/new-zealand-rated-best-place-to-survive-global-societal-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study citing ‘perilous state’ of industrial civilisation ranks temperate islands top for resilience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors of California's deadliest wildfire haunted as new blaze nears: 'I can't do it again'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivors-of-california-e2-80-99s-deadliest-wildfire-haunted-as-new-blaze-nears-i-can-e2-80-99t-do-it-again-e2-80-99/ar-AAMFNsT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As California’s biggest blaze of the year raged toward a haven for survivors of the 2018 Camp Fire, residents relived a nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK, GOOGLE will require...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/google-and-facebook-to-require-vaccines-for-in-office-employees-paving-the-way-for-rivals-to-follow/ar-AAMFtGw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's shift on masking creates new political difficulties, policy challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-shift-on-masking-creates-new-political-difficulties-policy-challenges/ar-AAMFr09?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s allies say his new message is a commendable response to the findings of scientists and health experts. But critics call it confusing and possibly damaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  Bring Vision of Metaverse to Life!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/facebook-q2-2021-1234989781/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s ad revenue increased 56 percent year over year for a total of $28.58 billion in the second quarter of this year, according to earnings reported on Wednesday. The majority of the co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25% of new cases in LA fully vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/over-25-of-new-covid-19-cases-in-los-angeles-county-are-fully-vaccinated-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June fully vaccinated people accounted for 20% of all the new cases diagnosed in LA County, while unvaccinated and partially vaccinated people accounted for 80% of the cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significance of breakthrough infections remains unclear; CDC hides data...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Experts-ask-to-see-data-behind-new-policy-16347545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - New recommendations from federal health officials this week on when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelina Jolie son 'may NOT have been orphan,' agent claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3361292/angelina-jolie-son-maddox-not-orphan-adoption-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angelina Jolie’s son Maddox may not have been an orphan like the actress once claimed, the agent who investigated a Cambodian “baby buying” scandal told The Sun in an exclusive in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How wealthy, Wall Street ruined housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/housing-market-prices-expensive-millennials-wealthy-rich-americans-wall-street-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buyers waiting for cheaper houses are out of luck. The wealthy, investment firms, and millennials are creating a permanently higher price floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK,</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/28/facebook-requiring-us-employees-to-be-vaccinated-to-return-to-work.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company will continue to evaluate its approach outside of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Private Schools Have Gone Woke...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/why-private-schools-have-gone-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dalton School hosts an annual conference for New York City private schools on diversity, equity, and inclusion. This May, it was Rodney Glasgow’s turn to deliver the keynote address. Glasgow, a longtime school administrator who has founded multiple DEI consultancies, used his speech to address the elephant in the room: the parental pushback to "antiracism" at Dalton and other elite private schools, which made national headlines after Dalton headmaster Jim Best resigned amid the uproar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: DISCOVERY 'Shark Week' -- Harmful To Sharks?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/shark-week-missed-opportunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors argue that these problems undermine the greater purpose of Shark Week, hindering efforts of shark scientists and harming the sharks themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema opposes $3.5 trillion price tag or Dems' sweeping social safety net bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/sinema-opposes-3-5-trillion-price-tag-democrats-sweeping-social-n1275330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona Democrat said she will, however, vote in favor of the budget resolution that begins the legislative process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Republicans Ready to Take Up Infrastructure Spending Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/key-republicans-say-theyre-ready-to-take-up-an-infrastructure-deal/ar-AAMFmCy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House and a bipartisan group of senators agreed on Wednesday on a far-reaching infrastructure bill, with a vote to advance it set for as soon as Wednesday evening, paving the way for action on a crucial piece of President Biden’s agenda. “We now have an agreement on the major issues, and we’re prepared to move forward,” said Senator Rob Portman, Republican of Ohio and a lead negotiator for his party on the infrastructure measure....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gymnast skirts protest ban with BLM raised fist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/costa-rican-gymnast-raises-fist-for-black-lives-matter-during-floor-routine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luciana Alvarado wrapped up her performance in the Olympic qualifying rounds in Tokyo by kneeling on the floor and looking up with a raised fist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player cut for 'stealing food' to take home...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/falcons/news/new-york-giants-cut-kelvin-benjamin-for-stealing-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first-round pick of the Carolina Panthers Kelvin Benjamin was cut by the New York Giants for the strangest reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Israel has 2 week window to halt 4th wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israels-two-week-window-to-halt-the-4th-covid-19-wave-675199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new daily cases has surpassed 2,000 for two days in a row and hospital heads say they are starting to feel the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Says No Jab, No Job!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/netflix-to-require-covid-vaccinations-for-all-actors-on-us-productions-1234801577/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Netflix has become the first major Hollywood studio to implement a blanket policy mandating vaccinations for the casts of all of its U.S. productions, as well as those who come into cont…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Star On Life Support, Friend Shot to Death Inside CA Movie Theater...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/28/rylee-goodrich-anthony-barajas-corona-movie-theater-fatal-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 18-year-old woman was killed and a 19-year-old man was taken to the hospital with life-threatening injuries after a shooting at a Corona movie theater, police said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floyd Mayweather 'TARGETED' in drive-by; Bodyguard wounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3366508/floyd-mayweather-targeted-drive-shooting-bodyguard-hurt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLOYD Mayweather’s bodyguard was shot protecting the retired boxing star from a “targeted” drive-by shooting that left him with a horrific wound. Greg La Rosa, 39, exclusively rec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA CONSIDERS 'DRASTIC ACTIONS'</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/national/coronavirus-surge-worsening-in-california-as-officials-consider-more-drastic-actions/article_ff6feae9-b4a7-59a9-8c9e-ecf697e83015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Faced with sustained increases in coronavirus infections and COVID-19 hospitalizations, California officials are considering new measures to hopefully cap the spike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers flare in House over new rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/565286-tempers-flare-as-some-in-gop-ignore-new-house-mask-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several GOP lawmakers refused to comply with the newly reinstated mask requirement on the House side of the Capitol on Wednesday, putting themselves at risk of having to pay hefty fines as punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Burning Man Without Burning Man?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnqek/what-is-the-future-of-the-burning-man-festival-canceled-covid-pandemic-v28n3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s most famous festival turned cultural phenomenon is canceled for the second year in a row. What will rise to fill the Technicolor void it leaves behind?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Dumps on 'Moron' McCarthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-republicans-refuse-to-follow-new-mask-mandate-leading-pelosi-to-call-mccarthy-a-moron-for-his-comments/ar-AAMF7BO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy contended that requiring masks again is “not a decision based on science.” House Speaker Nancy Pelosi responded, “He’s such a moron.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom's biggest recall danger: Complacent Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/newsom-s-biggest-recall-danger-complacent-democrats-who-don-t-turn-out-to-vote/ar-AAMFz3n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom's strategy appears two-pronged: Make sure Democrats turn out on Sept. 14, and cast the election as an attack on the state's progressive values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused of shooting neighbor's cat with crossbow...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/michigan-woman-allegedly-shot-neighbors-cat-with-crossbow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan woman, Taylor Rose Shipman, is facing felony charges for shooting her neighbor’s cat, Oliver, in the neck with a crossbow – claiming the animal was attacking her own pets, deputies said.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Dommes Demanding Their Submissives Get Vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/meet-dommes-demanding-submissives-vaxxed-142902734.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I specialize in toilet play, and I can't do it with people who are unvaccinated," says one domme requiring proof of vaccination for dungeon entry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSANTO illegally acquired data on journalists, activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210728-france-fines-monsanto-for-illegally-acquiring-data-on-journalists-activists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's personal data protection agency on Wednesday fined US firm Monsanto for illegally compiling files of public figures, journalists and activists with the aim of swaying opinion towards support…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE will require...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/28/google-postpones-return-to-work-until-october-will-require-vaccinations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the second delay to office returns amid the ongoing Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mandates back in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mask-mandates-are-coming-back-including-in-vegas-tourists-aren-t-happy/ar-AAMEccU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada reinstalled a statewide mask mandate within hours of a CDC announcement that even vaccinated people should wear masks indoors in public in high-transmission communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McBandit targets MCDONALD'S in armed robbery spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mcbandit-targets-mcdonalds-restaurants-in-robbery-spree</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is wanted in connection with a robbery spree that targeted McDonald's locations across the Bronx along with some other stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble looms for another candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/07/28/max-miller-ohio-congress-trump-profile-500187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say Max Miller has a history of aggressive behavior that includes slapping his ex-girlfriend, former White House press secretary Stephanie Grisham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screentime Leads to 'Cybersickness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/07/screentime-can-make-you-feel-sick-here-are-ways-manage-cybersickness/183977/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your devices can trigger symptoms similar to motion sickness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC GIVES CASH TO TAKE JAB...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/nyc-to-offer-100-incentive-for-vaccination-starting-friday/3181505/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting this Friday, New York City will pay $100 to anyone who goes to a city-run vaccination site for their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine, Mayor Bill de Blasio said. The announcement comes just days after the mayor said all city workers would have to be vaccinated or go through strict weekly testing protocols. It also comes amid a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramer Predicts 100 Million Sick in Next 60 days?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-jim-cramer-freaks-out-over-delta-variant-predicts-we-could-see-100-million-people-sick-in-9-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC financial pundit Jim Cramer sounded the alarm about the Delta variant of the coronavirus, predicting that the U.S. could see 100 million people stricken by the disease “in 9 weeks.” On Wednesday morning’s edition of The Street Live, Cramer delivered a dismal forecast based on recent market performance on the heels of news that […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants Turning To Robots As Employee Shortage Takes Toll...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/27/stockton-restaurant-hires-robot-as-employee-shortage-takes-toll-it-is-exhausting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newest restaurant worker might be a bit stiff without much personality, but more than likely it still wants those tips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE SET TO PASS NETFLIX IN REVENUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/netflix-beware-youtube-could-bring-in-more-money-in-2021-chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube could finish 2021 with higher annual sales than Netflix; here's why YouTube is on track to bring in more than $30 billion this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TRUMP PICK DOES DOWN IN TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/07/27/susan-wright-jake-ellzey-texas-6-congressional-seat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellzey, a state representative, beat fellow Republican Susan Wright, who was backed by former President Donald Trump. Ellzey will finish the term of Ron Wright, who died earlier this year after contracting COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST. LOUIS SHOWDOWN OVER MASKS</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/govt-and-politics/st-louis-county-council-votes-5-2-to-rescind-mask-mandate-throwing-rule-into-limbo/article_adac2c7d-85b7-5f36-b270-cc861a1e5c52.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;County Executive Sam Page’s administration maintains the mandate is not subject to council action, and the executive continued to tout the benefits of the order after the vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESTAURANTS:  NO VAX, NO SERVICE</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/with-covid-on-the-rise-more-restaurants-say-no-vax-no-service-11627429835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Establishments are requiring that customers be fully vaccinated, and they're running into protests in the process</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolf hunt in Wisconsin blew past kill quota in Feb. Another oming this fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-wolf-hunt-blew-past-its-kill-quota-in-february-another-hunt-is-coming-this-fall/ar-AAMECx4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin, increasingly divided between rural and urban views, faces hard, contentious questions of how big its remaining wolf population should be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOTS MANDATED FOR ALL FED WORKERS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/28/biden-will-require-federal-workers-to-get-the-covid-vaccine-or-submit-to-testing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration will require federal workers to be vaccinated for the coronavirus or else submit to strict testing measures, NBC News reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Hunting in El Salvador: Compound on Coast for $249,000...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/28/house-hunting-in-el-salvador-a-compound-on-the-coast-for-249000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Verdant Three-Bedroom Home in El Salvador $249,000 This low-slung villa compound is tucked into a lushly landscaped tropical garden,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation reveals extreme body temps endured...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9834635/Shocking-simulation-reveals-athletes-face-heatstroke-exhaustion-Tokyo-Olympic-Games.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effects of the hot, humid conditions on a male athlete competing in the 10,000m race at Tokyo's Olympic Stadium were simulated by experts at Swedish technology company Hexagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEOPARDY! contestant breaks record for lowest score EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3362235/jeopardy-contestant-breaks-record-for-lowest-score-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAST night’s Jeopardy! contestant broke the record for the lowest score EVER in the show’s history. Patrick Pearce’s huge loss came on Reading Rainbow and Star Trek star, LeVar Bu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaxxed will no longer have to quarantine when visiting England...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/28/no-quarantine-for-vaccinated-us-citizens-traveling-to-england.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. and EU travelers that have been fully vaccinated against the coronavirus will soon be allowed to visit England without having to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER data suggest third dose 'strongly' boosts protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/28/health/pfizer-third-dose-data-bn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX gov orders National Guard to arrest migrants...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/565134-texas-governor-orders-national-guard-to-arrest-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott (R) on Tuesday ordered the National Guard to help local law enforcement with arresting migrants as the state continues to see an influx of people crossing the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn off, turn on: Simple step can thwart top phone hackers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-government-and-politics-hacking-752db867fafbaba1f9cc34f7588944c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — As a member of the secretive Senate Intelligence Committee, Sen. Angus King has reason to worry about hackers. At a briefing by security staff this year, he said he got some advice on how to help keep his cellphone secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cop Jimmy 'Barbecue' Is Gangster King of Haiti Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvdny/ex-cop-jimmy-barbecue-is-the-gangster-king-of-haitis-chaos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti’s president was brutally murdered in early July. As the beleaguered nation’s official power brokers tussle for position, slumlord Barbecue is planning his next move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Jehovah's Witnesses' Secret Pedophile Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-jehovahs-witnesses-secret-pedophile-database</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vice TV doc “Crusaders” examines a secret database of thousands of Jehovah’s Witness child-sex offenders that’s been assembled by the Watch Tower Bible and Tract Society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART will cover 100% of college tuition for workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/27/business/walmart-college-tuition-benefit/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart will pay for full college tuition and book costs at some schools for its US workers, the latest effort by the largest private employer in the country to sweeten its benefits as it seeks to attract and retain talent in a tight job market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We do not owe anyone gold medal'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/28/us-gymnast-sunisa-lee-says-we-do-not-owe-anyone-a-gold-medal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US gymnast Sunisa Lee expressed support for her teammates after Simone Biles’ stunning Olympics withdrawal and defended their second-place finish.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
