<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UK PROTESTS TURN VIOLENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10323957/London-Covid-19-protests-turn-violent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large group of people opposed to Covid-19 restrictions has gathered in Westminster to demonstrate against Boris Johnson's Plan B announcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First S Florida election next year will pit progressive vs. Trump Republican vs. vax skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/politics/2022-s-first-south-florida-election-will-pit-a-progressive-democrat-vs-a-trump-republican/article_2091c6be-1dc9-5385-b8b8-8301e72ac8cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — South Florida voters have a vast range of options as they decide who to send to Washington, D.C., in the nation’s first congressional election in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters at DISNEY say guests 'in danger' because of short staffing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/firefighters-at-disney-world-say-guests-are-in-danger-because-of-short-staffing/article_d35806d0-9a05-505a-9c32-e19211ed168d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — A woman at a hotel within Walt Disney World had a heart attack in the middle of the day this past Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are motorists angrier these days?</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/motorists-angrier-days-whats-perception-140021174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motorists seem to be more aggressive and angrier than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMICRON CASES DOUBLE IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10324045/Omicron-cases-double-overnight-Variant-confirmed-45-states.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed Omicron cases in the US has nearly doubled in a period of 24 hours, with the variant now confirmed in all but five states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netherlands to go into Christmas 'lockdown'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/netherlands-set-announce-strict-christmas-lockdown-media-2021-12-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dutch hit the shops on Saturday as they prepared for a Christmas lockdown that is expected to close all but essential stores from Sunday, as the health minister said authorities were "extremely worried" about the Omicron variant of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Ends 'Horrible Year' With Divisions as Bitter as Ever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/18/congress-ends-horrible-year-with-divisions-as-bitter-as-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A congressional year that began with an assault on the seat of democracy ended at 4 a.m. Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON 'MAJOR INCIDENT'</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17079303/major-incident-declared-london-hospitals-covid-breaking-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SADIQ Khan declared a “major incident” in London today amid huge concern over the rise in Covid cases. The Mayor of London said he was “incredibly concerned” by the surge in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy Destroyers Harrassed By Mysterious Drones Off California For Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43561/mysterious-drone-swarms-over-navy-destroyers-off-california-went-on-for-weeks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new trove of documents shows that the still unsolved incidents continued far longer than previously understood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Justice May Demand That Weinstein Goes Free...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-justice-may-demand-harvey-001506541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNES EISELENew York Appellate judges grilled the District Attorney prosecuting Harvey Weinstein so intently this week that it appears they are poised to overturn his criminal conviction.The thought that a man who evaded justice for so long may do so again is infuriating. Whatever joy we experienced from Weinstein’s February 2020 conviction for rape and assault now feels like an old memory of a moment when the MeToo movement proved that women have rights, and powerful people could be held to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SPIDER-MAN' Scores 2nd Best Opening Day Of All Time...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/spider-man-no-way-home-50m-preview-easily-pandemic-record-all-time-for-sony-100m-friday-likely-1234898486/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SATURDAY AM: Refresh for chart and more analysis: If you’re wondering whether the Omicron variant is slowing down this weekend’s box office, the answer is ‘No’. Sony/Marvel&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump condemned by ADL chief for antisemitic tropes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/18/donald-trump-antisemitic-tropes-anti-defamation-league</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Greenblatt says that ‘insinuating that Israel or the Jews control Congress or the media is antisemitic’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gervais on offense, anger and infuriating Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2021/dec/18/ricky-gervais-on-offence-anger-and-infuriating-hollywood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He has made a career out of winding people up in everything from The Office to his Golden Globes speeches – but is the comedian’s bark worse than his bite?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 40.5% Of People Have No Symptoms At All...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-patients-no-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A global study of almost 30 million people found "silent" cases of COVID-19 are twice as prevalent than previous estimates feared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON 'MAJOR INCIDENT'</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/london-declares-major-incident-over-omicron-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British capital confirms more than 65,000 cases in seven days. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools close doors again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/schools-classrooms-close-doors-latest-covid-surge-rcna9193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As schools brace for the rapid rise in omicron cases amid delta’s continued onslaught and the onset of flu season, some are closing their doors once again and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark toughest month just beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/highly-vaccinated-countries-thought-they-were-over-the-worst-denmark-says-the-pandemic-e2-80-99s-toughest-month-is-just-beginning/ar-AARWzJr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 7 expats left USA to start over: 'We spend less on all expenses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/18/travelers-who-left-the-us-to-start-over-how-they-earn-income-and-save-money-overseas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinking of leaving the U.S.? From Mexico to Costa Rica to Italy, seven expats share how they earn an income and what life is like outside of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio credits success to 40 mins of meditation per day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/18/billionaire-ray-dalio-how-transcendental-meditation-helps-me-succeed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Ray Dalio takes CNBC Make It inside his daily meditation practice, which he says helps drive his financial success as a hedge-fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 anonymous media execs predict next year's industry-shaking events...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/18/10-anonymous-media-execs-predict-2022s-industry-shaking-events.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media executives anonymously predicted 2022's industry-shifting events, including Bob Iger coming back as Disney CEO and Shari Redstone selling ViacomCBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron in 89 countries, cases doubling fast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-united-nations-world-health-organization-d5fe2dff8b09f0f8bb834669122e7877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIENNA (AP) — The omicron variant of the coronavirus has been detected in 89 countries, and COVID-19 cases involving the variant are doubling every 1.5 to 3 days in places with community transmission and not just infections acquired abroad, the World Health Organization said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change, freedom, order: Chilean dreams differ ahead of historic vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-chile-election-voters/change-freedom-order-chilean-dreams-differ-ahead-of-historic-vote-idUSKBN2IX070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilean voters are split on what they want from the future ahead of a landmark presidential election on Sunday between polarized candidates - one offering social change and the other pledging to get tough on law and order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political row in Brazil over dystopian film 'EXECUTIVE ORDER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211218-political-row-in-brazil-over-dystopian-film-executive-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Brazil of the near future, the government has found what it calls the answer to righting the wrongs of slavery: send blacks back to Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW IT'S THREE: NY gov to add booster to definition of 'fully vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/586402-ny-governor-plans-to-add-booster-shot-to-definition-of-fully-vaccinated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Kathy Hochul (D) announced during a press conference on Thursday that she is planning to introduce legislation that includes a booster shot within the definition of being “fully vaccinated.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlamagne Tha God, Kamala heated exchange after question about who 'real president' is...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/586357-charlamagne-the-god-harris-get-into-heated-exchange-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris asserted that Joe Biden is president — not Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) — during a tense exchange on Charlamagne Tha God's Comedy Central show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired generals: Military must prepare now for '24 insurrection...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/12/17/eaton-taguba-anderson-generals-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military breakdown mirroring societal or political breakdown would put all Americans at severe risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble for tests across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/omicron-and-holidays-unleash-scramble-for-coronavirus-tests-across-the-us/ar-AARWozr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As fans return to high school sports, officials say student behavior has never been worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-fans-return-to-high-school-sports-officials-say-student-behavior-has-never-been-worse/ar-AARWH5K </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 may have killed people who never tested positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/coronavirus/covid-deaths-hospitalizations-new-jersey-home-heart-attacks-stroke-20211217.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home deaths were up while hospitalizations were down, a sign that missed care may have been a factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats facing frustrating end to stormy year...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democrats-are-facing-a-frustrating-end-to-a-16711762.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Sen. Chris Murphy walked out of a Democratic caucus lunch in the Capitol on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK RECORD</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/some-british-hospitals-struggle-with-staff-shortages-due-covid-19-2021-12-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New cases of COVID-19 in Britain hit a record high for the second day running on Thursday, as England's Chief Medical Officer warned daily hospital admissions could also hit new peaks due to the fast-spreading Omicron coronavirus variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC CASES HIT PANDEMIC HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/this-is-a-whole-new-animal-breakthrough-infections-rattle-nyc-amid-omicron-surge/3456543/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will NYC have to shut some things down again because of the omicron variant? Even the mayor appears less confident now that the answer is no.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No evidence' Omicron less severe than Delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.imperial.ac.uk/news/232698/modelling-suggests-rapid-spread-omicron-england/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.imperial.ac.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Omicron variant largely evades immunity from past infection or two vaccine doses according to the latest Imperial modelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Island went from 6.2 million tourists to 45...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/pandemic-travel-news-omicron-uk-france-ghana/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron is sweeping through Europe. The United States is preparing for full-throttle winter holiday travel. And Australia and the Caribbean island-nation of St. Kitts and Nevis are relaxing visitor restrictions. Here's the latest in travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON partnered with China propaganda arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/17/amazon-partnered-with-china-propaganda-arm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's compliance with the Chinese government edict is part of a deeper, decade-long effort by the company to win favor in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARYLAND SCHOOLS GO BACK VIRTUAL...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/prince-georges-county/2021/12/prince-georges-county-public-schools-shifts-to-virtual-learning-due-to-uptick-in-covid-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Prince George’s County Public Schools will move to virtual learning for the final stretch of the school year and into the first month of 2022 due to an uptick in cases found within the school system, the school system’s CEO announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFECTIONS SWEEP EUROPE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-travel-dcf7d5733163d3c851fa27f99edca92b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Nations across Europe are moving to reimpose tougher measures to stem a new wave of COVID-19 infections spurred by the highly transmissible omicron variant, triggering calls for protests from Paris to Barcelona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD BRACES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/omicron-hollywood-events-cancelations-1235136826/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, Sony Pictures Entertainment hosted a raucous premiere for “Spider-Man: No Way Home,” a superhero adventure widely expected to generate a new COVID-era record opening weekend.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TORONTO LIMITS INDOOR GATHERINGS TO 10...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/canada/2021/12/17/covid-19-coronavirus-updates-toronto-canada-december-17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, health experts have called on Ontarians to wear snug-fitting masks with at least two layers that eliminate gaps; Pfizer plans study of COVID-19 vaccine children under four.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVENGE: Enraged monkeys kill town's entire population of 250 dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10320853/Enraged-monkeys-kill-Indian-towns-entire-population-250-DOGS-throwing-heights.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The horrific incidents have been reported in the villages of Majalgaon, where 250 dogs are said to have been killed by rampaging primates, and nearby Lavul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court allows Biden employer vaccine mandate to take effect; Supremes Next...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-business-health-880d2052bb4127fb40bcaaca98514753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court panel on Friday allowed President Joe Biden’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate for larger private employers to move ahead. The 2-1 decision by a panel of the 6th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals reverses a decision by a federal judge in a separate court that had paused the mandate nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-travel-80caac77e0cfed7e0e08cfa024ed3a9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. officials intensified calls Friday for unvaccinated Americans to get inoculated in the face of the new omicron variant that contributed to a record number of infections in New York and threatened to wipe out a second holiday season in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHISLAINE DEFENSE RESTS; DOESN'T TAKE STAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/defense-rests-ghislaine-maxwell-trial-two-days-rcna9194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Closing arguments in the closely-watched sex trafficking trial of Jeffrey Epstein confidante Ghislaine Maxwell got the green light to get underway Monday after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANIC RETURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/we-ve-never-seen-this-before-new-york-plunged-back-into-covid-panic/ar-AARVCc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspector booted from bar for failing to show own proof of shot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/17/nyc-covid-inspector-booted-from-bar-for-failing-to-show-proof-of-vaccination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stunned bar manager Maggie Koronilian told The Post how she had to boot the Department of Health and Mental Hygiene employee from Big Nose Kate’s Saloon and Eatery on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacuum-Sealed Container From 1972 Moon Landing Will Finally Be Opened...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/vacuum-sealed-container-from-1972-moon-landing-will-fin-1848234198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 50 years, scientists will get a chance to study lunar gases collected during Apollo 17 mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL postpones games...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/17/nfl-will-postpone-some-games-over-covid-surge-source-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expected move by the NFL comes as the NHL has said it will postpone the games of several hockey teams due to a rise in Covid cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Could humanity catch a break?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/could-humanity-catch-break-omicron-120038070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the fast-spreading but less virulent Omicron variant, the coronavirus may finally be cutting humanity a little slack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA:  GUCCI, LOUIS VUITTON skin reptiles alive to make handbags...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/17/gucci-louis-vuitton-skin-reptiles-alive-to-make-pricey-handbags-peta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-end retailers are selling bags, belts and wallets made from snakes and lizards that were cruelly killed — some with their heads hacked off as they tried to scurry away — according to an ex…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORBES Testified Before Trump Grand Jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/randalllane/2021/12/17/forbes-testified-before-the-trump-grand-jury-yesterday--heres-why-we-fought-their-subpoena/?sh=29675ef73e77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters and prosecutors both serve the public, but in different ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators believe 'strategy' text to undermine election came from Rick Perry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/17/politics/rick-perry-jan-6-text-mark-meadows-nov-4/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHISLAINE WON'T TAKE STAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/17/ghislaine-maxwell-will-not-testify-in-sex-case-related-to-jeffrey-epstein.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
