<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Swastika found in State Department elevator...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/swastika-state-department-antisemitism-12dfeaf3-9116-442d-a16e-632f1a68dbc8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Hate has no place here at the State Department," an agency-wide notice said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NFL team will reportedly keep un-jabbed coach...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/07/27/vikings-rick-dennison-agree-on-a-deal-that-hell-remain-with-the-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vikings offensive line coach Rick Dennison is not leaving the team, contrary to a Friday report that he was out. Per a source with knowledge of the situation, the Vikings and Dennison have reached an agreement that allows him to remain in Minnesota. The agreement is more like an acknowledgement that team and coach will [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to test ALL travelers for virus on entry...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/coronavirus-germany-plans-new-covid-19-testing-rules-for-travelers-report/a-58655856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Ministry is reportedly planning to expand obligatory testing to all travelers, even from low-risk areas. The move has been criticized for going too far, as well as for not going far enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney braces for another MONTH in lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9830829/Coronavirus-Australia-Sydney-face-MONTH-lockdown-Woolworths-Coles-Bunnings-alert.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sydney's Covid lockdown is set to be extended for another month as case numbers surge, exposed venues skyrocket and the state's contact tracers are left overwhelmed by the India Delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't afford' more than a one-bedroom apartment...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9828003/Pete-Buttigiegs-husband-Chasten-claims-afford-one-bedroom-apartment-D-C.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with the Washington Post published on Monday, Chasten griped that a one-bedroom apartment including a den was out of their price range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempts vault, walks out...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcolympics.com/videos/simone-biles-exits-team-final-after-vault?chrcontext=wnbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcolympics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simone Biles competed in Team USA's first rotation on vault in the women's Olympic team final, bailing out of her Amanar and scoring a 13.766 for a 1.5 twist. Shortly after, she withdrew from the team contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo records record covid cases days after Olympics begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/tokyo-records-record-virus-cases-days-after-olympics-begin/3177598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan’s capital, Tokyo, has reported its highest number of new coronavirus infections days after the Olympics began</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Feels Like Weight Of World On My Shoulders'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/olympics/simone-biles-out-team-gymnastics-final-after-apparent-injury-n1275121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not clear if Biles will compete in Thursday's individual all-around competition, where she is the defending champion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rewards P. Bush for His Loyalty --  by Endorsing Opponent!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-rewards-george-p-bush-for-his-conspicuous-loyalty-by-endorsing-opponent-ken-paxton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump rewarded George P. Bush’s conspicuous loyalty by endorsing Ken Paxton, Bush’s opponent in the race for Texas attorney general. Trump made the announcement Monday night in one of the email statements he now uses in place of the social media platforms from which he has been banned: Endorsement of Texas Attorney […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco considering congestion tax on high-earning drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/san-francisco-considering-congestion-tax-on-high-earning-drivers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco County Transportation Authority is once again eyeing a tax on drivers in the busiest parts of the city's downtown, and has launched a study into a so-called "congestion pricing" plan as traffic begins to pick up following 2020's pandemic-induced lull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling families dumping pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-animal-shelter-sees-big-influx-of-surrendered-pets-and-strays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dogs and cats being surrendered to ACC aren't the ones that people adopted at the height of the pandemic. Instead, these pets are coming from households struggling financially as public assistance tapers off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS PREGNANT...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/27/paris-hilton-pregnant-expecting-baby-with-fiance-carter-reum/?_ga=2.70696400.135843039.1627351066-139950124.1626883625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hilton revealed in January that she had been undergoing IVF treatments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel hears of 'medieval' Capitol violence by MAGA rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/police-defended-u-capitol-testify-100228458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) -Four police officers delivered wrenching testimony on Tuesday on their struggle to defend the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 against a mob of then-President Donald Trump's supporters, describing to lawmakers how they were beaten, taunted with racial insults from rioters and faced threats like "kill him with his own gun." The testimony came as a Democratic-led House of Representatives investigatory committee held its first hearing, with chairman Bennie Thompson and a Republican panel member, Liz Cheney, emphasizing the need for a thorough probe. Thompson and Cheney warned against "whitewashing" the riot even as Trump allies try to downplay the incident and accuse the committee of political motivations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Starting to Slip, and He Can't Blame Virus for It...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-is-starting-to-slip-and-he-cant-blame-covid-for-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He promised “independence” from the virus, swore that inflation was “transitory,” and claimed the border crisis was “cyclical.” No wonder his poll numbers are sagging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye Scan Can Detect 'Long Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eye-scan-determines-long-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around one in 10 people infected by the virus will become COVID long-haulers. It has been suggested that small nerve fiber damage may underlie its development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable Airs Uncensored Testimony of Officer Who Was Called 'F*cking N***er' By Insurrectionists...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-cable-airs-gripping-uncensored-testimony-of-officer-who-was-called-fcking-ner-by-trump-insurrectionists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capitol Police Officer Harry Dunn revealed that the Trump fans who participated in the deadly Jan. 6 insurrection chanted “F*cking N***er” and other racist abuse at him, in testimony that was aired uncensored by all three cable networks. During Tuesday’s first day of hearings before the January 6th House Select Committee, Officer Dunn described the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger gets emotional...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/video/959840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Adam Kinzinger got emotional when he made an opening statement at a hearing on the Jan. 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dems Eye Path to Citizenship for 8 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/democrats-eye-path-to-citizenship-for-8-million-in-economic-plan-1.1633047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats will seek a pathway to citizenship for as many as 8 million undocumented immigrants in a broad economic package they want to pass this year, according to a Senate Democratic aide familiar with the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Feels Like Weight Of World On My Shoulders'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/07/27/simone-biles-olympics-2021-support-team-final/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Messages of positivity and support were sent Biles' way from across the sports landscape after she withdrew from the team final this morning citing a mental health issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta spa gunman pleads guilty to 4 counts of murder...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/atlanta-spa-gunman-robert-long-pleads-guilty-counts/story?id=79071269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta spa gunman Robert Long pleads guilty to 4 counts of murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police officer calls them 'terrorists'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/565019-police-officer-repeatedly-calls-jan-6-rioters-terrorists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C. Metropolitan Police Officer Daniel Hodges repeatedly referred to the Capitol rioters as “terrorists” while recounting his experience defending the Capitol on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC REVERSAL: MASKS FOR VAXXED INDOORS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/27/cdc-to-reverse-indoor-mask-policy-to-recommend-them-for-fully-vaccinated-people-in-covid-hot-spots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC is expected to recommend that fully vaccinated people begin wearing masks indoors again in places with high Covid transmission rates, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Polls show CA recall gaining steam...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564994-polls-show-california-recall-gaining-steam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The share of California voters who say they will vote to recall Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel hears of 'medieval' Capitol violence by pro-Trump rioters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210727142555-l3rc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CAPITOL/SECURITY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-U.S. panel hears of 'medieval' Capitol violence by pro-Trump rioters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO sounds alarm on 'harmful' e-cigs...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-07-alarm-e-cigarettes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Electronic cigarettes and similar devices are dangerous to health and must be regulated to curb the tobacco industry's tactics to get young people hooked on nicotine, the World Health Organization warned Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY CENTER STAGE...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/politics/live-news/jan-6-house-select-committee-hearing-07-27-21/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House select committee investigating the deadly Capitol riot is holding its first high-profile hearing today. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC REVERSAL: MASKS FOR VAXXED INDOORS</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/27/the-c-d-c-will-recommend-that-some-vaccinated-people-wear-masks-indoors-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reversing a decision made just two months ago, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is expected to recommend on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOO HELL: 'World's saddest bear' has spent entire life behind bars; 'Days without food'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3359466/worlds-saddest-bear-nelson-armenia-cafe-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE “world’s saddest bear” has spent his entire life behind bars in a small, filthy cage and goes days without food in a hellhole zoo. Nelson the brown bear has lived like this in the Armenian zoo …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What's Covid?' People at America's Hardest-Partying Lake Not About to Get Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/07/27/ozarks-lake-covid-unvaccinated-500784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Lake of the Ozarks, vaccines are shunned, masks are mocked and the long-term consequences take a back seat to the time at hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis, Praised for Florida COVID Response, Faces Surge in Hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ron-desantis-praised-florida-covid-response-faces-surge-hospitalizations-cases-coronavirus-masks-1613372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican governor didn't impose a statewide mask mandate in Florida and recently lifted local restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival gangs of wild monkeys fight in front of shocked drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9828415/Rival-gangs-wild-monkeys-fight-shocked-drivers-Thailand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows how the two rival gangs of wild monkeys fought each other at a busy junction near the ruins of a temple in Lopburi, Thailand, while shocked motorists watched on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked docs reveal death threats, roadblocks in Haiti assassination investigation...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/07/26/americas/haiti-moise-assassination-investigation-death-threats-intl-latam/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was no mistaking the meaning in last week's anonymous text message: Do what we say or die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says detains agents working for Israel, seizes arms cache...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210727093217-fpbm7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ISRAEL/PROTESTS:Iran says it detains agents working for Israel, seizes arms cache</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside KKK murder plot: Grab him up, take him to river...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-business-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-only-on-ap-2b4106de3ebcbfae85948439a7056031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALATKA, Fla. (AP) — Joseph Moore breathed heavily, his face slick with nervous sweat. He held a cellphone with a photo of a man splayed on the floor; the man appeared dead, his shirt torn apart and his pants wet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic champ Biles out of team finals with apparent injury...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-gymnastics-simone-biles-injured-463f9be556246eada6dec265297df4d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Reigning Olympic gymnastics champion Simone Biles is out of the team finals after apparently suffering an injury during the vault. The 24-year-old U.S. star, considered to be the greatest gymnast of all time, huddled with a trainer after landing her vault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prices for Young Cattle Soaring, Signaling Expensive Beef...</title>
      <link>https://www.farmprogress.com/beef/prices-young-cattle-are-soaring-signaling-expensive-beef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.farmprogress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent droughts and record-high temperatures have also forced cattlemen to send animals to slaughter earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Beekeeping Booming: Hive Is Box of Calm...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/27/why-beekeeping-is-booming-in-new-york-a-hive-is-a-box-of-calm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April 2020, during the height of the pandemic in New York, a delicate rescue mission took place. Andrew Coté</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groceries in 10 Mins: Delivery Start-Ups Crowd City Streets Across Globe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/27/groceries-in-10-minutes-delivery-start-ups-crowd-city-streets-across-globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Zipping around central London, among the bikes and scooters of Uber Eats, Just Eat and Deliveroo, is a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At first Jan. 6 hearing, police to detail violence, injuries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-government-and-politics-race-and-ethnicity-capitol-siege-racial-injustice-96fd6e07e1d2700417575880df2fde69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats are launching their investigation into the Jan. 6 Capitol insurrection Tuesday with a focus on the law enforcement officers who were attacked and beaten as the rioters broke into the building — an effort to put a human face on the violence of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disbelief after Osaka elimination...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-japan-naomi-osaka-osaka-2584eb017d946c69d9fa754983256de9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — “Masaka" — or, in English, “No way.” That's how an incredulous Japan reacted Tuesday to the unexpectedly early loss of Naomi Osaka at the Tokyo Olympics, erasing her chances for gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. viewership climbs to 20 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/u-viewership-tokyo-games-climbs-014908527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime-time viewership for NBC's broadcast of the Summer Olympics from Tokyo picked up some steam in the first two nights of competition, compared with a lackluster audience for Friday's opening ceremonies, preliminary ratings data showed on Monday. But the size of NBC's audience on Saturday and Sunday nights, including broadcast television and streaming, was off substantially from comparable totals five years ago during the first two nights of competition at the 2016 Summer Games in Rio de Janeiro. Sunday night's presentation from Tokyo, featuring swimming, women's gymnastics, women's beach volleyball and the triathlon, averaged roughly 19.8 million prime-time viewers across all platforms, including NBCOlyumpics.com and the NBC Sports app, according to Comcast-owned NBCUniversal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump endorses rival to P. Bush...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564957-trump-endorses-ken-paxton-over-george-p-bush-in-texas-attorney-general-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump endorsed Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton over Land Commissioner George P. Bush in the state's Republican attorney general primary on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. issues 'Do Not Travel' advisories for Spain, Portugal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-cdc-raises-concern-israel-181606940.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) -The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) and State Department on Monday both warned against travel to Spain, Portugal, Cyprus and Kyrgyzstan because of a rising number of COVID-19 cases in those countries. The CDC raised its travel advisory to "Level Four: Very High" for those countries telling Americans they should avoid travel there, while the State Department issued "Do Not Travel" advisories. The CDC on Monday also raised its rating to "Level Four" for Cuba, while the State Department already had Cuba at the highest "Do Not Travel" rating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Light-to-moderate drinking tied to lower risk of heart attack and death in patients with heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/light-moderate-drinking-tied-lower-000927341.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Light-to-moderate alcohol consumption is linked to a reduced risk of heart attack, stroke and death among those with heart disease, according to a study published in the journal BMC Medicine on Monday. The largest benefit - a 50% reduction in risk compared with non-drinkers - was seen in people with heart disease who drank an average of 6 grams of alcohol per day. People who averaged 8 grams per day had a 27% lower risk of death from heart attack, stroke or angina, compared with those who did not drink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tighter rules for Texas power grid are a shift for Gov. Greg Abbott, Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.chronline.com/stories/tighter-rules-for-texas-power-grid-are-a-shift-for-gov-greg-abbott-gop,269649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas &amp;mdash; When Gov. Greg Abbott issued a directive to the regulators of Texas' power grid earlier this month, he did something that could be considered unthinkable for a state chief &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama setting up big bash in Martha's Vineyard to celebrate his 60th...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/564944-obama-setting-up-big-bash-to-celebrate-his-60th</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama is planning a big bash for his 60th birthday in Martha's Vineyard, sources tell The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines cite concerns about fuel shortages at some airports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-c0366478225d9fc717df1f5b76a7c72c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas (AP) — The fuel needle is moving closer to “empty” at some U.S. airports. American Airlines says it’s running into fuel shortages at some smaller and mid-size airports, and in some cases the airline will add refueling stops or fly fuel into locations where the supply is tight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without crowd's roar, Tokyo Olympians search for spirit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-gymnastics-sports-lifestyle-japan-olympic-team-b86bfa6c8ac0287d7cc7332f3fec0072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The beloved American gymnast Sam Mikulak flipped off the parallel bars, stuck the landing and blew a kiss toward the camera. Those watching the men’s Olympics gymnastic competition on television back home knew they’d seen magic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Official Washington, Chasten Buttigieg is stranger in a [very] strange land...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-official-washington-chasten-buttigieg-is-a-stranger-in-a-very-strange-land/ar-AAMzcVF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg knows exactly what he’s doing here. His husband, Chasten, is still trying to figure it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt officials, health groups move to REQUIRE corona vaccines for workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-tipping-point-government-officials-health-groups-move-to-require-coronavirus-vaccines-for-workers/ar-AAMzzZM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New vaccine mandates are being rolled out at VA and the Mayo Clinic, and in California, New York City and elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Sen. Barbara Boxer assaulted, robbed in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/former-sen-barbara-boxer-assaulted-in-oakland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident, which happened “earlier” Monday, happened in or near Oakland’s Jack London Square, according to a tweet from the Democrat’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full House At Miami Hospital With Covid Surge...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/26/jackson-memorial-hospital-covid-icu-unvaccinated-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. David De La Zerda, the lead ICU physician at Jackson, is concerned about the growing number of unvaccinated patients being treated for COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINOVAC COVID VAX FADES AFTER 6 MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/antibodies-sinovacs-covid-19-shot-142748493.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antibodies triggered by Sinovac Biotech's COVID-19 vaccine decline below a key threshold from around six months after a second dose for most recipients, although a third shot could have a strong boosting effect, according to a lab study. Chinese researchers reported the findings from a study of blood samples from healthy adults aged between 18-59 in a paper published on Sunday, which has not been peer reviewed. For participants receiving two doses, two or four weeks apart, only 16.9% and 35.2% respectively still had a level of neutralising antibodies above the threshold six months after the second dose, the paper said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA, NYC to workers: Get jab or face weekly tests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-0f571cd04622cfb37eaf777449f408b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California and New York City announced Monday that they would require all government employees to get the coronavirus vaccine or face weekly COVID-19 testing, and the Department of Veterans Affairs became the first major federal agency to require health care workers to receive the shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos offers NASA $2 billion in exchange for moon contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3355561/jeff-bezos-nasa-moon-contract-blue-origin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFF Bezos has offered Nasa $2 billion in exchange for a contract to allow astronauts to land on the moon. The Amazon founder made his offer to administrator Bill Nelson in an open letter on Monday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman waving Trump flag crashes SUV on MN State Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3354826/woman-waving-trump-flag-crashes-minnesota-state-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FEMALE driver waving a Trump flag crashed a press conference at the Minnesota State Capitol by driving onto the lawn and allegedly speeding towards a crowd. The incident unfolded outside the stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Weed nuns' on mission to heal world with cannabis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3353105/meet-californias-weed-nuns-want-heal-world-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Sisters of the Valley, a group of self-ordained “weed nuns,” are putting their faith in the powers of cannabis to help heal the world. The nonreligious sect, comprised of a sorority…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom vows 'strongest verification system in US'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/newsom-vows-california-will-have-the-strongest-vaccine-verification-system-in-the-us-as-mandate-is-announced/ar-AAMAkzb?ocid=BingNews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California state employees and all healthcare workers must soon get vaccinated against COVID-19 or get tested weekly, Gov. Gavin Newsom announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mixing and matching' takes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/26/delta-people-are-mixing-and-matching-covid-vaccines-over-concerns-about-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Americans say they are finding ways to get extra Covid shots, with some even going as far as receiving the extra shots from different companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomer revolutionizes search for alien life with new project...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/groundbreaking-project-shifts-search-for-aliens-from-military-to-science-674930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new open data nonprofit scientific initiative by Harvard’s Prof. Avi Loeb will use a network of telescopes, cameras and computers to analyze astronomical data to scan for evidence of alien life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes of Bourdain's voice only taste of what's coming...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ai-deepfakes-anthony-bourdains-voice-120046258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI tech used to re-create Anthony Bourdain's voice in a documentary is already stirring legal, labor and ethical issues — and making Hollywood production faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor threatens to remove people with face masks from church...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article253026988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They will be serving Frosty’s in hell before we shut this place down.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIZEN app paying to livestream crime scenes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/25/citizen-pays-new-yorkers-25-an-hour-to-livestream-crime-scenes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to make $200 a day in New York City? Rush to the scene of a murder, a three-alarm fire or a traffic accident — then pull out your phone and start filming. That’s the pitch from Citizen, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA,</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/california-vaccine-verification-ca-state-employees-covid-testing-health-care-workers-coronvirus-vaccinations/10910038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Newsom and California health officials have announced a vaccine verification and testing program that will be implemented for all state employees and health care workers starting in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Expands Vax Studies of Kids 5 to 11...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/pfizer-and-moderna-are-expanding-vaccine-studies-of-kids-5-to-11/ar-AAMzNT9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the urging of federal regulators, two coronavirus vaccine makers are expanding the size of their studies in children ages five to 11 — a precautionary measure designed to detect rare side effects including heart inflammation problems that turned up in vaccinated people younger than 30. Appearing at a televised town-hall-style meeting in Ohio last week, President Biden said that emergency clearance for pediatric vaccines would come “soon.” The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless city workers will have to wear stickers declaring status...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/montclair-covid-stickers-mask/10909151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Monday in Montclair, city workers who choose not to wear a mask must wear stickers that prove they are fully vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers plans to play for PACKERS in stunning turn of events...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/26/aaron-rodgers-plans-to-play-for-packers-in-stunning-turn-of-events/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers may remain a Packer, after all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man blames 'imminent Antifa attack' for shooting woman who tore down his Nazi flag...</title>
      <link> http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/antifa-made-me-do-it-726508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 26--Antifa made me do it. That claim is central to the “stand your ground” defense being floated by the Oklahoma man charged with shooting an unarmed woman in the back as she ran from away from</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
