<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China reports first human case of H10N3 bird flu... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/15131742/first-human-case-h10n3-bird-flu-confirmed-china-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has confirmed the world’s first human case of the H10N3 bird flu. A 41-year-old man, from the eastern city of Zhenjiang, developed a fever and other symptoms and was hospitalised on Apr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers have 1 week to opt out of mass wireless sharing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/01/amazon-us-customers-given-one-week-to-opt-out-of-mass-wireless-sharing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics raise transparency fears over plan to turn all smart home devices into ‘mesh network’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers unite in disdain for Bibi...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/snubbed-fired-and-vilified-opposition-lawmakers-unite-in-disdain-for-netanyahu/ar-AAKCoSX </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA STILL THRIVES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-surreal-submerged-conspiratorial-trump-centered-political-universe-still-thrives/ar-AAKBjCz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various non-Trumps are leveraging the energy of his falsehoods and his base for their own ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Office Supply Hits Another Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/manhattan-office-supply-hits-another-record-even-as-nyc-opens-up/ar-AAKBi7Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan’s supply of office space has reached a fresh record even as leasing picks up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashes in with book...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9640605/Fauci-cashes-COVID-Doctor-release-book-TRUTH-appear-Disney-backed-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infectious disease expert, 80, will publish a tome titled 'Expect the Unexpected: Ten Lessons on Truth, Service, and the Way Forward'. It will be released on November 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTACART Wants to Replace Gig Shoppers With Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/instacart-looks-to-use-robots-over-people-to-do-grocery-shopping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instacart Wants to Replace Army of Gig Shoppers With Robots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon report clears use of drones made by Chinese...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/556370-pentagon-report-clears-use-of-drones-made-by-top-chinese-manufacturer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two drone models made by China’s largest manufacturer have been cleared for use by a Pentagon audit, according to a report summary obtained by The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK reports no new deaths!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601143331-tpr2n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-CASUALTIES (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-UK reports no new COVID-19 deaths for first time since March 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges after Capitol insurrection roil far-right groups...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-michael-pence-donald-trump-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-1e0560dbd5572944e3435e225f8be616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indictments. Infighting. Incarceration. Former President Donald Trump’s lies about a stolen 2020 election united right-wing supporters, conspiracy theorists and militants on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAT HACK SHAKES GLOBE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jbs-sa-lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-bf82114d3f54e5be2241bd5f9a0b2639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — The world’s largest meat processing company is getting back online after production around the world was disrupted by a cyberattack just weeks after a similar incident shut down a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will New York's Vaccine Passport Catch On?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/will-the-excelsior-pass-new-yorks-vaccine-passport-catch-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Upper East Side in Manhattan, a well-heeled crowd flashed it to get into a socially distanced dance performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas ready to roll dice on normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/01/us/las-vegas-reopening/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a giant clock counted down to 12:01 Tuesday morning, crowds cheered the complete reopening of downtown Las Vegas for the first time in more than a year, with live music and no mask or social distancing required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Elvis' stolen from Birthplace sign in Tupelo...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtva.com/content/news/Elvis-Birthplace-sign-vandalized-574538501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtva.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the past few days, someone stole the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA launches slavery reparations task force...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/1/california-launches-slavery-reparations-task-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark California committee to study reparations for African Americans is meeting for the first time, launching a two-year process to address the harms of slavery and systemic racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. hotel up for sale -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-s-company-puts-dc-hotel-lease-up-for-sale-again/ar-AAKBCzF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's company previously tried selling the lease to its luxury Washington hotel before covid struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disgruntled' firefighter kills co-worker,  sets property alight and kills himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9641547/Active-shooter-reported-Santa-Clarita-Police-respond-calls-one-dead-stand-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are responding to calls of an active shooter in Santa Clarita, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing beings on mix-and-match booster shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/01/booster-shot-us-begins-study-testing-mix-and-match-covid-vaccine-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial will include about 150 adults who have been fully vaccinated with the Johnson &amp; Johnson, Moderna or Pfizer Covid vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to suspend oil leases in Alaska Arctic refuge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alaska-arctic-wildlife-refuge-oil-gas-drilling-biden-b9f20088957d42e99b791ff94169198f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Tuesday suspended oil and gas leases in Alaska’s Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, reversing a drilling program approved by the Trump administration and reviving a political fight over a remote region that is home to polar bears and other wildlife — and a rich reserve of oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agent charged with attempted murder of man onboard Metro...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/montgomery-county/2021/06/fbi-agent-accused-of-shooting-metro-passenger-turns-self-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent accused of shooting a Metro passenger last December has turned himself in after facing charges of second-degree murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Body Found In Burning Home Possibly Linked To SoCal Fire Station Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/01/shooting-reported-at-agua-dulce-fire-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities were on scene of a house fire in Acton which may be linked to a shooting at an L.A. County Fire Department station in Agua Dulce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  'SPONGEBOB', 'TRANSFORMERS' Cost U.S. Taxpayers $4 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/spongebob-and-transformers-cost-u-s-taxpayers-4-billion-study-says-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dismissed by critics and devoured by fans, “Transformers: Age of Extinction” was the top box office film in 2014, bringing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavioral health check-ups to become routine for soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/06/01/behavioral-health-check-ups-could-soon-be-as-routine-for-soldiers-as-teeth-cleanings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One soldier suggested mandatory behavioral health checkups for troops that would occur every six months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mossad head hints at continued assassinations, attacks on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/new-mossad-head-barnea-hints-at-continued-assassinations-attacks-on-iran-669807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel would not be passive simply because the majority of the world was willing to look the other way on Iran’s nuclear program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old dies after being hit by electric scooter; DUI arrest made...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/elderly-man-dies-after-being-struck-by-electric-scooter-in-venice-dui-arrest-made-lapd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have arrested a man on suspicion of DUI in connection with a crash involving an electric scooter in Venice that resulted in the death of a 91-year-old man, police said Tuesday. The victim wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite vaccines, nursing homes struggle with outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-nursing-homes-coronavirus-pandemic-health-4575fbefb2cf87e96c82043ef94e5ff3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeannie Wells had hoped that regular visits would resume at her elderly mother’s New York nursing home once all the residents were fully vaccinated against COVID-19. Around Easter, her wish finally came true, and she was able to hold the 93-year-old’s hand more than a year after bringing her mother to the facility for rehabilitation for a fractured hip and knee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel on Edge as Politicians Wrangle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-on-edge-as-politicians-wrangle-over-coalition-to-oust-netanyahu/ar-AAKzE0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Israel’s political class was locked in frenzied horse trading on Monday, as opposition politicians struggled to strike a coalition deal to oust Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, who in turn was waging a last-ditch effort to cling to power. The bartering put a spotlight on the fragmentation of the Israeli political system, in which the short-term fate of the Israeli state — nearly paralyzed after four elections in two years,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rapper DaBaby allegedly involved in Miami shooting...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/06/01/rapper-dababy-allegedly-involved-in-miami-beach-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chart titan is allegedly being quizzed by Miami Beach Police Department after he and his entourage were involved in the shooting late on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's only mountain parrot 'moved to higher altitudes to avoid humans'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/06/01/worlds-only-mountain-parrot-moved-to-higher-altitudes-to-avoid-humans-14688980/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mischievous keas' alpine habitat is threatened by climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State to gather diplomats' health details in response to Havana syndrome...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/01/state-diplomat-health-havana-syndrome-491485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department has faced criticism for not taking the injuries seriously enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Barbershop owner accused of killing customer who refused to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/owner-of-maywood-barbershop-charged-with-killing-customer-who-refused-to-pay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of a suburban barbershop was ordered held in lieu of $250,000 bail Sunday after he allegedly shot and killed a customer who refused to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA STILL THRIVES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-surreal-submerged-conspiratorial-trump-centered-political-universe-still-thrives/ar-AAKBjCz?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various non-Trumps are leveraging the energy of his falsehoods and his base for their own ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Office Supply Hits Another Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/manhattan-office-supply-hits-another-record-even-as-nyc-opens-up/ar-AAKBi7Z?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan’s supply of office space has reached a fresh record even as leasing picks up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANSOM BEING NEGOTIATED?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9638747/Worlds-biggest-meat-supplier-JBS-hit-cyberattack-Canadian-Australian-facilities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JBS, a Sao Paulo-based company with operations in 15 countries, announced on Sunday that they had been hacked. Their Canadian and Australian facilities have been affected so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Seeks 'Lovable' Image in Sign of Diplomatic Rethink...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/china/xi-jinping-seeks-lovable-image-for-china-in-sign-of-diplomatic-rethink/articleshow/83143673.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China News: It remains to be seen whether the push would have any impact on China’s policies in disputes with countries such as the US or Australia. Views of Chin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN MARY in danger of sinking. Can it be saved?</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-06-01/queen-mary-could-capsize-without-urgent-repairs-report-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of court documents and inspection reports released last month reveal the extent of the Queen Mary’s disrepair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's greatest cardsharp reveals all...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/the-worlds-greatest-cardsharp-reveals-all/ar-AAKBf4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Vegas legend, Steve Forte is revered by magicians and gambling experts as the most skilled person ever to deal, shuffle and manipulate a deck of cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent pool 100ft above ground making people sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/viral/london-embassy-gardens-swimming-pool-b1857576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transparent swimming pool built more than 100ft above the ground is making people feel queasy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors Fear Bear-Themed Compound Will Be Next Ruby Ridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/neighbors-fear-bear-themed-compound-will-be-next-ruby-ridge/ar-AAKAD30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alt-right comedian’s plans for a remote patch of land in Idaho have terrified his neighbors, who fear it could become a hostile compound or mark the start of a new Ruby Ridge-style standoff. Comedian Owen Benjamin once had a moderately successful Hollywood career, landing roles in movies and TV shows and briefly becoming engaged to actress Christina Ricci. After moving to the right, he appeared on podcasts hosted by Joe Rogan, Steven Crowder,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Reportedly Telling People He Will Be Reinstated By August...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-is-reportedly-telling-people-he-will-be-reinstated-as-president-by-august/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump is reportedly telling people that he expects to get reinstated by August, according to New York Times reporter Maggie Haberman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living On Busy Road Could Trigger Parkinson's?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/living-on-busy-road-could-trigger-parkinsons-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In experiments on mice, exposure to ambient toxic particles were found to damage neurons that make dopamine, a hallmark of Parkinson's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Police Chief in Wyoming Lost War on Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-a-police-chief-in-wyoming-s-ranchlands-lost-her-war-on-drugs/ar-AAKzpKI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUERNSEY, Wyo. — It was a few days before New Year’s Eve 2019, and Terri VanDam, the chief of Guernsey, Wyo.’s three-person Police Department, had run out of options. For more than a year, Ms. VanDam and her sergeant, Misty Clevenger, had tried and failed to get to the bottom of the drug and alcohol problem in Guernsey, population 1,124. Methamphetamine use was rampant, and much of it was bought and sold right at the bars, they were told, but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close encounters: Dems, Republicans unified in taking UFOs seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/close-encounters-democrats-and-republicans-unified-in-taking-ufos-seriously/ar-AAKADYm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sightings — also known as Unidentified Aerial Phenomena, or UAPs, in official parlance — are having their moment in politics, and a bipartisan one at that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaken by virus, Americans try 'manifesting' positive result...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/shaken-by-covid-some-americans-try-manifesting-a-positive-result-01622511313 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: NATO war games; Russia to send troops west...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/31/us-nato-wage-war-games-europe-russia-send-troops-w/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and its NATO allies on Monday conducted a set of major war games across Europe, while Russia responded by announcing plans to send at least 20 new military units to its western border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian doctors protest 'yoga-beats-Covid' guru...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210601-indian-doctors-protest-yoga-beats-covid-guru</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian doctors protest 'yoga-beats-Covid' guru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tackled after running onto court at WIZARDS-76ERS game...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/556230-man-tackled-after-running-onto-court-at-wizards-76ers-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been banned from Capitol One Arena and could face charges after running onto the court during an NBA playoff game Monday night between the Washington Wizards and Philadelphia 76ers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Tensions Set to Rise as Inspectors Lay Bare Violations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-tension-set-rise-inspectors-095042101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A bleak assessment of Iran’s nuclear transparency cast a pall over months of arduous diplomacy aimed at restoring its atomic accord with world powers that has major implications for Middle Eastern security, global business and oil markets.Despite recent statements of optimism from Iranian and European officials, significant differences at the talks in Vienna remain over how to deal with Iranian enrichment advances and the removal of U.S. sanctions.On Tuesday, less than a day after International Atomic Energy Agency inspectors circulated two confidential reports in the Austrian capital that paint a far from rosy picture of Iran’s willingness to address concerns over its past and present nuclear activities, a top official in Tehran conceded that an agreement could take another two months.The IAEA’s conclusions circulated late Monday among diplomats in Vienna will feed into a parallel diplomatic track at an meeting next week, where the Persian Gulf nation could be subject to formal censure by the agency’s 35-nation board of governors.If Iran considers any condemnation to be especially harsh, the spat could introduce greater acrimony into the Vienna talks. They aim to reintroduce caps on Iran’s nuclear activities in exchange for relief from the sanctions imposed by former President Donald Trump, who all but collapsed the six-year-old accord by withdrawing U.S. participation.Ali Rabiei, spokesman for Iran’s government, said Tuesday that while there were “no obstacles” in the way to restoring the beleaguered agreement, President Hassan Rouhani may now need to use all the remaining time available to his administration to strike a deal.“We’re close to an understanding over principal, nuclear issues,” Rabiei told reporters in a televised news conference, adding “some differences such as Trump’s sanctions and Iran’s measures need to be worked out.”As a two-term president, Rouhani can’t contest Iran’s June 18 election. He’ll remain in office until early August but is widely expected to be succeeded by a conservative hardliner more hostile to the U.S. and the nuclear deal.IAEA Director General Rafael Mariano Grossi reported that Iran has continued to stonewall diplomats investigating decades-old traces of uranium found at undeclared sites, according to a copy of a 6-page document seen by Bloomberg.The Argentine diplomat’s suggestion that Iran could be providing incomplete information has potentially serious consequences. The entire international apparatus of rules that the IAEA enforces is based on verifying nations’ declared nuclear material and nuclear-related activities. Failures can result in referrals to the UN Security Council.“The lack of progress in clarifying the agency’s questions concerning the correctness and completeness of Iran’s safeguards declarations seriously affects the ability of the Agency to provide assurance of the peaceful nature of Iran’s nuclear program,” reads the document.Potentially more worrying, Iranian restrictions imposed on IAEA monitors are undercutting international safeguards, even as the country dramatically ramps up its nuclear activities. Monitors listed 15 areas in Iran where they can no longer do their job, including the verification of centrifuge machine shops and some parts of the uranium fuel cycle. Investigators no longer have daily access to key Iranian enrichment facilities at Fordow or Natanz.“The agency’s verification and monitoring activities have been affected as a result of Iran’s decision to stop the implementation of its nuclear-related commitments,” Grossi told diplomats in a second 13-page report.Historically, such conclusions would result in diplomatic censure of Iran in the form of an IAEA resolution. The country has been subject more than a dozen such motions since 2003, including the consequential 2006 referral to the Security Council that set off the subsequent waves of international sanctions that still linger.But with nuclear talks still in high gear and Iran’s election nearing, IAEA envoys may exercise more caution when they convene June 7. Iran had threatened to rip up a provisional monitoring arrangement if it faced censure at the last IAEA board meeting.Envoys will have to decide whether reconstituting intrusive nuclear inspections -- widely seen by world powers as the most important element of the 2015 nuclear deal -- requires diplomatic coercion or dialog.Success in Vienna could see significant quantities of Iranian oil flow into global markets, and ease tensions in the Persian Gulf that spiraled during the confrontation between the Trump administration and Tehran.(Adds Iranian spokesman in the second and sixth paragraphs,)More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Croatia yacht holidays in demand once again...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601103914-cgu99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CROATIA-LEISURE (TV, PIX): Escaping the crowds: Croatia yacht holidays in demand once again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow ready to stop 'unfriendly' foreign action...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531130429-gzqsb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-SECURITY/PATRUSHEV (URGENT):Russia says it is ready to use force to stop 'unfriendly' foreign action - Ifax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports human case of H10N3 bird flu, a possible first...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-bird-flu-flu-health-b5862e1d9892b25fdb470abf30432289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A man in eastern China has contracted what might be the world’s first human case of the H10N3 strain of bird flu, but the risk of large-scale spread is low, the government said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 years after Tulsa race massacre, Black residents await Biden, and reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210601-100-years-after-tulsa-race-massacre-black-residents-await-biden-and-reparations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;100 years after Tulsa race massacre, Black residents await Biden, and reparations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist tricks high-profile Republicans into retweeting pic of Lee Harvey Oswald...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/journalist-tricked-high-profile-republicans-013611320.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candace Owens claimed the portraits were photoshopped, despite Oswald being a former military member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osaka crisis throws light on stars' mental health and media 'voyeurism'...</title>
      <link>https://au.sports.yahoo.com/osaka-crisis-throws-light-stars-103642095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naomi Osaka's decision to withdraw from the French Open, after revealing her battle with depression and anxiety, has thrown the tournament into turmoil and cast a harsh light on the mental health of the sport's superstars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning ship covered beautiful beaches in plastic 'snow.' Now Sri Lanka faces environmental disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-burning-ship-covered-beautiful-beaches-in-plastic-e2-80-98snow-e2-80-99-now-sri-lanka-faces-an-environmental-disaster/ar-AAKADrb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists fear the plastic pellets could travel as far as the other side of Sri Lanka, killing wildlife and damaging sensitive ecosystems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He bashed police on FACEBOOK. Then chief threatened fake charges unless he deleted it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-bashed-a-police-chief-on-facebook-then-the-chief-threatened-fake-charges-unless-he-deleted-it-feds-say/ar-AAKAx5z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Hazleton Police Chief Brian Buglio was charged with threatening a man with fake criminal charges in retaliation for critical Facebook posts, federal prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
