<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/standing-ovation-niros-expletive-trump-094007450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood megastar Robert De Niro got a standing ovation at the Tony Awards for using an expletive to condemn US President Donald Trump. The Oscar-winning De Niro, 74, was at the annual event for the top US theater awards late Sunday to introduce a performance from rock legend Bruce Springsteen. "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot a rat? Real-time map aims to plot Paris sightings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spot-rat-real-time-map-aims-plot-paris-142222307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rats have become an increasingly common sight in Paris over the past few years, but one local official wants to make sure everyone knows just how many are being spotted daily in his corner of the French capital. Geoffroy Boulard, who heads the municipal council of the 17th Arrondissement, has set up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sphinx row reignites between Egypt and China after replica reappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/sphinx-row-reignites-between-egypt-144026437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt has vented fury at China after a full-size replica of the Great Sphinx of Giza reappeared in northern China two years after pressure from Cairo seemingly forced it to be torn down. The dispute began in 2014 when the statue was erected in Hebei province, sparking protests from ministers in Egypt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant man and flower power at London Men's Fashion Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pregnant-man-flower-power-london-mens-fashion-week-144707929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An imagined male pregnancy, flower necklaces and melting ice caps were some of the more striking images at London Men's Fashion Week, which wrapped up on Monday. Chinese designer Xander Zhou's collection featured a male model with a fake bump on show, wearing jeans and a white t-shirt reading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wit,  humility and deep knowledge of U.S. history likely tactics from Kim's playbook...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91ca528dd0cd4aa1bf5ab8f7388c17df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — Dry wit. Disarming humility. An appreciation for wiggle room, and lots of it.        After six years of self-imposed isolation from the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT!</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/asia/la-fg-trump-kim-summit-20180610-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American and North Korean diplomats held last-minute talks Monday in hopes of producing a substantive disarmament breakthrough at the historic meeting between President Trump and North Korea’s Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outsiders swoop in vowing to rescue rural hospitals... </title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/outsiders-swoop-in-vowing-to-rescue-rural-hospitals-short-on-hope-and-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The community of Surprise Valley, Calif., wrestled with the idea of selling its tiny, long-cherished hospital to a Denver entrepreneur who sees a big future in lab tests for faraway patients. Last …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S customers claim new toilet rule is causing them to wet themselves...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6499237/mcdonalds-new-toilet-rule-customers-wet-themselves/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUSTOMERS at a McDonald’s restaurant in Australia have taken to social media to complain about strict bathroom policies that have caused “accidents”.  In order to use the bathroom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARRAKHAN RANTS AGAINST 'JEWISH POWER'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/11/louis-farrakhan-jewish-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A friend of many</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TESLA software to offer 'full' autonomy, Musk says...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tesla-software-offer-full-autonomy-musk-says-133727418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An update to Tesla's Autopilot software coming in August will enable "full self-driving features" for the automaker's electric cars, chief executive Elon Musk says. Musk's comments come amid a race by automakers and tech firms to roll out fully autonomous vehicles, but also rising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC champion asks to meet Trump, rips 'Filthadelphia Eagles'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/391619-ufc-champion-asks-to-meet-trump-rips-filthadelphia-eagles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA says talks moving quickly, Trump to leave early...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4a5201ceceb44f896e2e497537ba116/US-says-NKorea-talks-moving-quickly,-Trump-to-leave-early</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — President Donald Trump plans to depart early from his unprecedented summit with Kim Jong Un, the White House said Monday, declaring that nuclear talks with North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crucial test of Ebola vaccine raises hopes, doubts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1bc4302e133540feb894814e612c8df9/Crucial-test-of-Ebola-vaccine-raises-hopes,-doubts-in-Congo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MBANDAKA, Congo (AP) — Irene Mboyo Mola spent 11 days caring for her husband as he died of Ebola in a hospital where she said nurses were too scared to get close. She helped him t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D'Souza to Compare Trump With Lincoln in Upcoming Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/dinesh-dsouza-compare-trump-lincoln-upcoming-film-1118718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;D’Souza acknowledges that the optics of a pro-Trump documentary will be deemed suspicious in some circles, given the president pardoned him May 31 for violating campaign finance laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beers at Ramadan: Dubai Relaxes Rules as Gulf Countries Adapt to Draw Business...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/beers-at-ramadan-dubai-relaxes-rules-as-gulf-countries-adapt-to-draw-business-1528719539</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia’s neighbors have loosened financial and cultural boundaries for fear of losing business as the kingdom attempts to remold itself as a financial and tourism hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Public Gets First Dose of Historic Meeting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e54d3ae89d554e9985ab5f482dc40957/North-Korea-gets-first-big-dose-of-Trump-summit-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — North Koreans got their first big dose of news Monday that their leader Kim Jong Un had arrived in Singapore for what even the state-run media was ca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver defecates on man in fit of road rage...</title>
      <link>http://www.lehighvalleylive.com/lehigh-county/index.ssf/2018/06/road_rage_defecation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lehighvalleylive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The accused and the victim got into a road rage argument, leading to the accused to defecate on the victim," Pennsylvania State Police said in a succinct news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman in San Diego stabbed after offering man GATORADE...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/sd-me-gatorade-stabbing-20180610-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 59-year-old man was arrested on suspicion of stabbing a woman who offered him a Gatorade in the Shelltown community Saturday night, San Diego police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama secret meetings with 2020 contenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/11/obama-2020-elections-sanders-warren-635165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still the reluctant leader of the Democratic Party, Obama has been providing counsel to Bernie Sanders, Elizabeth Warren and other presidential hopefuls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Fed Set Off Recession Alarm?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/will-the-fed-set-off-a-recession-alarm-1528714800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the Federal Reserve, just four months into his term, could be in the uncomfortable situation this week of signaling that a recession is coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothel bans weighed in Nevada as legal pimp runs for office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4e4b6dc9388455e884857db9da2d333/Brothel-bans-weighed-in-Nevada-as-legal-pimp-runs-for-office </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAHRUMP, Nev. (AP) — A state marketed as a place where people can indulge in all manner of sins is confronting its status as the only place in America where you can legally pay so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER can tell if drunk by way hold phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/uber-tell-drunk-way-hold-103219165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many commuters who have had one too many after work, Uber has been a godsend, allowing over-the-limit passengers to stumble into a cab and get dropped off outside their door at the touch of a button. But those days could be numbered after the taxi app invented a system for detecting drunk passengers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye ties number one streak with new album...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kanye-ties-number-one-streak-album-044619801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West has reached number one with all of his studio albums except his debut, 2004's "The College Dropout," and also topped the chart with a collaborative album with Jay-Z, "Watch the Throne," from 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Tips Brazil for World Cup After 1 Million Simulations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/11/goldman-tips-brazil-for-world-cup-after-1-million-simulations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Tips Brazil for World Cup After 1 Million Simulations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Tries to Halt March to Cashlessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/11/sweden-tries-to-halt-total-cashlessness-with-lawmaker-proposal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden Tries to Halt Total Cashlessness With Lawmaker Proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUPERT EVERETT: Gay actors in Hollywood treated like second-class citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.metro.news/gays-second-class-citizens-in-hollywood-says-rupert-everett/1095893/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.metro.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUPERT EVERETT says he has lost out on ‘three or four’ roles in big Hollywood films because he is gay. The ‘aggressively heterosexual’ film industry treats gay performers like ‘second-class citizens’, he said. ‘There’s tons of roles that I haven’t got for lots of different reasons, some of them probably for not being a good... View Article</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/tony-awards-2018-political-moments-1118098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor twice used an expletive to refer to the president while introducing Bruce Springsteen's performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE NIRO STUNS TONY AWARDS:  'F*CK TRUMP'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/legit/news/robert-de-niro-slams-trump-at-the-tonys-f-trump-1202839957/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro had a simple introduction to Bruce Springsteen’s Tony performance. “I just want to say one thing — F— Trump,” De Niro said while pumping his fists in th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER CEO Apologizes For Eating Chick-Fil-A...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/10/twitter-ceo-chick-fil-a-gay-marriage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Please delete this'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Kim to begin with one-on-one...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-and-kim-jong-un-will-begin-summit-with-one-on-one-meeting-ap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two leaders will meet for up to two hours, with translators, before an expanded meeting including their advisers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodel's quick flag ends Grand Prix one lap early...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/motor/formula1/2018/06/10/winnie-harlow-gaffe-ends-canadian-grand-prix-one-lap-early/689233002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winnie Harlow caused a premature end to the Canadian Grand Prix when she gave winner Sebastian Vettel the checkered flag on lap 69 instead of 70.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Terminates Channel of Firearms Parts Retailer 'Without Warning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/youtube-guns-brownells-channel-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube suddenly terminated the channel for the firearms parts company Brownells, the company claimed on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican leftist frontrunner widens lead for presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-election-poll/mexican-leftist-frontrunner-widens-lead-for-presidency-poll-idUSKBN1J700K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican presidential frontrunner Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador extended his lead to nearly 17 points over his nearest rival ahead of the July 1 vote, according to a poll published on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight diverted after passenger with blow up doll acts 'disgracefully'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/10/man-banned-life-bringing-blow-doll-flight-ibiza-7620477/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He will never be able to fly with Jet2 again after his 'deplorable' behaviour forced a flight to Ibiza to divert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of govt rises as local newspapers close...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/jun/10/cost-of-government-rises-when-local-newspaper-closes-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study inspired by a John Oliver segment has analysed data from 1,266 US counties and tallied the cost of losing a print watchdog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero pit bull saves baby from fire, carries by diaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article212886564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nana Chai, 30, says her pit bull Sasha saved her and her 7-month-old baby's life when a fire broke out in her fourplex. The dog tried to carry the baby away from the flames by her diaper, alerting Nana to the smoke creeping under one of her doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman drove 2 children in pet kennels...</title>
      <link>https://www.commercialappeal.com/story/news/2018/06/10/memphis-crime-grandma-charged-transporting-kids-dog-kennels/689124002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commercialappeal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grandmother, 62, has been charged with transporting two children in dog kennels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL:   Trump's action sobering, depressing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-trump-aide-says-trudeau-stabbed-us-back-141508742--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel, French President Emmanuel Macron and the other leaders clashed with Trump over steel and aluminum tariffs as well as his decision to abandon a deal with Iran to limit its nuclear program. The group managed a common statement in which they agreed to disagree on some issues, only to have Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MISSION OF PEACE'</title>
      <link>https://nz.news.yahoo.com/unorthodox-trump-faces-toughest-test-yet-nkorea-summit-051101169--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nz.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embarking on a self-described "mission of peace," President Donald Trump puts his seat-of-the-pants foreign policy to its toughest test yet as he attempts this week to personally broker an end to North Korea's nuclear program in talks with Kim Jong Un. The impulsive American president,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, advisers blast Canada's Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2be8832bbe7437cb0be5e9436dcb5f4/White-House-takes-up-fight-against-'back-stabbing'-Trudeau</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUEBEC CITY (AP) — Bashing the leader of one of America's venerable allies, the White House escalated its trade tirade and leveled more withering and unprecedented criticism Sunda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Special place in hell'...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/10/theres-special-place-in-hell-for-trudeau-after-his-g7-stunt-top-wh-trade-adviser-peter-navarro-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump should be careful not to become a propaganda tool duing his historic meeting with North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un in Singapore, Former U.S. ambassador to the United Nations Bill Richardson said on Fox News Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, advisers blast Canada's Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/06/10/trump-advisers-blast-canadas-trudeau/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attacks are meant to show strength ahead of the summit with North Korea's Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE BIG GAMBLE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/isolated-kim-takes-big-gamble-leaving-home-trump-010909043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — Spare a moment, as you anticipate one of the most unusual summits in modern history, to consider North Korea's leader as he left the all-encompassing bubble of his locked-down stronghold of Pyongyang on Sunday and stepped off a jet onto Singapore soil for his planned sit-down with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka and Jared pose with Capitals after Stanley Cup win...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/391574-ivanka-trump-jared-kushner-pose-with-capitals-after-stanley-cup-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump and Jared Kushner took a picture with recent Stanley Cup champions the Washington Capitals after reportedly running into each other at a restaurant in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's Long Road to Hell... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/venezuelas-long-road-to-hell-1528652625 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few countries have provided such a perfect example of socialist policies in practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stampede of Meatless Products Overrun Grocery Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-stampede-of-meatless-products-overrun-grocery-store-meat-cases-1528653236 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious cattlemen see the meat section as their turf, a private reserve of steaks and chops with one thing in common—a butchered animal carcass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Protests over plan for Muslim rapper to perform at Bataclan...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/10/protests-plan-muslim-rapper-perform-bataclan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A row erupted has over a planned performance by a controversial Muslim rapper at the Bataclan, where 90 people were killed during the November 2015 Paris attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely people twice as likely to die from heart problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/heart-problems-lonely-people-loneliness-cardiovascular-disease-new-study-european-society-of-a8391816.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Loneliness is more common today than ever before’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man bites straphanger's lip off in subway station brawl...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/10/man-bites-straphangers-lip-off-in-subway-station-brawl-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He bit off more than he could chew. A brawl between two Brooklyn straphangers turned gory over the weekend when one man bit off part of another guy’s lip, according to police and a video of the inc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polio makes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-06-polio-comeback-venezuela-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polio has been reported in Venezuela, a crisis-wracked country where the disease had been eradicated decades ago, the Pan-American Health Organization reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Predicts 'War Between Cross and Crescent'...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/jerusalem/2018/06/10/erdogan-predicts-war-between-the-cross-and-crescent-over-austria-mosque-closures/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan attacked Austria's impending closure of mosques and consequent expulsion of Turkish-funded imams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BELMONT STAKES: Losing owner calls for investigation into tactics used during race...</title>
      <link>http://www.kentucky.com/sports/spt-columns-blogs/sidelines-with-john-clay/article212919059.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Repole, co-owner of fourth-place finisher Vino Rosso and 10th-place finisher Noble Indy, said Sunday he hopes NYRA will look into tactics used by Restoring Hope's jockey in Saturday's Belmont Stakes. Restoring Hope is trained by Bob Baffert, who also trains Justify, the winner of the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Public Unaware Of Historic  Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2018-06-10/business-as-usual-in-north-korea-as-public-unaware-of-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With all the international attention focused on Singapore and the historic summit between President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, Pyongyang must be buzzing with excitement, right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia says new Yemen missile intercepted...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-arabia-says-yemen-missile-intercepted-185317972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi air defences on Sunday intercepted a ballistic missile over the southern city of Jizan after being fired from rebel-held territory in neighbouring Yemen, a Saudi-led military coalition said. Iran-backed Huthi rebels have in recent months ramped up missile attacks against neighbouring Saudi Arabia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration raid worries landscapers relying on foreign help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ba1ff783d0d34251b93c2659a851ab32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOLEDO, Ohio (AP) — Already facing a severe labor shortage, landscaping businesses that can't keep up with booming demand for backyard patios and fire pits worry that an immigrati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S FOR KIM?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5826669/Will-Kim-seek-burger-diplomacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean officials said the isolated regime wants to modernise its economy and become a 'normal country,' a South Korean revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report on Pennsylvania priest abuse to be most extensive yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/report-pennsylvania-priest-abuse-most-extensive-yet-145523867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — The results of a lengthy probe into the handling of sexual abuse claims by Roman Catholic dioceses throughout Pennsylvania, which victim advocates say will be the biggest and most exhaustive ever by a U.S. state, could be made public within weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summits are tricky: Kennedy, Nixon and Reagan learned the hard way...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/nation/article_99d6cf1c-44a4-5e05-b65b-d956bc8376d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In his 1961 inaugural address, President John F. Kennedy spoke about the possibility of daring diplomacy to thaw even the coldest of relationships: “Let us never negotiate out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel ban, gerrymandering top Supreme Court's closing flurry of cases...</title>
      <link>http://www.watertowndailytimes.com/national/travel-ban-gerrymandering-top-supreme-courts-closing-flurry-of-cases-20180610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.watertowndailytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Supreme Court is moving toward the end of its nine-month term with some of its biggest cases still to be decided, led by the fight over President Donald Trump’s travel ban. The justices also will rule on gerrymandering, union fees, internet sales taxes, credit card fees and cellphone privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget cutters may doom the International Space Station...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/technology/391528-budget-cutters-may-doom-the-international-space-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cutting off funding for the ISS now would be a fiscal, scientific and national security folly of the highest order.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
