<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Teen basketball player died after collapsing in 97-degree heat. Coaches now face murder charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-teen-basketball-player-died-after-collapsing-in-97-degree-heat-her-coaches-now-face-murder-charges/ar-AANesu2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two years after Imani Bell's death, her basketball coaches have been charged with murder, cruelty to children, involuntary manslaughter and reckless conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45-year-old Kansas mayor needs pacemaker after long-haul fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-45-year-old-kansas-mayor-needs-a-pacemaker-after-a-long-haul-covid-fight-i-thought-i-was-going-to-beat-it/ar-AANeg4Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The politician is one of millions thought to be suffering from long-haul covid, a lingering condition that leaves some facing heart palpitations, shortness of breath and other health problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says Bezos would be on Pluto by now 'if lobbying and lawyers could get you to orbit'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-jeff-bezos-103330328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the richest people on the planet locked in space race through their companies Blue Origin and SpaceX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis confronts growing resistance...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/567409-desantis-confronts-growing-resistance-over-covid-19-handling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE BEACH, Fla. – Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) is facing growing resistance to his hardline stance against COVID-19 restrictions and mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surf Instructor Killed Children and Claimed QANON Made Him Do It, FBI Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/12/surf-instructor-killed-his-children-and-claimed-qanon-made-him-do-it-f-b-i-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California surfing instructor confessed to killing his two children with a spearfishing gun after abducting them, telling investigators that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Qaddafi Comeback Gambit Sows New Conflict With West...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/putins-qaddafi-comeback-gambit-sows-new-conflict-with-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents asked to limit 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/covid-surge-prompts-one-florida-county-ask-residents-use-911-n1276561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can tell you compared to March or July where we were last year to where we are now, this is a lot worse," a Brevard County fire official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Britney Spears to political rivals, Joel Greenberg searched scores of names on confidential database...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/from-britney-spears-to-political-rivals-joel-greenberg-searched-scores-of-names-on-confidential-database/ar-AANcHff?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — During his time as Seminole County’s tax collector, Joel Greenberg used a confidential database to look up the personal information of fellow elected officials, political rivals, county employees, family members and even celebrities — including Britney Spears and Justin Timberlake — newly released records show. The names of hundreds that Greenberg pried into — ranging from U.S. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-UK relations strained as prince refuses to talk to investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prince-andrew-america-epstein-probes-cooperation-b1900854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears issue over Duke of York could affect wider efforts to collaborate on high-profile legal cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand hopes to relax border controls NEXT YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zealand-hopes-relax-border-controls-001300967.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's Jacinda Ardern said Thursday that strict border controls would remain this year but she hoped to cautiously reopen to the rest of the world in 2022 while maintaining the country's virus-free status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines begin to see another drop in travel demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/airlines-begin-to-see-drop-in-travel-demand-as-virus-numbers-rise/ar-AANcGwL?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surge in coronavirus caseloads across the nation is starting to dampen the enthusiasm of leisure travelers, and some airlines are warning of weaker bookings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida covid hospitalizations set another record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-hospitalizations-soar-for-another-day-led-by-broward-county/ar-AANdfzC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the 11th straight day, Florida hospitals set records for the number of COVID patients they are treating, and on Wednesday the state set a new high for daily cases. On Wednesday, Florida hospitals had 15,449 patients a significant jump from just two days earlier when admissions surpassed 14,000 to set a record. The high count reached Wednesday occurred with only 230 of 261 hospitals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICILY SIZZLES: Nearly 120°, threatens Europe's all-time heat record...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210811-new-heat-record-in-italy-as-lucifer-sweeps-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New heat record in Italy as 'Lucifer' sweeps in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Demands Vax Proof For Stores, Restaurants, Movie Theaters... MORE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/los-angeles-city-requires-vaccination-vaccine-indoors-1234813086/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles City Council voted 13-0 today to have the city attorney prepare an ordinance requiring people to show proof of at least partial vaccination against Covid to enter most public indoor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cz-YKyCmJBg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden asks OPEC to up oil output while limiting U.S. energy production...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/11/joe-biden-asks-opec-oil-output-while-limiting-us-e/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Wednesday made the embarrassing move to call on OPEC and its allies to boost oil production as gas prices continue to climb, underscoring alarms over the U.S. losing its energy independence under President Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge refuses to toss DONINION defamation suits against Giuliani and Lindell...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/11/judge-dominion-defamation-suits-powell-504000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling from the Trump appointee is likely to force depositions by the three allies of the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC TAX COLLECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-set-record-through-july-real-federal-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set a new record for the amount of taxes it collected through the first ten months of fiscal 2021 (October through July), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Tropical storm will approach Florida this weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-fred-forecast-track-us-florida-landfall-impacts/997558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm could falter as it encounters land in the Caribbean but will restrengthen over warm waters setting the stage for 18 inches of rain and 90-mph winds in parts of the Southeast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College professor charged with setting CA fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/11/gary-stephen-maynard-college-professor-charged-wit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A college professor suspected in a series of arson fires has been charged with setting a small blaze in a forest near Northern California’s massive Dixie Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Gov Escapes to Italy as Cases Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.northjersey.com/story/news/coronavirus/2021/08/09/gov-phil-murphy-italy-vacation-nj-delta-variant-cases-rise/5536749001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.northjersey.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NJ has seen a sharp rise in COVID hospitalizations and cases in the last five weeks due to the rapid spread of the highly contagious delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani told agents: OK to 'throw a fake' during political campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/giuliani-told-agents-it-was-okay-to-e2-80-98throw-a-fake-e2-80-99-during-political-campaign/ar-AANcUHm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You’re under no obligation to tell the truth,” Giuliani’s law partner said in defending the former New York mayor’s promise of an October surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel approves new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-hits-400-serious-covid-cases-ahead-of-corona-cabinet-meeting-676412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cabinet decided that starting August 18th the Green Pass will apply to everyone over the age of 3, and gatherings will be limited based on the number of participants and their vaccination status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi's Largest Hospital Converting Garage to Covid Ward...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mississippis-largest-hospital-converting-garage-covid-ward-state-short-icu-beds-1618487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There were ZERO available ICU beds in Mississippi as of early this morning. None," UMMC Dr. LouAnne Woodward said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel officials draft classified report as they near finish of 90-day Covid probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/11/politics/classified-report-covid-origins-under-review-90-day-probe/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence officials are nearing the end of a 90-day investigation into the origins of Covid-19 that was ordered by President Joe Biden, and have drafted a classified report that is now in the preliminary review process, according to three sources familiar with the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Sen. Scott Brown plans to jump back into politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-scott-brown-plans-to-jump-back-into-political-arena-8eae7d7c-c937-468d-8777-fc1e4b7a07da.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are two potentially attractive opportunities for Brown in his new home state of New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraway Planets Don't Seem So Distant Anymore...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/faraway-planets-don-t-seem-so-distant-anymore/ar-AANbGU7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers are stepping up their attempts to unravel the mysteries of exoplanets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden slams Trump for racking up $8 trillion in debt; Vows to tax rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-slams-trump-for-racking-up-8-trillion-in-debt-as-he-vows-democrats-will-pay-for-their-spending-plan-by-taxing-the-rich/ar-AANd9vW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Senate passed Biden's infrastructure plan, the president said his economic agenda won't be anything like Trump's "unpaid tax cuts."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KABUL SEIZED IN WEEKS?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/11/us-officials-warn-taliban-could-seize-kabul-in-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials have warned that the Taliban could seize Kabul in as little as one month amid the American troop withdrawal from Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Pay-for-play scandal behind many MAXIM, PLAYBOY 'covers'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/11/the-pay-for-play-scandal-behind-many-sexy-maxim-playboy-covers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any woman can be a magazine cover girl these days — if she’s willing to pony up the dough. Juliet Amelia, a 45-year-old licensed massage therapist from Florida, looked like the hottest model …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico drug cartel threatens prominent news anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/americas/mexico-cartel-milenio-azucena-uresti-intl-latam/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A masked man claiming to be the leader of the Jalisco New Generation Cartel threatens to "get" Milenio TV anchor Azucena Uresti for her coverage of the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICILY SIZZLES: Nearly 120°, threatens Europe's all-time heat record...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/europe-all-time-heat-record-set-sicily-065cef11-fdb7-4aaf-abd5-82b5b8d7a475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature record came in the midst of a regional heat wave that has contributed to wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANNETT cuts crime coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.poynter.org/reporting-editing/2021/gannett-launches-a-network-wide-push-to-rework-its-crime-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poynter.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer mugshots, additional context and moving beyond police narratives are just some of the changes its newsrooms are making</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul vows not to have 'toxic' workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/11/kathy-hochul-vows-big-difference-from-cuomo-administration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo stunned the state with his resignation. Kathy Hochul, his lieutenant governor, will replace him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE $4 TRILLION NEW SPENDING</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/democratic-led-senate-votes-spend-4-trillion-less-24-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate passed a $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill, which includes $517 billion in new spending, as well as a $3.5 trillion budget reconciliation proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Create 'Master Faces' to Bypass Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78ygn/researchers-create-master-faces-to-bypass-facial-recognition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the paper, their findings imply that facial recognition systems are “extremely vulnerable.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JEOPARDY!' announces 2 new hosts: Mike Richards, Mayim Bialik...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/tv/2021/08/11/jeopardy-mike-richards-and-mayim-bialik-permanent-hosts/8094579002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Jeopardy" announced Wednesday that Mike Richards and Mayim Bialik will take over as permanent hosts of the game shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA unveils tools to 'reduce abuse, racist comments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210811-instagram-unveils-new-tools-to-reduce-abuse-racist-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram unveils new tools to reduce abuse, racist comments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Macron Defends 'Democratic' Handling of Crisis as Protests Swell...</title>
      <link>https://www.luxtimes.lu/en/european-union/pandemic-france-s-macron-defends-democratic-handling-of-covid-crisis-6113d6c0de135b923673a23f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.luxtimes.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People’s status is displayed in a so-called health pass, or vaccine passport, that the government says is the only way to enable a return to normal life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of  doses face expiration...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/millions-of-coronavirus-vaccine-doses-around-the-world-face-expiration/ar-AANcyQI?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As demand slows in wealthy nations like the Netherlands, more dust is gathering — and more doses are expiring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAKE ELECTION':  Brazil's Bolsonaro follows the Trump playbook.</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-bolsonaro-follows-the-trump-playbook/ar-AANaTih?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics argue that the president, like Trump, is attempting to sow doubt around the upcoming 2022 election as he faces potential defeat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN, DELTA, SOUTHWEST will NOT mandate for employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/three-us-airlines-no-vaccine-mandate-workers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEOs of Southwest Airlines, American Airlines and Delta Air Lines say they are not requiring unvaccinated employees to receive the shot, breaking with United Airlines' mandate that workers get vaccinated by October 25 or face getting fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Suspends Rand Paul for Questioning Masks...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/youtube-censors-rand-paul-who-says-company-has-become-arm-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul says he's turning to other platforms like Rumble to upload content that YouTube censors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAMILY DOLLAR store closes after entire staff quits over low pay, long hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/family-dollar-employees-at-nebraska-store-walk-off-job-cite-low-pay-and-long-shifts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Family Dollar store was forced to temporarily close when the entire staff, fed up over poor pay, management, and long hours, walked off the job</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil Nas X fears for his safety after homophobic comments from other rappers...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/lil-nas-x-montero-industry-baby-1235038104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the 2021 Power of Young Hollywood Issue, Variety profiled three young stars making an impact in the entertainment industry. For more, click here.  Newfound fame has felled many a young supersta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge California fire grows; Montana blaze threatens towns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-fires-environment-and-nature-california-ae696fedb55c81fb3b0ae697546c602d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENVILLE, Calif. (AP) — California’s largest single wildfire in recorded history continued to grow after destroying nearly 550 homes while authorities in Montana ordered evacuations as a wind-driven blaze roared toward several remote communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1 million get booster shots without FDA approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/over-1m-people-have-obtained-covid-19-booster-shots-without-fda-approval</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government health experts estimate that at least 1.1 million people in the United States have received an extra dose of a COVID-19 vaccine due to concerns about the delta variant, according to a leaked document from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, US air force hold first-of-kind aerial drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/iaf-afcent-hold-first-aerial-drill-676402?_ga=2.157546623.455501693.1628679030-1969581575.1579377799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Air Force pilots flew alongside their United States counterparts in drill named 'Desert Eagle'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Apes say hello and goodbye, and judge politeness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/apes-say-hello-goodbye-judge-24739309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simians use the equivalent of human manners to work together, using gestures to say 'hello' and wrap up conversations by repeating 'okay, sounds good', scientists say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Suspends Rand Paul for Questioning Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/11/tech/rand-paul-youtube-suspension/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul, a Kentucky Republican, has been suspended from YouTube for seven days over a video claiming that masks are ineffective in fighting Covid-19, according to a YouTube spokesperson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT NEW RECORDS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/10/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Wednesday after inflation jumped, but not by quite as much as investors feared when stripping out volatile food and energy prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALARM:  PFIZER only 42% effective against infection in July...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-vaccines-pfizer-moderna-delta-biden-e9be4bb0-3d10-4f56-8054-5410be357070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Biden official called the preprint study "a wakeup call."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Market for Vaccination Cards Grows...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/11/a-black-market-in-covid-19-vaccination-cards-was-inevitable/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis says doubts reports of Florida ventilators request...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/567336-desantis-says-he-doubts-reports-of-florida-ventilators-request</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOUBLE AGENT: Brit arrested for 'spying for Putin' in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15837275/brit-embassy-worker-arrested-spy-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRIT working at the UK Embassy in Berlin has been arrested on suspicion of passing secrets to Russia. Scotland Yard said the 57-year old was arrested as part of a joint investigation between its …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The judge upending CA gun laws: 'Blessed' jurist or 'stone-cold ideologue'?</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/the-judge-upending-california-s-gun-laws-blessed-jurist-or-stone-cold-ideologue/article_685667a2-ba22-5abc-a3d3-73dc4ed22018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly two decades, U.S. District Judge Roger T. Benitez was a low-profile jurist handling routine immigration and drug cases in San Diego federal court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continued problems after massive beach sewage spill now hitting water supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/continued-problems-after-massive-beach-sewage-spill-now-hitting-water-supply-amid-drought/article_b97f70db-0a55-5a4d-9590-1aa700429224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES – Problems at a Los Angeles sewage treatment plant that caused a massive sewage spill into Santa Monica Bay last month have severely reduced the region's water recycling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal shelter puts lonely pets on TINDER...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210811134103-sgfll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-PETS (TV, PIX):A purrfect match! Animal shelter puts lonely pets on Tinder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Most Prefer To Get Revenge On Others Immediately...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/revenge-serve-hot-and-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;58 percent of participants preferred to take immediate revenge, even if it meant dealing a lesser blow to an enemy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of white people in USA declines first time in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881353/Minorities-drive-population-growth-number-white-people-declines-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data, set to be released on August 12, will reveal just how much the ethnic and racial make up of the nation has shifted over the past decade, with Hispanic and Asian populations on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Cuomo Hemorrhages Female Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/chris-andrew-cuomo-cnn-female-viewers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week's ratings took a tumble compared to this time last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOFUNDME topped $200K after woman said she and kids faced eviction. Then real mom came forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-gofundme-topped-200k-after-a-woman-said-she-and-her-kids-faced-eviction-then-their-real-mom-came-forward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dasha Kelly's online fundraiser caught the attention of many sympathetic people and media such as CNN. Money was flying in until the truth came out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German nurse injected patients with saline instead of vaccines, sparking fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-german-nurse-injected-patients-with-saline-instead-of-coronavirus-vaccines-sparking-fury/ar-AANbUwf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 9,000 people who may have been given bogus shots in the spring will be offered new vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sickos can plant porn on iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3452390/iphone-airdrop-apple-block-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERVS can put pornography on your iPhone by exploiting one of the gadget’s best features. We reveal how to stop people taking advantage of this handy trick. Read all the latest Phones &amp; G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China brutal death row with mobile injection vans, firing squads...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3452791/china-death-row-canadian-diplomat-sentenced-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CANADIAN man is set to join hundreds of shackled inmates on China’s degrading death row as they await agonising lethal injections or firing squads. Robert Schellenberg, believed to be 38, from Ab…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Abbott lacks predecessor star power. Yet nobody even close to him in gov race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/08/11/gov-greg-abbott-texas-502135</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Governor Greg Abbott lacks his predecessors’ star power. He’s constantly dodging attacks from the right. His state is facing another Covid surge. Yet nobody is even close to him in the governor’s race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 13, duct taped to seat after 'trying to kick out window' on flight...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/08/10/caught-on-camera-teenage-passenger-restrained-on-flight-from-maui-to-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight from Maui to Los Angeles was diverted to Honolulu after a 13-year-old boy became disruptive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder outspoken conservative radio rhetoric under scrutiny in recall election...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-08-10/larry-elder-views-newsom-recall-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Elder leapfrogs the others vying to replace Newsom, with provocative stances from firing teachers to downplaying the dangers of secondhand smoke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA new challenge to reaching moon: $1 billion spacesuit program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/nasa-has-a-new-challenge-to-reaching-the-moon-by-2024-its-241-billion-spacesuit-program/ar-AANbzgC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer prices rise 5.4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/11/cpi-report-july-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists surveyed by Dow Jones expected the Labor Department to report the consumer-price index rose 5.3% in July from a year earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Awards Secret $10 Billion Contract to AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2021/08/nsa-awards-secret-10-billion-contract-amazon/184390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the NSA’s most prized intelligence data may be moving to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANCHIN: IRRESPONSIBLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210811114919-j026v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/INFRASTRUCTURE-MANCHIN (URGENT):U.S. Democratic Senator Manchin objects to $3.5 trln spending bill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI Skysphere two cars in one...</title>
      <link>https://electrek.co/2021/08/10/audis-new-skysphere-concept-is-two-cars-in-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;electrek.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audi's new Skysphere concept may never make it to production, but it has some incredibly cool ideas we hope to see more of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heaven can wait, maybe, but not phone call for pope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-europe-religion-4ecf10f1cd7a4a2ba93bf0f5210a97ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Maybe heaven can wait, but a phone call for the pope could not. In a decidedly unusual break from protocol, Pope Francis took a cellphone from an aide while standing at center stage in a Vatican auditorium for his weekly Wednesday audience with the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul to become NY's first female governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-health-coronavirus-pandemic-cf6794c4cf5a82d6be7739009b8fe8fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — Kathy Hochul, a western New York Democrat unfamiliar to many people in the state even after six years as its lieutenant governor, was set to begin reintroducing herself to the public Wednesday as she prepared to take the reins of power after Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Vigorously for 4 Seconds. Repeat. Muscles May Thank You...</title>
      <link>https://lightlynews.com/2021/08/11/health/exercise-vigorously-for-four-seconds-repeat-your-muscles-may-thank-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lightlynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise Vigorously for four Seconds. Repeat. Your Muscles May Thank You. - LIGHTLYNEWS.COM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Women Muscle In on World of Vintage Cars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/11/more-women-muscle-in-on-the-world-of-vintage-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caroline Cassini, now 29, may have startled some neighbors in West Orange, N.J., when she announced that, rather than applying</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
