<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin denies 'concrete' plans for summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/kremlin-denies-putin-biden-summit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian president’s spokesman says no meeting is agreed — contradicting Elysée Palace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOSCOW KILL LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/21/us-says-russia-expected-to-invade-ukraine-very-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has compiled lists of Ukrainians to target after an invasion, a U.S. official has claimed, as Putin prepares to address his country's security council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting in Mexican Glamour Resort Tulum Leaves Two Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/shooting-in-mexican-glamour-resort-tulum-leaves-two-dead-1.1726275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were killed late Saturday in a shooting at a restaurant in the Mexican beach resort of Tulum as a wave of violence continued in the Riviera Maya region, the country’s top tourist destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron pleads for peace in two-hour phone call...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4733348/putins-private-parts-mocked-ukrainians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS Ukrainians mocked the size of Putin’s penis at demonstrations in Odessa yesterday. They shrugged off the threat of World War Three and an “imminent invasion” to poke fun at the president’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial killer says he was driven to kill by 'voice' he thought was God...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4732460/kill-murder-the-voice-god-yorkshire-ripper-peter-sutcliffe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUTCLIFFE always insisted that he killed because a voice in his head told him to. He was ­convinced it was from God. But what exactly was “the voice”? What did it sound like and what did it say? He…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politician punched on Ukrainian TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4727534/brawl-erupts-live-tv-politician-punched-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a mass brawl erupted during a live Ukrainian TV debate over Vladimir Putin. Dramatic footage shows Ukrainian journalist Yuriy Butusov punch pro-Russian politician Nestor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba support for Russia revives Cold War alliance...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-russia/cuba-to-deepen-ties-with-russia-as-ukraine-tensions-mount-idUSKBN2KO0J2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Cuba will deepen ties and explore collaboration in transportation, energy, industry and banking, Cuba's Foreign Ministry said late on Friday following a visit from Russia's Deputy Prime Minister Yuri Borisov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Putin agree to summit with France if Russia does not invade Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/us-intel-shows-russian-military-officials-order-proceed-invasion-ukrai-rcna17002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are always ready for diplomacy," White House spokeswoman says, adding that "currently, Russia appears to be continuing preparations for a full-scale assault on Ukraine."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New MAGA media to flag photos of guns?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/truth-social-developers-beta-app-pinochet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A beta version of Truth Social used by the development team at TMTG is publicly accessible online, allowing anyone to register an account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls grow for developers to spare 100-yr-old trees...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Calls-grow-for-developers-to-spare-100-yr-old-16933721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - There is both hope and dissent over the planned redevelopment of the Meiji Jingu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-60453566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She has mild symptoms and expects to continue "light duties" at Windsor, Buckingham Palace says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAT ROBERTSON:   Young people in America going to lead way of religious revival...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/RealAmVoice/status/1495114363648163843?s=20&amp;t=1ad1MdgQeC3wWjUsC6imJQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Turner Biographer Fears He is Suicidal...</title>
      <link>https://theankler.com/p/ted-turner-biographer-john-malonespeaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theankler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare Q&amp;A, the author, whose relationship with CNN's founder spans 48 years, describes his bond with CNN's most powerful critic and his opposition to 'what Zucker did with CNN'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes Revolt Against China's Big Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/02/olympics-closing-ceremony-review-china-ukraine-invasion-peacock-nbc-1234957371/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite all the high-tech tricks, political posturing and pyrotechnics, the best part of the Closing Ceremony of the 2022 Beijing Winter Olympics proved to be the athletes. Competing the past two w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group that brought down Keystone XL faces own agonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/20/350org-mckibben-boeve-keystone-00009866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the upstart that changed the face of America’s environmental movement. But 350.org, founded by the legendary Bill McKibben, has been laid low by a budget crunch, equity fights and union strife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing ceremony: Games marked by restrictions, boycotts, and doping scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/beijing-winter-olympics-draw-close-rcna16610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Games had the strictest Covid restrictions yet, and were overshadowed by a U.S.-led diplomatic boycott over China's human rights record and blindsided by a high-profile doping saga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserves easiest route to Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-cancels-plan-to-withdraw-troops-from-belarus-preserving-its-easiest-route-to-strike-ukraine-s-capital-kyiv/ar-AAU5PS8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard deploys for new emergency: Teacher shortages...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/20/new-twist-in-pandemics-impact-on-schools-substitutes-in-camouflage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESTANCIA, N.M. — The chorus of small voices ringing from a third-grade classroom on a recent morning signaled how far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next affordable city already too expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/The-Next-Affordable-City-Is-Already-Too-Expensive-16931227.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it was the date night when he and his wife spent two hours driving 19 miles to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowy money built steel empire -- with bank's help...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2022/02/20/Ihor-Kolomoisky-US-banks-warren-ohio-steel-plant-ukraine/stories/202202200063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months after Ukraine oligarch Ihor Kolomoisky and his partners abandoned an Ohio steel plant and left scores of workers without jobs, financial crime experts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madoff sister, husband dead in possible murder-suicide...</title>
      <link>https://bocanewsnow.com/2022/02/19/murder-suicide-bernie-madoffs-sister-dead-in-boynton-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bocanewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bodies Of Madoff Sister, Brother-In-Law, Found In Valencia Lakes. BY: ANDREW COLTON | Editor and Publisher BOYNTON BEACH, FL (BocaNewsNow.com) (Copyright © 2022 MetroDesk Media, LLC) [EXCLUSIVE] — The sister of disgraced financier Bernie Madoff was killed in a murder-suicide in Valencia Lakes, West of Boynton Beach. Her husband, Marvin Weiner, is also dead. The […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to arm resistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/19/west-plans-to-arm-resistance-if-russian-forces-occupy-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invasion ‘must be seen to fail’, says Boris Johnson, as western allies hold secret talks about how to give military backing to Kyiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abused' Prince Andrew 'sex slave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4724511/jean-luc-brunel-dead-jeffrey-epstein-prince-andrew-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s pal Jean-Luc Brunel who is alleged to have also abused Prince Andrew “sex slave” Virginia Giuffre has been found dead in prison. The disgraced fashion agent was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fortress Australia' re-opens after 2-year closure...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/fortress-australia-re-opens-after-two-year-covid-closure-01645362307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia opens its international borders to all vaccinated tourists Monday, nearly two years after the island nation first imposed some of the world's strictest Covid-19 travel restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine family 'fears for her safety'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/19/ghislaine-maxwells-family-fears-for-safety-after-jean-luc-brunel-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of Ghislaine Maxwell say they fear for her safety after model agent Jean-Luc Brunel was found hanged in his Paris prison cell on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky rips West for inaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/zelensky-rips-the-west-for-inaction-as-shelling-makes-russia-ukraine-war-seem-increasingly-imminent/ar-AAU4UGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia plans biggest war in Europe since 1945...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-60448162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson tells BBC that intelligence suggests Russia intends to launch an invasion encircling Kyiv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crises keep travel-hungry Biden close to White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/594971-crises-keep-travel-hungry-biden-close-to-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden wants to leave Washington more and promote his policies directly to the American people, but outside circumstances — such as the resurgence of the pandemic or the threat of war between Russia and Ukraine — keep pulling him back to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris: 'Real possibility of war in Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/video/ukraine-crisis-we-are-talking-about-the-real-possibility-of-war-in-europe-says-kamala-harris-12547076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Vice President Kamala Harris told reporters in Munich that "we are talking about the real possibility of war in Europe".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeii: Rebirth of Italy dead city that nearly died again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-technology-business-italy-europe-fd7499b179f254ad442c468fdc94394b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POMPEII, Italy (AP) — In a few horrible hours, Pompeii was turned from a vibrant city into an ash-embalmed wasteland, smothered by a furious volcanic eruption in A.D. 79. Then in this century, the excavated Roman city appeared alarmingly close to a second death, assailed by decades of neglect, mismanagement and scant systematic maintenance of the heavily visited ruins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron says final NBA season will be played with son...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/20/sport/lebron-james-cavaliers-lakers-bronny-nba-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebron James said there are no certainties over his future in the NBA, though he is certain about one thing -- he'd like to play his final season alongside his son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Infected in England won't need to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boris-johnson-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-pandemics-2a717a276b483431f30622f7fa7602cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — People with COVID-19 won't be legally required to self-isolate in England starting in the coming week, the U.K. government has announced, as part of a plan for “living with COVID” that is also likely to see testing for the coronavirus scaled back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE NUKE DRILLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-oversee-nuclear-drills-ukraine-crisis-mounts-2022-02-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's strategic nuclear forces held exercises overseen by President Vladimir Putin on Saturday, and Washington accused Russian troops massed near Ukraine's border of advancing and being "poised to strike".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minister dives for cover as frontline heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220219-ukraine-minister-dives-for-cover-as-frontline-heats-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bent in a semi-crouch Ukraine's interior minister ran back from an exposed frontline position, as mortar shells crashed in the fields around him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
