<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RED LIGHTS OFF:  Amsterdam officials to vote on plans for 'erotic center' away from city in bid to clean up sex-and-drugs reputation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9207675/Amsterdam-officials-reveal-plans-erotic-centre-away-city-centre.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the new plans she has put forward, Amsterdam Mayor Femke Halsema is hoping to turn the focus away from sex and drugs and make the inner city more livable for locals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGETS SILVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/31/silver-futures-jump-7percent-as-reddit-traders-try-their-squeeze-play-with-the-metal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Futures contracts tied to silver were surging higher on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAN. WAS WORST MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EtGd42qWMAA-NQE?format=jpg&amp;name=large</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIRES TWO DEFENSE LAWYERS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republican-party-future-balance-trump-175159539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former US president Donald Trump announced Sunday he had picked two lawyers to head his defense team days before his historic second impeachment trial, as Republicans braced for a battle over the future of their party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LOSES IMPEACHMENT TEAM</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Legal-team-exits-as-Trump-fixates-on-false-claims-15912903.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The implosion of former president Donald Trump's legal team comes as Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT seeks to fill void if GOOGLE exits Australia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/microsoft-seeks-fill-void-google-020046084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has a "Plan B available" if Google follows through on threats to leave Australia over plans to compel digital giants to pay news organisations for content, local media reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Protesters shut DODGERS Stadium vax site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-vax-mob-closed-dodger-235818591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protest left several city leaders infuriated, with some questioning why police didn't do more to move the demonstrators out of the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden hits harsh Washington reality in dash for post-Trump reset...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-hits-harsh-washington-reality-in-dash-for-post-trump-reset/ar-BB1dfX88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden’s presidency began at a choreographed sprint, with a series of executive actions to erase Donald Trump’s legacy and reset the nation’s course. But as his first full week in office came to a close, the new president was discovering the limits of his power. His administration’s efforts to bolster vaccine production ran into the same hurdles that plagued the Trump administration -- bottlenecks both at factories and in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden health adviser warns of variants, future lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/biden-health-adviser-warns-of-virus-variants-future-lockdowns/ar-BB1dgjTD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top health adviser to President Joe Biden warned Sunday that a new variant of the coronavirus circulating in the U.K. will likely become the dominant strain in the U.S. and may lead to future restrictions on in-person gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger takes on MAGA:  'We traffic in lies'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/traffic-lies-house-republican-launches-171530693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam Kinzinger, an Illinois Republican, is out to prove there is a GOP voter base that wants to give up the division and conspiracy theories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous new strains may incubate in sickest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dangerous-coronavirus-strains-may-incubate-192505798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 patients who take months to overcome their coronavirus infections despite treatment can become incubators of dangerous new strains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young men accuse LINCOLN PROJECT co-founder of harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-33a03c2280fff515a09c4d51365cb83d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The influential anti-Donald Trump group Lincoln Project is denouncing one of its co-founders after multiple reports that over several years he sexually harassed young men looking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Govt accused of deliberately allowing spread....</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13896814/brazilian-government-coronavirus-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Brazilian Government has been accused of deliberately allowing coronavirus to spread as the country’s death toll hit over 222,000. Authorities were “intentionally” trying to i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire trying to build new Garden of Eden!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-putin-friendly-billionaire-trying-to-build-the-garden-of-eden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire (and ex-Georgia prime minister) Bidzina Ivanishvili’s obsession with shipping exotic trees across oceans to build a “Garden of Eden” is explored in “Taming the Garden.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Drone footage shows huge crater on California US1...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2236456/shocking-footage-highway-one-california-washed-away-landslide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING drone footage shows a massive crater along California’s Highway One after a landslide washed part of the road away. The landslide sent a big chunk of the road in Monterey County, abo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands break rules for funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/brisk-yeshiva-head-rabbi-meshulam-dovid-soloveitchik-passes-away-at-99-657288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rabbi Meshulam Dovid Soloveitchik, one of the scion’s of the Soloveitchik dynasty and leaders of the Brisk yeshivas, passed away at the age of 99</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans to set their own moods using brain chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/hi-tech-brain-implants-size-23417127</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in South Korea have suppressed cocaine-induced behaviour in rats injected with the drug using the chips, even working out how to charge them remotely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIZZARD:  '21:  NYC 2 FEET OF SNOW? DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2021-01-30-winter-storm-orlena-forecast-northeast-midwest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major winter storm will dump heavy snow in the Northeast early this week. Here's the latest. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel extends lockdown, sees delay in covid turnaround...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210131211623-nidpj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Israel extends lockdown, sees delay in COVID-19 turnaround</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police put on massive show of force...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210131185849-hh9sf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV):UPDATE 8-Russia detains more than 5,000 at protests backing jailed Kremlin critic Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULTRA-ORTHODOX, ULTRA DEFIANT!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-benjamin-netanyahu-jerusalem-ed5afe4c752ed813017da93ee0b2a183</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Thousands of ultra-Orthodox Israelis thronged a pair of funerals for two prominent rabbis in Jerusalem on Sunday, flouting the country's ban on large public gatherings during the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOTLAND CONSIDERS FINANCIAL PROBE</title>
      <link>https://www.scotsman.com/news/politics/scottish-parliament-hold-vote-unexplained-wealth-order-donald-trumps-finances-3118810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scotsman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSPs will be asked to vote this week on whether the Scottish Government should pursue an Unexplained Wealth Order (UWO) to investigate the source of financing for Donald Trump’s Scottish resorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 LAWYERS LEAVE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-parts-ways-with-five-lawyers-handling-impeachment-defense/ar-BB1dfAJr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald J. Trump has abruptly parted ways with five lawyers handling his impeachment defense, just over a week before the Senate trial is set to begin, people familiar with the situation said on Saturday. Those departures include his lead lawyer, Butch Bowers, whose hiring was announced last week, a person familiar with the situation said. Four other lawyers who were reported to be joining, including Deborah Barbier, a criminal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems building elaborate, emotionally charged impeachment case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-democrats-building-elaborate-emotionally-charged-case-against-trump/ar-BB1ddVdf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House managers are scouring for new video evidence and police witnesses, even as the Senate tries to limit former president Donald Trump’s impeachment trial to a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shocked world with 16 split personalities  --  then admitted she'd made it all up!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/woman-shocked-world-16-split-23403123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shirley Mason, the subject of the 1973 book 'Sybil', sparked a global fascination when she claimed to have 16 distinct alter egos — but she once confessed it was all faked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LOSES IMPEACHMENT TEAM</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/30/politics/butch-bowers-deborah-barbier-trump-impeachment-team/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's five impeachment defense attorneys have left a little more than a week before his trial is set to begin, according to people familiar with the case, amid a disagreement over his legal strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joan Didion Has Nailed America's Weirdness for Half Century...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joan-didion-nailed-america-weirdness-100303225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neville Elder/Corbis via GettyIn The Center Will Not Hold, the 2017 Netflix documentary about Joan Didion’s life, New Yorker staff writer Hilton Als said of the author, “The weirdness of America somehow got into this person’s bones and came out on the other side of a typewriter.” A new collection of vintage pieces by Didion, Let Me Tell You What I Mean, further proves this alchemy to be true.Didion’s uncanny strength is to be both of-the-moment and beyond-the-moment. Her writing rests on “the idea that the truth is provisional, and the only thing backing it up is who you are at the time you wrote this or that, and that your joys and biases and prejudices are part of writing, too,” Als notes in the collection’s foreword. But she is equally “farsighted,” her timely inquiries identifying wider behavioral patterns that make her writing seem oracular.California Dreaming With Joan DidionThe 12 pieces, some published as early as 1968 and the latest in 2000, join her canon of novels, reportage, and screenplays. “As with any writer, it is always revealing and interesting to see the early work and state of mind,” Shelley Wanger, Didion’s editor since 1991, said in an email. Als, via email, concurred: “You want to understand and feel connected to her process of intellection. The new book lifts a curtain on those early years, when she was a different kind of writer—more directly opinionated.” Half the pieces here are from the same era as her landmark nonfiction collection Slouching Towards Bethlehem, also published in 1968—and in no way feel second-tier, so it’s unclear why they have re-materialized only now.The collection provides perspicacious glimpses: into the flawed framework of the press, into the spurious narratives at support group meetings, into larger-than-life personalities like Ernest Hemingway and Robert Mapplethorpe. These glimpses illuminate Didion’s ability to infuse breadth of observation, wit, and pathos within concise parameters. “I do not think in abstracts,” she noted in “Why I Write” (published in The New York Times Magazine in 1976). “My attention veered inexorably back to the specific, to the tangible.” Didion deploys specifics to get at social ambiguities, at the unspoken. She is attentive but skeptical—towards others, and towards herself. The latter skepticism is often expressed regarding the very exercise of writing: a self-audit folding into the choices of how to depict the examined subject. Incongruities and absurdities are inflected with “humor and a dry little sigh of exasperation,” as Als puts it in the foreword: bemusement mixing with disquiet.The contemporaneity of these writings often gives the reader moments of whiplash. In “Alicia and the Underground Press” (published in the Saturday Evening Post, 1968), Didion dismantles “conventional press postures” and laments “the inability of all of us to speak to one another in any direct way, the failure of American newspapers to ‘get through.’” Reading this in the present moment—while reckoning with post-Trump media accountability, as well as problematic racial and gender representation within the field of reporting—it’s discomfiting to see the limitations of the journalistic milieu remain so a century later. Moreover, Didion admonishes the media for alleging to dish out impartial truths: “I admire objectivity very much indeed, but I fail to see how it can be achieved if the reader does not understand the writer’s particular bias.” Yet Didion’s powerful voice led the way, in fact, to loosening that institutional journalistic tone. Illusory objectivity is not as grave a problem as it once was, and her style had a hand in spurring a more fallible—and therefore more trustworthy—tone and approach.Didion is an expert at outing a disingenuous narrative. In “A Trip to Xanadu” (published in 1968 in the Saturday Evening Post), she deems press magnate William Randolph Hearst’s California mansion “a sand castle, an implausibility.” Its symbolism—flashy surface with dubious underpinnings—could be applied to almost any of the American mythologies she deftly deconstructs. In “Pretty Nancy” (Saturday Evening Post, 1968) she surveys Nancy Reagan—then the wife of the governor of California—in her careful performance of normalcy. Didion, slyly inspecting her in the company of a TV newsman and two cameramen, comments on the “cinéma vérité study… watching and being watched.” It’s a Real Housewives-style voyeurism, replete with hard-to-grasp boundaries of what constitutes reality and what is expressly staged for an audience. In “Getting Serenity” (Saturday Evening Post, 1968), Didion examines the cultishness of betterment, a kind of pre-wellness narrative in which people strive to patch up the black hole of their addictions. She notes the oversight at the center of this effort: “mea culpa always turns out to be not entirely mea.” Moreover, "spiritual" leveling up is something she discredits the merit of altogether. Rather than aspiring to a more placid lifestyle, “serenity,” she notes, “is a word I associate with death.”Joan Didion’s 'Blue Nights' Just Released Christopher Dickey Writes About His Love for HerIn the Saturday Evening Post article “On Being Unchosen by the College of One’s Choice,” she dissects “that most conventional middle-class confrontation,” namely: “the child vs. the Admissions Committee.” Grateful to her father for shrugging when she didn't get into her first-choice college, she marvels at the pressures placed on “children whose lives from the age of two or three are a series of perilously programmed steps” for standardized success. Parents demand their child “make good not only for himself but for the greater glory of his father and mother… we are deluding ourselves if we pretend that desirable schools benefit the child alone.” (One need only gesture at Lori Loughlin or Felicity Huffman, who landed time in federal prison for meddling with college admissions, to confirm this predicament has gone truly haywire.)In the most recent piece from this collection, “everywoman.com" (published in The New Yorker, 2000), Didion parses the cultural weight of Martha Stewart, noting that she “presents herself not as an authority but as the friend who has ‘figured it out’; the enterprising if occasionally manic neighbor who will waste no opportunity to share an educational footnote.” Didion recognizes that, rather than some caricatured Betty Crocker, “the dreams and the fears into which Martha Stewart taps are not of ‘feminine’ domesticity but of female power.” It’s a premonition of the way conversations around gender and authority would come to be reframed—if incrementally, and grudgingly.Didion explores how her own authorial self-worth was forged in “Telling Stories” (published in New West, 1978). She recalls wrestling with imposter syndrome in a creative writing class: “I listened to other people’s stories read aloud and I despaired of ever knowing what they knew.” She experienced the paralyzing refrain lurking behind every creative person’s ambition: “a yearning to be good and a fright that I never would be… that any sentence I committed to paper would expose me as not good enough.” But the irony is, of course, that she articulates these fears in near perfect prose.Superstition and paranoia forestall most creative types from probing their methodology, alarmed that it might unravel or “ruin” it. (Anyone who has read an artist profile knows exactly what this maddeningly evasive hedging sounds like.) But Didion is not scared of atomizing what she does. That fearlessness is why she’s so magnetic to a reader. It’s not only that she’s astute. It’s that she is always more curious than cautious.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New clinical trials raise fears coronavirus learning how to resist vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/clinical-trials-raise-fears-coronavirus-040855671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers once believed t would take months or even years for the virus to develop resistance to vaccines. The speedy evolution is largely a result of the virus' unchecked spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT army trolls Wall Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2240915/gamestop-reddit-army-troll-wall-street-billionaires-banners-billboards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDITORS took over billboards across the US to show they won’t back down from their investments in GameStop after the stock saga. The GameStop phenomenon that hijacked US markets is still gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The other rebellion: Dozens of MI restaurants defy state order...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-other-rebellion-dozens-of-michigan-restaurants-defy-state-coronavirus-order/ar-BB1dePbw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, many of the state’s hospitals are operating at 90 to 100 percent capacity and struggling to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMESTOP co-founder's son active on WallStreetBets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/31/gamestop-craziness-hits-close-to-home-for-ben-kusin-co-founders-son.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Kusin, whose dad co-founded the predecessor to GameStop in the 1980s, is an avid follower of the WallStreetBets forum on Reddit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat-related deaths soar to new record in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-environment/2021/01/31/heat-killed-record-number-people-arizona-last-year/4294654001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heat-related deaths soared to a new record in Arizona. As climate pushes temperatures higher, experts call for an urgent response to save lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests now available in airport vending machines...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/31/oakland-airport-is-first-to-sell-covid-19-tests-from-vending-machines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The self-administered kits are available for about $150 at the contactless kiosks in each terminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How taxpayers spent $161 million keeping 9/11 mastermind alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/guantanamo-cost-prisoners-khalid-sheikh-mohammed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has spent over $161,500,000 housing the suspected mastermind of the 9/11 terror attacks – Khalid Sheikh Mohammed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny's wife among thousands arrested during protests in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/31/yulia-navalny-among-scores-arrested-during-protests-in-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yulia Navalny was detained during a huge rally in the capital, Moscow, at least the second time she has been detained during the mass protests in support of her 44-year-old husband who survived a p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI finds evidence of coordination at Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/be-ready-to-fight-fbi-probe-of-u-s-capitol-riot-finds-evidence-detailing-coordination-of-an-assault/ar-BB1deSl2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents are probing interactions between on-the-ground instigators and the leaders of national extremist groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan says Chinese fighters, U.S. aircraft both entered defense zone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210131124958-22pto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (PIX):Taiwan says Chinese fighters, U.S. aircraft both entered defence zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vast Web of Vengeance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/30/a-vast-web-of-vengeance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guy Babcock vividly remembers the chilly Saturday evening when he discovered the stain on his family. It was September 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence plans political group to move beyond...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/pence-plans-form-political-group-he-moves-beyond-time-trump-n1256259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president plans to settle back in Indiana, where he has been staying with family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron gambles by saying 'non' to lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210131-macron-gambles-by-saying-non-to-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron gambles by saying 'non' to lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Focus on Antifa Distracted From Far-Right Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-trump-s-focus-on-antifa-distracted-attention-from-the-far-right-threat/ar-BB1deJBk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Trump’s efforts to focus his administration on the antifa movement and leftist groups did not stop the Justice Department and the F.B.I. from pursuing cases of right-wing extremism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO teams visits Wuhan food market in search of virus clues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-virology-coronavirus-pandemic-wuhan-china-3550eea48910db04933e5c95353171bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WUHAN, China (AP) — A World Health Organization team looking into the origins of the coronavirus pandemic on Sunday visited the food market in the Chinese city of Wuhan that was linked to many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous private eye Jack Palladino gravely injured in robbery...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Famous-private-eye-Jack-Palladino-gravely-injured-15910909.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Jack Palladino, the private investigator who worked on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters shut DODGERS Stadium vax site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dodger-stadiums-covid-19-vaccination-233339650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The demonstrators included members of anti-vaccine and far-right groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law firm ordered to release records in New York probe...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/business-and-practice/ex-trump-law-firm-ordered-to-hand-over-records-in-asset-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A law firm that recently cut ties with Donald Trump’s real estate company was ordered to hand over records of communications to New York investigators looking into whether the former president’s business manipulated the value of assets for loans and tax breaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL blockbuster trade: LIONS-RAMS swap QBs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/30/nfl-trade-lions-ship-matthew-stafford-to-rams-for-jared-goff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is rare to see a two quarterback trade in the NFL, but it happened Saturday night. The Lions are dealing veteran signal caller Matthew Stafford to the Rams, and Detroit will get quarterback Jare…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry, arrests in Turkey over Mecca poster with LGBT flags...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-turkey-mecca-istanbul-arrests-faccf466f8bdd4c50bbc3a8fd96e6398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Two students have been arrested in Turkey on charges of inciting hatred and insulting religious values for a poster depicting Islam’s most sacred site with LGBT flags. Their...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
