<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FAKE SITES: Trump Consultant Trolling Dems With Biden Site That Isn't Biden's...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/29/us/politics/biden-trump-consultant-disinformation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed with bogus websites that mock leading candidates, a Trump campaign worker is exploiting tensions on the left with Russian-style disinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Kamala Shotguns Joe Sixpack...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/29/opinion/sunday/kamala-harris-joe-biden-debate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden should know, as the Irish say, that the past is never past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunters shipped 300k endangered animals around world in past decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/trophy-hunters-shipped-300k-endangered-17279128 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Shocking statistics reveal toll on African elephants, lions, leopards and other dying species — four years on from Cecil the lion's death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer robots declared 'existential human threat'; Fear of fatal uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/787029/killer-robots-human-threat-ai-tech-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts' Supreme Court defies easy political labels...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/222dd32b7609458f98a811cb00c44848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers at 'World's Largest Brothel' Divided Over Sex Robots...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/viral/201906291076099664-sex-machines-brothel-opinion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While some courtesans seemed to approve of the sex doll fetish, others argued that becoming “too comfortable” with an inanimate object might cause a person to distance themselves from “any possibility of a healthy sex life”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American caravan arrives in Canada for cheaper medicine...</title>
      <link>https://ca.reuters.com/article/topNews/idCAKCN1TU0T4-OCATP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A self-declared "caravan" of Americans bussed across the Canada-U.S. b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Caves to China Demands?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/at-osaka-g20-donald-trump-bows-to-xi-jinpings-huawei-demands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selling American chips to a company branded as a security risk was only one of the areas where Trump gave ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran set to exceed enriched uranium limit under nuke pact...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-nuclear-limit/iran-to-soon-exceed-enriched-uranium-limit-under-nuclear-pact-fars-news-agency-idUSKCN1TU0OU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will soon exceed an enriched uranium limit under its nuclear deal, after re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro dismisses Trudeau handshake...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/justin-trudeau-jair-bolsonaro-xi-jinping-g20-summit-handshake-watch-video-8980586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUROPE 'HIT WITH BLOWTORCH'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/heat-tops-45c-france-deadly-heatwave-roasts-europe-143732689.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe sweltered Saturday on the sixth day of a widespread, deadly heatwave that has fuelled record-breaking temperatures, huge blazes and pollution peaks. With France, Italy, Spain and some central European nations posting all-time high temperatures, officials pleaded with people to take precautions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILDFIRES AND POWER CUTS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190629105639-l0ib3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extreme heat is expected to ease on Saturday in southern France but highs are still forecast at close to 40 degrees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Maduro targeted as US turns screws on Venezuela leader's son...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/28/nicolas-maduro-son-venezuela-sanctions-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US has imposed sanctions on Nicolasito, 29, who claims to be an economist and a flautist and has faced claims of nepotism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heatwave cooks mussels in shells on California shore...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jun/28/california-mussels-cooked-heat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures lead to what appears to be largest local die-off in 15 years, raising fears for broader ecosystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near death experiences felt by one in 10 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/06/28/one-10-people-has-had-near-death-experience-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in 10 people has had a near death experience, in which they report strange phenomena such as out-of-body sensations, or distorted time, a new study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala raises $2 million in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/29/kamala-harris-biden-debate-1390512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris’ debate performance in Miami was considered the strongest of both nights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big music fest abruptly ended over fraud suspicion, security...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c482f4490a954669afe9907e27077bce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face-Reading AI Will Tell Police When Suspects Hiding Truth...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/face-reading-ai-tell-police-145927474.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- American psychologist Paul Ekman’s research on facial expressions spawned a whole new career of human lie detectors more than four decades ago. Artificial intelligence could soon take their jobs.While the U.S. has pioneered the use of automated technologies to reveal the hidden emotions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Start Building Wall Monday Crumbles in Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/federal-judge-blocks-trump-from-using-2-5b-in-military-funds-for-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California federal judge issued a ruling blocking Trump from using $2.5 billion in military funds to build a wall along the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman banned from WALMART for eating half a cake, refusing to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/06/29/walmart-ban-texas-woman-reportedly-banned-police-cake-theft/1604324001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six months after a Texas woman was banned by Wichita Falls police for drinking wine from a Pringles can, a second has been banned for taking the cake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hero 9/11 first responder with cancer dies; Testified to Congress with Jon Stewart...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/hero-9-11-first-responder-dies-53-congress-jon-stewart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 9/11 first responder has died two weeks after appearing on Capitol Hill with Jon Stewart, according to a report Saturday. He was 53.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabotage? Space clean-up drones could have military implications...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/space/space-junk-or-sabotage-space-cleanup-drones-could-have-military-implications/news-story/e2cbbb479ea620a64a43ddc0d860c30c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China calls them scavengers, Russia calls them inspectors and the US calls them threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summit still relevant?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190629-who-needs-g20-question-gets-louder-osaka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who needs the G20? Question gets louder in Osaka</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMZ diplomacy? Trump outreach to Kim for border rendezvous...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12c0389ada294c158ff1989bc7049cad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recreational Drug Use Surges Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/recreational-drug-surges-worldwide-un-130000996.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some 271 million people globally, or more than one in 20 of the population aged 15 to 64, used recreational drugs in 2017, according to newly released data from the United Nations World Drug Report. That’s a 30% increase from 2009.The use of cannabis, cocaine, amphetamines and prescription</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott by Whites of SAfrican Restaurant Reflects Growing Sense of Grievance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/29/world/africa/south-africa-spur-boycott.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Afrikaners are spurning a once-cherished restaurant chain to protest its banning of a white man. The boycott has drawn “an eye roll” among many black South Africans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrors of dog festival where animals are boiled ALIVE to make stew...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-horrors-yulin-dog-festival-17264832</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The defenceless dogs whimper and howl in terror before they are boiled and burned alive at the festival in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: U.S. Oil Output Tops 12 Million Barrels a Day for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-oil-output-tops-12-120000720.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. crude output soared to new heights in April, highlighting OPEC’s dilemma just days before the producer group meets amid growing geopolitical threats.A government report on Friday showed U.S. production grew 2.1% in April to 12.16 million barrels a day. Booming shale production from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING 737 Max Software Outsourced to $9-an-Hour Engineers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boeings-737-max-software-outsourced-204657048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It remains the mystery at the heart of Boeing Co.’s 737 Max crisis: how a company renowned for meticulous design made seemingly basic software mistakes leading to a pair of deadly crashes. Longtime Boeing engineers say the effort was complicated by a push to outsource work to lower-paid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Godzilla' Divorce Approaches With $38 Billion Bezos Breakup...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/38-billion-divorce-jeff-mackenzie-100000923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- One of the biggest wealth transfers in history is expected in coming days.With the flick of a judge’s pen, a $38 billion stake in Amazon.com Inc. will pass to MacKenzie Bezos as part of her separation from company founder Jeff Bezos.“This is the Godzilla of all divorces,” said Peter Walzer</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
