<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How will solar system end? Distant planet offers hints...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/space/will-solar-system-end-distant-planet-offers-hints-rcna3187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A darkened planet circling the feeble remnant of a burned-out star about 6,000 light-years from Earth shows what our own solar system will look like at the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipping Containers That Spent Weeks Aboard Ships Dumped In Neighborhoods...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/cargo-ship-bottleneck-port-la-long-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of the shipping containers that spent weeks onboard ships waiting to be unloaded are now being dumped in nearby neighborhoods once they're emptied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia proposes week-long workplace shutdown as deaths highest ever...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211019120350-znh2u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-CASES (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Russia proposes week-long workplace shutdown as COVID deaths hit new record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien world under Austria's doomed glaciers tells tale of collapse...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211019115519-aoft3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-CHANGE/GLACIER-ALPS (PIX):Alien world under Austria's doomed glaciers tells tale of their collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian space movie director says Mars could be next...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211019114517-21zw7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-EXPLORATION/RUSSIA-MOVIE (PIX, TV):Russian space movie director says moon or Mars could be next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samples from China mission show Moon 'active' more recently than thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211019-samples-from-china-mission-show-moon-active-more-recently-than-thought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samples from China mission show Moon 'active' more recently than thought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand cases hit record despite vax push...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211019-new-zealand-covid-cases-hit-record-despite-vaccination-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Covid cases hit record despite vaccination push</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five critically endangered monkeys shot dead in Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211019-five-critically-endangered-monkeys-shot-dead-in-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five critically endangered monkeys shot dead in Vietnam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSU football coach fired for refusing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/college-football/news/washington-state-coach-nick-rolovich-four-assistants-fired-for-cause-over-covid-19-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second-year Washington State coach sought a religious exemption to a state and university policy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli diver discovers ancient Crusader sword...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-lifestyle-middle-east-israel-8f0d1f2d3a209cf79af5fbaf48514176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — An Israeli scuba diver has salvaged an ancient sword off the country's Mediterranean coast that experts say dates back to the Crusaders. Israel's Antiquities Authority said Monday the man was on a weekend dive in northern Israel when he spotted a trove of ancient artifacts that included anchors, pottery and a meter-long (yard-long) sword.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dangerous time': Portland, Oregon, sees record homicides...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/portland-oregon-homicides-25699ecd9f885cc61f63774c2fed48ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — It was nearly last call on a Friday when  Jacob Eli Knight Vasquez went to get a drink across the street from the tavern where he worked in northwest Portland — an area with a thriving dining scene, where citygoers enjoy laid-back eateries, international cuisines and cozy cafés.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy crunch hits global recovery as winter approaches...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-business-russia-health-70b97e36da53f62eba588b44f2b394bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Power shortages are turning out streetlights and shutting down factories in China. The poor in Brazil are choosing between paying for food or electricity. German corn and wheat farmers can't find fertilizer, made using natural gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman finds AMAZON has thousands of recordings of her from home devices...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/woman-finds-amazon-thousands-recordings-25240984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TikTok star found that Amazon had huge folders full of audio clips of her voice, a full list of contacts from her phone, her location, and said she is 'not totally comfortable'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Faces Fiscal Problems Dwarfing Those From Covid, OECD Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/world-faces-fiscal-problems-dwarfing-those-from-covid-oecd-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Faces Fiscal Problems Much Worse Than Those From Covid, OECD Warns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho Republican power struggle underscores fissures in GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/577307-idaho-gops-power-struggle-underscores-fissures-in-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Idaho Republican gubernatorial primary between Gov. Brad Little and Lt. Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Sued Over Animal Abuse Videos, Accused of Not Enforcing Ban...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/19/youtube-sued-over-animal-abuse-videos-accused-of-not-enforcing-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The videos are disturbing. A giant python wraps its thick body around the neck of a puppy, which thrashes and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Orban Effect: Inside Conservative Romance With Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/19/the-orban-effect-inside-the-right-wing-romance-with-hungary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. For one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sirens: Loud, Ineffective and Risky, Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/19/sirens-loud-ineffective-and-risky-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The barking Dalmatians that once warned pedestrians to clear a path ahead of horse-drawn carriages with firefighting equipment have long</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli diver finds 900-year-old sword, said to be Crusader knight's weapon, on Mediterranean seabed...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Israeli-diver-finds-900-year-old-sword-said-to-16544539.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An amateur diver off the coast of Israel has discovered a sword that is likely to have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Japan's yakuza mob weakens, former gangsters struggle to find role outside crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/As-Japan-s-yakuza-mob-weakens-former-gangsters-16542936.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KITAKYUSHU, Japan - Noodle chef Takashi Nakamoto moves so deftly as he boils, strains and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Germany's far-right gained, even as it lost...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-germany-e2-80-99s-far-right-gained-even-as-it-lost/ar-AAPGq2g </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHISH fan falls to his death at San Fran concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/fan-falls-to-his-death-at-phish-concert-in-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Phish concert in San Francisco on Sunday turned tragic after a fan fell to his death, officials said. Two other concertgoers were seriously injured in a separate falling incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripped naked, beaten, forced to shout 'Viva Fidel!': Inside Cuba's crackdown on dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Stripped-naked-beaten-forced-to-shout-Viva-16544255.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Cubans took to the streets in July for the biggest challenge to the communist state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador president declares state of emergency over drug violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211019-ecuador-president-declares-state-of-emergency-over-drug-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador president declares state of emergency over drug violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires sub-launched ballistic missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/north-korea-ballistic-missile-submarine-test-launch-south-korea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If confirmed it wouldn't be the North's 1st test of a missile designed for launch from underwater, but experts say this may have been a newer generation weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK:  NEW WEB RULES AFTER POL STABBED TO DEATH?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/oct/18/pm-urged-to-enact-davids-law-against-social-media-abuse-after-amesss-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for crackdown on threats to public figures and an end to online anonymity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bongino threatens to quit radio over vaccination mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/conservative-pundit-dan-bongino-threatens-to-quit-radio-giant-over-vaccination-mandate/ar-AAPFVBl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to scale back Treasury's IRS bank reporting plan amid uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-to-scale-back-treasury-e2-80-99s-irs-bank-reporting-plan-amid-gop-uproar/ar-AAPFE2r?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration has faced an uproar over the plan from Republicans and industry groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Envisioned moving GOP 'close to the spirit of Lincoln'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Powell-envisioned-moving-the-GOP-close-to-the-16543762.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Powell had kept the political world guessing: Was he a Democrat or a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's new culture war: Did a pyramid light show 'decolonize' or rewrite history?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexicos-culture-war-did-pyramid-173036983.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monument removals and a replica of the Templo Mayor pyramid infuriated critics, but can Mexico's populist government spark an Indigenous cultural renaissance?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLIN POWELL DEAD FROM COVID*</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/18/politics/colin-powell-dies/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Powell, the first Black US secretary of state whose leadership in several Republican administrations helped shape American foreign policy in the last years of the 20th century and the early years of the 21st, has died from complications from Covid-19, his family said on Facebook. He was 84.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>*WAS FIGHTING CANCER, PARKINSON'S</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/18/powell-whose-immune-system-was-weakened-died-of-covid-19-despite-being-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin L. Powell, whose immune system was weakened by treatment for multiple myeloma, died of complications of Covid-19 despite being</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 90-Minute Naps Boost Motor Skills, Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/naps-motor-skills-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team finds that sleep can enhance a person's ability to learn challenging motor tasks since it helps the brain to process and focus on the new skill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cam Newton Gets Jab to Keep NFL Hopes Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/cam-newton-gets-vaccinated-to-keep-nfl-hopes-alive-and-blasts-critics-for-undue-judgement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free agent quarterback Cam Newton announced he is now vaccinated against Covid-19, in hopes of boosting his chances at getting another NFL opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes will consider fast track appeal of Texas abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/18/supreme-court-will-consider-fast-track-appeal-of-texas-abortion-law.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The petitioners last month had submitted the unusual request for the Supreme Court to take up the case before final judgment in lower courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Keep Students Home From School To Protest...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/parents-keep-students-home-protest-newsom-state-wide-vaccine-mandate-all-school-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media posts called for parents who disagree with the vaccine mandate for students to keep them home from school Monday, in a state-wide protest. There does not appear to be a formal group behind the protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA wants psychiatric exam for Kobe Bryant's widow...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/oct/18/vanessa-bryant-kobe-bryants-widow-psychiatric-exam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County is seeking to compel psychiatric evaluations for Kobe Bryant’s widow and others to determine if they truly suffered emotional distress after first responders took and shared graphic photos from the site of the 2020 helicopter crash that killed the basketball star, his teenage daughter and seven others, court documents say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don sues Jan 6 committee, National Archives...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/18/trump-sues-jan-6-committee-national-archives-516209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president’s lawyers filed the suit in D.C. district court on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Inside Enormous Cosmic Tunnel, New Research Proposes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93yex5/the-earth-is-inside-an-enormous-cosmic-tunnel-new-research-proposes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new model proposes a filament-like magnetic tunnel encompassing the entire solar system, explaining two mysterious features of the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New meth creating wave of severe mental illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/11/the-new-meth/620174/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Different chemically than it was a decade ago, the drug is creating a wave of severe mental illness and worsening America’s homelessness problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA lines could slow to crawl when mandate enforced...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/atlanta-airport-blog/tsa-works-to-increase-60-employee-vaccination-rate-ahead-of-mandate/JGZ5V736RVBJVCN6Q72WQTAY54/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSA is working to increase its employee vaccination rate ahead of a federal mandate deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC suspends most of METRO trains over safety issue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-transportation-f58865105824287ef4c4e1d646ce23d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Washington's regional Metro system abruptly pulled more than half its fleet of trains from service early Monday morning over a lingering problem with the wheels and axles that caused a dramatic derailing last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why White Nationalists Are Toasting the Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8g7w/hard-not-to-respect-that-why-white-nationalists-are-toasting-the-taliban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White supremacists and jihadists may despise each other, but their violent extremist movements have a surprising amount in common, with shared enemies, tactics and a similar worldview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor warns America ALREADY in recession that could be as bad as '08...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10103413/US-recession-bad-2008-paper-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Blanchflower (pictured) says that every slump since the 1980s has been foreshadowed by 10-point drops in consumer indices from the Conference Board and University of Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICAHN:  Market will certainly 'hit wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/18/carl-icahn-says-the-market-over-the-long-run-will-certainly-hit-the-wall-because-of-money-printing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime activist investor Carl Icahn said Monday that U.S. markets could see challenges over the long term in the face of easy money and rising inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz associate sentence postponed; Helping feds with investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-judge-is-postponing-matt-gaetz-associate-joel-greenberg-s-sentencing-since-he-s-helping-with-a-federal-investigation/ar-AAPFHiY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg's attorney and federal prosecutors both asked for his sentencing to be pushed back to March 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War role was stain -- and he regretted it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/iraq-war-role-was-a-stain-on-powell-s-record-one-he-openly-said-he-regretted/ar-AAPFCal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His military and national security bona fides boosted the Bush administration’s case for war in 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still unvaccinated in Ontario? Expect govt call...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/still-unvaccinated-in-ontario-expect-a-call-from-the-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Norway attack victims stabbed not shot with arrows, say police...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/18/norway-attack-victims-stabbed-not-shot-with-arrows-say-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacker was armed with bow and arrows but five people who died had in fact been stabbed, police confirm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY fans tearing each other apart: 'Start calling you Hitler'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/disneyland/article/Disneyland-has-toxic-online-fans-16532319.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The happiest place on Earth’ is bringing out the worst in people online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price of arthritis drug jumps to $10,000 -- 52x original price...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/indocin-suppository-drug-prices-assertio-zyla-egalet-3278e307-d900-475c-92c9-8e5ff828a7da.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indocin shows how Martin-Shkreli-type price increases never disappeared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC Reporter Smeared as Anti-Putin 'Special Ops' Temptress...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/american-journalist-smeared-special-ops-142908150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mikhail Svetlov/GettyRussian State media pundits and personalities are claiming that the experienced CNBC journalist, who interviewed President Putin last week, was part of an American “special operation” designed to sway and tantalize the Russian leader.Putin started the pile-on himself by implying that Hadley Gamble was too beautiful to understand his remarks during an on-stage interview at a Russian Energy Week panel in Moscow.His media minions have amplified the patronizing attitude in line</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pass protest continues at Italian port despite police water cannon, tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018172356-n6tl1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Health pass protest continues at Italian port despite police water cannon, tear gas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fasting, not calorie count, boosts lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211018-fasting-not-calorie-count-boosts-lifespan-in-mice-study-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fasting, not calorie count, boosts lifespan in mice: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top editor dismissed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018165021-x8wmn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AXEL SPRINGER-EDITOR/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Germany's Axel Springer dismisses top Bild editor after media reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,200 Chicago Cops Defying...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/chicago-police-union-fop-vaccine-reporting-mandate-mayor-lori-lightfoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Fraternal Order of Police has said the city's vaccine mandate is a change to employment policies that must be negotiated with the union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Aimed at Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-18/china-sets-sights-on-taiwan-with-new-hypersonic-missile-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The game-changing technology that reportedly caught the U.S. by surprise is not designed to spark a global arms race, Chinese insiders say, rather to retake what Beijing considers its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Delays Could Soon Leave Wine Glasses Empty...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/10/16/supply-chain-delays-could-soon-leave-wine-glasses-empty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supply chain delays could soon leave your wine glasses empty, but the problem isn't the grapes, it's the packaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale nude photos highlight disappearing Dead Sea...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/18/200-israelis-strip-naked-for-photo-shoot-near-the-dead-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One photo shoot stopped 200 Israelis dead in their tracks. Two-hundred Israeli volunteers stripped naked for a photo shoot designed to draw attention to the shrinking of the Dead Sea. The uninhibit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump website taken over by 'Muslim hacktivist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3880424/donald-trumps-website-hacked-turkish-muslim-hacktivist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s website was reportedly hacked by a Turkish and Muslim Hacktivist warning, “do not be like those who forgot Allah.” Hacker RootAyyildiz took credit for the hacking o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Virginia Gov. has had 'long covid' for a year...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/news/health/vp-nw-coronavirus-northam-long-covid-20211017-zcx4uy7ojvbltc5nv7mnmzo5e4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sense of smell or taste returns within six months for four out of five COVID-19 survivors who have lost these senses, according to an ongoing Virginia Commonwealth University study. But the 20% who don’t get better means millions could have permanent loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Anchor Deletes Tweet Claiming Death Raises Questions About Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-john-roberts-slammed-for-deleted-tweet-claiming-death-of-colin-powell-raises-new-concerns-about-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' John Roberts drew a great deal of public criticism for using Colin Powell's to call the long-term effectiveness of coronavirus vaccines into question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA rapper hits top of iTunes chart with anti-Biden track...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/anti-biden-lets-go-brandon-song-tops-itunes-hip-hop-chart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-President Biden rap song inspired by the viral “Let's go Brandon” trend is now sitting at the top of the iTunes hip-hop chart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer nears make-or-break moment to deliver on Dem agenda...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/schumer-democrats-dwindling-time-good-060000929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer faces staggering policy challenges -- President Joe Biden’s economic agenda, voting rights legislation and another risky debt limit fight -- constrained by GOP leader Mitch McConnell’s hardball tactics and Democratic disunity in the 50-50 Senate.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightW</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator calls for senility test for leaders in all branches of govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bill-cassidy-senility-test-biden-age-4044e32c-25b5-4cb7-bdd7-269c11a96645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"And I'm saying this as a doctor."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAGE AGAINST MACHINE' Rocker Goes Corporate With NYT Newsletter...</title>
      <link>https://mtracey.substack.com/tom-morello-fight-the-power-by-subscribing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mtracey.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blearily scanning the New York Times homepage yesterday morning as I sometimes reluctantly do, usually out of a faint sense of obligation, I was jolted into sudden hyper-alertness by the sight of an extraordinary revelation: turns out Tom Morello, the hard-charging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Workers Protest Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/dallas-southwest-protest-vaccine-manadate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former Southwest Airlines workers gathered to protest recent COVID-19 vaccination mandates on Monday, Oct. 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 105 days, COVID death toll in Florida counties went missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2581184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 105 days this summer, while COVID-19 deaths soared across the state, Floridians had no idea how many of their neighbors were dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: California driest year in century...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-records-driest-century-120035397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average accumulation of rain and snowfall across the state totaled only 11.87 inches during the 2021 water year, which ran Oct. 1, 2020, through Sept. 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Communist's American Surveillance State...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/10/china-america-surveillance-hikvision/620404/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With generous state support at home and low-cost sales abroad, Hikvision has become a world heavyweight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Bipartisan Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/a-genuine-american-hero-the-death-of-colin-powell-sets-off-massive-bipartisan-tribute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tributes are pouring in from members of Congress, journalists, and others following the death of Colin Powell.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
