<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Stalin Approval Among Russians Hits Record High 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2019/04/16/stalins-approval-rating-among-russians-hits-record-high-poll-a65245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Clinton adviser punched liberal journalist who asked Hillary tough questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/ny-times-enflames-hillary-bernie-feud-with-report-on-neera-tanden-once-punching-current-sanders-aide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shareholders fed up with 'dictator'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hiltzik/la-fi-hiltzik-mark-zuckerberg-facebook-20190416-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shareholder proposals at Facebook's annual meeting will call for Zuckerberg's voting majority to be eliminated. It won't happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected rapist arrested on 100 counts, spanned decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.kalb.com/content/news/RPSO-arrests-Pineville-man-for-100-counts-of-first-degree-rape-508508621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kalb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pineville man is under arrest for 100 counts of first-degree rape that began in the 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing couple rescued from crocodile-infested marsh, wrote 'HELP' in mud...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-04-16/help-written-in-the-mud-saves-missing-couple/11019220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young Kununurra couple survives a 26-hour ordeal after getting bogged on a fishing trip to the remote Keep River National Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan scavengers vie with vultures for Brazilian trash...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-venezuela-politics-brazil-landfill/venezuelan-scavengers-vie-with-vultures-for-brazilian-trash-idUKKCN1RS205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrounded by vultures perched on trees awaiting their turn, Venezuelan migrants...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-year-old MLB phenom has league in awe...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/columnist/bob-nightengale/2019/04/16/fernando-tatis-jr-san-diego-padres/3483672002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few believed that Fernando Tatis Jr. would be in the majors to begin the season, but the 20-year-old is looking like a five-tool player in his first few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLEEP MYTH:  Less than 5 hours OK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8873012/sleep-myths-busted-serious-health-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COMMON myths about sleep pose a serious threat to our health, according to a new study. Scientists say the idea you can get by on less than five hours of shut-eye or having a nightcap helps you nod…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Prominent' DJ charged in kidnap attempt of SF toddler...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/perth-dj-roski-kidnap-charges-sf-mission-13772059.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roscoe Bradley Holyoake, 34, was arrested on April 12 after police say he grabbed a 2-year-old boy from his mother's arms near Market and 17th streets. Bystanders said he ran half a block with the boy before Good Samaritans tracked him down. He was detained by the witnesses until police arrived on the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US retailers already closed 6,000 stores this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/16/business/store-closures-retail-bankruptcies/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America has too many stores. This year, US retailers have announced that 5,994 stores will close. That number already exceeds last year's total of 5,864 closure announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX crashes on earnings report...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/16/netflix-earnings-q1-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix reported its first quarter 2019 earnings after the bell as more media companies enter the streaming space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETWORK IN TALKS WITH MAYOR PETE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/439088-buttigieg-fox-news-in-talks-on-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg is in talks with Fox News about appearing in a town hall event on the network, a campaign spokesperson told The Hill on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man On Trip From NY Infected With Measles Spreads Virus To Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/04/16/rockland-county-measles-outbreak-next-steps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county is currently dealing with 186 confirmed measles cases. Meanwhile in New York City, the health department shut down a Brooklyn preschool after it allegedly refused to provide vaccination records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim outlook for future of Air Force pilot shortage...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/dod-personnel-notebook/2019/04/new-study-shows-grim-outlook-for-future-of-air-force-pilot-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Watched Town Hall Of Campaign Season...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/80676f95802541dea83feb2454031e1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sen. Bernie Sanders took heat from some Democrats for holding a town hall on Fox News Channel but there's one result hard to argue with: it was the most-watched candidate event in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many employers drop 'zero tolerance' drug tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/business/article229311214.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to allow lawsuits against firms doing business in Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cuba/trump-to-allow-u-s-lawsuits-against-foreign-firms-doing-business-in-cuba-official-idUSKCN1RS1VY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration will allow lawsuits in U.S. courts for the first time a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Journalists have no idea how 2020 will go...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/16/business/media/2020-campaign-journalism-advice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political journalists gathered in Chicago to discuss the mistakes of 2016 and how to avoid them the next time around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange wins EU journalism award...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/breaking-news/julian-assange-wins-eu-journalism-award/news-story/f1bea94a9b040db4f7caa08897f7f6c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange has been given an award established in honour of an assassinated journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Roy Moore leads AL Republican field...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/poll-roy-moore-leads-republican-field-challenge-doug-jones-n995021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey suggests the former Alabama Supreme Court chief justice is currently favored by his state's GOP voters for a rematch against the Democratic senator in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to Rebuild in 5 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/europe/french-president-macron-vows-rebuild-notre-dame-cathedral-within-five-n995106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will make the Cathedral of Notre Dame even more beautiful. We can do this," the French president said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Namaste, Oil Drillers: Yoga Mats Debut at Industry Meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-16/namaste-oil-drillers-yoga-mats-debut-at-texas-industry-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior's weakness for scams may be warning sign of dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/health-med-fit-science/senior-weakness-for-scams-may-warning-sign-dementia/8ja63oxrn3eFIks46eOh6I/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does an older friend or relative have a hard time hanging up on telemarketers? Or get excited about a "You've won a prize" voicemail? New research suggests seniors who aren't on guard against scams also might be at risk for eventually developing Alzheimer's disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Viewers for Candidate Town Hall This Year...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/farhip/status/1118215315631087619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Inbox: @foxnews town hall with @BernieSanders last night attracted 2.55 million viewers, most for a candidate town hall this year (previous high: @KamalaHarris town hall on @CNN, 1.95 million). Sanders all the more impressive since his aired 6:30-7:30 pm, others during primetime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslims convert to Christianity in town once besieged by ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-syria-islamic-state-christians/christianity-grows-in-syrian-town-once-besieged-by-islamic-state-idUSKCN1RS19N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A community of Syrians who converted to Christianity from Islam is growing in Ko...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet awash in conspiracies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/16/tech/conspiracy-theories-notre-dame-cathedral-fire/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before the blaze at Notre Dame was extinguished, conspiracy theories and fake news about the fire had ricocheted around the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA reveals origin of Stonehenge builders...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47938188</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancestors of the people who built Stonehenge travelled west across the Mediterranean to get to Britain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran labels US troops in Mideast as terrorist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8db0cc234b7d44119d9133eec4dfb02a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's lawmakers on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a bill labeling U.S. forces in the Middle East as terrorist, a day after the U.S. terrorism designation for Iran's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRACLE: MOST INTERIOR INTACT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0978e08a5e4848348cdb80745ab2ab8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on the fire that swept through Paris' Notre Dame cathedral (all times local): 7:15 p.m. The White House says the bells of Notre Dame cathedral "will sound...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYOR PETE:  Capitalism has let a lot of people down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/16/politics/pete-buttigieg-2020-socialism-capitalism-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 Democratic hopeful Pete Buttigieg affirmed his belief in capitalism on Tuesday but suggested that the US economic system has let a lot of Americans down and called for greater "fairness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE reverses decision to deport husband of US soldier after her death in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/immigration/2019/04/15/ice-deports-gonzalez-spouse-u-s-soldier-killed-afghanistan/3477332002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE has deported the spouse of a U.S. soldier killed in Afghanistan, leaving the couple's 12-year-old daughter in the United States without parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETWORK IN TALKS WITH MAYOR PETE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/439088-buttigieg-fox-news-in-talks-on-town-hall  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg is in talks with Fox News about appearing in a town hall event on the network, a campaign spokesperson told The Hill on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlook cloudy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-manufacturing-output-unchanged-march-131859320--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAINED-GLASS WINDOWS SURVIVE...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190416141738-746ml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/PATRIMONY (PIX, TV):Notre-Dame's famed rose window spared but blaze harms priceless artworks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality TV comes of age with its own fan convention...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190416134634-2tdbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TELEVISION-MTV/REALITY (PIX):Reality TV comes of age with its own fan convention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No sign of arson...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190416123058-ee2q1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-No sign of arson in Notre-Dame blaze as nation grieves for symbol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar cleric films shocking guide on how Muslim men should beat their wives...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8876237/world-cup-cleric-qatar-guide-muslim-men-beat-wives/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LEADING academic and cleric from World Cup host country Qatar has filmed a shocking guide on how Muslim men should beat their wives. The vile video features Abd Al-Aziz Al-Khazraj demonstrating h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left's frustration with Pelosi rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Liberals-frustration-with-Pelosi-rises-over-her-13769941.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far left's frustration with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is on the rise, as liberal advocates and lawmakers fume that she hasn't done enough to defend freshman Rep. Ilhan Omar of Minnesota from attacks by President Donald Trump and other Republicans and has undermined their policies and leaders, including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez of New York.  Omar's allies over the weekend were upset by what they viewed as Pelosi's delayed response in standing up for one of the two Muslim women in Congress after Trump accused Omar of playing down the tragedy of the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks. Pelosi, whose initial statement criticizing Trump made no mention of Omar, said Monday that it was "beneath the dignity of the Oval Office" for Trump to have shared a video on Twitter of Omar spliced with footage of the burning twin towers.  But liberals seethed that Pelosi (California) and Democratic leaders did too little, too late. They were equally baffled by Pelosi's quip seeming to dismiss Ocasio-Cortez during a CBS "60 Minutes" interview Sunday, suggesting her "wing" of the party included "like five people."  "What we're seeing here is old-guard leadership trying to marginalize some of the big change agents who were elected in 2018 because they're afraid of what it means to their leadership in the future," said Charles Chamberlain, chair of the liberal group Democracy for America.  Using Pelosi's oft-repeated phrase - "Diversity is our strength and unity is our power" - Chamberlain said that when the speaker "tries to marginalize some of the newest leaders who are fighting hard . . . it's not a good look and it's not a smart strategy."  The tensions underscore Democrats' struggle to discern the best way to respond to Trump and the GOP's attacks on their far-left flank, criticism frequently centered on women of color. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FURY AT FOXNEWS FOR HOSTING BERNIE!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-opens-fire-on-fox-news-for-crazy-bernie-town-hall-bret-baier-was-so-smiley-and-nice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRE BREAKS OUT NEAR MOSQUE ON TEMPLE MOUNT...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/OMG/Fire-breaks-out-near-mosque-on-Temple-Mount-586985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marwani Prayer Hall, also known as Solomon's Stables, is located at the base of the corner of the Temple Mount where the Southern and Eastern walls meet, near the stairs up to the Al Aqsa Mosque.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing flat in March, capping weak Q1...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190416-us-manufacturing-flat-march-capping-weak-q1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US manufacturing flat in March, capping weak Q1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERO PRIEST RESCUED RELICS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6927345/Fire-chaplain-helped-Bataclan-victims-entered-burning-Notre-Dame-save-Crown-Thorns-relic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jean-Marc Fournier, chaplain of the Paris Fire Brigade, saved the Blessed Sacrament and the Crown of Thorns from the blazing Notre Dame cathedral on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50,219,667 Tax Filers Paid $0 or Less!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/irs-50219667-tax-return-filers-paid-0-or-less-income-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Zach Gibson)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: It's his nominatoin to lose...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/835216/bernies-clear-lane-democratic-nomination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the moderates stay fractured, it's his nomination to lose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MORNING AFTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abf11681d6164918982e5cbca0957548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Firefighters declared success Tuesday in a more than 12-hour battle to extinguish an inferno engulfing Paris' iconic Notre Dame cathedral that claimed its spire and roof, but spared...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Dog rescued while swimming 135 miles off Thailand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a4e0bf519d094444b11146afdebcd202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — A dog found swimming more than 220 kilometers (135 miles) from shore by workers on an oil rig crew in the Gulf of Thailand has been returned safely to land. A worker on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48 HOURS:  Redacted Mueller report coming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/25c40e71762048e3ba49acb8eb342a5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The president isn't waiting. As Washington counts down the final hours until publication of the redacted special counsel report — now expected Thursday — Donald Trump stepped up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redaction nation: US history brims with partial deletions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c3d1b8d106f41c6bf2e15e49ee1dc4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Somewhere in the shadows of federal bureaucracy, there was an issue about the drinking habits of Augusto Pinochet. The National Security Archive, an advocate for open...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman trashes burger joint over lack of chocolate ice cream...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/food-assault/ice-cream-rage-702834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incensed that a St. Louis hamburger joint had run out of chocolate ice cream, a female suspect went on a 2:25 AM rampage, breaking out the restaurant’s windows with a baseball bat and spitting on em</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandals. Backstabbing. Resignations. Record profits. Time Bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-15-months-of-fresh-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scandals. Backstabbing. Resignations. Record profits. Time Bombs. In early 2018, Mark Zuckerberg set out to fix Facebook. Here's how that turned out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS LAUNCH CRIMINAL PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8872572/notre-dame-cathedral-fire-criminal-probe-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETECTIVES have begun interviewing specialist restorers linked to the Notre Dame Cathedral fire as demands grow for the ‘idiot’ responsible to face justice. As the flames were finally extinguished …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nashville booming; No longer simply country music capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/apr/16/bachelorettes-bibles-and-amazon-nashvilles-boom-brings-growing-pains</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No longer simply the country music capital of the world, the city is expanding rapidly – but its unique culture is feeling the strain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Was Raised 23 Mins Before Blaze Detected...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/paris-notre-dame-fire-extinguished-revealing-massive-damage-to-the-800-year-old-landmark-situation-still-precarious</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive fire that destroyed much of Paris’s famed Notre Dame cathedral Monday night left destruction and hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stop Sanders' Dems Agonizing Over Momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/stop-sanders-democrats-are-agonizing-over-his-momentum/ar-BBVZ7Hq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAINED-GLASS WINDOWS SURVIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6926807/Devastating-aftermath-Notre-Dame-inferno-leaves-world-mourning.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A catastrophic fire at Paris's Notre Dame Cathedral has left a nation mourning the devastation of its cultural 'epicentre' as French President Emmanuel Macron vowed to rebuild the landmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/16/new-pictures-inside-notre-dame-show-charred-remains-offer-hope-9220616/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the rose windows appears to be unharmed, but the roof is almost completely gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House officials fear being exposed as sources...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/white-house-officials-concerned-about-being-exposed-mueller-report-n994861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the dozen-plus officials interviewed by Mueller are concerned about president's "wrath" if they are seen as a source of damaging information in Thursday's report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Presides Over Rare Unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/macron-presides-over-rare-unity-as-nation-grieves-notre-dame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron Presides Over Rare Unity as Nation Grieves Notre Dame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got a minute? Global attention span narrowing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/apr/16/got-a-minute-global-attention-span-is-narrowing-study-reveals </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research combed from everything from movie tickets to social media finds more to focus on but less time to do so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg leveraged user data to fight rivals and help friends, leaked docs show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/social-media/mark-zuckerberg-leveraged-facebook-user-data-fight-rivals-help-friends-n994706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s leaders seriously discussed selling access to user data — and privacy was an afterthought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGE, DESIGN FOILED FIREFIGHTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e7c110edc8a34707ac0f0fa451c1388c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Is there anything firefighters could have done to control the blaze that tore through Paris' historic Notre Dame Cathedral sooner? Experts say the combination of a structure...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossilized Bacteria in Meteorite From Mars is 'Proof of Life'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201904161074178206-mars-study-meteorite-fossilized-bacteria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Similar claims have been made before, with NASA announcing in 1996 that it had found signs of life on Mars in another space rock, known as ALH 84001, also citing the appearance of the strands and filaments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could take DECADES to rebuild...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/years-decades-uncertainty-over-time-needed-rebuild-notre-111811083.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebuilding the Notre-Dame cathedral in Paris could take decades after it was gutted by a fire, experts warned Monday, even as its most senior cleric expressed hope he could celebrate mass there within years. Parisians and people around the world watched in horror on Monday evening as a huge fire ripped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man's Future in Question Amid Fight with Feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/burning-mans-future-in-question-amid-fight-with-feds-11555407000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the main principles of Burning Man is “radical inclusion,” but organizers of the festival are taking radical exception to government proposals they say would kill its countercultural spirit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering golden eagle found poisoned in Yellowstone...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/apr/16/pioneering-golden-eagle-found-poisoned-in-yellowstone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As bird is found with large amounts of lead in its body, a biologist asks ‘Is Yellowstone as protected as we once thought?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror group celebrates 'punishment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6927101/Have-nice-day-ISIS-fanatics-revel-Notre-Dames-destruction-describing-punishment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Islamic State propaganda wing has uploaded a chilling poster of the Notre Dame Cathedral inferno accompanied by a heartless message bidding 'au revoir' to the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercenaries, Spies, Double Agents Gather in Bogota; Plot Control of Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/mercenaries-spies-and-double-agents-gather-en-masse-in-bogot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercenaries, Spies, and Double Agents Gather En Masse in BogotÃ¡</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON 'flooded by fake five-star reviews'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-flooded-fake-five-star-reviews-073822576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Which? investigation reveals the tech products with the most 'fake' reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pledges pour in to help rebuild...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pledges-pour-help-rebuild-notre-dame-fire-070941279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires and private donors pledged hundreds of millions of euros on Tuesday to help rebuild Notre-Dame cathedral in Paris which has been devastated by fire. President Emmanuel Macron has vowed the emblematic monument will be rebuilt after its spire and roof collapsed Monday night in a blaze thought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Cotulla, Texas, life rises and falls with price of oil...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cotulla-texas-life-rises-falls-price-oil-014536578.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cotulla (United States) (AFP) - Small town Cotulla, a self-proclaimed "hotel capital" in Texas oil country, is riding high on the recent recovery in crude prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE:  FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O8yyiEfHIRA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch FRANCE 24 live in English on YouTube for free Subscribe to France 24 now https://f24.my/YouTubeEN Watch France 24 live news: all the latest news live b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROWN OF THORNS DRAMA</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8871835/notre-dame-fire-jesus-christs-crown-of-thorns-likely-destroyed-treasures-rose-window/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s most priceless relics – Jesus Christ’s Crown of Thorns – has been miraculously saved from the Notre Dame inferno. But as the fire rages at the great cathedral in Pari…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK 2016:  ISIS behind failed Notre Dame attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/sep/09/cell-of-french-women-radicalised-by-isis-behind-failed-notre-dame-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say another operation was planned by group, one of whom had been engaged to two men who carried out deadly attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:   Car filled with seven propane tanks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/an-isis-plot-to-blow-up-notre-dame-cathedraland-rule-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elderly, taxi drivers, flower sellers—all are fair game in the ISIS rule book: You obey them, or you’re dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided new Congress is getting little accomplished...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/us-politics/la-na-pol-congress-divided-house-senate-passing-few-laws-20190415-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress has passed just 12 new laws since January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUL OF PARIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-notredame-fire/fire-devastates-notre-dame-beloved-architectural-gem-at-heart-of-paris-idUSKCN1RR1UO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive fire consumed Notre-Dame Cathedral on Monday, gutting and destroying t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan president says island not intimidated by Chinese military drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-taiwan/taiwan-president-says-island-not-intimidated-by-chinese-military-drills-idUSKCN1RS03B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen said on Tuesday the self-ruled island is not intim...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Subpoena Banks as They Probe Trump Finances...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/15/democrats-subpoena-deutsche-bank-1277199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers also subpoenaed other banks — including JPMorgan Chase, Bank of America and Citigroup — seeking information on Russian money laundering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tears and shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/paris-is-disfigured-tears-and-shock-as-notre-dame-burns/ar-BBVY3mG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inglewood's stadium deal threatening one of California's last black enclaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/inglewoods-stadium-deal-is-threatening-one-of-californias-last-black-enclaves/ar-BBVX02i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungry Alligators Invading FL Streets, Homes, Pools...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hungry-alligators-are-invading-streets-homes-and-pools-in-florida/ar-BBVWQlu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATHEDRAL SAVED FROM TOTAL DESTRUCTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190415-liveblog-fire-paris-france-notre-dame-cathedral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters battled a massive blaze at the French capital's iconic Notre-Dame Cathedral on Monday that caused the collapse of the medieval church's spire, though officials said the main structure of the building had been saved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New sport first ever created by Artificial Intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/04/15/ai-sport-speedgate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neural network tech has developed a brand new sport, Speedgate, by studying existing sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOD SAVE NOTRE DAME</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6925015/Fire-breaks-historic-Notre-Dame-cathedral-Paris.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An official in the French interior ministry said saving the building 'is not certain' after the spire and part of the roof collapsed on Monday - adding that it may not be possible to stop the blaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials save 86 cats living in house, charge owner with cruelty...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/news/mount-clemens-woman-found-living-with-86-cats-1-dog-charged-with-animal-cruelty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickondetroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Mar. 28, Macomb County deputies were asked to assist Macomb County Animal Control at a home on Roseview Boulevard in Mount Clemens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican William Weld launches primary challenge against president...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2019/04/15/weld/f2AiETr0E6dcDB8Izk7nUI/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Weld, the former GOP governor of Massachusetts, formally announced his candidacy for president on Monday, becoming the first Republican to launch an official primary challenge to President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLY WEEK HORROR...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47941794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major operation continues overnight at Paris' iconic Gothic building after the spire and roof collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  AFP...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/macron-vows-rebuild-notre-dame-after-devastating-fire-doc-1fo2eb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS audience cheers after host asks if they'd support 'Medicare for all'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/439027-sanders-townhall-audience-cheers-after-fox-news-host-asks-if-theyd-support</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The audience at a Fox News town hall erupted in cheers and applause when asked by moderator Bret Baier if they would support Sen. Bernie Sanders's (I-Vt.) "Medicare for All" proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROSS REMAINS IN THE RUINS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/15/photos-show-center-of-notre-dame-cathedral-miraculously-intact/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos from inside Notre Dame show the central part of the historic Gothic cathedral still intact. Rows of wooden pews and much of the nave appears to have been saved, according to the images. &amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NINE CENTURIES OF HISTORY BROUGHT CRASHING DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/fire-breaks-out-at-notre-dame-cathedral-11694910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron declares a national emergency as authorities rule out arson or terror-related motives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATASTROPHIC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7538fdb8fc8b476b8c442f0c2ac52115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A massive fire engulfed the upper reaches of Paris' soaring Notre Dame Cathedral as it was undergoing renovations Monday, threatening one of the greatest architectural treasures of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 31, Tim Tebow is one final step from MLB...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/At-31-with-the-NFL-behind-him-Tim-Tebow-is-one-13769494.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRACUSE, N.Y. - Tim Tebow was 18 years old, in green shorts and a gray T-shirt, walking from left field toward home plate for an offseason chat. He'd come to meet with his high school baseball coach, Greg Mullins, after school. Something's wrong, Mullins thought as Tebow approached. "Can we talk?" Tebow asked, and they moved to the dugout bench.  It was 2005, and Tebow, not yet a celebrity, had plotted out his future. His voice wavered. A few minutes into the conversation, Tebow shed a tear. He wouldn't play his senior season of baseball. He had decided to enroll early at Florida to pursue a football career.  "One of the hardest decisions I ever made was choosing to go football over baseball," Tebow said this month of that day at Nease High School in Florida, just south of Jacksonville. "It's an itch I've always had and a passion I've always had, and it didn't go away after years."  It's been 13 and a half years since the day Tebow's baseball career ended. Well, could have ended. Now, just weeks into year three of a rise through the minors, Tebow is one step from the major leagues. One step from his ultimate dream, which he set out for after his professional football career ended. While his foundation was growing and he was working as an ESPN college football analyst, he considered how the rest of his life would go. Maybe he'd give his "first love" another try. Maybe he'd try to play in the majors.  As his baseball odyssey extends into this spring, the question is how he'll handle the pitching for the Class AAA Syracuse Mets. The task at hand: cut down on strikeouts, hit for power, track down fly balls in the outfield. In Class AA, he struck out in more than 30 percent of his at-bats, but he hit a respectable .273. Through nine games this season, he's 5 for 31 with 13 strikeouts.  At 31, he is now being recognized for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Orbital billboards' to project enormous ads into night sky...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/pepsi-orbital-billboard-night-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"An hour and a half after the launch we concluded that the test was successful."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumps 10 years of tax returns, details millionaire status...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-sanders/bernie-sanders-releases-10-years-of-tax-returns-details-millionaire-status-idUSKCN1RR2CJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Democratic presidential contender Bernie Sanders released 10 years of tax r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where do nightmares come from? Scientists may have answer...</title>
      <link>https://www.earth.com/news/angry-dreams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.earth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from the Society for Neuroscience has pinpointed a pattern of brain activity associated with anger during dreams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorologist says received death threats for interrupting MASTERS with tornado watch updates...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/radiotvtalk/death-threats-cbs46-ella-dorsey-for-tornado-watch-interruptions-during-masters/2gCWn45fe5FP9cT52OSiYI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Originally posted Sunday, April 14, 2019 by RODNEY HO/rho@ajc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne plastic particles blanket remote mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/airborne-plastic-particles-blanket-remote-mountains-study-doc-1fo0gp1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
