<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Daily Power Walk Wards Off Alzheimer's, Slows Mental Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/physical-activity-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have found that physical activity dampens inflammation in the brain, protecting against mental decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruel or cute? Monkey jockey show at Florida county fair sparks outcry from animal activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/cruel-or-cute-monkey-jockey-show-at-florida-county-fair-sparks-outcry-from-animal-activists/article_fe49534a-4474-57c2-82b7-1f862d6525d5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARGATE, Fla. —These jockeys weigh only 6 pounds and they’re not riding horses — they’re riding dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany mulls full lockdown, shot mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/582954-germany-mulls-full-lockdown-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German officials are mulling the possibility of enacting stricter coronavirus restrictions across the country amid a surge in daily infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans moving less than ever...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/582904-americans-moving-less-than-ever-before</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer Americans are moving to new homes than at any time since the government began keeping track, as demographic trends collide with a hot housing market in which prices are rising over lack of supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Public Being Primed for War...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/will-putin-invade-ukraine-russians-are-being-told-to-get-used-to-the-idea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin’s propaganda campaign at home is getting people ready for a ‘reluctant’ move into Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Pandemic Star Loses Some Luster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/11/vermont-covid-19-coronavirus-surge/620792/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont’s COVID-19 surge could point the way toward an uncertain endemic future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON: 82-Year-Old Motorist Surrounded, Assaulted By Gang Of 40 Dirt Bike Riders...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/24/brookline-man-attacked-dirt-bike-atvs-boston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 82-year-old man was surrounded and assaulted by a group of people riding dirt bikes and ATVs in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz frontrunner in PA Senate race?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/dr-oz-equipped-to-fill-void-in-pennsylvania-senate-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity surgeon Mehmet Oz is poised to shake up the Pennsylvania Senate race, bolstered by a vast personal fortune to invest in a 2022 campaign and enviable poll numbers that suggest the Republican would be an immediate front-runner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rittenhouse Meets With Trump at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rittenhouse-mar-a-lago-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president revealed the meeting himself during an interview with Fox News' Sean Hannity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden heir? Buttigieg presidential buzz has penetrated White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/24/pete-buttigieg-presidential-buzz-white-house-523281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 39, he is the most recognizable and powerful transportation secretary in modern memory. And he wants you to believe his eye isn’t on the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for ET looks at nearest galactic neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/search-extraterrestrial-life-going-look-nearest-galactic-neighbor-rcna6313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are starting to look for life in our galactic backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havana Syndrome Hits FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fbi-acknowledges-agents-may-havana-syndrome-symptoms-rcna6504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an internal email, the FBI told a former agent reporting symptoms of Havana syndrome that there were "no medical programs in place" to help him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to keep borders closed another five months...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/582938-new-zealand-planning-to-keep-borders-closed-for-another-five-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's borders will remain closed to most international travelers over the next five months as the country takes precautions to fight the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy to restrict access of unjabbed to indoor venues...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211124132922-751o9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-CURBS (PIX):Italy to restrict access of unvaccinated to indoor venues - sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petrolhead, novelist, trampolinist for post-Merkel cabinet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211124-petrolhead-novelist-trampolinist-for-post-merkel-cabinet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olaf Scholz, who is on the brink of succeeding Angela Merkel after 16 years as German chancellor, has assembled a team of strange bedfellows to share power at the helm of his centre-left government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving challenges airlines as travel nears pre-pandemic levels... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-travel-business-lifestyle-993ff944573478e1290d0b96dda536d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Determined to reclaim Thanksgiving traditions that were put on pause last year by the pandemic, millions of Americans will be loading up their cars or piling onto planes to gather again with friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany faces grim milestone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-germany-western-europe-national-elections-a2162d75c29a865353e4e079c378f080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESCHWEILER, Germany (AP) — Germany is poised to pass the mark of 100,000 deaths from COVID-19 this week, a somber milestone that several of its neighbors crossed months ago but which Western Europe's most populous nation had hoped to avoid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Jury in Arbery death 2nd day of deliberations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-georgia-brunswick-f2549024973cdcc757c02bd0a07bf5cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — Jury deliberations were scheduled to resume for a second day Wednesday in the trial of three white men charged with chasing and killing Ahmaud Arbery after the 25-year-old Black man was spotted running in their coastal Georgia neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Top Movie Ever Is War Epic About American Defeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/china-s-top-movie-ever-is-war-epic-about-u-s-defeat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Top Movie Ever is War Epic About U.S. Defeat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Executes Man Arrested For Murder At Age 17...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/iran-executes-man-arrested-for-murder-at-age-17-judiciary-01637739906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran executed a man Wednesday who was arrested for murder at the age of 17, the judiciary said, despite appeals to spare his life by rights groups including Amnesty International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations set record again in Minnesota...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/covid-19-hospitalizations-set-2021-record-once-again-in-minnesota/600120021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Tim Walz outlined steps the state is taking to protect hospital capacity amid the latest pandemic surge that has the state facing a critical time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Burner Phones' Used to Communicate with White House?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/jan-6-rally-organizers-trump-white-house-1262122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key planner of the Jan. 6 rally near the White House insisted the burner phones be purchased with cash, a source says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost 500 people dead: Philly to set grim record for homicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia-homicide-rate-2021-record-20211123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With nearly six weeks remaining in the year, the number of lives lost will likely far exceed the 500 people who were killed in 1990.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden's Andersson elected as nation's first woman PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211124-sweden-s-andersson-elected-as-nation-s-first-woman-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden's parliament on Wednesday elected Social Democratic party leader and current Finance Minister Magdalena Andersson as the country's first woman prime minister, after she clinched a last-minute…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland on edge ahead of Covid pass vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/switzerland-on-edge-ahead-of-covid-pass-vote-01637742907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Swiss will vote on Sunday on the country's Covid-19 laws, after a campaign characterised by unprecedented levels of hostility in the wealthy Alpine nation, including even death threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Forms Group to Examine Unexplained Aerial Sightings...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/pentagon-forms-a-group-to-examine-unexplained-aerial-sightings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Pentagon on Tuesday night announced a new group to investigate reports of unidentified aerial phenomena in sensitive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Hard for Hungry Families to Come By. Enter These Deer Hunters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/meat-is-hard-for-hungry-families-to-come-by-enter-these-deer-hunters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Aversa, a semiretired accountant, goes hunting as often as possible. He uses the first six or seven deer he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Defamation Case Signals Crackdown on Ordinary Citizens, Critics Say...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/australia-defamation-case-signals-a-crackdown-on-ordinary-citizens-critics-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia — Australia’s defense minister on Wednesday won a defamation case over a six-word tweet that called him a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomber Flights Prompt Russia, China to Announce Military Cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/us-bomber-flights-prompt-russia-china-announce-military-cooperation-1652653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian Defense Ministry said that the nations "expressed a shared interest in stepping up strategic military exercises and joint patrols."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Final Days: Celeb Reminiscing and Running Toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/what-new-documents-reveal-about-jeffrey-epstein-s-final-days/ar-AAR1Qk4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholz Seals Coalition Deal to Become Next German Chancellor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/scholz-secures-german-chancellorship-after-forging-new-alliance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scholz Seals Coalition Deal to Become Next German Chancellor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa urges members to take up up arms after Rittenhouse verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/23/antifa-urges-members-take-arms-after-kyle-rittenho/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of Antifa are responding to the acquittal of Kyle Rittenhouse last week by getting guns themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooks rapped 'we TERRORISTS' --  but cops rule out terror motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4127569/darrell-brooks-lyrics-waukesha-rapped-terrorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect in the Waukesha Christmas parade crash that killed five people had rapped about being a “terrorist” and a “killer in the city”, according to songs he posted onli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at judge for setting $5M bond for Xmas parade suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235965/Waukesha-SUV-killer-Darrell-Brooks-appears-court-face-six-murder-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darrell Brooks Jr, 39, appeared in court in Wisconsin on Tuesday for his bail hearing. Bail was set at $5 million in cash, which the judge described as 'extraordinary' but appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidens Thanksgiving at billionaire's private island compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10236561/Hunter-baby-Beau-gaggle-grandkids-join-Joe-Jill-Biden-Thanksgiving-Nantucket.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe and Jill Biden arrived on Nantucket for Thanksgiving after the White House defended their stay at billionaire David Rubenstein's private compound with Hunter and gaggle of grandkids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as Australians ordered to wear masks even as 95% of population is fully vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10236353/Coronavirus-Australia-Backlash-mask-rule-NSW-reaches-95-cent-vaccination.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal by NSW health bureaucrats to extend the mask wearing rule for millions of shoppers beyond the pre-Christmas rush has sparked furious backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge extends ban on keeping NYT from publishing material about PROJECT VERITAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235207/Judge-extends-New-York-Times-ban-Project-Veritas-coverage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York judge extended a ban keeping the New York Times from publishing or seeking certain materials concerning Project Veritas, a conservative activist group, on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Bond movie could  lose up to $100 million...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/no-time-to-die-highest-grossing-movie-losing-money-blockbusters-1235111919/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the weekend, “No Time to Die” eclipsed $730 million in global ticket sales, making the James Bond sequel both the year’s highest-grossing Hollywood film and the top performin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even in Highly Vaccinated New England, Hospitals Are Suffering...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/even-in-highly-vaccinated-new-england-hospitals-are-suffering/ar-AAR3y5h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AstraZeneca gives longer protection?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/health/medical/astrazeneca-vaccine-may-give-longer-protection-that-is-shielding-uk-from-new-covid-wave/ar-AAR1YSM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AstraZeneca vaccine may give longer protection that is shielding UK from new Covid wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETAILERS SOUND ALARM ON ORGANIZED THEFT</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/retail/retailers-sound-alarm-organized-theft-states-warn-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illinois and California have stepped up anti-shoplifting efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Renews Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2021/11/23/denver-mask-mandate-covid-19-cases-surge-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mandate, which takes effect Wednesday, will require businesses and other indoor public spaces to wear masks until Jan. 3 to curb the spread of coronavirus infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's Recovery Trails Other Cities as Tourism Loss Weighs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nyc-recovery-trails-other-u-190403960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- New York City’s recovery from the Covid-19 pandemic is lagging behind that of other major U.S. metropolitan areas as the iconic destination continues to suffer from the loss of tourism jobs, Fitch Ratings said Tuesday.Most Read from BloombergAsia’s Richest Man Looks to Walton Family Playbook on SuccessionThe 24-Year-Old Aiming to Dethrone Victoria’s SecretNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsThe Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rwandan mountain gorillas a rare conservation success...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rwanda-gorillas-60-minutes-2021-11-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 Minutes cameras visited the gorillas and their babies in the Rwandan mountains for a new Lesley Stahl report airing Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll rises to 6...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/wisconsin-waukesha-christmas-parade-car-plow-11-23-21/h_266f4489fda50b7993eee51b67a85ad8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial charges are expected to be filed Tuesday against the suspect in Sunday's fatal incident at the Waukesha Christmas parade. At least five people were killed and more than 40 were injured when an SUV plowed into the crowd. Follow here for the latest news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Files emergency order to immediately reinstate mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10235075/Biden-files-emergency-order-reinstate-sweeping-vaccine-mandate-private-companies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOJ filed with the Sixth Circuit Court of Appeals, which a federal judicial panel designated as the court that will decide legal challenges related to Biden's vaccine-or-test rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some deer ingested chemicals, shouldn't be eaten, Maine says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-environment-maine-wildlife-pollution-8c08f6ce0e0f020ba6b16107c0024004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAIRFIELD, Maine (AP) — Deer harvested by hunters in part of central Maine should not be consumed as food because of elevated levels of an environmental pollutant, authorities in the state said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO REQUIRE JABS FOR ALL BORDER CROSSERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-business-health-07c377d92f85bc061bf7e2c690f4bbca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will require essential, nonresident travelers crossing U.S. land borders, such as truck drivers, government and emergency response officials, to be fully vaccinated beginning on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising theft 'traumatizing' BEST BUY employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/business/best-buy-retail-theft/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Buy CEO Corie Barry said theft is a growing problem at the company's stores — and it is implementing added security measure to safeguard employees and shoppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Covid Made Democracies More Authoritarian...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/23/covid-19-made-democracies-more-authoritarian-and-authoritarianism-even-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 pandemic is contributing to a significant decline in democratic values across the globe as many countries have taken aggressive and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K., Chappelle Nominated for GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/23/dave-chappelle-louis-ck-cancel-culture-grammy-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis C.K. and Dave Chappelle both grabbed Grammy nominations, despite their individual battles with "cancel culture", a signal maybe "canceling" people is on the wane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GENERAL HOSPITAL' actor fired for refusing shot...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/general-hospital-steve-burton-vaccine-mandate-soap-actor-fired/11265347/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Steve Burton, a fixture on "General Hospital" for more than three decades, has been fired from the soap for his refusal to get vaccinated, he told fans on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys, Oath Keepers probed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/23/january-6-subpoena-proud-boys-oath-keepers-523255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House select committee’s latest round of summonses target leaders of the groups, as well as a third far-right entity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media use linked to depression in adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/social-media-use-linked-depression-adults-rcna6445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While social media has been widely linked to anxiety and depression in teenagers, new evidence suggests that platforms such as TikTok and Instagram can leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Responds to Jan. 6 Subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/alex-jones-issues-emergency-message-concerning-jan-6th-congressional-subpoena/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a declaration of war against free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury awards millions in damages for Unite the Right violence...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/unite-jurors-begin-day-deliberations-81344570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jury has ordered white nationalist leaders and organizations to pay more than $25 million in damages over violence that erupted during the deadly 2017 Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Says U.S. Rehearsed Nuclear Strike Against Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-11-23/russia-notes-significant-increase-in-u-s-bomber-activity-in-east-minister</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild hogs running rampant outside LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/feral-hogs-corona-california-yards-destroyed-wild-pigs/11265222/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wild hogs are running rampant in Corona and residents say it's becoming a growing problem that's posing a threat to the safety of families and pets all across the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Declared Him Dead. He Came Out Alive From Freezer 6 Hours Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awvmw/declared-dead-man-alive-in-morgue-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I touched his cheeks. To my happiness and horror, it was warm. He was breathing,” says a relative who came to identify the body at the morgue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT faces extended ban on 'VERITAS' coverage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123192426-1aml0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PROJECT VERITAS/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-New York Times faces extended ban on Project Veritas coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY chef wants to change diets -- 1 bug at a time...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/chef-joseph-yoon-brooklyn-bugs-insect-diet-spc-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chef Joseph Yoon wants to introduce the US to the delights of insect-based cuisine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury holds pharmacies responsible for role in opioid crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-ohio-medication-opioids-d778b97c0eb409aa0d53dcfd9e4f2ad0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — Three retail pharmacy chains recklessly distributed massive amounts of pain pills in two Ohio counties, a federal jury said Tuesday in a verdict that could set the tone for U.S. city and county governments that want to hold pharmacies accountable for their roles in the opioid crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leto's 'Super Mario' Italian accent mocked...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/23/jared-letos-house-of-gucci-accent-mocked-as-super-mario/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruthless Twitter critics have lasered in on Jared Leto’s accent, taking potshots at the actors’ performance, which many analogized to the titular character in “Super Mario.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House members describe roiling animosity among lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/politics/congress-anger-house-fights/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many members within the House of Representatives told CNN in recent days that they find themselves in a toxic work environment, wrought with bitter exchanges, threats and fears about what the erosion of decorum in the chamber will mean for a body that has still not recovered 10 months after the Capitol Hill riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE sues company known for hacking iPhones on behalf of govts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/apple-sues-nso-group-company-known-for-hacking-iphones-on-behalf-of-governments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bail draws questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/suspect-e2-80-99s-bail-draws-questions-as-investigations-begin-into-wisconsin-parade-tragedy/ar-AAR1Ww2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  WAIT ANOTHER YEAR FOR INFLATION TO COOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.macaubusiness.com/monthly-us-inflation-to-return-to-0-2-0-3-pct-in-second-half-of-2022-yellen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macaubusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Island ER forced to close over lack of vaccinated nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/shortage-of-vaccinated-nurses-prompts-closure-of-er-on-long-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mount Sinai South Nassau said the decision to close the Long Beach Emergency Room came after all options were exhausted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZEN ROBBERS HIT CALI LUXE</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/23/update-shaken-holiday-shoppers-changing-plans-in-wake-of-retail-smash-and-grab-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent smash-and-grab robbery spree targeting retail shops across the Bay Area has shoppers, store employees and business owners on edge at the start the holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMAS SMASH AND GRAB</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/breed-brazen-takeover-robbers-hitting-130021558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-end retailers such as Nordstrom and Louis Vuitton have been targeted by brazen robbers in Northern and Southern California, raising alarm among authorities, politicians and retailers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Arrested On Nov. 5 For Punching Woman, Then Running Over Her In Same SUV!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/waukesha-christmas-parade-darrell-brooks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darrell Brooks, 39, was charged with five counts of murder after he allegedly plowed through a Christmas parade in Waukesha, Wisconsin, on Sunday, killing at least five and injuring dozens more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes of terror recounted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/waukesha-wisconsin-christmas-parade-crash-what-happened-daee4565c7a36e88029c5fe6393d1be3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours before it started, they were already there — people sitting on lawn chairs or wrapped in blankets, awaiting an event the city's mayor described as straight out of Norman Rockwell. The Waukesha Christmas Parade, a tradition in its Milwaukee suburb for six decades, was to be particularly special this time around after its pandemic-related cancellation last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Expect To Gain 8 Pounds During Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/holiday-weight-gain-8-pounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holiday weight gain is inevitable for many of us who can't help but to take a second slice of grandma's pecan pie or another slice of turkey (or three).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Warms to Saudi Money Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywood-saudi-arabia-money-again-1235051906/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t too long ago that power brokers rushed to distance themselves from the country after the killing of columnist Jamal Khashoggi. Now it’s hosting a star-studded film festival and backing big-budget features with U.S. talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News Hedging on Streaming Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/cnn-fox-msnbc-streaming-plan-1235051688/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While touting new platforms (think: CNN+ or Fox Nation), top broadcast and cable executives are incentivized to protect the linear status quo, given that’s where the money is — even if it’s a rapidly declining business model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Deploying Highway Patrol...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/police-smash-and-grab-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stopping the swarm of smash and grabs as holiday shoppers begin their buying spree, local police have a plan to keep criminals out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense after new covid curbs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123142632-1ol47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-GUADELOUPE (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving challenges airlines as travel nears pre-pandemic levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/23/thanksgiving-travel-airports-staffing-cancelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers fear airport chaos as airlines contend with staffing shortages, which could lead to flight cancelations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR TREE Gives Up on Buck With $1.25 Price Standard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/dollar-tree-says-dollar125-price-point-to-become-new-standard/ar-AAR2CvB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
